TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1791	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIRST	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
DALBY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
opposite	O
Rolls-buildings	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCI	O
.	O
N.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Letters	O
and	O
Messages	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
left	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
instantly	O
attended	O
to	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
,	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wallace	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bundy	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Gwynn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gleaves	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mabberly	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Snuggs	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Corbyn	I-pers
John	B-pers
Vigurs	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Shabner	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wilshen	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Lewis	B-pers
Gieler	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
Barnard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Hitchen	I-pers
William	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Rymer	I-pers
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
Bilton	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
John	B-pers
Boozey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
William	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
Aaron	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
William	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
Percival	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Shakespeare	I-pers
1.	O
JOHN	B-pers
AUSTIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silvershoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
stone	O
breast-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leather-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
before	O
five	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
into	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
one-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	O
Archer	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
any	O
violence	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
door	O
is	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
directly	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
Keys	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
certain	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
set	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
locked	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
open	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
with	O
the	O
landlord	O
.	O
There	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
violence	O
done	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
judge	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
other	O
persons	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
keys	O
to	O
let	O
themselves	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
walking	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
flew	O
open	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
screamed	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
screamed	O
out	O
on	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
,	O
you	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
's	O
,	O
except	O
1	O
s.	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
Keys	O
come	O
down	O
after	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
is	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
an	O
easy	O
chair	O
.	O
We	O
held	O
him	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
then	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
He	O
tussled	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shagreen	O
watch	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
of	O
the	O
Sunday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
her	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struggling	O
with	O
the	O
brother	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
picklock	O
key	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Deposes	O
to	O
the	O
articles	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
worth	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
4	O
s.	O
stone	O
breast	O
buckle	O
1	O
s.	O
thimble	O
,	O
three	O
plain	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
6	O
d.	O
child	O
's	O
bell	O
and	O
wire	O
ring	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
no	O
value	O
on	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
2.	O
MORGAN	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
callico	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Small	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Madgwick	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
opened	O
the	O
case	O
.	O
HEMRY	O
SMALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tavistock-street	B-place
;	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Edward	B-pers
Madgwick	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
us	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
callico	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
Q.	O
C.	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
.	O
The	O
callico	O
is	O
our	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
worth	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
small	O
remnant	O
of	O
Irish	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
chambers	O
,	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
from	O
some	O
suspicion	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
from	O
some	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
property	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
FRANCIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
offered	O
this	O
remnant	O
of	O
callico	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
LANE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
pledge	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
VINCENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
Morgan	O
Lewis	O
.	O
(	O
Prosecutor	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
here	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
articles	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barrister	O
at	O
law	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
also	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
miniature	O
picture	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Shelley	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
SHELLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Henrietta	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
miniature	O
painter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
there	O
saw	O
a	O
miniature	O
picture	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
this	O
picture	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
pictures	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
repairing	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KIMBER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
unable	O
to	O
attend	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
picture	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
to	O
exchange	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
pin	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
pin	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
picture	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
delivered	O
the	O
picture	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
picture	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
LAVENDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Heather	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
magnifying	O
glass	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Shelley	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shelley	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
two	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shelley	O
.	O
This	O
picture	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
The	O
shilling	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
think	O
the	O
glass	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
neckcloths	O
I	O
believe	O
also	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
shilling	O
honestly	O
;	O
the	O
magnifying	O
glass	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
sweeping	O
out	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
always	O
washed	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DURHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cutt	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
eight	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
coloured	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
white	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Cutt	I-pers
.	O
AMELIA	B-pers
CUTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
33	I-place
,	I-place
Eagle-street	I-place
,	I-place
Red-lion-square	I-place
;	O
my	O
brother	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
coal-shed	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
seven	O
in	O
family	O
;	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
let	O
to	O
one	O
family	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
watch	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
passage	O
from	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
the	O
bedroom	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Brother	O
,	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
a	O
thief	O
!	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
bundle	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
pursued	O
him	O
immediately	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
street-door	O
is	O
always	O
open	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
light	O
both	O
ways	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CUTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
sister	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Brother	O
,	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
running	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
light	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
Holborn	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
20	O
yards	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
stopped	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
WALKER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
before	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
out	O
stumbling	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
past	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
followed	O
him	O
down	O
Dean	O
street	O
about	O
threescore	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
by	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
back	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
that	O
arm	O
and	O
his	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
those	O
who	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
that	O
wanted	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cutt	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Amelia	B-pers
Cutt	I-pers
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
three	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
loose	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
through	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
COWLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
twenty-six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
agent	O
for	O
merchants	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
responsible	O
for	O
every	O
article	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
goes	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
alone	O
responsible	O
:	O
this	O
cheese	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
custom-house	O
keys	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
cheeses	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
cheese	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
cheese	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
cheese	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
second	O
crane	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
wool-key	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
take	O
the	O
cheese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
the	O
second	O
crane	O
,	O
next	O
Wool-key	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
cheese	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
jacket	O
on	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
off	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
cheese	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
cheese	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
the	O
other	O
cheeses	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
marks	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
kind	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
114	O
baskets	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
one	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
corresponded	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
has	O
transported	O
above	O
forty	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
seven	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hobbins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pinchin	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PORTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
called	O
Chester	B-place
Key	I-place
Warehouse	I-place
,	O
which	O
we	O
belong	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
under	O
our	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
three	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
soldier	O
,	O
where	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
capstan	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
all	O
over	O
sugar	O
,	O
his	O
breeches	O
were	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
lined	O
all	O
round	O
his	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
seven	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
clothes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
raw	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
weighed	O
the	O
hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
wanted	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
seven	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
West-India	O
Merchants	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
property	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
sugar	O
of	O
a	O
sailor	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SKELTON	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
bar	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoners	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
Skelton	O
had	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
bar	O
iron	O
,	O
weighing	O
32	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
Martin	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
weighing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
claimed	O
the	O
property	O
I	O
produce	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swan-yard	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farrier	O
.	O
This	O
iron	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
This	O
bar	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
stouter	O
than	O
that	O
which	O
I	O
usually	O
use	O
in	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Parr	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
observing	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
used	O
all	O
the	O
iron	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
.	O
Skelton	O
asked	O
Parr	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
bar	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
work	O
up	O
that	O
iron	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
unhandy	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
because	O
Parr	O
refused	O
him	O
drink	O
.	O
This	O
bar	O
is	O
cracked	O
,	O
which	O
renders	O
it	O
remarkable	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoners	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
iron	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLUER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
one	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
eighteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
three	O
base	O
metal	O
counters	O
resembling	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Romulus	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
my	O
wages	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
eighteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
three	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
I	O
bought	O
in	O
London	O
resembling	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Running	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
shipmate	O
,	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
provide	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
passage	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
sudden	O
jerk	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
tin	O
box	O
and	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
left	O
me	O
one	O
copper	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
lodging-house	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
many	O
heavy	O
oaths	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
half-guinea	O
pieces	O
resembling	O
half-guineas	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
ashes	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
tin	O
box	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
schoolboy	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Salutation	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
you	O
drank	O
at	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Near	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
What	O
liquor	O
did	O
you	O
drink	O
?	O
-	O
Part	O
of	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
at	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
space	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
You	O
drank	O
there	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
fighting	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
after	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
so	O
sober	O
as	O
to	O
recollect	O
all	O
that	O
happened	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
off	O
when	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
paid	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
public-house	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
Bull	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Aye	O
,	O
recollect	O
yourself	O
;	O
and	O
recollect	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
less	O
offence	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
getting	O
drunk	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
voyage	O
than	O
in	O
swearing	O
against	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bull	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
you	O
invited	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
to	O
pass	O
the	O
night	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
woman	O
's	O
company	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
countryman	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
West	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
then	O
,	O
she	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
through	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
landlord	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
something	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
see	O
her	O
backside	O
as	O
see	O
her	O
face	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
after	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
ungallant	O
surely	O
as	O
an	O
English	O
sailor	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
herself	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
eating-house	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
you	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
pleasant	O
circumstance	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
continue	O
drinking	O
there	O
?	O
You	O
drank	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation	O
,	O
then	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
eating-house	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
again	O
;	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
which	O
you	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
drop	O
of	O
a	O
nip	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
slip	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
it	O
all	O
myself	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
off	O
did	O
you	O
pass	O
your	O
night	O
from	O
these	O
running	O
horses	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
fighting	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
No	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
dress	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
after	O
all	O
this	O
drinking	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
really	O
think	O
you	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
and	O
sensible	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
and	O
did	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
VIOLET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Bryant	O
paid	O
for	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
nobody	O
else	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
passed	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
pipe-maker	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
reckoning	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
weigh	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
sailor	O
charged	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
your	O
neighbourhood	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
frequented	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
there	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
accustomed	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
all	O
into	O
the	O
pipe-furnace	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
conscious	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
the	O
sailor	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
we	O
do	O
let	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
offered	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLAMTREE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pipe-maker	O
in	O
Brentford	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
publick	O
house	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
medals	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
were	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
me	O
at	O
William	B-pers
Violet	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
;	O
the	O
sailor	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
above	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
pay	O
the	O
prisoner	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
on	O
an	O
average	O
;	O
I	O
seldom	O
paid	O
him	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
offered	O
me	O
any	O
gold	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
applied	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
very	O
half-guineas	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
half-guineas	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
treat	O
Bryan	O
at	O
that	O
very	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
or	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
lost	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
to	O
Violet	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
had	O
worked	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
some	O
months	O
,	O
what	O
character	O
did	O
he	O
bear	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Did	O
Clamtree	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
Bryan	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
very	O
good	O
friends	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
give	O
Clamtree	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
to	O
Clamtree	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
you	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
tap-room	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
secret	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	O
BROWN	O
sworn	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
at	O
Old	O
Brentford	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
throw	O
down	O
a	O
pocket	O
piece	O
to	O
the	O
sailor	O
,	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
coin	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
golden	O
guinea	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
the	O
over-night	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Cluer	I-pers
and	O
the	O
sailor	O
.	O
Had	O
any	O
complaint	O
been	O
made	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
offence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
piece	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
criminal	O
throw	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
cordwainer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
beer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
me	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
with	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
sailor	O
recollected	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
the	O
overnight	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
magistate	O
,	O
nor	O
is	O
your	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
first	O
applied	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
Doctor	O
Forster	B-pers
.	O
Was	O
you	O
examined	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
examination	O
in	O
writing	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PETERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Old	O
Brentford	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Bryantthere	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
pint	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
plenty	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
saved	O
up	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
Christmas	O
holidays	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
pipe-clay	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
18	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
money	O
;	O
what	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
say	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
beckoned	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
sob	O
of	O
his	O
trowsers	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
half	O
guineas	O
or	O
counterfeits	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
and	O
keep	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
they	O
were	O
demolished	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Callaghan	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
called	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lad	O
?	O
-	O
Thirteen	O
,	O
last	O
September	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Suppose	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Go	O
to	O
the	O
devil	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Sworn	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Violet	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
dunghill	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Violet	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
has	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
about	O
two	O
stones	O
throw	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
live	O
much	O
nearer	O
?	O
Yes	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
tin	O
box	O
I	O
found	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
certificate	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
guinea	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
pocket-piece	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Violet	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
this	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
certificate	O
and	O
card	O
.	O
This	O
medal	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
scratch	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
of	O
these	O
medals	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
?	O
-	O
Three	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
scratch	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
head	O
side	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
a	O
long	O
one	O
all	O
down	O
the	O
crown	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
very	O
long	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
reach	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
?	O
-	O
Almost	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
side	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
for	O
certainty	O
;	O
now	O
it	O
happens	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
the	O
tail	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
(	O
Shews	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
)	O
Which	O
is	O
the	O
head	O
side	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
(	O
He	O
points	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
persists	O
in	O
the	O
scratch	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
side	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
chuck	O
this	O
medal	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
That	O
which	O
you	O
call	O
the	O
medal	O
resembles	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
?	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Bryant	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
place	O
,	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
alley	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
a	O
jerk	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
yourpocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
your	O
property	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
force	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
trouble	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
the	O
guinea	O
I	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
have	O
:	O
my	O
defence	O
is	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
master	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pocket-pieces	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
all	O
his	O
money	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
pocket-pieces	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Clamtree	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
tap-room	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
backwards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
leave	O
the	O
Running	O
Horses	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
home	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
then	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
character	O
and	O
simplicity	O
.	O
)	O
10.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SLACK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
fifty-six	O
rabbit	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
William	B-pers
Borrodaile	I-pers
,	O
Richardson	B-pers
Borrodaile	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BORRODAILE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
furrier	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
that	O
those	O
skins	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
furrier	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
fifty-two	O
skins	O
offering	O
for	O
sale	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
servant	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
this	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bred	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
large	O
number	O
of	O
rabbits	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
dried	O
them	O
very	O
nice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
hung	O
them	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
nose	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
foreign	O
skins	O
;	O
I	O
threatened	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
sold	O
me	O
some	O
skins	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHRISTIAN	I-pers
SCHRIEBER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Borrodaile	O
;	O
these	O
skins	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
quality	O
of	O
those	O
we	O
lost	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
Flemish	O
skins	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
coming	O
from	O
London-wall	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
skins	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
11.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WADE	I-pers
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
onewooden	O
tub	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
sixty-nine	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
41	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
PETER	B-pers
BUCKLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
a	O
cheese-monger	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-hill	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
unloading	O
a	O
cart	O
of	O
cheese	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
carman	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
man	O
has	O
taken	O
away	O
a	O
firkin	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Irish	O
butter	O
and	O
salt	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
and	O
Smith	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Giltspur-street	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
Wade	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
firkin	O
dropped	O
off	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
Smith	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
the	O
skin	O
of	O
my	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
smock	O
frock	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
knocked	O
my	O
master	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
upon	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
face	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
firkin	O
,	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
349	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
began	O
to	O
collect	O
round	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
in	O
Cow-cross	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
in	O
that	O
pursuit	O
by	O
the	O
patroles	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
two	O
men	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Giltspur-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
crying	O
murder	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
white	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
smock	O
frock	O
.	O
-	O
WILLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
different	O
houses	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
evidence	O
Buckland	O
into	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
thieves	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
RICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
their	O
persons	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
identify	O
which	O
.	O
Buckland	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
my	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
say	O
to	O
one	O
Douglas	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
butter	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
ten	O
hog	O
a-piece	O
:	O
Smith	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
was	O
a	O
lusty	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
tipt	O
him	O
his	O
gruel	O
as	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
Smith	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
White-horse	O
cellar	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Wade	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Cow-cross	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
12.	O
BARTHOLOMEW	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
ingots	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Penton	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Penton	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FARRELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass-founder	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Penton	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Penton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
square	I-place
,	I-place
Shoe-lane	I-place
;	O
they	O
are	O
brass-founders	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
privy	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
ingot	O
of	O
brass	O
tucked	O
into	O
a	O
hole	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
that	O
lead	O
up	O
into	O
another	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
necessary	O
is	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
also	O
is	O
that	O
hole	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ingot	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
John	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
Walton	O
marked	O
the	O
brass	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
brass	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
we	O
watched	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
Walton	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Penton	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
nothing	O
happened	O
then	O
;	O
we	O
watched	O
again	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
metmy	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
master	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
stood	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
master	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
ingot	O
of	O
brass	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
called	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
!	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
take	O
the	O
ingot	O
of	O
brass	O
from	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
by	O
Walton	B-pers
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PENTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass-founder	O
,	O
in	O
New-street	O
square	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Penton	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
punch	O
that	O
marked	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
our	O
mark	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
new	O
brass	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
brass	O
ever	O
since	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
neither	O
promises	O
nor	O
threats	O
used	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
13.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
JENKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
we	O
lost	O
some	O
cheese	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
two	O
cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
cheeses	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Prosecutrix	O
deposes	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Angel	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
they	O
stopt	O
another	O
man	O
before	O
they	O
did	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
14.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
GILMORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GERMAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
parish	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
HARVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Enfield-highway	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
cry	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
shirts	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
mate	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
shirts	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirts	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
LAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
shirts	O
;	O
Harvey	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
GERMAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
shirts	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
wet	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ranafter	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Harvey	O
and	O
Smith	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Harvey	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
conducted	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hertford	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
travelled	O
about	O
four	O
miles	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
sister	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
walked	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
bundle	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
called	O
Halloobulloo	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
thief	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
enough	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
winter	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
property	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Germain	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
but	O
the	O
shirts	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
shirts	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
60	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
15.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEACH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
covered	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
steel	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BOURNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
7	I-place
,	I-place
Wardour-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
;	O
I	O
hung	O
up	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JOYCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
candles	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
running	O
across	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
-	O
SANDERS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Bourne	O
was	O
holding	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
Joyce	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Sanders	O
.	O
(	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
holiday	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
respectable	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
16.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
forty-nine	O
pounds	O
of	O
grain	O
tin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Swabey	I-pers
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
SWABEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Black	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
apprehended	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
this	O
tin	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
,	O
they	O
detained	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
hesaid	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Swabey	O
,	O
of	O
Vauxhall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
,	O
a	O
coachmaker	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
manufactory	O
;	O
one	O
branch	O
of	O
his	O
business	O
was	O
to	O
boil	O
tin	O
and	O
lead	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
employed	O
in	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
ashes	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
to	O
burn	O
;	O
on	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
deficient	O
in	O
quality	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
they	O
wanted	O
the	O
due	O
proportion	O
of	O
tin	O
;	O
we	O
ascertain	O
the	O
quality	O
by	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
ashes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Addington	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
during	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
examination	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
various	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
promised	O
any	O
favour	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
Wright	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
this	O
tin	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
tin	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Swabey	O
,	O
near	O
Vauxhall	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
right	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
coachmaker	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
coachmakers	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
Howard	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
last	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
upon	O
this	O
tin	O
,	O
in	O
return	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
sold	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
half-a-crown	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
labour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
this	O
tin	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
patroles	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
17.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chorley	I-pers
,	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHORLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
lead	O
from	O
some	O
houses	O
I	O
had	O
recently	O
built	O
in	O
Union-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
following	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
fitted	O
the	O
lead	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
I	O
worked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
nail-holes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
my	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
down	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
the	O
piece	O
weighed	O
about	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
;	O
the	O
piece	O
I	O
describe	O
completely	O
filled	O
up	O
the	O
vacancy	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
blue	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
slang	O
for	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
examination	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
seven	O
months	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
estate	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
has	O
been	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
under	O
my	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
W.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DUNCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
hole	O
does	O
not	O
run	O
right	O
through	O
,	O
it	O
runs	O
upon	O
an	O
angle	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
detached	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
some	O
fitting	O
one	O
house	O
and	O
some	O
another	O
.	O
OLIVER	B-pers
BURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
present	O
.	O
(	O
Deposes	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
shadow	O
of	O
doubt	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
identical	O
lead	O
fitted	O
toMr	O
.	O
Chorley	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
pains	O
to	O
satisfy	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
hundred	O
for	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
to	O
send	O
into	O
Hertfordshire	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
building	O
a	O
little	O
tenement	O
;	O
Turner	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
cadee	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
stole	O
beer	O
and	O
pork	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
confined	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
for	O
striking	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
rape	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
18.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FOOT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
bay	O
coach-horses	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
La	I-pers
Hoope	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
-	O
lays	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LOURN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
La	O
Hoope	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
your	O
horses	O
very	O
early	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
a	O
job	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
to	O
drive	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
gentleman	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
three	O
years	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
week	O
board-wages	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
two	O
suits	O
of	O
livery	O
;	O
this	O
passed	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
stables	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
some	O
soon	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
coach-dog	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
's	O
service	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
those	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
feed	O
of	O
corn	O
before	O
they	O
set	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
horse-cloth	O
upon	O
each	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
lives	O
in	O
Hamilton-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
up	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
would	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
horses	O
in	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
any	O
in	O
exchange	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
delivered	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
employed	O
and	O
sent	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hamilton-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bay	O
geldings	O
in	O
the	O
employ	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
La	O
Hoope	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
intimated	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
La	O
Hoope	O
that	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
change	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
had	O
an	O
intention	O
of	O
changing	O
Mrs.	O
La	O
Hoope	O
's	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
intention	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
known	O
in	O
my	O
stables	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
purchased	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
long-tailed	O
horses	O
for	O
her	O
use	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
RIX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachmaster	O
at	O
Putney	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
coach	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Feltham	O
,	O
of	O
Bedford-square	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
her	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
twenty-five	O
guineas	O
a-piece	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
30	O
l.	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
less	O
than	O
thirty	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
one	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
word	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
only	O
twenty-five	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
horses	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
about	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
horses	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
Barnes	O
Common	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
furze	O
bush	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
horses	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Rix	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
were	O
those	O
I	O
had	O
let	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
La	O
Hoope	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
19.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BEAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
black	O
gelding	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
,	O
a	O
stable-keeper	O
,	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
head	O
hostler	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
stables	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
hostler	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
whether	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
horse	O
stood	O
there	O
at	O
livery	O
?	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
have	O
recommended	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
horse	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Low	O
Layton	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
saying	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
again	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Low	O
Layton	O
,	O
on	O
particular	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
should	O
return	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
nothing	O
was	O
said	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
stick	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
clerk	O
and	O
rider	O
to	O
some	O
great	O
shop	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Brown	O
:	O
he	O
mentioned	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
repository	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
bought	O
him	O
in	O
spring	O
.	O
My	O
reason	O
for	O
being	O
particular	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
customer	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
past	O
four	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
half	O
past	O
four	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
rather	O
duskish	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
faith	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
Richardson	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
yard	O
is	O
very	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
lighted	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
not	O
hired	O
generally	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
return	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUMPHRIES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
repository	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
paying	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
compting-house	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
paying	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
just	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
your	O
pardon	O
for	O
disturbing	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
pleasure	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
thank	O
you	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
spare	O
one	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
men	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
morrow	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
succeed	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
lend	O
you	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
succeed	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
under	O
or	O
over	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
spoke	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
for	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
rode	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
a	O
saddle	O
and	O
bridle	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
booked	O
it	O
at	O
eight	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
himI	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Park-lane	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
succeeded	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
consider	O
the	O
horse	O
a	O
pawn	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
should	O
return	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
ride	O
that	O
horse	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hack	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
expecting	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
behind	O
a	O
pheaton	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
him	O
waiting	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
succeeded	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
pressed	O
me	O
very	O
hard	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
another	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Blick	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
the	O
second	O
guinea	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
left	O
this	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
certain	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
letter	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
second	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
should	O
settle	O
the	O
business	O
;	O
the	O
time	O
was	O
fixed	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
at	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
eight	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
at	O
five	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
settle	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
:	O
Wise	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bean	O
?	O
this	O
convinced	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
wrong	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
entered	O
his	O
name	O
Robins	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
name	O
always	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
drawing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
horse	O
?	O
I	O
rather	O
suspect	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
some	O
foreign	O
gentleman	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
he	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
did	O
know	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
other	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
France	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
address	O
?	O
he	O
pulled	O
a	O
pencil	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
number	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-le-grand	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
plain	O
direction	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
write	O
it	O
with	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
be	O
convinced	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
right	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
lady	O
waiting	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
gateway	O
end	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
plain	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
his	O
address	O
was	O
fictitious	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
hesitate	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
settled	O
without	O
going	O
there	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
repaid	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
would	O
I	O
be	O
then	O
satisfied	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
serious	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
light	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
pressed	O
me	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
settle	O
it	O
;	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
injure	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
for	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
serious	O
thing	O
to	O
myself	O
:	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
horse	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
of	O
Chiswell-street	O
:	O
Mott	O
came	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
letter	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
stable-yard	O
is	O
this	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
place	O
for	O
sale	O
and	O
a	O
livery-yard	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
repository	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
private	O
contract	O
;	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
sell	O
by	O
public	O
auction	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
not	O
done	O
for	O
these	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
custom	O
then	O
of	O
the	O
repository	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
horses	O
from	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
comes	O
,	O
without	O
enquiring	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
aboutthem	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
always	O
take	O
the	O
address	O
.	O
What	O
capacity	O
might	O
you	O
be	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Foreman	O
to	O
the	O
salesman	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
Anything	O
you	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
's	O
account	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
by	O
bringing	O
a	O
horse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jocelyn	O
's	O
of	O
London-wall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
conversation	O
about	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
horse	O
was	O
not	O
owned	O
till	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
brought	O
no	O
horse	O
before	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
a	O
horse	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
that	O
charge	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
discharged	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Jocelyn	O
did	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
horse	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
that	O
other	O
warrant	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
horse	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Let	O
us	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
receipt	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
see	O
by	O
this	O
receipt	O
you	O
gave	O
him	O
seven	O
guineas	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
is	O
received	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
,	O
seven	O
guineas	O
for	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
unknown	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
hinder	O
any	O
body	O
bringing	O
horses	O
to	O
us	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
especially	O
if	O
we	O
have	O
any	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
had	O
suspicions	O
,	O
or	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
had	O
one	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
enquiries	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
enquiry	O
I	O
made	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
did	O
come	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
acquainted	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
first	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
particularly	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
brought	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pair	O
that	O
he	O
drove	O
in	O
his	O
curricle	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sound	O
one	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
ailed	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
hair	O
was	O
rubbed	O
off	O
the	O
side	O
with	O
the	O
harness	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pointed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
sale	O
for	O
eight	O
guineas	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
keep	O
;	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
keep	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
mentioned	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
distressed	O
or	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
this	O
last	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
intire	O
black	O
one	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
single	O
star	O
in	O
the	O
forehead	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
material	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
a	O
white	O
leg	O
before	O
or	O
behind	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
people	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
Six	O
nights	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
you	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
many	O
times	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
by	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
stall	O
till	O
an	O
owner	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
fed	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
horse	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
leg	O
,	O
should	O
not	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
particular	O
reason	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
other	O
horse	O
;	O
nor	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Which	O
horse	O
was	O
chopped	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
other	O
horse	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
frequently	O
saw	O
this	O
horse	O
fed	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
horse	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
by	O
Mott	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
man	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
once	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
horse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
and	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
;	O
Mott	O
only	O
led	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
mentioned	O
Low	O
Layton	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
applied	O
for	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
ride	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
four	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Islington	O
road	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
horse	O
went	O
so	O
very	O
lame	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
rode	O
him	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
rode	O
him	O
into	O
Hopkins	O
's	O
livery	O
stables	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
put	O
that	O
horse	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
I	O
:	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
credit	O
would	O
lend	O
me	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
pawn-broker	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
consider	O
the	O
horse	O
as	O
brought	O
there	O
for	O
sale	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
conversation	O
that	O
took	O
place	O
under	O
the	O
compting-house	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
With	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
being	O
booked	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
has	O
an	O
undoubted	O
right	O
to	O
write	O
what	O
he	O
pleases	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
book	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
pledge	O
:	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
that	O
night	O
requesting	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
eight	O
guineas	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
conceived	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
lent	O
on	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
does	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
again	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
presently	O
after	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
oblige	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
disappointed	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
after	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Allingham	O
,	O
a	O
sheriff	O
's	O
officer	O
,	O
to	O
arrest	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
that	O
owed	O
him	O
thirty-seven	O
pounds	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
then	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
another	O
guinea	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
borrowed	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
has	O
stated	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mott	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
might	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
say	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Bean	O
instead	O
of	O
Brown	O
?	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Mott	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
LILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bell-savage-yard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
always	O
a	O
genteel	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
best	O
company	O
:	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Perryn	I-pers
.	O
In	O
what	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
has	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
fancy	O
,	O
mostly	O
on	O
his	O
relations	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
understood	O
so	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
of	O
no	O
trade	O
or	O
profession	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
very	O
industrious	O
in	O
drawing	O
maps	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Humphries	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
talked	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
having	O
two	O
stone	O
colts	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
horse	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
first	O
horse	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
stone	O
colts	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
the	O
first	O
horse	O
he	O
brought	O
you	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
in	O
general	O
keep	O
an	O
errand-poney	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
lads	O
to	O
ride	O
on	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
that	O
buys	O
post	O
chaises	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
exchanged	O
with	O
Perkins	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
the	O
poney	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
considered	O
as	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
fair	O
valuation	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
case	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Brown	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
moved	O
in	O
arrest	O
of	O
judgment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
addition	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
alias	O
dictus	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
substantive	O
name	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
therefore	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
jury	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
collected	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
right	O
it	O
ought	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
that	O
therewas	O
uncertainty	O
apparent	O
on	O
the	O
record	O
:	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
objection	O
,	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
weight	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
respite	O
the	O
judgement	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
cases	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
then	O
any	O
doubts	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
save	O
the	O
case	O
for	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
.	O
20.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
glass	O
lamp	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CHARLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
employed	O
by	O
Messrs.	O
Lucas	O
and	O
Spencer	O
,	O
the	O
contractors	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
Spring-gardens	B-place
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ladder	O
raised	O
to	O
the	O
lamp-iron	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
round	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
tin	O
oil-pot	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
glass	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
lamp	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
iron	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yours	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
mark	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
save	O
you	O
that	O
trouble	O
;	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
decide	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
lamp	O
or	O
mine	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lamp	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
encounter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
lamps	O
round	O
the	O
statue	O
,	O
but	O
somebody	O
had	O
lighted	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
:	O
the	O
lamp-iron	O
had	O
no	O
lamp	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lamp	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Charle	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Charle	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
works	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Spikes	O
,	O
who	O
contracts	O
for	O
the	O
Board	O
of	O
Green	O
Cloth	O
.	O
Charle	O
the	O
elder	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
contracts	O
for	O
the	O
private	O
lamps	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
this	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
