TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1791	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Boydell	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Islington	O
:	O
Sold	O
also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCI	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
,	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOYDELL	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hackett	I-pers
John	B-pers
Garner	I-pers
George	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newbald	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Edland	I-pers
James	B-pers
Slann	I-pers
*	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
attended	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Slann	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Slarck	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
James	B-pers
Kearsley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dowers	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kendleside	I-pers
James	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Eskelby	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dinning	I-pers
William	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Teasdale	I-pers
George	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
.	O
382.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
KELLY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooker	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealingtherein	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BROOKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
65	I-place
,	I-place
Gray's-inn-lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
safe	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
my	O
apartments	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
separate	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
different	O
entrance	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
different	O
tenements	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
does	O
not	O
reside	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
windows	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
ten	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
dark	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
discern	O
people	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
a	O
woman	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
step	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
assistance	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
there	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
skirt	O
and	O
stays	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
the	O
Talbot	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
lodger	O
to	O
stand	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
violence	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
some	O
guineas	O
,	O
some	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
crowns	O
and	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
recovered	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
violence	O
on	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
picked	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
sleep	O
at	O
the	O
Canns	O
in	O
Holborn	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
it	O
lets	O
the	O
apartments	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
inn-lane	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
householder	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
out	O
the	O
apartments	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
landlord	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
,	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
found	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
your	O
coming	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
stays	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Turner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
slightly	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Collyer	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
HARRIET	I-pers
BROOKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
child	O
's	O
skirt	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
this	O
skirt	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
being	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
skirt	O
and	O
stays	O
are	O
attached	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
call	O
these	O
things	O
skirt	O
and	O
stay	O
,	O
or	O
stay	O
and	O
skirt	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
one	O
and	O
sometimes	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
washed	O
separate	O
,	O
but	O
worn	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
call	O
the	O
thing	O
which	O
a	O
child	O
wears	O
under	O
its	O
chin	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
stay	O
.	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
objected	O
to	O
the	O
naming	O
of	O
the	O
stays	O
and	O
skirt	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
erroneous	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
overruled	O
the	O
objection	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVID	I-pers
BURKENBUSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
coming	O
up	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot	O
inn	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
something	O
away	O
,	O
it	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
or	O
napkin	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
sound	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
sound	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
an	O
instrument	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
a	O
crow	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
instrument	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
dragged	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
strong	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
BECKHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
a	O
compting-house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
jingle	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
instrument	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
HAYWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
iron	O
in	O
the	O
cradle	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
noise	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
crow	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
M'MANUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
examined	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
try	O
the	O
crows	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fitted	O
every	O
place	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
the	O
crows	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WYNCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
HUSSEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
at	O
law	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
Talbot	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
struggling	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
a	O
jingle	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
picklock	O
keys	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
instrument	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
its	O
having	O
been	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
file	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
This	O
person	O
that	O
prosecutes	O
keeps	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Peacock	O
Burton	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
word	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
they	O
seized	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
AARON	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
conversed	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Brooker	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
Kelly	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
his	O
other	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
suspected	O
Johnson	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
;	O
searched	O
Kelley	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
right	O
man	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
flurried	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
suspected	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
absconded	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot-inn	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
but	O
a	O
foul	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
breches	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
SNEER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
skirt	O
being	O
found	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
trod	O
upon	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
heels	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
many	O
ill	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
his	O
pardon	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
18	O
d.	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
breaking	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
383.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PARKINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
30th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
Manchester	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
marry	O
and	O
take	O
to	O
wife	O
one	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
her	O
was	O
then	O
married	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
and	O
in	O
full	O
life	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
HENRY	O
ASPINALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
parish-clerk	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
the	O
collegiate	O
church	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
in	O
Manchester	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
original	O
marriage	O
entries	O
,	O
``	O
No	O
.	O
823.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
this	O
``	O
parish	O
and	O
town	O
of	O
Manchester	O
,	O
glazier	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Manchester	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
``	O
widow	O
,	O
married	O
by	O
banns	O
.	O
''	O
It	O
isregularly	O
entred	O
,	O
and	O
subscribed	O
by	O
the	O
parties	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
dated	O
29th	O
November	O
1789.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
parish	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
Holborn	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
Holborn	O
,	O
bachelor	O
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burns	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
this	O
church	O
by	O
licence	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
1791	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
attested	O
the	O
marriage	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
at	O
our	O
church	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHARLES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
accused	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
this	O
copy	O
of	O
a	O
certificate	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
truth	O
must	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
knew	O
when	O
I	O
married	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
four	O
children	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
wife	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
certificate	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
marriage	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
arraigns	O
.	O
)	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
BURNS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
September	O
;	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
following	O
Monday	O
I	O
discovered	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
living	O
in	O
Manchester	O
,	O
I	O
married	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
husband	O
living	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
she	O
eloped	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
marry	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
384.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAINSLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
cloth	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wiles	I-pers
;	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HOLMES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
maid	O
of	O
all	O
work	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wiles	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
a	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
the	O
great	O
coats	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
saw	O
upon	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
dropped	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
well	O
stair	O
case	O
;	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
then	O
burning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
thrown	O
down	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WILES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
very	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
where	O
I	O
always	O
keep	O
them	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
well	O
stair	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
;	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
coats	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BARROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
glass	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
assist	O
Mr.	O
Wiles	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
of	O
Wiles	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
two	O
bundles	O
,	O
seeing	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
different	O
way	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
bundle	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
inhabited	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
from	O
Wiles	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
them	O
tight	O
;	O
Petticoat-lane	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wiles	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
bundles	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thorpe	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wiles	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
first	O
bundle	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wiles	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
JACOB	B-pers
LYON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
concealed	O
;	O
this	O
great	O
coat	O
was	O
across	O
the	O
bundle	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
he	O
twisted	O
round	O
and	O
hurt	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
lame	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
said	O
damn	O
your	O
eyes	O
you	O
Jew	O
b	O
-	O
r	O
,	O
I	O
sha'nt	O
weigh	O
forty	O
yet	O
;	O
he	O
after	O
that	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
strike	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
strike	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GILDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
hallooed	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
Lyon	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Lyon	O
who	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bundle	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
seat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
nearly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
baize	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
callimanco	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
In	O
fact	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Catherine-wheel-alley	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
cousin	O
's	O
;	O
Lyons	O
accused	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
385.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
four	O
cotton	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
pieces	O
containing	O
thirty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Anstie	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ANSTIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
in	O
Catherine-street	B-place
,	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
of	O
New	O
Compton-street	O
,	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
us	O
as	O
our	O
calenderer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
coming	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
his	O
wrapper	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
whatever	O
we	O
had	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
frequently	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
within	O
reach	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
of	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
articles	O
,	O
four	O
cotton	O
shawls	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
for	O
gowns	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JEALOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Cranfield	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
20	O
,	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Richmond	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
sitting	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Richmond	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
my	O
eye	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
chintz	O
,	O
and	O
attempting	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Richmond	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
box	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
locked	O
and	O
one	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
box	O
this	O
property	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Anstie	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
pieces	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
where	O
theywere	O
sitting	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
four	O
cotton	O
shawls	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
five	O
more	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
articles	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
that	O
piece	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Jealous	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
paper	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
calendar	O
glazer	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
,	O
his	O
business	O
was	O
to	O
collect	O
things	O
and	O
carry	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Jealous	O
to	O
Richmond	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
Richmond	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
sitting	O
round	O
a	O
table	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
immediately	O
on	O
seeing	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
alarmed	O
;	O
Jealous	O
called	O
Richmond	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
immediately	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
begun	O
crying	O
out	O
;	O
Richmond	O
said	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
must	O
hear	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
began	O
crying	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
goods	O
in	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
much	O
agitated	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
window	O
;	O
Jealous	O
immediately	O
held	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
found	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
CRANFIELD	B-pers
RICHMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
20	O
,	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
to	O
board	O
at	O
three	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
goods	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
callicos	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
from	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
trunk	O
open	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
it	O
contained	O
things	O
in	O
brown	O
papers	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
open	O
which	O
contained	O
muslins	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Jealous	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
trunks	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
trunks	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
RICHMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
board	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
muslins	O
;	O
Jealous	O
came	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
boxes	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
contained	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sam	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
wish	O
that	O
trunk	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
he	O
brought	O
home	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
South	O
Sea	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Jealous	O
and	O
Welch	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
goods	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
Samuel	B-pers
Young	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Sam	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
shew	O
you	O
his	O
goods	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
his	O
ownself	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
nine	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
brought	O
those	O
articles	O
which	O
Jealous	O
took	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
colouring	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Watson	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
ever	O
sell	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
we	O
do	O
sometimes	O
on	O
the	O
shawls	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
any	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
callico	O
which	O
have	O
no	O
marks	O
,	O
but	O
are	O
our	O
sort	O
and	O
pattern	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
name	O
and	O
mark	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
this	O
mark	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
price	O
and	O
shop	O
mark	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
we	O
sometimes	O
sell	O
these	O
articles	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
possession	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
ever	O
was	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
go	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
.	O
These	O
shawls	O
have	O
the	O
private	O
mark	O
of	O
Anstie	O
and	O
Baker	O
,	O
I	O
cannottell	O
who	O
made	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
patterns	O
of	O
these	O
pieces	O
that	O
have	O
Welch	O
's	O
marks	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
such	O
patterns	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
pieces	O
without	O
marks	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
those	O
patterns	O
;	O
the	O
sixth	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Welch	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
proves	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
certainty	O
that	O
at	O
some	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
this	O
piece	O
from	O
Anstie	O
and	O
Baker	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
made	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
chalk	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
hasty	O
way	O
to	O
mark	O
hundreds	O
and	O
thousands	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
B.	O
I	O
recollect	O
no	O
other	O
customers	O
whose	O
names	O
begin	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
Anstie	O
and	O
Baker	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
has	O
an	O
A.	O
only	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
satisfactory	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
articles	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
four	O
cotton	O
shawls	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
chintz	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
is	O
worth	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
other	O
articles	O
are	O
worth	O
5	O
l.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
informed	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
twelve	O
indictments	O
against	O
this	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
386.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MUCKSTAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DUTTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
;	O
this	O
property	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
or	O
more	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
roll	O
tobacco	O
;	O
on	O
missing	O
it	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
neighbouring	O
tobacconists	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STOLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
tobacco	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
this	O
roll	O
of	O
tobacco	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
at	O
18	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
fair	O
price	O
,	O
we	O
pay	O
upwards	O
of	O
2	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
wholesale	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dutton	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dutton	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
roll	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hand	O
labour	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
shipmate	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
tobacco	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
who	O
sealed	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
JOB	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Dutton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
manufactured	O
it	O
myself	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
some	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stole	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
weighed	O
about	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
10	O
oz	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
distinguish	O
it	O
as	O
my	O
manufacture	O
,	O
at	O
York	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
kingdom	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
tobacco	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
shape	O
for	O
exportation	O
(	O
unrolls	O
the	O
tobacco	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
tobacco	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
a	O
fold	O
in	O
the	O
ends	O
peculiar	O
to	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
shipmate	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
drink	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
being	O
weary	O
with	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
roll	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
distressed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
bought	O
my	O
smoking	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
open	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scar	O
on	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
387.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
CHANDLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
fork	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Red-cross-street	B-place
,	I-place
East	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
very	O
early	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Venetian	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
turn	O
out	O
early	O
for	O
?	O
I	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
bag	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
Monarch	O
;	O
I	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
his	O
pockets	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
my	O
knife	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
escaped	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
knife	O
and	O
fork	O
.	O
(	O
Prosecutor	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
fork	O
produced	O
by	O
Dawson	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
this	O
knife	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
On	O
board	O
that	O
ship	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
knives	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
knife	O
only	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
388.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TENNANT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
six	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
tame	O
hen	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
geese	O
and	O
a	O
tame	O
hen	O
fowl	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
them	O
up	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Etherington	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
Kilburn	O
,	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
Sir	O
Sampson	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
told	O
us	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
most	O
we	O
could	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
nearly	O
spoiled	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
claw	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
bred	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
fowl	O
was	O
a	O
double	O
comb	O
pullet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ever	O
seen	O
by	O
me	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
GEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Etherington	O
,	O
of	O
Kilburn	O
Wells	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
collector	O
of	O
the	O
tolls	O
.	O
The	O
15th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
far	O
he	O
was	O
travelling	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
geese	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
robbing	O
a	O
hen	O
roost	O
?	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
fowls	O
and	O
six	O
geese	O
,	O
all	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
quite	O
hot	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
appeared	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
OSBORN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
Wilkinson	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
wasblood	O
in	O
the	O
out-house	O
where	O
the	O
geese	O
were	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
six	O
geese	O
and	O
a	O
tame	O
fowl	O
,	O
the	O
fowl	O
roosted	O
on	O
the	O
rack	O
with	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
geese	O
and	O
fowl	O
,	O
having	O
known	O
them	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
exceptions	O
of	O
the	O
fowls	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
common	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
these	O
geese	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
sack	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Gee	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
three	O
miles	O
from	O
the	O
turnpike	O
where	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
Aged	O
28	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
389.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MANNIKEY	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KINCAID	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
live	O
goose	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphrey	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUMPHREY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-end	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
goose	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
market	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
discovered	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
goose	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bethnal-green	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cow-keeper	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Humphrey	O
's	O
goose	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
out-house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
stick	O
put	O
over	O
the	O
fence	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
cut	O
its	O
throat	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
under	O
weeds	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Humphrey	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
.	O
-	O
PRESTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goose	O
taken	O
by	O
Fairfax	O
,	O
with	O
its	O
throat	O
cut	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
MANNIKEY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MANNIKEY	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KINCAID	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
[	O
Kincaid	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Mannikey	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
390.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
London	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
LONDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
hostler	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
across	O
Little	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
London	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
stockings	O
and	O
bed	O
gown	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
West-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
a	O
sweep	O
chimney	O
took	O
me	O
right	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
390.	O
MARY	B-pers
WOODHOUSE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
149	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-without	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
linen	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
's	O
,	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
serving	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
this	O
woman	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
serving	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COADISH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
liquor	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detained	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
where	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
serving	O
some	O
sheetings	O
;	O
the	O
printed	O
cotton	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
within	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
some	O
sheeting	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
what	O
she	O
bought	O
was	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hops	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
cotton	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cotton	O
at	O
Franklin	O
's	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
on	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
letters	O
are	O
,	O
U.	O
M.	O
X.	O
all	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
that	O
article	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
entered	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HOPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Irish	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
cotton	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
customer	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GADSDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
inst	O
.	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
liquor	O
shop	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Franklin	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
improperly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
property	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
part	O
tucked	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SACKWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
printed	O
cotton	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
(	O
Prosecutor	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
cotton	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
about	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
stock	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
that	O
customer	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
linen	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
is	O
30	O
s.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
ALBIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
gets	O
her	O
living	O
by	O
mending	O
gowns	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
three	O
children	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
391.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
NAIRN	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
NOON	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
TALBOT	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
RILEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
ten	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Twiddle	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anthony	O
.	O
LEVY	B-pers
TWIDDLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
whenthe	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
them	O
over	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
cut	O
off	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
fetch	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
something	O
for	O
shirts	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
secured	O
,	O
we	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
swear	O
positively	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
ten	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
several	O
pieces	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
shewed	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
shop	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
different	O
pieces	O
have	O
different	O
marks	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
this	O
piece	O
under	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
piece	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Sheldon	O
and	O
two	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
besides	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
SOLOMON	B-pers
SHELDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Twiddle	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
witness	O
attended	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
cloak	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
following	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
brought	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
muslin	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
muslin	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
in	O
characters	O
made	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
characters	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
sell	O
goods	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
sometimes	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
wrapper	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
opened	O
that	O
day	O
until	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
propriety	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
value	O
is	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
customers	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
EDMUNDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
person	O
to	O
help	O
fold	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
a	O
lady	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
adjoining	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
folded	O
part	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
loose	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
hers	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
owner	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
returned	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
owner	O
said	O
she	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
name	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
.	O
She	O
repeatedly	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
of	O
whom	O
?	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
property	O
to	O
Christian	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Gilson	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
shop	O
mark	O
to	O
Twidle	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
first	O
came	O
she	O
appeared	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
she	O
appeared	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
CHRISTIAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
each	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
after	O
all	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
she	O
appeared	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
way	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Twidle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
our	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
three	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
she	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Rosemary	O
Branch	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
pledge	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
the	O
gentleman	O
shewed	O
me	O
only	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
he	O
took	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
392.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
UNDERWOOD	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
WHITAKER	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
And	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PURSER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MEADOWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dyer	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pint	O
mug	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
SWALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
with	O
three	O
artichoaks	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Whitaker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
ordered	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Fogg	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
or	O
mistress	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
apprentice	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
twist	O
the	O
stalks	O
off	O
the	O
artichoaks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
lad	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
mug	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
wait	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
street	O
where	O
my	O
master	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
mug	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RICHARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
laying	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
on	O
some	O
straw	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Whitaker	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Purser	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Whitaker	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
denied	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
squatted	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
I	O
pulled	O
this	O
mug	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BENCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
patrol	O
took	O
this	O
mug	O
out	O
of	O
Whitaker	O
's	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Purser	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
mug	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
crest	O
,	O
a	O
hawk	O
upon	O
a	O
coronet	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
is	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
50	O
s.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Whitaker	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
him	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
sent	O
any	O
artichoaks	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
WHITAKER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
absent	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
this	O
accident	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
from	O
two	O
to	O
four	O
at	O
the	O
waterside	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
drop	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
let	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
destitute	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
lay	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
that	O
lived	O
up	O
stairs	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
artichoaks	O
to	O
sell	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Whitaker	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
WM	O
.	O
UNDERWOOD	O
,	O
alias	O
WHITAKER	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PURSER	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
393.	O
SIMON	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
coach	O
cushions	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAYSTICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cushion	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coach	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
from	O
the	O
stand	O
in	O
West	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Petticoat-lane	B-place
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tobit	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
drive	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
drive	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
an	O
alley	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
turn	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public-house	O
and	O
drank	O
some	O
negus	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
coach	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
coach	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
off-side	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
seats	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
a	O
Jew	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
my	O
seats	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
alley	O
opposite	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
Simon	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
bring	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
never	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Shimmer	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
seats	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
hand	O
me	O
over	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
your	O
things	O
shall	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
it	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Simon	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
with	O
my	O
seats	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
thank	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
five	O
minutes	O
later	O
you	O
never	O
would	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
seats	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
him	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
seats	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Shimmer	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
seats	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
have	O
only	O
played	O
the	O
rogue	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
serve	O
you	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
you	O
any	O
good	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
ten	O
years	O
hence	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
394.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WALLIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Kaye	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
KAYE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cheese	O
on	O
Monday	O
forenoon	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cheese	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
A	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
offered	O
one	O
to	O
sale	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cheese	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
cheese	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
H	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
eight	O
in	O
a	O
pile	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
Mr.	O
LEE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
this	O
cheese	O
from	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Kaye	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
here	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
395.	O
MARY	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
and	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MANN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Dartmouth-street	O
to	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
;	O
she	O
unbuttonedmy	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
connected	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
her	O
civil	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
star	O
light	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JENNINGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
two	O
more	O
women	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
I	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
by	O
whose	O
order	O
?	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
She	O
then	O
delivered	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
fell	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
far	O
off	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
till	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
you	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
396.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CLOUGH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Wolfe	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Wolfe	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
.	O
WOLFE	O
LEVY	O
sworn	O
.	O
Coming	O
down	O
Winfield-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
this	O
girl	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
into	O
her	O
lodgings	O
in	O
George-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
hat	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
beds	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
many	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
.	O
She	O
throwed	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
opera	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
patrol	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LEYDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
patrol	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
half	O
undressed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
397.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TELLFAIR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
twelve	O
striped	O
Bath	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
five	O
Bath	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
thirteen	O
pair	O
of	O
fustian	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
velveret	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
And	O
ANN	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROUNGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
slopman	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
aMr	O
.	O
Buckwell	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
at	O
Tenterden	O
,	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RANDAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brounger	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
to	O
the	O
George	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	I-place
Borough	I-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
wrappers	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Buckwell	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
Tenterden	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Willoughby	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLOUGHBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Randall	O
,	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
directed	O
as	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
ELLIOT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
package	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
directed	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
in	O
London	O
before	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
waggon	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
one	O
Pass	O
drove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
searched	O
nothing	O
else	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
ropes	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
covered	O
waggon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
partner	O
,	O
or	O
joint	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
we	O
received	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
a	O
waggon	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
proceeded	O
from	O
Day	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Old-street	B-place
;	O
we	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
Carpmeal	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Tellfair	O
standing	O
over	O
this	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
divided	O
,	O
being	O
all	O
unpacked	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
,	O
come	O
hither	O
,	O
whose	O
property	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
yours	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Townsend	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
Tellfair	O
)	O
brought	O
it	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
-	O
CARPMEAL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Townsend	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
's	O
daughter	O
opened	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
bills	O
of	O
parcels	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
said	O
,	O
Tellfair	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Brounger	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
TELLFAIR	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TELLFAIR	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
398.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KITCHIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Abada	I-pers
.	O
AARON	B-pers
ABADA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
servant	O
,	O
or	O
chairwoman	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ABADA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
the	O
spoon	O
taken	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
necessity	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Abada	O
.	O
)	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
399.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
lead	O
pencil	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
MIDDLETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
stationer	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
pencil	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pencil	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
HUGH	B-pers
PICKERING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
pencil	O
cases	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
several	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
alone	O
,	O
nobody	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
patrol	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
PATROL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
a	O
lady	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
having	O
stolen	O
a	O
silver	O
pencil	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
pencils	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
's	O
patrol	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
's	O
patrol	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
pencil	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
sleeve	O
.	O
-	O
STEWART	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
's	O
patrol	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pencil	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Pickering	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
pencil	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
send	O
another	O
to	O
my	O
cousins	O
at	O
school	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Patrol	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
that	O
pencil	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
intrinsic	O
value	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
4	O
s.	O
not	O
5	O
s.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
400.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLINCH	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BLAIR	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
metal	O
pap	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
twelve	O
metal	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
thirty-six	O
metal	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
EDMUND	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
pewterer	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
20	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
informing	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
some	O
goods	O
about	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
at	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
every	O
workman	O
;	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
spoons	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
another	O
dozen	O
found	O
under	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
spoons	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
readthe	O
letter	O
;	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
spoons	O
were	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
behind	O
where	O
Clinch	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rustling	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Owen	O
shuffling	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bundle	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
between	O
his	O
legs	O
;	O
neither	O
Clinch	O
nor	O
Blair	O
stooped	O
down	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
carpet	O
on	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
over	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
spoon	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
paper	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SILK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
journeymen	O
;	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
sharp	O
look	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
placed	O
myself	O
opposite	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
reading	O
the	O
letter	O
I	O
observed	O
Clinch	O
stoop	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
under	O
the	O
chair	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
spoons	O
,	O
which	O
master	O
opened	O
;	O
then	O
Pitt	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
then	O
:	O
while	O
these	O
spoons	O
were	O
examining	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
parcel	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Owen	O
,	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
chair	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
before	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
between	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
charged	O
he	O
moved	O
his	O
situation	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DODSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
search	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
nothing	O
particular	O
till	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Owen	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
shift	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stoop	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
dropped	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
HURST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
I	O
sell	O
hard	O
ware	O
and	O
spoons	O
;	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Clinch	O
offered	O
and	O
sold	O
me	O
some	O
spoons	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
dozen	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
make	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoons	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
near	O
Clinch	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
marked	O
R.	O
Y	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
marked	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
CLINCH	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
about	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
table	O
spoons	O
and	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
a	O
message	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
stands	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
OWEN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
that	O
night	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLINCH	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
one	O
year	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BLAIR	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
401.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
yards	O
of	O
sacking	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
and	O
Frederick	B-pers
Klein	I-pers
.	O
FREDERICK	B-pers
KLEIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
sacking	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
BROTHERHEAD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
sacking	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CATOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
this	O
man	O
Brotherhead	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
100	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
bring	O
itback	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
is	O
marked	O
D	O
7	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
24	O
yards	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
20	O
pieces	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
20	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
made	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
sack	O
?	O
-	O
All	O
in	O
a	O
roll	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
POCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
sacking	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
back	O
quietly	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sacking	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
whom	O
knew	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
402.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CHAMBERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Marseilles	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sattinet	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kinslen	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Howden	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KINSLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
opposite	O
Little	O
Britain	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
nine	O
last	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
front	O
room	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
of	O
stealing	O
several	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
fire	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
shoes	O
fourteen	O
duplicates	O
;	O
her	O
bed-room	O
is	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
above	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
upon	O
examining	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
pledged	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
the	O
breeches	O
are	O
velveteen	O
,	O
the	O
stockings	O
are	O
worsted	O
;	O
a	O
coat	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
clothes	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
HOWDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
mended	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
stockings	O
;	O
those	O
stockings	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
(	O
Prosecutor	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
403.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
NORRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
breast-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOVELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HITCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ware	O
,	O
Herts	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
breast-buckle	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
in	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
then	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Ware	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
away	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
's	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
breast-buckle	O
with	O
Hitch	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
CROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
two	O
spoons	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
enough	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
till	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
beat	O
Brown	O
;	O
he	O
beat	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
some	O
relation	O
to	O
Lovell	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
LOVELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
say	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
niece	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
prove	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
spoons	O
:	O
those	O
five	O
tea-spoons	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
marked	O
I.	O
P.	O
my	O
first	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
or	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sleep	O
there	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
married	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
aunt	O
.	O
(	O
Deposes	O
to	O
the	O
table-spoons	O
and	O
breast-buckle	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
marked	O
W.	O
A.	O
L.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
breast-buckle	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
gave	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Green-street	O
,	O
Enfield	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
(	O
Aged	O
17	O
.	O
)	O
Privately	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
404.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
DORAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twenty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KENDALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
lead	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
yesterday	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
gates	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
pursued	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
some	O
lead	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Kendall	O
's	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
hostler	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
.	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
deposit	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Ball-yard	O
.	O
``	O
(	O
The	O
lead	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
foreman	O
of	O
the	O
carpenters	O
cut	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
another	O
time	O
with	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
fourteen	O
pence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
405.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Baltus	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
BALTUS	B-pers
FORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
31	I-place
,	I-place
Swallow-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
miss	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
pair	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
often	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
particularly	O
concerning	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
hair-dressing	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
in	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
,	O
is	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shoes	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
406.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
lives	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
2	I-place
,	I-place
Percy-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
Stevens-street	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
accidentally	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DOLSTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
by	O
a	O
watch-box	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
part	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
pump	O
next	O
the	O
mews	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
is	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
KNIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
building	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
mews	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
AMMETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
nine	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WHITEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
detained	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
the	O
lead	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
;	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
ript	O
off	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Matthews	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Stephen-street	O
,	O
how	O
near	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dennis	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
200	O
yards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lead	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
407.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
CRAWLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
bed	O
furniture	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Marseilles	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
dimity	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Assen	I-pers
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
ASSEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perfumer	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
10	I-place
,	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
theshop	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
loose	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
I	O
once	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DALTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
picking	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHILDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
first	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
articles	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
offered	O
me	O
sixpence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
408.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
COBURN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Egan	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
four	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Devon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
then	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
EGAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Egan	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CAMPBELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Egan	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
City	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Devon	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
family	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
attacked	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
pass	O
by	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Devon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
room	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
