TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SIXTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Islington	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
DALBY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
opposite	O
Rolls-buildings	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCII	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Letters	O
and	O
Messages	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
left	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
instantly	O
forwarded	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
,	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BULLER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Highgate	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
*	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Burr	I-pers
served	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Minchin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shanck	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Ibberson	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hodgkinson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Walbank	I-pers
Zachariah	B-pers
Broxop	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
James	B-pers
Elliott	I-pers
George	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
George	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Herrick	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hyder	I-pers
Lewis	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Sudlow	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
311.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
and	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Farrer	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealingtherein	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
white	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
check	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
tin	O
canisters	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
large	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
;	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
nine	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
eight	O
unmade	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beckett	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
FARRER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
58	I-place
,	I-place
Penton-street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
house	O
there	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
every	O
shutter	O
and	O
door	O
and	O
window	O
myself	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
alarmed	O
till	O
I	O
rose	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
window	O
shutter	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strange	O
tinder	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
bunch	O
of	O
matches	O
and	O
flint	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
to	O
strike	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
kitchen	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dresser	O
drawer	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
linnen	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
Whitman	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WHITMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
by	O
Underwood	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BLACKETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
UNDERWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Southampton-place	O
,	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
Road	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Farrer	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rattle	O
spring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
big	O
bundle	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
garden	O
pails	O
and	O
a	O
court	O
I	O
stopped	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
Joshua	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
I	O
took	O
my	O
ownself	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
he	O
stopped	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
brother	O
;	O
them	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
Johnson	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
while	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Whitman	O
looked	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
Whitman	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
cross	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Constitution	O
Row	O
,	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
with	O
bundles	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
,	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
they	O
crossed	O
into	O
a	O
brick	O
field	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
his	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
road	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
perceived	O
us	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
to	O
them	O
little	O
huts	O
called	O
Mortimer	O
's	O
Folly	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
watchman	O
in	O
Southampton	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
chuck	O
away	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Farrer	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
from	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discover	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
countenance	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
After	O
day	O
break	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
day	O
break	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HERBERT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
the	O
cow-keeper	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
farm	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
with	O
bundles	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
bundles	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
thrown	O
their	O
bundles	O
away	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BUNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
jump	O
over	O
a	O
bank	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Farrer	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
bank	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bottle	O
there	O
afterwards	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
three	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
hill	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
bundles	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
lead	O
mill	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
club	O
that	O
morning	O
till	O
near	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
liqour	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
hours	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
hours	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
late	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
work	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
rightly	O
what	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
club	O
meet	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
,	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
39	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
312.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HOUGHTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	O
PERRY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
but	O
retired	O
to	O
Wolverhampton	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Tavistock	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Charles	B-place
street	I-place
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
a	O
shabby	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
met	O
me	O
I	O
supposed	O
by	O
accident	O
;	O
two	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
immediately	O
and	O
pinioned	O
my	O
arms	O
;	O
they	O
pushed	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
who	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
round	O
and	O
pushed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
against	O
some	O
shutters	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
stood	O
behind	O
me	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
reel	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
watch	O
was	O
set	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Russel	O
Court	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
any	O
body	O
after	O
that	O
till	O
I	O
met	O
these	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
motion	O
about	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
struck	O
;	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
pointed	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
set	O
out	O
a	O
running	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
up	O
Tavistock	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Tavistock	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
faced	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
people	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
were	O
close	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
coat	O
did	O
you	O
describe	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
dark	O
blue	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
robbed	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
Immediately	O
,	O
perhaps	O
not	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
?	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
Thompson	O
and	O
Forbes	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
taken	O
hold	O
of	O
another	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
;	O
in	O
Tavistock	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
east	O
end	O
,	O
near	O
Charles	O
street	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
paces	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
bustle	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
stagger	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
hastily	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
exclaimed	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
!	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
repeated	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
fix	O
upon	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
up	O
Tavistock	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Perry	B-pers
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ruins	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
burned	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
violently	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
escaped	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
retreated	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
the	O
crowd	O
knocked	O
us	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
Mr.	O
F.	O
made	O
his	O
way	O
through	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
FORBES	O
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
shop	O
is	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Tavistock	O
court	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
making	O
a	O
set	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fight	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
retreated	O
and	O
Thompson	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
seeing	O
him	O
a	O
respectable	O
looking	O
character	O
I	O
followed	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
sparring	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
came	O
up	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
's	O
him	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
MORANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
from	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
garden	O
stuff	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
CHIEF	O
BARON	O
.	O
313.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ABBOTT	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
KING	I-pers
KEELING	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Howarth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
twelve	O
lawn	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
four	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
six	O
callico	O
half-handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoebuckles	O
,	O
value	O
63	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
lancet	O
case	O
,	O
containing	O
six	O
lancets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
hand	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-pot	O
stand	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
sugar	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
And	O
PHILIP	B-pers
GOODWIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
a	O
muslin	O
neck	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
lancets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
razor	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Schoen	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separately	O
,	O
by	O
desire	O
of	O
prisoner	O
Keeling	O
.	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
HOWARTH	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
about	O
eight	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
informed	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bureau	O
and	O
trunk	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
closet	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
area	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
round	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
neck	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
at	O
Keeling	O
's	O
lodgings	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
bureau	O
I	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
wafer	O
seal	O
;	O
Abbott	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Keeling	O
's	O
lodgings	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
linen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
two	O
houses	O
in	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
MILLINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howarth	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
made	O
perfectly	O
fast	O
;	O
Keeling	O
came	O
that	O
night	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
message	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
Keeling	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
Drury	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DRURY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howarth	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Keeling	O
and	O
Abbott	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
,	O
in	O
Stafford	O
street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
they	O
proposed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
brake	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
in	O
Dover	O
street	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
should	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Caverner	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
bolts	O
open	O
;	O
Keeling	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
leave	O
only	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
materials	O
once	O
to	O
break	O
all	O
the	O
bolts	O
in	O
the	O
kingdom	O
;	O
Keeling	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
shrub	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
sleep	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
plate	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
terrified	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
surely	O
be	O
taken	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
swore	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
expected	O
to	O
find	O
many	O
quid	O
,	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Abbott	O
and	O
Keeling	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
a	O
soup	O
ladle	O
dropped	O
by	O
Keeling	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
Mr.	O
H	O
's	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
the	O
word	O
quid	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
means	O
guineas	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
never	O
proposed	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
drunk	O
at	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
conversations	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
!	O
was	O
you	O
always	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
always	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
conversation	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CAVERNER	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Abbott	O
and	O
Keeling	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Howarth	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
Keeling	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
Burn	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Howarth	O
's	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
Keeling	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
sleep	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
prison	O
twelve	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
three	O
conversations	O
with	O
York	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
proposed	O
by	O
Burn	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GRANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
in	O
Lancaster	O
court	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Abbott	O
and	O
Keeling	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
quitted	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
whether	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
or	O
left	O
.	O
HARRY	B-pers
PLUME	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Dover	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
Keeling	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
weeks	O
ago	O
Keeling	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SHERLOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
property	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
magistrate	O
:	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Howarth	O
,	O
some	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gabriel	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Howarth	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Howarth	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
and	O
several	O
handkerchiefs	O
)	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
knee	O
buckles	O
;	O
(	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Goodwin	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
Lord	O
Mazarene	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Abbott	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KING	I-pers
KEELING	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ABBOTT	I-pers
,	O
PHILIP	B-pers
GOODWIN	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
recommended	O
Keeling	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
314.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DYER	I-pers
,	O
BISHOP	B-pers
UNDERWOOD	I-pers
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
muslin	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Enoch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
immediately	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
BISHOP	O
UNDERWOOD	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DYER	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
BULLER	O
.	O
315.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LIGHTOWLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
falsely	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
,	O
forge	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
cause	O
and	O
procure	O
to	O
be	O
falsely	O
made	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
willingly	O
act	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
false	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
order	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
dated	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
thereto	O
subscribed	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hugh	I-pers
Hoare	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
description	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Hoare	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
96	O
l.	O
the	O
tenor	O
of	O
which	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
order	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
``	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
pay	O
``	O
the	O
bearer	O
96	O
l.	O
yours	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
,	O
``	O
April	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
1792	O
;	O
Messrs	O
.	O
Hoare	O
.	O
''	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hugh	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
feloniously	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
,	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
order	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
count	O
.	O
Charging	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
with	O
feloniously	O
and	O
falsely	O
making	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
same	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
.	O
A	O
fourth	O
count	O
.	O
For	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Coust	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLOUGHBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Hoare	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
firm	O
of	O
their	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hugh	I-pers
Hoare	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
firm	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
day	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
come	O
to	O
their	O
banking	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
somewhere	O
near	O
four	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
banking	O
shop	O
and	O
presented	O
the	O
draft	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
as	O
the	O
draft	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
for	O
payment	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
receiving	O
the	O
draft	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
four	O
20	O
l.	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remainder	O
in	O
cash	O
;	O
the	O
draft	O
is	O
for	O
96	O
l.	O
upon	O
his	O
answering	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
draft	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
persuaded	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
;	O
I	O
again	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
question	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
same	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
referred	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
who	O
concurred	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
questions	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
put	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
better	O
tell	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
draft	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
Bow	O
Street	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
drawn	O
on	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
very	O
frequently	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
cash	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
(	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
draft	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
again	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
firmly	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
judgment	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
doubt	O
that	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
draft	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
conceived	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
should	O
you	O
have	O
paid	O
on	O
his	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
Most	O
certainly	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
mode	O
of	O
your	O
judgment	O
,	O
whether	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
's	O
,	O
is	O
derived	O
from	O
the	O
drafts	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
presented	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
.	O
Your	O
judgment	O
at	O
present	O
is	O
made	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
writing	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
other	O
writing	O
of	O
drafts	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
paid	O
?	O
-	O
Just	O
so	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
make	O
up	O
your	O
mind	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
drafts	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
's	O
presented	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
honoured	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
hand	O
writing	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
that	O
;	O
read	O
,	O
``	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
pay	O
the	O
bearer	O
96	O
l.	O
yours	O
G	O
.	O
``	O
Hardinge	O
.	O
''	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Besides	O
this	O
being	O
very	O
dissimilar	O
to	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
mode	O
of	O
his	O
drawing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
present	O
draws	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
check	O
,	O
and	O
signs	O
his	O
name	O
different	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Had	O
that	O
taken	O
place	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
some	O
peculiar	O
circumstance	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
ask	O
what	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
had	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Hoare	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hoare	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
his	O
person	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
blind	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Bow	O
street	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
a	O
draft	O
being	O
shewn	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
perfectly	O
well	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
-	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
marked	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
's	O
handwriting	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
very	O
particularly	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
knowing	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
degree	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
knowledge	O
you	O
have	O
of	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisonerat	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
your	O
hearing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
State	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
what	O
passed	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
accidentally	O
sitting	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
immediately	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
seeing	O
the	O
draft	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
therefore	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
round	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
posted	O
myself	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
interrogated	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
whether	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
morning	O
or	O
the	O
preceding	O
evening	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
received	O
it	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
persuaded	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
circuit	O
to	O
Wales	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
town	O
the	O
preceding	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
what	O
purpose	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
some	O
horses	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
had	O
purchased	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
at	O
Llandovery	O
in	O
Wales	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
other	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
related	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
recollect	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
persuade	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
passed	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
draft	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Which	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
reason	O
why	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
always	O
write	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
nor	O
confine	O
himself	O
to	O
one	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
writing	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
South	O
Wales	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
a	O
check	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
drew	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
writing	O
he	O
writes	O
so	O
different	O
in	O
drawing	O
his	O
drafts	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
letters	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
every	O
day	O
and	O
every	O
hour	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
South	O
Wales	O
till	O
Saturday	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
reason	O
then	O
for	O
your	O
thinking	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
's	O
writing	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Wales	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
presented	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
reason	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
That	O
note	O
you	O
know	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
written	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
reason	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
this	O
note	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
a	O
check	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Otherwise	O
you	O
say	O
Mr.	O
Hardinge	O
writes	O
so	O
many	O
hands	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
say	O
which	O
is	O
which	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
writes	O
in	O
so	O
different	O
a	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
writes	O
as	O
different	O
hands	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
letters	O
in	O
the	O
alphabet	O
almost	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
MACMANUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
attending	O
the	O
Publick-office	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
confession	O
signed	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Permit	O
me	O
to	O
ask	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
were	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hoare	O
's	O
shop	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
not	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
yourself	O
had	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
:	O
for	O
this	O
was	O
drawn	O
up	O
before	O
Isaw	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Kitchener	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Rant	O
that	O
is	O
under-clerk	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Lightowler	O
was	O
taken	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
talked	O
a	O
deal	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
turned	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
signed	O
this	O
confession	O
then	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
question	O
that	O
is	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
asked	O
you	O
before	O
this	O
is	O
read	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
to	O
your	O
knowledge	O
,	O
made	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
,	O
or	O
used	O
any	O
threats	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
passed	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
magistrate	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
over	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lavender	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Read	O
.	O
``	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
The	O
``	O
voluntary	O
examination	O
and	O
confession	O
of	O
``	O
Richard	B-pers
Lightowler	I-pers
,	O
charged	O
with	O
forgery	O
,	O
``	O
taken	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
``	O
who	O
acknowledges	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
order	O
``	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
purporting	O
``	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
``	O
on	O
Messrs.	O
Hoare	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
handwriting	O
``	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
,	O
``	O
but	O
was	O
wrote	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
examinant	O
,	O
``	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
,	O
consent	O
,	O
or	O
approbation	O
``	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Hardinge	I-pers
,	O
``	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
for	O
payment	O
.	O
''	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
entirely	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
your	O
counsel	O
has	O
not	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Clearly	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
suggest	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
grand	O
mistake	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Macmanus	O
's	O
evidence	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
confession	O
was	O
ever	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
to	O
Macmanus	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Lightowler	O
says	O
.	O
Macmanus	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lavender	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
likely	O
person	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
thoughts	O
of	O
its	O
doing	O
me	O
a	O
service	O
:	O
this	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
very	O
candidly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Macmanus	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lavender	O
read	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
Lavender	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
prepared	O
then	O
to	O
say	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
over	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
Lavender	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
serve	O
me	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
harm	O
in	O
your	O
suggestion	O
of	O
the	O
question	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
or	O
Jury	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
do	O
it	O
yourself	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
here	O
.	O
Apprehending	O
from	O
the	O
message	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
worthy	O
solicitor	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
trial	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
prepare	O
myself	O
with	O
any	O
witnesses	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
uttering	O
,	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Forgery	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
bowed	O
respectfully	O
,	O
and	O
retired	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
316.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
inside	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
outside	O
tortoiseshell	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
stone	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rowntree	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROWNTREE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3	I-place
,	I-place
Great	I-place
York-street	I-place
,	I-place
Swan-yard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
.	O
Iam	O
a	O
copper-plate	O
printer	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
and	O
cook's-shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back-room	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
dinner	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
victuals	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
lad	O
and	O
got	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
lay	O
behind	O
a	O
shutter	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
It	O
cost	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
when	O
new	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
chain	O
and	O
seals	O
cost	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
at	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
behind	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
18	O
minutes	O
after	O
twelve	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pursued	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
watch	O
behind	O
a	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
Mr.	O
Rowntree	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
One	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
ringing	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
coals	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
error	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
mercy	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
but	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
52	O
,	O
in	O
Skinner's-street	O
;	O
she	O
knows	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
goal	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Stealing	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
317.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
8	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
gravy	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
soup	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Breynton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
.	O
VALENTINE	O
COOK	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Dr.	O
John	B-pers
Breynton	I-pers
,	O
he	O
lodges	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
63	I-place
,	I-place
Edgeware-road	I-place
,	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
before	O
four	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
lift	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
themselves	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
gentleman	O
of	O
74	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
foot	O
was	O
too	O
quick	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
silver	O
soup	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
6	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
and	O
the	O
gravy	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
wanting	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
sold	O
any	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WEBSTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
64	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
word	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
those	O
spoons	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
fetched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
begging	O
pardon	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
articles	O
are	O
,	O
and	O
judge	O
what	O
the	O
value	O
is	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
318.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Lowden	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
A	O
third	O
count	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FOREMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Southend	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
on	O
some	O
business	O
for	O
my	O
masters	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Lowden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Walworth-stairs	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
masters	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Builder	O
's	O
Price-book	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Middle-row	O
,	O
Holborn	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
about	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
subpoenaed	O
on	O
a	O
trial	O
from	O
Lincolnshire	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
tired	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Walking	O
up	O
Holborn	O
in	O
conversation	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
stooped	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
a	O
publick-house	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
who	O
kept	O
it	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
receipt	O
,	O
bought	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
diamond	O
cross	O
,	O
value	O
230	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
diamond	O
cross	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
never	O
in	O
London	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
fool	O
then	O
?	O
what	O
passed	O
next	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
the	O
receipt	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
unless	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
prize	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
cross	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
expected	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
half	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
pretending	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
card	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Blundell	O
,	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Holborn	O
Hill	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Blundell	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Blundell	O
's	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
you	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
your	O
money	O
yet	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Blundell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ram	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
quartered	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Blundell	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Ram	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
trial	O
on	O
from	O
Lincolnshire	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
home	O
a	O
fortnight	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Old-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
into	O
Old-street	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
slipped	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
this	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
officers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
98	O
guineas	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
officer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carpmeal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Foreman	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
difficulty	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
in	O
parting	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
bargain	O
which	O
you	O
know	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
your	O
master	O
intrusted	O
you	O
with	O
this	O
money	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
pay	O
the	O
men	O
at	O
Southend	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
this	O
purse	O
dropt	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
that	O
proposed	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
gentleman	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
That	O
gentleman	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
most	O
active	O
part	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
BRADY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Castle	O
inn	O
:	O
I	O
recollect	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
gentleman	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
the	O
business	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foreman	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Foreman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
ruined	O
me	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
what	O
have	O
they	O
done	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
105	O
guineas	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
this	O
discourse	O
,	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
in	O
:	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Foreman	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
to-day	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Foreman	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
105	O
guineas	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
drank	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Owen	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Brady	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Owen	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
Foreman	O
first	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
when	O
Foreman	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
all	O
till	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
parties	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
in	O
company	O
but	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Foreman	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
Foreman	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
me	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
promise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
last	O
,	O
me	O
and	O
Carpmeal	O
and	O
another	O
officer	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clayton	O
's	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
remained	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back-yard	O
seeing	O
them	O
play	O
at	O
skittles	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
somebody	O
calling	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
-	O
do	O
not	O
beat	O
me	O
!	O
-	O
do	O
not	O
beat	O
me	O
!	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Carpmeal	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
all	O
this	O
noise	O
about	O
,	O
somebody	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
a	O
fighting	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
surprise	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
were	O
apparently	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
fighting	O
.	O
Owen	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
hair	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
entry	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
all	O
this	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Foreman	O
,	O
was	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
oh	O
!	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
pity	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
-	O
robbed	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
;	O
why	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
dropped	O
a	O
purse	O
;	O
oh	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
this	O
cross	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
worthabout	O
half-a-guinea	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
thereabout	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cross	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
98	O
of	O
the	O
guineas	O
have	O
been	O
recovered	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
105	O
;	O
Carpmeal	O
has	O
them	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARPMEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Townsend	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
this	O
property	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
received	O
for	O
the	O
cross	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
7	O
guineas	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
98	O
guineas	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
purse	O
with	O
the	O
cross	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
half	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
it	O
is	O
valuable	O
property	O
,	O
indeed	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
note	O
payable	O
to	O
the	O
bearer	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
130	O
l.	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
that	O
105	O
guineas	O
and	O
the	O
100	O
l.	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
diamond	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
appointment	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
moved	O
to	O
arrest	O
the	O
judgment	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
the	O
judgment	O
be	O
respited	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
.	O
319.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
DAKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
PIPPARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
footstep	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
petticoat	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
petticoat	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
my	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stupefied	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
:	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
320.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Jerdein	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAYLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Jerdein	O
's	O
coachman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
from	O
the	O
coach-house	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
dress	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
coach	O
in	O
the	O
coach-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
shift	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
withthe	O
coat	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
chuck	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
stable-yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
321.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
proper	O
monies	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
one	O
bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HERBERT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Fountain	I-place
in	I-place
Shire	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
tea	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
pint	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
recourse	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
bag	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
bank-notes	O
and	O
cash	O
were	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
with	O
himself	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
first	O
at	O
Union	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
confession	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
signed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
I	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
voluntary	O
examination	O
and	O
confession	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
read	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
322.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STONEHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
,	O
Penelope	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
their	O
properties	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MATTHEW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
in	O
Oxford-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
two	O
sisters	O
,	O
Penelope	O
and	O
Rebecca	O
:	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
shop-window	O
was	O
broke	O
last	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
near	O
eleven	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
and	O
another	O
lad	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
at	O
supper	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
glass	O
crack	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
a	O
remnant	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
-	O
DODRY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produced	O
these	O
seven	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
sawthe	O
prisoner	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hardly	O
knew	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
confusion	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
REDMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Great	O
Argyle-street	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Argyle-street	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
PRATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
Swallow-street	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
glass	O
break	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
across	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
nigh	O
King-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
sarsenet	O
facing	O
Sharp	O
the	O
brewer	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
Little	O
Argyle-street	O
into	O
Great	O
Argyle-street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
sarsenet	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
wine	O
merchant	O
,	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
running	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
running	O
and	O
his	O
clothes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
gave	O
it	O
immediately	O
to	O
Matthew	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CLAIR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Dodry	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
window	O
break	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Apple-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
.	O
-	O
SMITH	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
Oxford-Road	O
on	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
window	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
dragging	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
and	O
me	O
followed	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
men	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
rather	O
retreated	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
those	O
two	O
fellows	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shop	O
had	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
across	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MORRENNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
following	O
past	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
sprung	O
my	O
rastle	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
captain	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
to	O
Bridge	O
Town	O
in	O
Barbadoes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
ten	O
months	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
Captain	O
Carey	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Blackheath	O
.	O
A	O
lad	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
same	O
ship	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
met	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
plasterer	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mob	O
came	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
323.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
steal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PROCTOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
How	O
,	O
Theobald	O
's	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Queen-street	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
person	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
home	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
down	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
knocked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
nor	O
as	O
far	O
off	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
from	O
you	O
:	O
a	O
boy	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
but	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
JOHN	O
M'COY	O
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
I	O
heard	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
hair	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
charge	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRESNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
ten	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rattle	O
sprang	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
assisted	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
deposited	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
VALENTINE	O
RUMLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watch-house-keeper	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
landlord	O
belonging	O
to	O
this	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
so	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
parents	O
poor	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
little	O
Boy	O
set	O
up	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Twelve	O
years	O
old	O
this	O
summer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
you	O
are	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
speak	O
when	O
you	O
swear	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
to	O
tell	O
lies	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
what	O
is	O
truth	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
lie	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
right	O
.	O
(	O
Sworn	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
mind	O
you	O
are	O
sworn	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
you	O
appeal	O
to	O
God	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
is	O
truth	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newtener	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
coal-shed	O
,	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
Cross	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
Cross	O
Lane	O
goes	O
into	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
goes	O
into	O
Queen-street	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
rattle	O
sprung	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
give	O
charge	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
May	O
be	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
''	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
looking	O
besides	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
laying	O
between	O
two	O
tubs	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
our	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
whole	O
parcel	O
of	O
blackguards	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
landlord	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
``	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
!	O
''	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
soul	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
324.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MEAD	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
21	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WAKEFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
mare	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
missing	O
by	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BOWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
dealt	O
in	O
horses	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
mare	O
of	O
Holbrook	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mead	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
19	O
guineas	O
and	O
another	O
horse	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Bishop	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
I	O
was	O
applied	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wakefield	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
doctor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
gaol	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HOLBROOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
stole	O
Mr.	O
Wakefield	O
's	O
mare	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wakefield	O
's	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
stable	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
one	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
we	O
set	O
off	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Taddle	O
House	O
,	O
near	O
Frome	O
in	O
Somersetshire	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowell	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
fine	O
mare	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
sell	O
her	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
make	O
a	O
chop	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
35	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
19	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
poney	O
;	O
the	O
19	O
guineas	O
was	O
shared	O
among	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
this	O
line	O
of	O
thieving	O
18	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
stolen	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mead	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
to	O
Dixon	O
or	O
Bruce	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Taddle	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
mare	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Mead	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
credit	O
16	O
or	O
18	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
people	O
to	O
testify	O
that	O
Holbrook	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
was	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
a	O
farthing	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
supposed	O
I	O
would	O
steal	O
this	O
or	O
other	O
horses	O
without	O
benefit	O
to	O
myself	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Lucas	O
brought	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Bowell	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Akerman	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowell	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
one	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coal-dealer	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Holbrook	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Holbrook	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
since	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
their	O
hearing	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
would	O
become	O
of	O
Mead	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
liberty	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
subpoenaed	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
.	O
SQUIRE	O
BRUCE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
rope-maker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Dixon	O
when	O
Holbrook	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hurt	O
Mead	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
himself	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
;	O
this	O
conversation	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
When	O
Bowell	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gaol	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
FIELD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mead	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
imprisoned	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
debt	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
examination	O
of	O
Holbrook	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Jury	O
retired	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
a	O
verdict	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MEAD	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
325.	O
HENRY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
umbrella	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRADLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
an	O
umbrella	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
with	O
the	O
umbrella	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
umbrella	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MUCHMARSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
umbrella	O
off	O
the	O
hook	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
326.	O
MARY	B-pers
STINSTON	I-pers
and	O
MARIA	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
other	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BARRETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Chapel-street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
muslin	O
from	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
six	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
different	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
yards	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
s.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Mary	B-pers
Stinston	I-pers
before	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
Irish	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
per	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
sold	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
14	O
d.	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
higher	O
than	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
fetched	O
some	O
cloth	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
muslins	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
lay	O
some	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
conveyed	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
the	O
muslins	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
do	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
boy	O
warning	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
charge	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Stinston	I-pers
,	O
said	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
muslin	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
stockings	O
,	O
dropped	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
peak	O
of	O
Maria	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
stays	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
from	O
Stinston	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
I	O
observe	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
on	O
petty	O
larceny	O
for	O
10	O
d.	O
You	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Stinston	O
some	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
been	O
a	O
customer	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
respectable	O
family	O
?	O
-	O
For	O
aught	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
muslin	O
under	O
her	O
feet	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
standing	O
near	O
each	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SIMMONDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Barrett	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
there	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Stinston	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
cloth	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
muslin	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Irish	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
within	O
reach	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
muslin	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
muslin	O
,	O
or	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
observe	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
touch	O
the	O
muslin	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
that	O
the	O
muslin	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
good	O
bit	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
master	O
intimation	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Maria	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
nothing	O
was	O
delivered	O
up	O
but	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOODWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Stinston	I-pers
,	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
STINSTON	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
MARIA	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
327.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LIGHTWOOD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
three	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
one	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
1st	O
regiment	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
in	O
Spun-yard	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
lost	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
sixpence	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
first	O
blow	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Dark-entry	B-place
,	I-place
Lower	I-place
East	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
the	O
blow	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
ear	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
action	O
of	O
stooping	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
is	O
not	O
high	O
enough	O
to	O
walk	O
upright	O
;	O
that	O
blow	O
flung	O
me	O
forward	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
(	O
Davis	O
)	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
stomach	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
which	O
rendered	O
me	O
insensible	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
nor	O
Davis	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
Davis	O
)	O
use	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
hit	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Lightwood	O
)	O
kick	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
foot	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
Davis	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
Davis	O
was	O
gone	O
quite	O
off	O
before	O
Lightwood	O
kicked	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
Davis	O
whistled	O
to	O
his	O
dog	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
he	O
is	O
;	O
the	O
tall	O
man	O
(	O
Lightwood	O
)	O
went	O
straight	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Bear	O
and	O
me	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine's-lane	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
DAVIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
:	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
given	O
to	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
drunken	O
case	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
give	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
My	O
friends	O
live	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
soul	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
LIGHTWOOD	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
WM	O
.	O
LIGHTWOOD	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
BULLER	O
.	O
328.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
M'GOWING	I-pers
and	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
SCANDLING	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
cloth	O
jackets	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
striped	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
window-pin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
68	I-place
,	I-place
Cable-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
Monday	O
week	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
house	O
fastened	O
forwards	O
and	O
backwards	O
;	O
my	O
children	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
seven	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
eldest	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
jackets	O
and	O
shirts	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
andthe	O
pin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
;	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
glass	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
pin	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
string	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
key	O
fell	O
out	O
in	O
turning	O
the	O
pin	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
fastened	O
myself	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
general	O
rule	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
by	O
two	O
officers	O
going	O
to	O
Justice	O
Staples	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
IVERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
)	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
on	O
Michael	B-pers
Scandling	I-pers
about	O
half	O
after	O
one	O
,	O
or	O
nigh	O
two	O
,	O
at	O
Saltpetre	O
Bank	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
secured	O
:	O
M'Gowing	O
had	O
another	O
small	O
bundle	O
which	O
contained	O
these	O
child	O
's	O
breeches	O
and	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
clothes	O
and	O
these	O
breeches	O
and	O
the	O
jacket	O
and	O
trowsers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
wish	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
often	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
within	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
a	O
desperate	O
gang	O
of	O
water-pirates	O
?	O
-	O
Whether	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
sold	O
me	O
things	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
in	O
custody	O
about	O
some	O
Prussian	O
blue	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
affair	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
committed	O
from	O
Litchfield-street	O
for	O
robbery	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
you	O
at	O
present	O
stand	O
indicted	O
?	O
-	O
Was	O
I	O
committed	O
for	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
no	O
robbery	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
perhaps	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
committed	O
;	O
why	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
that	O
somebody	O
said	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
an	O
indictment	O
against	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
admitted	O
a	O
witness	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
about	O
some	O
callico	O
;	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
was	O
I	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Answer	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
admitted	O
a	O
witness	O
for	O
the	O
crown	O
in	O
Hog-lane	O
or	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
bears	O
both	O
names	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
some	O
callico	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
eighteen	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
how	O
long	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
!	O
-	O
You	O
never	O
was	O
charged	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
archbishop	O
's	O
plate	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
,	O
master	O
Moses	O
?	O
how	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
purchasing	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
tea	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
;	O
because	O
though	O
this	O
is	O
passing	O
off	O
pretty	O
easily	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
shorthand-writer	O
taking	O
down	O
your	O
answers	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
purchased	O
any	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
question	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
never	O
been	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
.	O
Is	O
Mrs.	O
Moses	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
indicted	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
man	O
has	O
been	O
guilty	O
once	O
of	O
a	O
fault	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
always	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
you	O
sufficient	O
housekeepers	O
