TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
DALBY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
opposite	O
Rolls-buildings	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCII	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Letters	O
and	O
Messages	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
left	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
instantly	O
forwarded	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
,	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHURST	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
Miles	B-pers
Maskew	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Goldfinch	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Doyce	I-pers
William	B-pers
Southwaite	I-pers
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
William	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
David	B-pers
Bryson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rodbard	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Simm	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
*	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
served	O
the	O
seventh	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
James	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
Christoph	B-pers
.	I-pers
Langworthys	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clishold	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
Dennis	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dalstone	I-pers
William	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
220	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
HENDERSON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
GOODALL	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
Susannah	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Lordthe	O
King	O
,	O
then	O
being	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
their	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
clasped	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Susannah	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
right	O
breast	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
,	O
stab	O
,	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
penetrate	O
,	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
striking	O
,	O
stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
cutting	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
indictment	O
further	O
charges	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
abetting	O
,	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Susannah	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
jurors	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
oaths	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
said	O
prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Susannah	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
their	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
charged	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
murder	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
Susannah	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shawe's-court	B-place
,	I-place
Newtoner	I-place
's	I-place
lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
left	O
off	O
work	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
's	O
room	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
;	O
Field	O
and	O
Laurence	O
live	O
together	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
words	O
between	O
Anderson	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
either	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	O
Anderson	O
began	O
upon	O
me	O
almost	O
directly	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
he	O
began	O
upon	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
naked	O
knife	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
it	O
into	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
also	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
he	O
began	O
afresh	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
jumped	O
up	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Bob	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
hurt	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
Bob	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
you	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
stick	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
defend	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
throwing	O
Bob	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
round	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Bob	O
do	O
not	O
hurt	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
angry	O
word	O
then	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
seeing	O
Anderson	O
so	O
resolute	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Laurence	O
and	O
dragged	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
he	O
would	O
score	O
her	O
-	O
that	O
was	O
said	O
before	O
Field	O
took	O
Laurence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
Bob	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
strike	O
my	O
wife	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
-	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
directly	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
oh	O
Lord	O
!	O
oh	O
Lord	O
!	O
they	O
have	O
killed	O
my	O
wife	O
!	O
they	O
have	O
killed	O
my	O
wife	O
!	O
Goodall	O
begged	O
of	O
Anderson	O
for	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Bob	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
serve	O
it	O
out	O
among	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
wound	O
:	O
he	O
repeated	O
those	O
words	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
then	O
upon	O
my	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
Goodall	O
followed	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
with	O
a	O
naked	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
beside	O
the	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
scull	O
open	O
-	O
he	O
hit	O
me	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
where	O
in	O
my	O
fright	O
.	O
-	O
Then	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
round	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
not	O
many	O
yards	O
from	O
Shawe's-court	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
knives	O
then	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
Goodall	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
knife	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
serve	O
me	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
served	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
those	O
words	O
,	O
till	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
them	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
certainly	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
killed	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
had	O
not	O
provoked	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
or	O
given	O
them	O
anyangry	O
words	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
lived	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
some	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
Six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
improper	O
connection	O
between	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
cohabited	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
flew	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
all	O
lived	O
on	O
friendly	O
terms	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
These	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
together	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
very	O
unfortunately	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
should	O
seem	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
liquor	O
got	O
amongst	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
landlord	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
expression	O
that	O
Goodall	O
used	O
in	O
asking	O
for	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
while	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
Anderson	O
were	O
struggling	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Goodall	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
knife	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
produced	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asking	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
knife	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
knife	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
prevented	O
mischief	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
fully	O
bent	O
on	O
murder	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
so	O
;	O
you	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
quarrel	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
directly	O
opposite	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
where	O
Dell	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
recollect	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
me	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
porter	O
between	O
us	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
Matthew	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
and	O
Anderson	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
together	O
about	O
two	O
shillings	O
as	O
Goodall	O
owed	O
Anderson	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
struck	O
Goodall	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
hollowed	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
Anderson	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
ashamed	O
;	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Anderson	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
licking	O
.	O
Anderson	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
hearing	O
Anderson	O
's	O
voice	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
sailor	O
was	O
not	O
Dell	O
:	O
-	O
then	O
Susan	O
Dell	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
came	O
up	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
another	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
John	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
paid	O
for	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
drinking	O
the	O
beer	O
two	O
little	O
boys	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
little	O
boys	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Anderson	O
said	O
to	O
Dell	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
said	O
to	O
Anderson	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
a	O
stick	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
licking	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
stick	O
twice	O
:	O
Anderson	O
immediately	O
passed	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
take	O
the	O
fender	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
defend	O
yourself	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
Susan	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
ran	O
between	O
them	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
round	O
the	O
neck	O
because	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
husband	O
:	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Bob	O
(	O
to	O
Henderson	O
)	O
do	O
not	O
hurt	O
my	O
husband	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
Suke	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
shall	O
stick	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
let	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Matthew	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
Matt	O
.	O
Matt	O
.	O
take	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
knife	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Goodall	O
said	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
serve	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
think	O
Goodall	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
knife	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
hurt	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
knife	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
tocut	O
some	O
pig	O
's	O
face	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
accident	O
happened	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
somehow	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
Anderson	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
leave	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
themselves	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
danger	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
coroner	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
said	O
while	O
the	O
woman	O
held	O
him	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
get	O
up	O
I	O
will	O
score	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
Dell	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
have	O
murdered	O
Suke	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
followed	O
Dell	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
leaning	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
walked	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
Anderson	O
during	O
Dell	O
's	O
absence	O
;	O
she	O
liked	O
one	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
malice	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
LAURENCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
room	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
beer	O
some	O
words	O
arose	O
about	O
money	O
between	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Goodall	O
;	O
Anderson	O
said	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
half-a-crown	O
,	O
and	O
Goodall	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
threepence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
pay	O
you	O
now	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
cut	O
Goodall	O
across	O
the	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
cut	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
knife	O
cutting	O
Goodall	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
knife	O
frightens	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
struck	O
Goodall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
heard	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
ashamed	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
thrash	O
you	O
:	O
Anderson	O
took	O
the	O
knife	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
some	O
blows	O
passed	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
Goodall	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
struck	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
Susan	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
came	O
down	O
and	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
return	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
husband	O
:	O
Anderson	O
and	O
him	O
began	O
to	O
joke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Anderson	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
with	O
;	O
Susan	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Bob	O
do	O
n't	O
hurt	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
arms	O
round	O
him	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
Anderson	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
score	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
by	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
Goodall	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
go	O
it	O
,	O
Bob	O
,	O
go	O
it	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
serve	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
meant	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
immediately	O
James	O
Field	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
on	O
what	O
occasion	O
he	O
first	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
street-door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Dell	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
Anderson	O
followed	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Goodall	O
throw	O
the	O
quart	O
pot	O
at	O
Dell	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Anderson	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
bleeding	O
;	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
.	O
JOHN	O
FOX	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Goodall	O
both	O
with	O
knives	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
standing	O
before	O
Dell	O
in	O
Newtoner's-lane	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Dell	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Bob	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
had	O
killed	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
serve	O
him	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARLET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
see	O
Susannah	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
breast	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
given	O
with	O
a	O
sharp	O
instrument	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
inches	O
deep	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
almost	O
divided	O
the	O
axillary	O
artery	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
that	O
wound	O
being	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
ANDERSON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
witnesses	O
with	O
myself	O
were	O
all	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
Dell	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
shoulder	O
with	O
the	O
fender	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
regard	O
for	O
the	O
deceased	O
to	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
Dell	O
has	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
with	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
the	O
very	O
night	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
buried	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
now	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
GOODALL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Dell	O
and	O
Anderson	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
Dell	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
fender	O
and	O
struck	O
Anderson	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
GOODALL	I-pers
,	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
Sentence	O
of	O
death	O
was	O
immediately	O
passed	O
on	O
Anderson	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
on	O
Monday	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
body	O
to	O
be	O
dissected	O
and	O
anatomized	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
sentence	O
.	O
221.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOYSES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
cloath	O
coats	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
lodging	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
slept	O
together	O
in	O
Long-alley	B-place
;	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
lawyer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
trunk	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Half-moon-alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
where	O
we	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
struck	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
early	O
hour	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
move	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
discovered	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
night-cap	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
)	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Produces	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
then	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
the	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
every	O
thing	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
I	O
marked	O
before	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Half-moon	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
when	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
27	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
222.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
M'COUL	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
purse	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cogle	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COGLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
out	O
pensioner	O
of	O
Chelsea	O
College	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
purse	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
andfour	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
buying	O
clothing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Westminster	B-place
Arms	I-place
,	I-place
Tothill-street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
M'Coull	O
came	O
in	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
:	O
-	O
M'Coull	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
my	O
hands	O
across	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
waiter	O
saw	O
her	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
cloathing	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DOWNS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Westminster	O
Arms	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
peppermint	O
and	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
continued	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
near	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
purse	O
to	O
pay	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Seeing	O
him	O
getting	O
a	O
little	O
forward	O
in	O
liquor	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
begged	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
reckoning	O
and	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
company	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
;	O
M'Coull	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
served	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ELTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Downs	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
half-and-half	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
another	O
girl	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
A	O
WITNESS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Westminster	O
Arms	O
on	O
this	O
day	O
;	O
this	O
old	O
gentleman	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Westminster	O
Arms	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
M'Coull	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
left	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
company	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
directly	O
after	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
M'Coull	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
across	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
shaking	O
hands	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
.	O
DUNCAN	B-pers
GRANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
money	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
produce	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
pattern	O
for	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
M'COULL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
at	O
this	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Downs	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
grant	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
God	O
and	O
you	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
M'COULL	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
223.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
BUNDY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17thday	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
umbrella	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
identify	O
.	O
LUKE	B-pers
WINGFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
put	O
his	O
foot	O
on	O
the	O
skirting	O
board	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
reached	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
silk	O
umbrella	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
umbrella	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
umbrella	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
materially	O
altered	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
umbrella	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GHENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
umbrella	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
umbrella	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Wingfield	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
umbrella	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
umbrella	O
in	O
Basing-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
spout	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
along	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Watling-street	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
224.	O
GILES	B-pers
SALISBURY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
24	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
;	O
6	O
1/2	O
calico	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
print	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
NICHOLSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bridge-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Hobbs	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
wife	O
lived	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
slept	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
on	O
by	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hobbs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
goods	O
in	O
their	O
servant	O
's	O
possession	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
suppose	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
was	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
but	O
the	O
half	O
shawl	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
neck	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
shawls	O
)	O
;	O
these	O
shawls	O
are	O
marked	O
N.	O
M.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
escaped	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
these	O
articles	O
being	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
lives	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
Sunday	O
22d	O
April	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
daughter	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
shawls	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Nicholson	O
of	O
my	O
suspicions	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
ANN	B-pers
HOBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
(	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nicholson	O
;	O
I	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
goods	O
as	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Nicholson	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
sold	O
six	O
shawls	O
together	O
of	O
that	O
pattern	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
the	O
shop	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kicked	O
against	O
this	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
it	O
white	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
125.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GLOVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
sugar-boiler	O
,	O
in	O
Martin	B-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
servants	O
were	O
taking	O
in	O
ten	O
hogsheads	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
after	O
two	O
loads	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
number	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
395	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
objected	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
guinea	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
returned	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
carman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
that	O
number	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
guinea	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Fish-street	O
,	O
the	O
guinea	O
slipped	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
people	O
looked	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
odd	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
126.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
ten	O
live	O
tame	O
cock	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
eight	O
live	O
tame	O
hen	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Debonnair	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
ten	O
live	O
cock	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
eight	O
live	O
tame	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
pigeons	O
being	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
kept	O
and	O
confined	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
pigeon-house	O
belonging	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
DEBONNAIR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bromley	B-place
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pigeons	O
in	O
question	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
feed	O
them	O
every	O
day	O
almost	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
sort	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
early	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
eighteen	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
recovered	O
seven	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
recovered	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wooller	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
recovered	O
two	O
others	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lowe	O
's	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
cages	O
lent	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
pigeon-house	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
resorted	O
to	O
their	O
nests	O
,	O
particularly	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
left	O
their	O
young	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
dog	O
within	O
a	O
fortnight	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
pigeons	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
WOOLLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
bird-shop	O
facing	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
pigeons	O
and	O
fowls	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
seven	O
pigeons	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
market	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LOWE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brown's-lane	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
pigeons	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
.	O
RICHARD	O
COWLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Miss	O
Debonnair	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pigeons	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
some	O
tiles	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
thepigeon-house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
footman	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
pigeons	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
pigeon-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
old	O
places	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Miss	O
Debonnair	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
pigeons	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
tame	O
;	O
I	O
valued	O
the	O
six	O
at	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
worth	O
a	O
guinea	O
apiece	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Raike	O
,	O
cooper	O
at	O
Stratford	O
,	O
for	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
weeks	O
past	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
I	O
knew	O
by	O
sight	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
some	O
pigeons	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
dispute	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
bargain	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
bid	O
me	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
waited	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Brown's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seven	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
three	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
three-pence	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
my	O
Lords	O
and	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
consider	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
breasts	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
think	O
any	O
person	O
can	O
with	O
safety	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pigeon	O
which	O
is	O
brought	O
,	O
which	O
always	O
shifts	O
its	O
feathers	O
twice	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
127.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CROPPER	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
MOUNTAIN	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
POTTS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
MESSER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
twelve	O
plain	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
twelve	O
twist	O
and	O
cut	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
nine	O
gold	O
breast-pins	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
twelve	O
gold	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
twelve	O
gold	O
trinkets	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
gold	O
fancy	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
fifty	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pap-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
salt-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
caster-tops	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
five	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
butter-ladles	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
shirt-pins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
eight	O
silver	O
bladed	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
pencil-cases	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
base-metal	O
candlestick	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
ditto	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
ditto	O
half-pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
paste	O
stock-buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
base-metal	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
base-metal	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
ivory	O
tooth-pick	O
cases	O
,	O
mounted	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
baskets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
caddy-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
forty	O
fancy	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
stone	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
base-metal	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Red-lion-street	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
gold-smith	O
,	O
and	O
hardware-man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
at	O
twelve	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
shop	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
were	O
alarmed	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
floorempty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
greater	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
the	O
hearth-stone	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
of	O
a	O
cellar	O
that	O
we	O
let	O
to	O
Mr.	O
M'Cray	O
,	O
an	O
oil-man	O
;	O
my	O
kitchen	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
ground-floor	O
,	O
over	O
Mr.	O
M'Cray	O
's	O
cellar	O
;	O
the	O
hearth	O
part	O
was	O
arched	O
with	O
bricks	O
;	O
Mr.	O
M'Cray	O
has	O
a	O
separate	O
entrance	O
,	O
quite	O
distinct	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
more	O
;	O
the	O
prices	O
are	O
low	O
and	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
under	O
the	O
real	O
value	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
Cropper	O
,	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
to	O
search	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
that	O
same	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Cropper	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
in	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
some	O
people	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Cooke	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edge	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Cook	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
searching	O
Cropper	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
soil	O
of	O
the	O
necessary	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
chapes	O
and	O
tongues	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edge	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Cohen	O
,	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
something	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
iron	O
crow	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
nothing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
another	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
pocket	O
we	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
Cohen	O
's	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
no	O
further	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
bottle-stands	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Potts	O
at	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Messer	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
;	O
Cropper	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Cropper	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Cropper	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
they	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
servants	O
that	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
adjoining	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
way	O
from	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
persons	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
this	O
disturbance	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
without	O
their	O
hearing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
late	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
was	O
the	O
archway	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
so	O
high	O
as	O
this	O
sounding-board	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
possible	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
my	O
situation	O
(	O
being	O
lame	O
)	O
could	O
get	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
Jury	O
must	O
judge	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
exception	O
of	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
headboroughs	O
of	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
before	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
went	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
nicking	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
publican	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Moody	O
;	O
Cropper	O
came	O
by	O
from	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
Cropper	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
Moody	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
doing	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
pass	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
to	O
Moody	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
Cropper	O
said	O
,	O
Moody	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
up	O
this	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
Cropper	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
past	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
day-light	O
;	O
as	O
Cropper	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
right	O
shoulder	O
was	O
dirty	O
with	O
dry	O
mortar	O
,	O
apparently	O
from	O
a	O
broken	O
wall	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
squeezed	O
through	O
a	O
broken	O
brick	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
countenance	O
fell	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
afterCropper	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
Messer	O
passed	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
hat-crown	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
Cropper	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
voice	O
within	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
Messer	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
out	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Potts	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
Cropper	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
common	O
corn-sack	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
to	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
shoulders	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
market	O
;	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
plated	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
articles	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
an	O
old	O
iron-shop	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
Cropper	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Moody	O
's	O
;	O
Cropper	O
came	O
in	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Moody	O
for	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
?	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
;	O
Moody	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
note	O
?	O
Moody	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
Cropper	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
kettle	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
and	O
two	O
runners	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
parlour	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Cropper	O
,	O
Mercer	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
discharged	O
;	O
we	O
handcuffed	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Cropper	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
Cooke	O
searched	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
several	O
silver	O
articles	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
privy	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
tongues	O
and	O
chapes	O
of	O
buckles	O
:	O
Cohen	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
Mrs.	O
Cohen	O
,	O
Cooke	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
silver	O
articles	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
Cohen	O
delivered	O
up	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
Potts	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
sealed	O
up	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
privy	O
;	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
tea-caddy	O
,	O
a	O
plated	O
candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
plated	O
mustard-pot	O
,	O
one	O
plated	O
salt-cellar	O
,	O
a	O
plated	O
bottle-stand	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
rims	O
of	O
plated	O
buckles	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
chapes	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
plated	O
coffee-pot	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
Potts	O
;	O
these	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
privy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
counted	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
dozen	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
buckles	O
which	O
Cooke	O
took	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
rims	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
new	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Cropper	O
Will	O
he	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
found	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
necessary	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
:	O
another	O
house	O
opened	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
yard	O
.	O
Cropper	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
to	O
five	O
houses	O
.	O
Edge	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
two	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
more	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
I	O
behave	O
when	O
you	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
came	O
?	O
-	O
With	O
as	O
much	O
civility	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
could	O
do	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
dirt	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
dry	O
mortar	O
,	O
by	O
rubbing	O
against	O
some	O
place	O
,	O
with	O
pressure	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
me	O
into	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
nothing	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
prudent	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
headboroughs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
Bateman	O
,	O
Edge	O
,	O
and	O
West	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Messer	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
discharged	O
:	O
on	O
Mrs.	O
Cropper	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
property	O
;	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
new	O
,	O
tied	O
together	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
two	O
odd	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
new	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Justice	O
Staples	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
Cropper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
25	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
No	O
.	O
3997	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
memorandum	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
near	O
;	O
Cropper	O
,	O
hiswife	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
further	O
at	O
Cropper	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cohen	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cohen	O
's	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
new	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
sealed	O
up	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edge	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
were	O
present	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
else	O
:	O
Cohen	O
gave	O
in	O
this	O
parcel	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
magistrate	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
writing	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
these	O
are	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
several	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
a	O
boatswain	O
's	O
whistle	O
,	O
all	O
new	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
bundle	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Edge	O
,	O
containing	O
rims	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Cropper	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
dirt	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
spots	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
remember	O
a	O
day	O
before	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
white-washing	O
and	O
yellow-ochring	O
my	O
room	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
take	O
both	O
you	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Edgehall	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
loft	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
white	O
washing	O
his	O
room	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
or	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Cropper	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
remember	O
saying	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
strip	O
and	O
employ	O
your	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edge	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
shoulder	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
passed	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
appearance	O
which	O
could	O
be	O
occasioned	O
by	O
wet	O
mortar	O
from	O
the	O
brush	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
washer	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
you	O
described	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
wet	O
mortar	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
dry	O
mortar	O
rubbed	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
the	O
spots	O
on	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
ASHER	B-pers
COHEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
dealer	O
I	O
understand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
delivered	O
some	O
things	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
when	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
but	O
William	B-pers
Cropper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
126	O
,	O
some	O
doors	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Cohen	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
just	O
looked	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
were	O
buckles	O
and	O
spoons	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
a	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
,	O
does	O
this	O
come	O
to	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
shall	O
bring	O
you	O
some	O
more	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
will	O
settle	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
before	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
goods	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
;	O
then	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
half	O
shut	O
;	O
some	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
silver	O
found	O
on	O
my	O
wife	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
settled	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
red	O
ink	O
writing	O
on	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
name	O
in	O
Hebrew	O
characters	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
goods	O
very	O
often	O
before	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
,	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pretty	O
general	O
dealer	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
melting	O
pot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Cropper	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
do	O
you	O
buy	O
silver	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
always	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
an	O
ounce	O
before	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
bargain	O
about	O
this	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
besides	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
ago	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
tried	O
at	O
this	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
tried	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
For	O
stealing	O
of	O
pots	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
goal	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
surrendered	O
.	O
Your	O
wife	O
was	O
convicted	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
atHicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
:	O
so	O
was	O
you	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
bandanas	O
for	O
smuggled	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
witness	O
for	O
the	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
informer	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
gave	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Bandana	O
handkerchiefs	O
you	O
produced	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
above	O
two	O
pounds	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
he	O
says	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
gets	O
me	O
into	O
trouble	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
yesterday	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
false	O
charge	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
ROSE	B-pers
COHEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Jewess	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wentworth-street	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
voice	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
bought	O
some	O
silver	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
getting	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
the	O
curiosity	O
(	O
women	O
they	O
say	O
seldom	O
have	O
)	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
six	O
tea-spoons	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
angry	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
settled	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
dozen	O
tea-spoons	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
God	O
's	O
speed	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Cooke	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Cropper	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
bank	O
notes	O
did	O
I	O
give	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
one	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
somebody	O
bring	O
your	O
husband	O
a	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
pull	O
out	O
your	O
pocket	O
book	O
and	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
twenty-five	O
bank	O
notes	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
one	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
COHEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cohen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
came	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
and	O
found	O
Cropper	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
by	O
yourself	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
your	O
father	O
is	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
father	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
cash	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Cropper	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
here	O
presently	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
settle	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
father	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
note	O
,	O
only	O
what	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Cropper	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
publick-house	O
near	O
the	O
magistrates	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
father	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
First	O
the	O
property	O
produced	O
here	O
by	O
Cooke	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
which	O
Cohen	O
bought	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
buckle-rims	O
without	O
private	O
marks	O
,	O
R.	O
U	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
Potts	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
is	O
some	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
rims	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
:	O
next	O
those	O
tongues	O
and	O
chapes	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
privy	O
appearing	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
those	O
rims	O
in	O
size	O
,	O
and	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
shape	O
:	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
our	O
mark	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
chapes	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
black	O
stone	O
knee-buckle	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
meltable	O
value	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
one	O
chape	O
amongst	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
next	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Cropper	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
other	O
buckle	O
;	O
next	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Cohen	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
bundle	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Cohen	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
salt	O
spoons	O
and	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
articles	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
salt-cellar	O
we	O
have	O
sometimes	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
D.	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
these	O
things	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
fairly	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
as	O
silver	O
:	O
my	O
house	O
is	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Cropper	O
's	O
house	O
PRISONER	O
CROPPER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
You	O
understand	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
to	O
casualty	O
lodgers	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
two	O
men	O
who	O
were	O
apprehended	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shed	O
;	O
they	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
sold	O
the	O
property	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cohen	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shed	O
asked	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
Potts	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
bridge	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
ask	O
him	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
that	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
chief	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
coming	O
in	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
swear	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
kept	O
to	O
do	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
sick	O
and	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
hospital	O
,	O
that	O
knows	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
habitation	O
till	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thing	O
impossible	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
situation	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
scarce	O
able	O
to	O
stand	O
or	O
walk	O
without	O
crutches	O
or	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
POTTS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Cropper	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
two	O
men	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Who	O
hired	O
you	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Cropper	O
.	O
Cropper	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
call	O
any	O
witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Potts	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CROPPER	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
ANN	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
POTTS	I-pers
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
MESSER	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
128.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blackburne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blackburne	I-pers
.	O
Esq	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLACKBURNE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
some	O
money	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
offender	O
,	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
last	O
I	O
marked	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
them	O
near	O
a	O
canvass	O
bag	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
cross	O
under	O
the	O
curl	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
escrutore	O
I	O
then	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Blackburne	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
escrutore	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
marked	O
guineas	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
in	O
guineas	O
,	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
particularly	O
marked	O
in	O
the	O
O	O
of	O
George	O
;	O
this	O
ten	O
pounds	O
so	O
marked	O
we	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
canvass	O
bag	O
to	O
the	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bureau	O
again	O
opened	O
;	O
on	O
examining	O
the	O
bag	O
I	O
discovered	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
on	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
do	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
offender	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
all	O
the	O
servants	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
would	O
search	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
we	O
found	O
two	O
marked	O
guineas	O
in	O
his	O
purse	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
POTTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Williams	O
myself	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
these	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
)	O
these	O
two	O
guineas	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
canvass	O
bag	O
,	O
(	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
)	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
BLACKBURNE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
all	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Blackburne	O
had	O
locked	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
opened	O
it	O
or	O
gave	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
dressing	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
servants	O
had	O
certainly	O
access	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
BLACKBURNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Blackburne	O
having	O
lost	O
money	O
fromher	O
bureau	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Blackburne	O
shewed	O
me	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
canvass	O
bag	O
:	O
one	O
guinea	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
canvass	O
bag	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
229.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FITZGERALD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Stanyard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STANYARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
company	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
damned	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bowl	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
tongs	O
,	O
pokers	O
,	O
and	O
fire-shovels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
brick	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HUTTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
coat	O
was	O
ripped	O
up	O
the	O
back	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
recover	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
he	O
shewed	O
us	O
,	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
people	O
for	O
my	O
friend	O
's	O
hat	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
brick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
another	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
another	O
with	O
a	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
:	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
brick	O
at	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
,	O
b	O
-	O
r	O
their	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
kill	O
every	O
Englishman	O
that	O
came	O
along	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WICKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
more	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
described	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
terribly	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BEAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
tied	O
to	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
open	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
first	O
bloody	O
thief	O
that	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
poker	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
large	O
iron	O
shovel	O
;	O
she	O
strove	O
to	O
beat	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
great	O
difficulty	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
EDMUND	B-pers
RAWLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
a	O
hard	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
witnesses	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
row	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
row	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Troth	O
Pat	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
does	O
the	O
bull	O
run	O
?	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
of	O
our	O
country	O
folks	O
apprehended	O
the	O
word	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
asked	O
that	O
?	O
Which	O
way	O
does	O
the	O
bull	O
run	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
fair	O
hair	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Rawley	O
.	O
Another	O
man	O
apprehended	O
the	O
word	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Who	O
struck	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
rightly	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
could	O
lay	O
legs	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
and	O
Fitzgerald	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
your	O
Lordship	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
oath	O
that	O
Fitzgerald	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
row	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
row	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
affray	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
tongs	O
.	O
Rawley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
hat	O
indeed	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
QUIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
lad	O
,	O
Stanyard	O
,	O
came	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
or	O
coat	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Fitzgerald	O
do	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
out	O
to	O
fight	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
MILES	B-pers
BURKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
dispute	O
began	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
opposite	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
row	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
for	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
break	O
the	O
windows	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
these	O
witnesses	O
came	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
230.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
WARBURTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
paper	O
band	O
box	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
Morocco	O
shoes	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
necklaces	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
And	O
JOHN	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
a	O
parcel	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
MILNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Harris's-court	B-place
,	I-place
Oxford-street	I-place
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
Hannah	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
took	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
words	O
passed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
she	O
clicked	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
then	O
,	O
she	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
stamped	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
rendered	O
me	O
incapable	O
of	O
getting	O
my	O
bread	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
hurt	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
upwards	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
recovered	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
SLAUGHTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
some	O
articles	O
which	O
were	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Matthews	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
MILNER	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MANSFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
Lords	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
Matthews	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SAGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
past	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
trod	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
another	O
patrol	O
sworn	O
,	O
Who	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
conducted	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
The	O
inspector	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
WARBURTON	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoebinder	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Adam-and-Eve-court	O
to	O
take	O
home	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
coming	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
woman	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
her	O
pattens	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
sober	O
.	O
To	O
Davis	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
deliver	O
the	O
pattens	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
one	O
patten	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
MATTHEWS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
church-yard	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
there	O
;	O
several	O
waggons	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
WARBURTON	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
Stealing	O
.	O
JOHN	O
MATTHEWS	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
231.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
of	I-pers
Huntley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
THE	O
MARQUIS	O
OF	O
HUNTLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Cranford-bridge	B-place
,	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
before	O
12	O
:	O
one	O
man	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
heads	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
door	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left-hand	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bayonet	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
horses	O
heads	O
,	O
came	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
carriage	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
robbers	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
your	O
chaise	O
seat	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
chaise	O
seat	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
another	O
search	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
searched	O
another	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Cranford-bridge	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
servants	O
at	O
Cranford-bridge	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
;	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
out	O
immediately	O
;	O
we	O
returned	O
back	O
with	O
three	O
men	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nobody	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
an	O
information	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
express	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
,	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Cranford-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MENZIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Huntley	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
detained	O
in	O
town	O
after	O
my	O
Lord	O
set	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
his	O
Lordship	O
returning	O
to	O
town	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
dragoons	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
before	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
consideration	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
two	O
in	O
front	O
get	O
down	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
at	O
which	O
my	O
Lord	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
dragoons	O
seeing	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
jumped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bayonet	O
found	O
near	O
his	O
heels	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARPMEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
and	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Menzie	O
)	O
;	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
my	O
Lord	O
Huntley	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
near	O
Cranford-bridge	O
(	O
confirms	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Lord	O
Huntley	O
and	O
of	O
Menzie	O
)	O
;	O
at	O
day	O
light	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
scattered	O
about	O
upon	O
the	O
heath	O
,	O
almost	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
likewise	O
found	O
this	O
trunk	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
attempt	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
so	O
exceeding	O
dark	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GIBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
dragoons	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
jumped	O
down	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
signal	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
arms	O
and	O
my	O
comrade	O
held	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bayonet	O
dropped	O
down	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
leg	O
;	O
it	O
dropped	O
on	O
my	O
foot	O
.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
23	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
Lord	O
Huntley	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
232.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CARROLL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
George	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
chain	O
and	O
seals	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
OLIVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Plumbtree-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
-	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bear	O
which	O
attracted	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
notice	O
who	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
linked	O
in	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
following	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
he	O
thrust	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
right	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
seized	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
faced	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
posture	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
immediately	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
rendered	O
insensible	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
who	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
myself	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
callico	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BATTIE	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Oliver	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bear	O
going	O
down	O
Plumbtree-street	O
,	O
which	O
excited	O
my	O
curiosity	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
close	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
Oliver	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
half	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
Oliver	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HINE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knock	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
this	O
robbery	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
Wright	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
233.	O
SARAH	B-pers
RANDAL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
callico	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
apron	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
shawl	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
an	O
old	O
white	O
bed	O
gown	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
red	O
skirt	O
;	O
she	O
dragged	O
me	O
along	O
to	O
a	O
lone	O
place	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
witness	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
well	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
home	O
to	O
sleep	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
AINSLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
petticoat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
deplorable	O
condition	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
Randall	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOODFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
was	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
or	O
where	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Peter-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
woman	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bonnet	O
hung	O
up	O
,	O
this	O
cloak	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
table	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
apron	O
and	O
cap	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BEETHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Brown	O
and	O
Ashman	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
for	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
in	O
Fleet's-gardens	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
naked	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
small	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
pink	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ELLIOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
duplicate	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
things	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Stealing	O
,	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
234.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Meene	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MEENE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Mews	I-place
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
or	O
less	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
short	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TRING	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seaman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Mews	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
take	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Meene	O
has	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Stealing	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
235.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PEPLOW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
steel	O
elastic	O
truss	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SQUIRE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Carnaby-market	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Hyde-park	B-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
review	O
:	O
somebody	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
truss	O
;	O
about	O
four	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
SANDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
lad	O
and	O
another	O
picking	O
pockets	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
slide	O
the	O
truss	O
away	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BLACKBURN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
Sanders	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
man	O
(	O
corroborates	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
)	O
;	O
Sanders	O
has	O
kept	O
the	O
truss	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Hyde-park	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
by	O
an	O
arch	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
paper	O
lying	O
with	O
a	O
truss	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
writing	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
tried	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
to-day	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
seven	O
years	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
236.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HEYLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
