TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Islington	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
DALBY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
opposite	O
Rolls-buildings	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCII	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Letters	O
and	O
Messages	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
left	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
instantly	O
forwarded	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
LLOYD	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
KENYON	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
:	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Vivian	I-pers
John	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Newham	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Lacey	B-pers
Punderson	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hartshorn	I-pers
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Appleford	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Stemetz	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Varney	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wardell	I-pers
David	B-pers
Conty	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
Clements	B-pers
Leeds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lawn	I-pers
James	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
John	B-pers
M'Cord	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Clew	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Gaitshell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Henfree	I-pers
447.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HUGH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lascelles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-bone	I-place
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
livery	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
:	O
seven	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
woolen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
bodkin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
ivory	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
with	O
silver	O
bows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pen	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
top	O
of	O
pepper	O
castor	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pencil	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Westmaker	I-pers
;	O
and	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
unmade	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lascelles	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WESTMAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Westmaker	I-pers
,	O
lives	O
butler	O
to	O
Captain	O
Edward	B-pers
Lascelles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
helper	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
is	O
a	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
apartment	O
was	O
over	O
Captain	O
Lascelles	O
'	O
stables	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
some	O
things	O
there	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
enumerating	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
were	O
worth	O
five	O
pounds	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
Justice	O
Bond	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
door	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
fastened	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
.	O
ROGER	B-pers
HODGKING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
property	O
except	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
;	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
ready	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
all	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
friend	O
within	O
a	O
hundred	O
miles	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
39	O
s.	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
448.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
on	O
business	O
,	O
from	O
John-street	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
:	O
Brown	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stout	O
stick	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
just	O
right	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
without	O
speaking	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stunned	O
by	O
the	O
blow	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
first	O
blow	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
blows	O
before	O
I	O
fell	O
:	O
Graham	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
recovered	O
my	O
senses	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
giving	O
me	O
many	O
blows	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
:	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
John	O
Brown	O
walked	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
returning	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
blow	O
:	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
withhis	O
fist	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
then	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
publick	O
road	O
for	O
foot	O
and	O
horse	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
carriage-way	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
punctual	O
in	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
pass	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Staple	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
irons	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
altogether	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Brown	O
.	O
When	O
Justice	O
Staple	O
's	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mayne	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
one	O
was	O
tall	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
short	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
to	O
a	O
publican	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
very	O
nigh	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Graham	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
shortest	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
Catherine's-lane	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
three	O
pounds	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
:	O
Brown	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
offered	O
twenty	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
Brown	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
and	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Sun	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
Watts	O
:	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
Graham	O
Would	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
us	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
met	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
some	O
pieces	O
that	O
correspond	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
BROWN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Frenche	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Church	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blacksmith	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
only	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
GRAHAM	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
too	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
often	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
449.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CARPENTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ponsonby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
commonly	O
called	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ponsonby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ponsonby	I-pers
,	O
called	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ponsonby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spring	I-place
Gardens	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
steps	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
seldom	O
shut	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
,	O
or	O
Walch	O
,	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Sponsby	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
name	O
Ponsonby	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Ponsonby	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
:	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
:	O
the	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
kitchen	O
dresser	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
thank	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
steps	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Saturday	O
week	O
after	O
;	O
this	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
mydescription	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
milk	O
pot	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
little	O
as	O
five	O
minutes	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
both	O
times	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
regular	O
in	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
general	O
rise	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
kitchen	O
table	O
dusting	O
coppers	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
black	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shortish	O
person	O
,	O
nobody	O
pointed	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
opening	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ponsonby	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
about	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Ponsonby	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
in	O
Coventry-street	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
and	O
told	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
patrols	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Suffolk-street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Hope	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CHEW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrol	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
other	O
patrole	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
present	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
pointed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
as	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
milk	O
pot	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
handsome	O
high	O
newfashioned	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
stood	O
on	O
a	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
lid	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
market	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
buying	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
apples	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
by	O
selling	O
on	O
a	O
jackass	O
;	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
450.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CASTLEDINE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
composition	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
New	I-pers
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
FORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Gloucester	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
job	O
of	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
Margrave	O
of	O
Anspach	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Fearon	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
White	O
Horse	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
victuals	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
White	O
Horse	O
Cellar	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
five	O
;	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Albemarle-street	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
just	O
come	O
into	O
town	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
Albemarle-street	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
walking	O
down	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
countryman	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
walked	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Gloucestershire	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
Stroudwater	O
,	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
about	O
several	O
other	O
village	O
places	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
one	O
Hickman	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
:	O
in	O
walking	O
200	O
yards	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
lady	O
's	O
purse	O
on	O
a	O
step	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
whipped	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
purse	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
slapped	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
athwart	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
strangers	O
just	O
come	O
into	O
town	O
,	O
God	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
fine	O
prize	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
notknow	O
that	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
a	O
stout	O
lusty	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
note	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
a	O
locket	O
valued	O
at	O
135	O
l.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
locket	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
tortoise	O
shell	O
case	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
living	O
up	O
higher	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
would	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
half	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
friend	O
and	O
fetch	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
share	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
locket	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
News	O
,	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Silver-street	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
step	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
locket	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
companion	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
the	O
valuation	O
of	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
then	O
returned	O
,	O
saying	O
his	O
friend	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
purse	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
bought	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
with	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
walked	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
had	O
you	O
agreed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
bargain	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
thoughts	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
when	O
he	O
when	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
then	O
pulled	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
locket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
Cellar	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
locket	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
nothing	O
was	O
said	O
about	O
his	O
having	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
not	O
the	O
locket	O
from	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
locket	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
security	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
locket	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
again	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
(	O
the	O
locket	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
till	O
afterwards	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
diamond	O
stone	O
.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
NEW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
in	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
;	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
parlour	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
from	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
the	O
tap-room	O
several	O
times	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
in	O
conversation	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tap-room	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
was	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
Ford	O
came	O
out	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
doubt	O
I	O
am	O
wronged	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
shew	O
for	O
it	O
but	O
this	O
locket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
was	O
worth	O
very	O
little	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
JONH	O
BECK	B-pers
HEATHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
the	O
utmost	O
value	O
of	O
this	O
locket	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
6	O
s.	O
or	O
7	O
s.	O
at	O
most	O
;	O
the	O
stones	O
are	O
ordinary	O
paste	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Walking	O
down	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
we	O
walked	O
on	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
purse	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
there	O
lays	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
halves	O
immediately	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
countryman	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
West	O
countryman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
country	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
countrymen	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
New	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
locket	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
locket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
locket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
keep	O
this	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
ever	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
his	O
money	O
and	O
his	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
as	O
an	O
indemnification	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
48	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
451.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FOULKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
1791	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
copper	O
money	O
called	O
halfpence	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spice-gardens	O
,	O
Ratcliffe-highway	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
1791	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Stepney	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
business	O
requires	O
my	O
early	O
rising	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gillespie	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	O
:	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Stepney	O
,	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foulkes	I-pers
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
morning	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
morning	O
for-mushrooms	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
them	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
here	O
are	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
people	O
gather	O
them	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Bow-common	O
there	O
are	O
plenty	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
notion	O
of	O
going	O
so	O
far	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
are	O
from	O
the	O
North	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
you	O
be	O
a	O
penny	O
to	O
my	O
penny	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
at	O
the	O
Walnut-tree	O
,	O
they	O
know	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
opposite	O
the	O
Walnut-tree	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
large	O
enough	O
to	O
admit	O
a	O
carriage	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
round	O
the	O
field	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
man	O
talking	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
before	O
met	O
with	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
Walnut-tree	O
were	O
then	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
then	O
have	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
Smallwood	O
,	O
bring	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
face	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
over	O
your	O
pump	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
lip	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
down	O
his	O
lip	O
and	O
shewed	O
the	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
remarked	O
his	O
lip	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
him	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
gin	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
wood	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
inches	O
square	O
every	O
way	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
joist	O
for	O
flooring	O
,	O
sawed	O
off	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
leave	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
wood	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Bow-common	B-place
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
me	O
:	O
Bow-common	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
road	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
indifferent	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
merely	O
for	O
the	O
air	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
walked	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
towardsBow-common	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
any	O
particular	O
place	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
brick	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
come	O
over	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
chance	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
get	O
some	O
mushrooms	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
that	O
butcher	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
steak	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
for	O
a	O
sixpence	O
;	O
but	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
known	O
at	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
so	O
they	O
will	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
my	O
companion	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
made	O
towards	O
the	O
road	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
with	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
wood	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
any	O
,	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
take	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
or	O
look	O
I	O
will	O
cut	O
your	O
throat	O
with	O
my	O
knife	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
face	O
with	O
the	O
wood	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
blow	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
blow	O
put	O
me	O
past	O
speaking	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
second	O
blow	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
fingers	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
else	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
this	O
happened	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
:	O
I	O
lay	O
senseless	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
senseless	O
from	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
state	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
clock	O
strike	O
seven	O
when	O
I	O
recovered	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
two	O
pence	O
for	O
gin	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
a	O
penknife	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
fell	O
out	O
when	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
under	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
helped	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
by	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
gin	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Walnut-tree	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
washed	O
my	O
wounds	O
and	O
poured	O
some	O
brandy	O
down	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ten	O
months	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
ten	O
months	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
to	O
the	O
magistrates	O
in	O
Wellclose-square	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
description	O
to	O
the	O
runners	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
was	O
laid	O
up	O
four	O
months	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
cross	O
road	O
from	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
London	O
Hospital	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
struck	O
with	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
fear	O
;	O
the	O
features	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
ran	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
rest	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
weak	O
and	O
tired	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
assistance	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
)	O
just	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Coleman-street	O
through	O
a	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
run	O
past	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
name	O
Foulkes	O
?	O
the	O
butcher	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Foulkes	O
;	O
he	O
whispered	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
narrow	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
ally	O
into	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
left	O
me	O
for	O
dead	O
in	O
Stepney-fields	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
draymen	O
standing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
name	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
boy	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
five	O
minutes	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Clerk	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
seeing	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
ten	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
;	O
if	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
upon	O
such	O
a	O
recollection	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
weight	O
.	O
-	O
Looking	O
at	O
the	O
cut	O
of	O
his	O
lip	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
feature	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
nothing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
first	O
hearing	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
as	O
an	O
assault	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
my	O
first	O
complaint	O
was	O
both	O
an	O
assault	O
and	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
complaint	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Lord	O
Kenyon	O
.	O
It	O
should	O
be	O
understood	O
that	O
the	O
magistrates	O
ought	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
examinations	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SMALLWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Walnut	O
Tree	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
a	O
sabbath	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
them	O
;	O
Dunn	O
paid	O
twopence	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Mile	O
End	O
Road	O
together	O
,	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
;	O
Dunn	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
two	O
acquaintances	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
and	O
Fat	O
Jack	O
,	O
a	O
waterman	O
;	O
Dunn	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
mangled	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
situation	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
brandy	O
inwardly	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
outwardly	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
little	O
inwardly	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
all	O
outwardly	O
;	O
his	O
left	O
cheek	O
was	O
cut	O
terribly	O
,	O
swelled	O
ever	O
so	O
big	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
and	O
abused	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
mentioned	O
a	O
robbery	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
charge	O
my	O
memory	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
frightened	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
second	O
examination	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
having	O
the	O
accident	O
of	O
the	O
cut	O
on	O
his	O
lip	O
,	O
by	O
tumbling	O
over	O
a	O
pump	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
recollected	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
and	O
murdered	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
expression	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rupert	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Chest	O
at	O
Chatham	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
honourable	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
assure	O
you	O
I	O
grant	O
the	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
Dunn	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
in	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Walnut	O
Tree	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smallwood	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
drank	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
ever	O
hurting	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
putting	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
place	O
he	O
has	O
crossed	O
himself	O
very	O
much	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
carman	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
murdered	O
me	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
carman	O
(	O
begging	O
your	O
pardon	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
)	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
murdered	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
before	O
any	O
magistrate	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
innocence	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
arm	O
and	O
arm	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
where	O
'Squire	O
Boydell	O
was	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Clarke	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
only	O
swore	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
hearing	O
that	O
I	O
committed	O
very	O
violent	O
assault	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
mentioned	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
robbing	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
two-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
committed	O
for	O
a	O
violent	O
assault	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
session	O
the	O
grand	O
jury	O
found	O
a	O
bill	O
for	O
robbery	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Smallwood	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
certain	O
piece	O
of	O
timber	O
of	O
three	O
inches	O
broad	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
quartering	O
,	O
of	O
floor	O
joist	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sick	O
ward	O
this	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
seven	O
weeks	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
weak	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
38	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
452.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
enteringthe	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
of	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
velveret	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardiner	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
Kingsland	B-place
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
at	O
nine	O
to	O
breakfast	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
large	O
nail	O
in	O
the	O
shutter	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
cottage	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
ten	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
nail	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pots	O
of	O
mirtles	O
broke	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
patten	O
rings	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
but	O
one	O
boarded	O
floor	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wet	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
nobody	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
my	O
neighbours	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
very	O
low	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
velveret	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
unlocked	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brickmaker	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
publick-house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
going	O
to	O
Ball	O
's	O
Pond	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
duplicates	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harper	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pepperall	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
;	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
two	O
shillings	O
or	O
half-a-crown	O
;	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
almost	O
new	O
,	O
worth	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
the	O
shirt	O
is	O
worth	O
one	O
shilling	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PEPPERALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
town	O
:	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
things	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
:	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
three	O
duplicates	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
duplicates	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
mislaid	O
or	O
lost	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mr.	O
How	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
duplicates	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
2	O
s.	O
(	O
Aged	O
23	O
)	O
,	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
453.	O
SARAH	B-pers
COWDEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
without	O
lawful	O
cause	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Akerman	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
in	O
February	O
1788	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
certificate	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
of	O
her	O
conviction	O
;	O
in	O
June	O
1789	O
she	O
received	O
a	O
conditional	O
pardon	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
her	O
for	O
transportation	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Lady	O
Juliana	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
her	O
person	O
whatever	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
read	O
)	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Spital-street	B-place
;	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
silk	O
way	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
enquiries	O
into	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
as	O
Mayne	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
hard	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
ship	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
since	O
she	O
escaped	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
for	O
honesty	O
and	O
industry	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
join	O
my	O
recommendation	O
.	O
Lord	O
Kenyon	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
let	O
loose	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
pursue	O
the	O
same	O
line	O
of	O
industry	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
character	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
given	O
you	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
454.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DODRIDGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
eighty-one	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Eagleton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
shopman	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Eagleton	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
tea	O
dealer	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
tea	O
;	O
we	O
examined	O
our	O
stock	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
deficient	O
;	O
we	O
knew	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
4683	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
chest	O
at	O
Hercules	O
'	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
constable	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
a	O
paper	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
contained	O
about	O
eighty-two	O
pounds	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RENSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
along	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
through	O
Finch	O
Lane	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Threadneedle-street	O
;	O
they	O
pitched	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
for	O
Hunt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
dropped	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
Renshaw	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
his	O
shoulders	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
tea	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
(	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
tea	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
stove	O
by	O
falling	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
This	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
4683	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
initial	O
letters	O
,	O
G.	O
C.	O
they	O
signification	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
the	O
General	O
Coote	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
chests	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
ship	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
amongothers	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
shop	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
cary	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
heavy	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
?	O
-	O
do	O
n't	O
over	O
value	O
it	O
,	O
place	O
it	O
rather	O
under	O
than	O
over	O
the	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
at	O
least	O
10	O
l.	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
455.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
16	O
pounds	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
officer	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
India	O
merchants	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
sugar	O
tied	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
wrapped	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
the	O
Hannah	O
,	O
from	O
Jamaica	O
;	O
Wells	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
hada	O
little	O
bag	O
in	O
his	O
jacket	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
bags	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
)	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
(	O
a	O
cane	O
scoop	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
thing	O
commonly	O
used	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
Aged	O
49	O
)	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
456.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
MATHERS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
thirty-six	O
pounds	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DOLLOWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Gibson	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
come	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
some	O
casks	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
copper	O
and	O
brass	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
adjoining	O
the	O
Custom	O
House	O
quay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
Mathers	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
brass	O
under	O
Gibson	O
's	O
jacket	O
;	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
Gibson	O
then	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
Greenwood	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
brass	O
from	O
;	O
Mather	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
Gibson	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
Mather	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
-	O
THORNTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mather	O
assist	O
Gibson	O
in	O
taking	O
this	O
brass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
and	O
Gibson	O
assisted	O
Mather	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GREENWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weigher	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
noon	O
tender	O
took	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Gibson	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Gibson	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
inscriptions	O
given	O
of	O
Mathers	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
brass	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
457.	O
HENRY	B-pers
COWARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cambric	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Tower	I-place
Hill	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothe	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
sailor	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
shipmates	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
their	O
desire	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
kindness	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
Oct.	O
4th	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
birth	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
sloop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
either	O
that	O
evening	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
that	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
18th	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
hanging	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
clothe	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
waistcoat	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
shew	O
me	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
I	O
.	O
B.	O
JAMES	B-pers
M'EWEN	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
60	O
,	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
propertywhich	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
either	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
for	O
17	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
size	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
try	O
them	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
occasion	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
own	O
.	O
Clark	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
among	O
my	O
shipmates	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
458.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
CHANT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Compton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
our	O
apprentice	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
any	O
body	O
gone	O
out	O
?	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
sent	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
across	O
Northampton-street	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
hat	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
fight	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
coat	O
he	O
dropped	O
.	O
Joshua	O
Walker	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STONE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
somebody	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
459.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLANCEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
printing	O
types	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
.	O
SIMON	B-pers
STEPHENSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
letter	O
founder	O
in	O
Bream's-buildings	O
,	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
printer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
types	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russell-court	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
a	O
printer	O
and	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
sister	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
to	O
whom	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
flurried	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
lie	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
brother	O
a	O
printer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
founder	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Twelve	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
becomes	O
of	O
boys	O
who	O
tell	O
lies	O
?	O
-	O
Go	O
to	O
a	O
bad	O
place	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephenson	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
up	O
the	O
letters	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
letters	O
upon	O
a	O
stick	O
to	O
be	O
dressed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
things	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bedford-bury	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
parcels	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
in	O
Bream	O
's	O
buildings	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Orange-street	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bedford-bury	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
types	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
lad	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
heavy	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Orange-street	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
run	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
run	O
faster	O
than	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
dodge	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephenson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
type	O
,	O
the	O
letter	O
X	O
has	O
a	O
flaw	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
kicked	O
against	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
more	O
value	O
to	O
a	O
printer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
in	O
Russell-court	O
,	O
who	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
460.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MILLHOLLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
ruffled	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
articles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
eight	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Crockett	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
:	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
,	O
laying	O
the	O
robbery	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Castell	O
,	O
Powell	O
,	O
Sumner	O
,	O
and	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
witnesses	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SUMNER	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lombard-street	B-place
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Castell	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
is	O
the	O
firm	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
butler	O
;	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
care	O
;	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Crockell	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
property	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
a	O
banking-house	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
Kennedy	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Carnaby-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
shirts	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
shirt	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
eight	O
spoons	O
and	O
two	O
waiters	O
;	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
wanted	O
twelve	O
guineas	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
waiters	O
were	O
only	O
plated	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
asked	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Crockett	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
waiters	O
are	O
silver	O
,	O
oh	O
yes	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sufficient	O
cash	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public-office	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
with	O
Kennedy	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
police	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
ten	O
duplicates	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
TYLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Dixon	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
decanters	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
were	O
pledged	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledge	O
the	O
shirts	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
duplicates	O
delivered	O
.	O
WADE	B-pers
KENDREW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sumner	O
.	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
a	O
particular	O
kind	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
purpose	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
shirt	O
marked	O
with	O
red	O
silk	O
,	O
or	O
red	O
cotton	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
(	O
Aged	O
32	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
461.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
bacon	O
hams	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
PHILIP	B-pers
SEWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
hams	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
cheese	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
shilling	O
hard	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
in	O
picking	O
up	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Newman	O
was	O
reaching	O
something	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
only	O
two	O
hams	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
Newman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
another	O
ham	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
Newman	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
one	O
ham	O
clear	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
they	O
dropped	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
recovered	O
the	O
ham	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
hams	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
hams	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
lost	O
only	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
more	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wade	O
,	O
cabinet-maker	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
ABBOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Newman	O
have	O
a	O
ham	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
ham	O
to	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
fetched	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dusk	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
say	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
ham	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
produce	O
a	O
ham	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ELBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
nine	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
462.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
worsted	O
stuffs	O
called	O
wildbores	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DEACON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
59	I-place
,	I-place
Walling-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
wild-bores	O
from	O
my	O
warehouse	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
bell	O
tingle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
rolls	O
of	O
wildbores	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
returning	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
roll	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
463.	O
ANN	B-pers
THORN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
man	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
PHILIP	O
BOND	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gun-maker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
upon	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
I	O
speak	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
shoes	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
knowing	O
this	O
loss	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
ABIGAIL	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
mantua-maker	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bond	O
said	O
she	O
missed	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
missed	O
two	O
spoons	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
duplicates	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bond	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taxed	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bond	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
:	O
they	O
begged	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
every	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CRORKEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
one	O
sheet	O
and	O
a	O
napkin	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
things	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
frequented	O
our	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
Langbourne	O
Ward	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
checked	O
muslin	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
near	O
forty	O
duplicates	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
five	O
in	O
this	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
a	O
stocking	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Stewart	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
is	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bond	O
's	O
sheet	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
A.	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
;	O
the	O
napkin	O
is	O
marked	O
P.	O
A	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
shoes	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
this	O
spoon	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
those	O
things	O
not	O
with	O
any	O
design	O
to	O
wrong	O
my	O
master	O
or	O
mistress	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
duplicates	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
464.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CAUSEWAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
four	O
metal	O
watch	O
chains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hardwareman	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-market	B-place
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
gilt	O
watch	O
chains	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
my	O
glass-case	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
show-glass	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
said	O
search	O
his	O
hair	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
Barrington	O
's	O
scheme	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chains	O
dropped	O
down	O
from	O
his	O
hair	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
school-fellow	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
playing	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
here	O
before	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Five	O
or	O
six	O
times	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
465.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twenty	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Hungerford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
HENRIETTA	B-pers
MARIA	I-pers
HUNGERFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cavendish	B-place
Square	I-place
;	O
it	O
is	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
great	O
confusion	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
were	O
missing	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
amount	O
:	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
Police	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
eighty-three	O
duplicates	O
on	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
chiefly	O
the	O
lady	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
THACKERAY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
table	O
cloth	O
from	O
Martha	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
-	O
MULCASTER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
sheet	O
and	O
petticoat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
sheet	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
SEPTIMIUS	B-pers
SADLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
five	O
sheets	O
and	O
two	O
bolster	O
cases	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1791	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
sheet	O
and	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
long	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
lying-in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
urged	O
by	O
the	O
greatest	O
distress	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs	O
Hungerford	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
difference	O
between	O
us	O
now	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
466.	O
ANN	B-pers
LUMLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
neck-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
nankeen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MANNING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
1	I-place
,	I-place
Little	I-place
White	I-place
Lion-street	I-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
clean	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
I	O
placed	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
neck-cloth	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
locksmith	O
:	O
I	O
threw	O
my	O
foul	O
shirt	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
dust	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
:	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
linen	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
since	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
my	O
shop-mate	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
at	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shirt	O
and	O
neck-cloth	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
breeches	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MINGAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
John	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
's	O
dirty	O
shirt	O
and	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
clean	O
things	O
laying	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
will	O
get	O
dirty	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
old	O
silk	O
to	O
lay	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
-	O
HALES	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Long	O
Acre	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
neck-cloth	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
though	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
one	O
shilling	O
on	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
sixpence	O
on	O
the	O
neck-cloth	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirt	O
and	O
neck-cloth	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
neck-cloth	O
through	O
distress	O
:	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
owes	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
worth	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
467.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
REEVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Reeve	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
villain	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
him	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
wrenched	O
my	O
arm	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
Bray's-buildings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
468.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twenty-nine	O
pounds	O
of	O
pork	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
elevenpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
two	O
pewter	O
pots	O
and	O
two	O
quarts	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
SAWYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
porter	O
and	O
change	O
for	O
half	O
a-crown	O
,	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
No	O
.	O
30	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
for	O
another	O
pot	O
,	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
pipes	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
by	O
force	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
or	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
masters	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
up	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
porter	O
and	O
pots	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
see	O
about	O
the	O
beer	O
and	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
makes	O
no	O
difference	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
beer	O
and	O
pots	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
30	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
thepots	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
ordered	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
two	O
pots	O
of	O
porter	O
and	O
two	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
eleven-pence	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
469.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BURN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MORTIMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
Road	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
.	I-place
I	O
lost	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
loft	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
KELLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milk-carrier	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
hay	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
;	O
I	O
packed	O
the	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
this	O
hay	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mortimer	O
;	O
the	O
cutting	O
and	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
hay	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
bands	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
twisting	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
a	O
rick	O
that	O
heated	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mouldy	O
place	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CAMMELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
Kelley	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
hay	O
,	O
which	O
hay	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
470.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ANKLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
damask	O
cushion	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LANE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
15	I-place
,	I-place
Daker-street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cushion	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Maidenhead-court	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
people	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
like	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
two	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
officers	O
belonging	O
to	O
Queen-square	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
cushion	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
had	O
the	O
cushion	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
TROTMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
Daker-street	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
cushion	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SHANNAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Snow's-rents	O
,	O
Maidenhead-court	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
cushion	O
;	O
I	O
believethat	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
softly	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
cushion	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Queen-square	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Another	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
cushion	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
regiment	O
my	O
husband	O
does	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Trotman	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
pass	O
your	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
dress	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRIDLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
at	O
Queen-square	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
coat	O
:	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
cushion	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
cushion	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
cushion	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cushion	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
many	O
persons	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
coat	O
;	O
one	O
may	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
471.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BENEFIELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Agnes	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
.	O
AGNES	B-pers
M'CARTY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
81	I-place
,	I-place
Berwick-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
they	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MACKEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
unpinned	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
afterwards	O
produced	O
by	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
-	O
HAMILTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
area	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
wisp	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
gown	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
472.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovat	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LOVAT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
shillings	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
Piazza	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sitting	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
breeches	O
were	O
cut	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
cut	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
searched	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
threepence	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
-	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
eight	O
shillings	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RYLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
473.	O
MARY	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twelve	O
leather	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
covered	O
with	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
twelve	O
clasp	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
MIDDLETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stationer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
to	O
ascertain	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BECK	I-pers
HEATHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
five	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
pledge	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Bow	O
Street	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
abroad	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
shoe	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
eight	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
MIDDLETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
drank	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sold	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
pocket	O
books	O
were	O
in	O
drawers	O
without	O
locks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
Aged	O
14	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
474.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BUSKIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
iron	O
handled	O
