TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Islington	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
DALBY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
opposite	O
Rolls-buildings	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCII	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Letters	O
and	O
Messages	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
left	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
instantly	O
forwarded	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	O
GOULD	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Arnott	I-pers
Calend	B-pers
Luscombe	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Battinson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
Cotton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Cockburne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hailes	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Black	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
James	I-pers
Sower	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Readder	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
William	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bramble	I-pers
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Moorby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fregent	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Glossop	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
George	B-pers
Fife	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Desborough	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
^	O
^	O
John	B-pers
Simes	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
William	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
360.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
four	O
live	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
live	O
greese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUMPHREYS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile	B-place
End	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
ducks	O
and	O
two	O
geese	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GROVES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
ducks	O
and	O
geese	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
orchard	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
acre	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
ducks	O
and	O
geese	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
this	O
bag	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Groves	O
.	O
The	O
morning	O
after	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
ducks	O
and	O
geese	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
four	O
ducks	O
and	O
two	O
geese	O
.	O
Groves	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
geese	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
lives	O
at	O
Bow	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
my	O
hat	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
361	O
JOHN	B-pers
ABSOLUM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
at	O
the	O
Willow-walk	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
private	O
lodgings	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
quarters	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Willow-walk	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
crutch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
drink	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
sixpence	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
sixpennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
purse	O
now	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
out	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
threatened	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
country	O
upon	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
I	O
will	O
throttle	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
aimed	O
to	O
push	O
me	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
two-pennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
was	O
this	O
man	O
searched	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
my	O
purse	O
was	O
returned	O
with	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HUBBARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
for	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Willow-walk	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
murder	O
cried	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
the	O
Willow-walk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
a	O
bended	O
posture	O
by	O
the	O
trees	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Absolum	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
brownish	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
ragged	O
coat	O
and	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knapsack	O
and	O
a	O
purse	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Westminster	O
he	O
was	O
rescued	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
this	O
purse	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
cripple	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
purse	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
snatched	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
that	O
dayI	O
had	O
just	O
received	O
my	O
pension	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
guineas	O
all	O
but	O
three	O
farthings	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NEIGHBOUR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
soldier	O
and	O
the	O
cripple	O
go	O
lovingly	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
directly	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
knapsack	O
and	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
money	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
rescued	O
from	O
us	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Monster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Willow-walk	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
I	O
heard	O
murder	O
!	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recovering	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
rescued	O
at	O
Westminster	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Privy	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
violently	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
362.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
JOHN	I-pers
IRSON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
gilt	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LEWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
between	O
Newington-green	B-place
and	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
sticks	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
before	O
they	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
sticks	O
and	O
cutlasses	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
moonlight	O
night	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
heavens	O
;	O
they	O
beat	O
on	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
most	O
horribly	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
single	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
teem	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
bled	O
so	O
much	O
from	O
the	O
wounds	O
;	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
says	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
draw	O
your	O
cutlass	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
open	O
,	O
murder	O
the	O
bug	O
-	O
r	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
drew	O
their	O
cutlasses	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
cut	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
eye	O
;	O
they	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
my	O
wrist	O
in	O
defending	O
the	O
blow	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hollowed	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
murder	O
!	O
murder	O
!	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
heard	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
ran	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stamped	O
on	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
farm	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
arms	O
rubbed	O
with	O
brandy	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
they	O
were	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
minutes	O
(	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
below	O
the	O
mark	O
)	O
beating	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
senses	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
lightish	O
coat	O
on	O
and	O
blue	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
wounds	O
dressed	O
my	O
brother	O
sent	O
three	O
servants	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
sat	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CANNON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
returning	O
home	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
!	O
three	O
men	O
were	O
engaged	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
stood	O
beating	O
the	O
man	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
within	O
fifty	O
yards	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
enough	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
STAINES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
;	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Ball	O
's	O
Pond	O
turnpike	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
the	O
turnpike-man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
out	O
of	O
murder	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
and	O
got	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
turnpike-house	O
;	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
turnpike-house	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
again	O
;	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
rate	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
thief	O
:	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
damn	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
by	O
your	O
running	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
soon	O
proved	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
stick	O
and	O
cutlass	O
laying	O
near	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
immediately	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
nine	O
hundred	O
or	O
a	O
thousand	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
run	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
any	O
person	O
of	O
my	O
size	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
hardest	O
work	O
to	O
overtake	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
drab	O
coat	O
and	O
blue	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
fresh	O
blood	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
produced	O
and	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
with	O
one	O
drop	O
of	O
blood	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
bathe	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
towards	O
the	O
road	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sing	O
out	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
friends	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
363.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveteen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
stuff	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Paddington	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
dinner	O
at	O
twelve	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
then	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
at	O
one	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
but	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
four	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
drawn	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
ground	O
floor	O
;	O
a	O
bundle	O
laid	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
which	O
contained	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
but	O
not	O
packed	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
were	O
in	O
drawers	O
;	O
I	O
value	O
them	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
364.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
AYRES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
velveret	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gunsmith	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hemmings	O
's	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
the	O
garret	O
where	O
Islept	O
,	O
I	O
last	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
White-horse	O
public-house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fetched	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shoved	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
rushed	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
candle	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
old	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
three	O
shirts	O
of	O
mine	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
persons	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Myself	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
Hemmings	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
CONSTABLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
coat	O
cost	O
me	O
40	O
s.	O
they	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
that	O
good	O
,	O
though	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
old	O
things	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
365	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRIAN	I-pers
and	O
DAVID	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
red	O
Morocco	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
tin	O
can	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Sprang	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
WALTER	O
SPRANG	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lewsome	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
loose	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
those	O
stays	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
some	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
relate	O
the	O
circumstances	O
truly	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Well	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
atonement	O
you	O
can	O
make	O
for	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WAYLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sprang	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
b	O
-	O
r	O
me	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
opposite	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shoved	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
;	O
Brian	O
turned	O
up	O
King-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
under	O
Brian	O
's	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Fisher	O
turned	O
back	O
short	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
can	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stays	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
hat	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Fisher	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
tin	O
toy	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tin	O
can	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
SIMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
stay	O
maker	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
calls	O
himself	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
from	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
speaking	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
punch	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
this	O
man	O
goin	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
punch	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
hustle	O
him	O
about	O
,	O
then	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
contained	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
both	O
come	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
accommodate	O
you	O
with	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
stays	O
under	O
your	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
rain	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
ladies	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
case	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
down	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Axe	O
and	O
Gate	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
chuse	O
it	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
people	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
robbed	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
FISHER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
fence	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knocked	O
his	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
his	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Allow	O
all	O
the	O
witnesses	O
their	O
expences	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
drunken	O
man	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
366	O
GEORGE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tablespoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fitzhugh	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KELSALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fitzhugh	O
,	O
we	O
lost	O
four	O
silver	O
forks	O
and	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mistook	O
one	O
area	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
27	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
367	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boytell	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BOYTELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
five	O
tea-spoons	O
from	O
a	O
closet	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
spoons	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SPENCER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
M.	O
Boytell	O
's	O
servant	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
are	O
marked	O
A.	O
E.	O
M.	O
T.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Boytell	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Sally	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
whose	O
mother	O
lived	O
at	O
Bethnal-Green	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
gingling	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
five	O
spoons	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
368	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
ofJuly	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
MORSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
from	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
MORSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
adjoining	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
court	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SOWERBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
;	O
a	O
boy	O
(	O
Harvey	O
)	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
HARVEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
poulterer	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
boots	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
MORSE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boots	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Morse	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
BLAGROVE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
these	O
boots	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HOLLOWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
boots	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Morse	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
man	O
just	O
before	O
me	O
dropped	O
the	O
boots	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
369	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
NEWTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langley	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Grosvenor	B-place
Place	I-place
;	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
salt	O
were	O
on	O
a	O
sideboard	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
near	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
money	O
for	O
two	O
newspapers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
with	O
a	O
newspaper	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
salt-holder	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
articles	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
and	O
salt-holder	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Langley	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
serve	O
newspapers	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
370	O
HENDRICK	B-pers
HENDERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nutter	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
NUTTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
reed-maker	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
pull	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
BAYLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stopthief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
lad	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
drop	O
from	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Sapwell	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bayley	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Prosecutor	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
371.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WALLIS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KIRK	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Septenmber	O
,	O
one	O
Isabella	O
Bolton	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
four	O
muslin	O
cauls	O
for	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
seventeen	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
six	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
eight	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
thread	O
and	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separately	O
by	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
ISABELLA	O
BOLTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
cook	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
Robert	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
came	O
to	O
invite	O
himself	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
woman	O
friend	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
come	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
acquaintance	O
came	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
bell	O
rang	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Eddington	I-pers
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
hallowing	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
without	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
ruffled	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
Wallis	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
stopped	O
Kirk	O
,	O
Wallis	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
afterwards	O
they	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
and	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
Wallis	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
when	O
Wallis	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
women	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
EDINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
,	O
an	O
house-maid	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cook-maid	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	O
Bolton	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
's	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
standing	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
three-parts	O
shut	O
to	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
on	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
nobody	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
his	O
hat	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
supposed	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
screeming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
locked	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
Robert	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
and	O
Isabella	O
Bolton	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
somebodyup	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Wallis	O
said	O
,	O
pho	O
pho	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
six	O
sticks	O
of	O
sealing-wax	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
ruffled	O
shirt	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
lady	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Edington	I-pers
,	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
in	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Starkey	O
;	O
the	O
articles	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
down	O
stairs	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
some	O
bed	O
curtains	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
cook	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Starkey	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
called	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
pushed	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
below	O
stairs	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
here	O
will	O
acquaint	O
you	O
how	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
linen	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
EDINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Edington	I-pers
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Sept.	O
4	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
dinner	O
below	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
heard	O
her	O
shrieking	O
;	O
the	O
cook	O
and	O
me	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Starkey	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shovel	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
shoes	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
articles	O
of	O
linen	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
shoes	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
's	O
bed-chamber	O
;	O
three	O
drawers	O
and	O
a	O
book-case	O
drawer	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
Wallis	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
cook	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
came	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
came	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BENDFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gale	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
counting-house	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
's	O
cook	O
,	O
Boulton	O
,	O
let	O
in	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
red	O
hair	O
,	O
tied	O
behind	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Robert	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
;	O
he	O
let	O
in	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
;	O
Wallis	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
Kirk	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
cook	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
on	O
Wallis	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
shut	O
it	O
;	O
Robert	O
Wallis	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
and	O
beckoned	O
over	O
against	O
Church-court	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Kirk	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
the	O
men	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
go	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
STARKEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
James	B-pers
Edington	I-pers
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
strip	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Wallis	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PINNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
these	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Taddy	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
servants	O
were	O
all	O
present	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
emptied	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
by	O
the	O
cook	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
to	O
Appleton	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
bag	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
full	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
quite	O
full	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bendfield	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
candles	O
were	O
not	O
lighted	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
lamps	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
APPLETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
shirt	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
initials	O
and	O
number	O
;	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
has	O
my	O
name	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
stick	O
of	O
sealing	O
wax	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
such	O
sort	O
from	O
the	O
bookcase	O
in	O
my	O
counting-house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Edington	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
by	O
Taddy	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
APPLETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
this	O
bag	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
bedroom	O
,	O
the	O
rooms	O
are	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GOBIHAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Kirk	O
,	O
and	O
Wallis	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
charge	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
KIRK	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
WALLIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoners	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
ROBT	O
.	O
WALLIS	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
THOS	O
.	O
KIRK	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
372.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Macpherson	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
MACPHERSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Macpherson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Sept.	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
bason	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
EDMUND	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
heave	O
the	O
cloak	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Macpherson	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
your	O
honor	O
there	O
was	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
running	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
something	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stooped	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
373.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RILEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
sash-saw	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
oilstone	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
tools	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
work-shop	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
some	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
saws	O
were	O
mine	O
beyond	O
all	O
doubt	O
:	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
saws	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
saws	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
oil-stone	O
,	O
and	O
wait	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
coming	O
across	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
that	O
young	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
374.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WILLETT	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HINTON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Pollman	I-pers
.	O
ABIGAIL	B-pers
DAVIDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Willett	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
road	O
between	O
Kensington	O
and	O
Knightsbridge	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
more	O
people	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
Willett	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
brought	O
all	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
close	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
distant	O
more	O
than	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
officer	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
Hinton	O
;	O
Hinton	O
received	O
the	O
gown	O
from	O
Willett	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Willett	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
speaks	O
fair	O
between	O
God	O
and	O
man	O
,	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
BONTHORPE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Willett	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CONNOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
upon	O
guard	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
stopped	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BURKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hinton	O
drop	O
the	O
gown	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
C.	O
WILLETT	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
W.	O
HINTON	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
28	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
375.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
PLACE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
articles	O
of	O
furniture	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	O
MASON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
furnished	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woollen	O
rug	O
,	O
two	O
flat-irons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
irons	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
something	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
patrol	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLATCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
Iknow	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lately	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
376.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLAYLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
fitted	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
my	O
lad	O
attended	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
other	O
customers	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
shoes	O
)	O
Hawkes	O
has	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
binding	O
and	O
the	O
manufacture	O
;	O
these	O
shoes	O
were	O
never	O
tried	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
two	O
inches	O
too	O
small	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
on	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
half-a-crown	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
this	O
man	O
half-a-guinea	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
known	O
of	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAWKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
several	O
pairs	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
some	O
shoes	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Hawkes	O
I	O
had	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Archibald	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
taken	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HAWKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
accused	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
shoes	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
half-a-crown	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
AVERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
half-a-crown	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
returned	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
half-a-guinea	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
concealed	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
32	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
377.	O
MARY	B-pers
BURGESS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
transported	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
clerk	O
of	O
arraigns	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
1787	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
;	O
in	O
June	O
,	O
1789	O
,	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
pardon	O
,	O
on	O
condition	O
of	O
being	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
her	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Lady	O
Juliana	O
;	O
she	O
escaped	O
soon	O
after	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
in	O
Long	O
Reach	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Billings-court	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
;	O
she	O
appearedunwell	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
said	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
sold	O
old	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
exceedingly	O
well	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
378.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GAMMON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Meek	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
silk-cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MEEK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
in	O
Penton-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
loss	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	O
FOX	O
sworn	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
FIELDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
opposite	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
about	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
mentioned	O
some	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
just	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
lodged	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
ABYHALLMAN	O
WYATT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
a	O
black	O
silk-cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
feet	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
got	O
through	O
this	O
business	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
see	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
lost	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
have	O
fetched	O
this	O
man	O
from	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
379.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Tomlins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
TOMLINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
jean	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
closet	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
as	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
fastened	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
supposing	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
closet-door	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FLINT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
380.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
anchorstock	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Judd	I-pers
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Privately	O
whipped	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
381.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Hopgood	I-pers
;	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
being	O
within	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petty	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
POTTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Knightsbridge	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
before	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HAWKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
she	O
robbed	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
attended	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GREGG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
from	O
a	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
guards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
person	O
these	O
clothes	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
POTTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
Deposes	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
if	O
I	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
impudence	O
to	O
wear	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
lent	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
her	O
any	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
But	O
not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
382.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
gelding	O
,	O
price	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROWLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
has	O
a	O
joint	O
property	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
about	O
,	O
being	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
greens	O
,	O
and	O
roots	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
rags	O
;	O
my	O
arm	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
leave	O
)	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
's	O
field	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
bricks	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
vacancies	O
for	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BOSWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
licensed	O
for	O
slaughtering	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
lad	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
should	O
perjure	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
detained	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
blind	O
,	O
his	O
knees	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
lame	O
withal	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
boy	O
brought	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
situation	O
,	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
must	O
give	O
pain	O
to	O
your	O
minds	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
ours	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
brother	O
Gould	O
,	O
whose	O
humanity	O
is	O
as	O
large	O
as	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
has	O
suggested	O
tome	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
have	O
been	O
cases	O
in	O
which	O
a	O
jury	O
have	O
fixed	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
10	O
d.	O
now	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
that	O
very	O
case	O
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
it	O
will	O
of	O
course	O
save	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
punishment	O
attendant	O
on	O
the	O
crime	O
of	O
horsestealing	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
(	O
Aged	O
14	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
application	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Anderson	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
privately	O
whipped	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
383.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
COBB	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
glass	O
quart	O
bottle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
geneva	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
twelve	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
inquiring	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
winter	O
's	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
sixpence	O
for	O
dinner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
sale	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
WHEELER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
gown	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
near	O
Turnham	O
Green	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
384.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
SWEET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
the	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
privately	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Anderson	O
's	O
order	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
385.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WAINE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
three	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
cruet	O
stand	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
plated	O
bread	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
wine	O
funnel	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
soup	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
fish	O
trowel	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
salt	O
cellars	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
gravy	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
seven	O
bottle	O
labels	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
sauce	O
boats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
sauce	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
twelve	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
nine	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
reading	O
glasses	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
ADAM	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Broad	I-place
Street	I-place
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
three	O
female	O
servants	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
all	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
our	O
bed	O
time	O
is	O
generally	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eleven	O
;	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
ringing	O
of	O
the	O
bell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
linen	O
laying	O
about	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
half	O
way	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
watchmen	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
alarmed	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
forced	O
open	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
shoved	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
arm	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
light-hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
part	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
plate	O
is	O
worth	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
rewards	O
.	O
-	O
WRIGHT	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pantry	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
MARIA	B-pers
UPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
John	O
Monk	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Waine	O
before	O
Easter	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
came	O
home	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
evening	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
Percival	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
about	O
eleven	O
Waine	O
came	O
;	O
upon	O
Waine	O
's	O
coming	O
,	O
Percival	O
said	O
to	O
Monk	O
,	O
come	O
Jack	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
he	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
another	O
night	O
;	O
Percival	O
said	O
the	O
family	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
this	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Deacon	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
and	O
a	O
rook	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Plant	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
pulled	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
place	O
in	O
Broad	O
Street	O
;	O
Monk	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Money	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
some	O
new	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
that	O
looked	O
as	O
though	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
hoarded	O
;	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
Waine	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
handbill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
capital	O
robbery	O
has	O
been	O
done	O
in	O
Broad	O
Street	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
all	O
our	O
countenances	O
changed	O
;	O
then	O
Monk	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
,	O
some	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
shillings	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
;	O
Monk	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
twenty	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
Waine	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
our	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
removed	O
from	O
those	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Spiller	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DEACON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
Robert	O
Percival	O
came	O
to	O
Monk	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Maria	B-pers
Upwell	I-pers
;	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
Waine	O
came	O
:	O
Waine	O
asked	O
Monk	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
Monk	O
said	O
,	O
another	O
night	O
will	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
;	O
Percival	O
said	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
family	O
are	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Monk	O
returned	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
Waine	O
came	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
handbill	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Monk	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
do	O
with	O
my	O
silver	O
?	O
and	O
Waine	O
said	O
,	O
mine	O
is	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
Waine	O
had	O
a	O
cane	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
down	O
the	O
first	O
who	O
touched	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
a	O
thick	O
cane	O
about	O
eighteen	O
inches	O
long	O
produced	O
)	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
cane	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
place	O
underneath	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
their	O
tools	O
;	O
William	O
Waine	O
took	O
a	O
Rook	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
do	O
which	O
he	O
removed	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
Monk	O
and	O
Upwell	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Monk	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
them	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
at	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
shop	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Waine	O
only	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
these	O
people	O
went	O
out	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
upon	O
jobs	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cane	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
John	O
,	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
cane	O
in	O
the	O
coset	O
overnight	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MONK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
past	O
supported	O
myself	O
by	O
thieving	O
;	O
Waine	O
and	O
Percival	O
assisted	O
me	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
Percival	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
plasterer	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
defer	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
great	O
consequence	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
Percival	O
said	O
then	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
get	O
a	O
greatdeal	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
tools	O
we	O
used	O
were	O
under	O
a	O
board	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bedstead	O
;	O
Upwell	O
and	O
Deacon	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Waine	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
ride	O
,	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
large	O
iron	O
crow	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
phosphorus	O
;	O
Waine	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
piece	O
of	O
cane	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
to	O
knock	O
down	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
molest	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
plain	O
piece	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
cane	O
at	O
a	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
sample	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
fetch	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
plenty	O
more	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Broad	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
Waine	O
having	O
the	O
crow	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
area	O
rails	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
us	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
;	O
Waine	O
prepared	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
plated	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
by	O
cutting	O
the	O
bottoms	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
Waine	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
ring	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
case	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
dark	O
coloured	O
case	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
inside	O
case	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
plate	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
five	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
off	O
their	O
beat	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Broker	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
Charles	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
myself	O
,	O
Waine	O
,	O
and	O
Percival	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
this	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
waiter	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
Waine	O
had	O
a	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
articles	O
tied	O
in	O
a	O
bird's-eye	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bunhill	O
Row	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
had	O
plate	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
each	O
parcel	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bird's-eye	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Cowheel-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
people	O
something	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
conceal	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
a	O
purchaser	O
;	O
Waine	O
sent	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Paget	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
plate	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
per	O
ounce	O
;	O
my	O
share	O
for	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
plated	O
basket	O
and	O
watch	O
for	O
four	O
guineas	O
;	O
Percival	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
rings	O
;	O
Waine	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
for	O
ourselves	O
;	O
Waine	O
came	O
about	O
twelve	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Percival	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
handbill	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
hoards	O
;	O
Percival	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
to	O
Waine	O
27	O
s.	O
(	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Bell-alley	O
,	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
pig	O
in	O
his	O
cellar	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
bury	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
another	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
frequented	O
public	O
houses	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Clarke	O
to-day	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Clarke	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
CHARLES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookbinder	O
,	O
in	O
Queen's-square	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Waine	O
,	O
Percival	O
,	O
and	O
Monk	O
,	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
carrying	O
bundles	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
colour	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
paler	O
colour	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
different	O
patterns	O
;	O
Waine	O
and	O
Percival	O
's	O
handkerchiefs	O
appeared	O
a-like	O
,	O
Monk	O
's	O
was	O
inferior	O
in	O
quality	O
,	O
and	O
paler	O
in	O
colour	O
,	O
Monk	O
's	O
did	O
not	O
quite	O
cover	O
the	O
contents	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
white	O
metal	O
,	O
silver	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
very	O
quick	O
,	O
and	O
Monk	O
nodded	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
Waine	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
between	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
four	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
only	O
by	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Waine	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lottery	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
there	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
letin	O
none	O
but	O
those	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
only	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
recompence	O
for	O
loss	O
of	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
LAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Enfield	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
at	O
Ponder's-end	O
towards	O
Enfield	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
Lisle	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
jumped	O
over	O
a	O
gate	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LISLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
at	O
Ponder's-end	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
Waine	O
at	O
Ponder's-end	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
leaped	O
over	O
a	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
over	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
was	O
a	O
field	O
in	O
Bedwell	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
days	O
.	O
ANOTHER	O
WITNESS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Ponder's-end	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
386.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BUCKLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
CLARKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Pultney-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
eight	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
daughter	O
to	O
Essex-street	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clarkson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Longacre	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CLARKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
handbills	O
to	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
there	O
.	O
JOHN	O
BROWN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
nephew	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
1	O
l.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
?	O
Yes	O
.	O
An	O
extraordinary	O
character	O
?	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
families	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Clarence	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Queensbury	O
,	O
Lord	O
Tankerville	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
387.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
COGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Eager	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
EAGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardner	O
,	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
lodging	O
to	O
Coge	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
weeks	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
3	O
s.	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
furnished	O
,	O
she	O
staid	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
's	O
rent	O
unpaid	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
his	O
wages	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
week	O
's	O
rent	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
half	O
opened	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
discovered	O
my	O
loss	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
EAGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
PAWNBROKER	O
's	O
SERVANT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
first	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
sheet	O
2	O
s	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
another	O
sheet	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
blanket	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Eager	I-pers
.	O
The	O
sheets	O
are	O
marked	O
A.	O
E.	O
the	O
blanket	O
has	O
a	O
dirty	O
stain	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Deposes	O
to	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Eager	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicates	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
redeemed	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
34	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
6	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
388.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BURFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Sommerville	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SOMMERVILLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
door	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
wandered	O
about	O
till	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
sold	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOODWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-lane	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
VINCENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
money	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
of	O
taking	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
my	O
defence	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
some	O
follies	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
before	O
violated	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
my	O
country	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
humbly	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
389.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GAITSKILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckclothes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PRATER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
became	O
my	O
servant	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
on	O
August	O
14th	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
examine	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
examined	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
examine	O
further	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
Mr	O
.	O
Husband	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
looked	O
further	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
not	O
not	O
marked	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
looked	O
both	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Mr	O
.	O
Husband	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
to	O
come	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
reconciled	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
depart	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Botany-Bay	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
so	O
at	O
lenth	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
property	O
which	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
24	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
390.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KELLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
cotton	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perrot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Askell	I-pers
Bushnell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PARROT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bushnell	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missed	O
from	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
.	O
BARNABAS	B-pers
BRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
coachman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
John	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
;	O
somebody	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
also	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
four	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
every	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
MARTHA	B-pers
ROUND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CUTLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bushnell	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
lad	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
plumber	O
and	O
glazier	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
as	O
others	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
391.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
MASHALL	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
RYAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
apiece	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PROBERT	I-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
35	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Oxford	I-place
Road	I-place
,	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
alone	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
