TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SECOND	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
DALBY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
opposite	O
Rolls-buildings	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCII	O
.	O
Letters	O
and	O
Messages	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
left	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
instantly	O
forwarded	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
,	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BULLER	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Waites	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Collingham	I-pers
John	B-pers
Distoff	I-pers
John	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
David	B-pers
Betson	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Solomon	B-pers
Erwood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
Cornelius	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
George	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
William	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
George	B-pers
Hollands	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
George	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
James	B-pers
Maitland	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
James	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Burne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
48.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WALLIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
smith	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
stranger	O
;	O
this	O
happened	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
worked	O
down	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
hoop-bender	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
shop	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
kicked	O
my	O
heels	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
knee	O
upon	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
lustily	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
plenty	O
of	O
lamps	O
near	O
:	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
stopped	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Christmas-day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
boxing-day	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
knowed	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
knee	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
hat	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
had	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
a	O
sore	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
STEWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
sworn	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
and	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Fourteen	O
,	O
next	O
May	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
swear	O
what	O
is	O
false	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
prentice	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Findley	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
61	O
,	O
Cable-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
hat	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
the	O
hat	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
ever	O
in	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
since	O
I	O
released	O
this	O
hat	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
pawn	O
that	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
before	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
FINDLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
pawned	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
well	O
by	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
hat	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Findley	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
active	O
part	O
about	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Forrester	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
by	O
Mayne	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
told	O
the	O
officer	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mayne	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
your	O
knowledge	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
till	O
Sunday	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
40	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
49.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CRAGGS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
three	O
clasp	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WOODCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cutler	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
adjoining	O
a	O
shop	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Woodcock	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
certainly	O
somebody	O
at	O
your	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
division	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
which	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
something	O
drawing	O
out	O
,	O
either	O
an	O
instrument	O
or	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
place	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
mind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
got	O
about	O
300	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
they	O
almost	O
immediately	O
crossed	O
between	O
two	O
drays	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
almost	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Craggs	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
knives	O
naked	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
twisted	O
him	O
about	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
the	O
baker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
baker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hubbard	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
stop	O
this	O
man	O
while	O
I	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
duplicate	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
knife	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
knife	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
knife	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Woodcock	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
Drury-lane	O
two	O
boys	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
8	O
d.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
me	O
directly	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
turner	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
,	O
Old	O
Bethlem	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woodcock	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
lads	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
at	O
your	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
CHIEF	O
BARON	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
GALONEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pillar	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
in	O
a	O
walnut-tree	O
gilt	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Pillar	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PILLAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lower	B-place
Shadwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
large	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
to	O
seven	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
it	O
gone	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
before	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
stranger	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
my	O
servant	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
bread	O
for	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
mentioned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
boys	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
myself	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boys	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
I	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
,	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
glass	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
one	O
Willington	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
glass	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
myhouse	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
back	O
,	O
drawing	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
an	O
officer	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pillar	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
the	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Willington	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
of	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fenner	I-pers
;	O
and	O
this	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Andrew	B-pers
Galoney	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
FENNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Galoney	I-pers
,	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Willington	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
;	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
keeps	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
girls	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
lets	O
lodgings	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WILLINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fenner	I-pers
left	O
it	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
WINTER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
confession	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pillar	O
's	O
platform	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
glass	O
behind	O
the	O
bags	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pillar	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
prosecute	O
me	O
no	O
further	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Pillar	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
above	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
plate	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
that	O
crime	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
SIMON	B-pers
SOLOMONS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mercer	O
and	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
Without	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
front	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
unscrewing	O
the	O
shutters	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
until	O
I	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
piece	O
was	O
dropt	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
footway	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dowsy	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nigh	O
where	O
the	O
cloth	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
feet	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
shop	O
situated	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
Without	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
persons	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
,	O
except	O
myself	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
large	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
shopmen	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
getting	O
his	O
hair	O
dressed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boywas	O
doing	O
his	O
ordinary	O
work	O
,	O
cleaning	O
knives	O
and	O
shoes	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
boy	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
you	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
you	O
turned	O
your	O
head	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
observed	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
heard	O
something	O
drawing	O
across	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
heard	O
somebody	O
drawing	O
something	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
naturally	O
look	O
round	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
caused	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
round	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
instant	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
you	O
saw	O
linen	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
linen	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
one	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
every	O
door	O
myself	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
opened	O
any	O
Irish	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
packed	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
paper	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Probably	O
you	O
bought	O
a	O
greater	O
quantity	O
than	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
been	O
opened	O
at	O
all	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
bought	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
opened	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
contained	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
opened	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
what	O
it	O
might	O
contain	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
you	O
only	O
suppose	O
from	O
measuring	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
how	O
many	O
yards	O
it	O
contained	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
mark	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
marked	O
my	O
own	O
private	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mark	O
how	O
many	O
yards	O
it	O
contained	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
dyed	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
calendered	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
calenderer	O
to	O
mark	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
the	O
yards	O
on	O
it	O
which	O
it	O
contains	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
yourself	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
had	O
observed	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DOWSEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
weaver	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
goods	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
threshold	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
let	O
fall	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
goods	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
I	O
saw	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
was	O
dropped	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brown	O
Irish	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
private	O
mark	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
delivered	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
bought	O
two	O
pieces	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
exactly	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
on	O
that	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
received	O
this	O
from	O
the	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
Most	O
certainly	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
kept	O
that	O
piece	O
which	O
the	O
witness	O
Dowsey	O
gave	O
you	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
immediately	O
.	O
It	O
hath	O
had	O
no	O
connection	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
;	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
With	O
regard	O
to	O
that	O
piece	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
only	O
seen	O
it	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LAMBE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
or	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
54	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Augustus	I-pers
Berkley	I-pers
,	O
Earl	O
of	O
Berkley	O
,	O
and	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
Lord	O
Berkley	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Grafton-street	B-place
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
house	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
flat	O
roof	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
no	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
lead	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
leads	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
was	O
the	O
leads	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TODD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
groom	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Amyand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Grafton-street	O
on	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dugar	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
jump	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
and	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
servant	O
and	O
me	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
jumped	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
smock	O
frock	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
very	O
quietly	O
till	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Evans	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
obstinate	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
himself	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
the	O
patrol	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
knife	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DUGAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
given	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
the	O
wall	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
short	O
smock	O
frock	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
sham	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Berkley	O
's	O
premises	O
;	O
next	O
to	O
that	O
wall	O
is	O
this	O
wall	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
dead	O
garden	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
walls	O
join	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
is	O
the	O
highest	O
by	O
two	O
foot	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CREW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
,	O
the	O
plumber	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
examined	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
corresponds	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NORRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
29	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
Parrott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
affixed	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MEREDITH	I-pers
PARROT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
lead	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
room	O
which	O
forms	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
in	O
Bridge-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
the	O
preceding	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
thoroughfare	O
behind	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
called	O
Bridge-court	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
this	O
room	O
was	O
flat-roofed	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
with	O
lead	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
patrol	O
notice	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
communicated	O
to	O
them	O
my	O
loss	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
premises	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
they	O
brought	O
some	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
my	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
lead	O
they	O
brought	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
,	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
appearance	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
WAYLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
passed	O
me	O
just	O
by	O
Privy-Gardens	O
,	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
lead	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
lately	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
directly	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
29	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
knife	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Parrott	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
St.	O
George's-row	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
over	O
Westminster-bridge	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
hard	O
frost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
past	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
prize	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
watch-house	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILLIS	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
For	O
stealing	O
6	O
Cwt	O
.	O
of	O
hemp	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COMYN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
Eliza	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
ship	B-place
Eliza	I-place
,	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
boat	O
was	O
fastened	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
to	O
take	O
our	O
supper	O
;	O
at	O
past	O
eight	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
the	O
boat	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Haywood	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KELLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Eliza	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
boat	O
fast	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
supper	O
;	O
the	O
boat	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
passed	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
came	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
painter	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
fast	O
on	O
board	O
ship	O
yet	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
painter	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PATERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
a	O
patrol	O
to	O
prevent	O
thieves	O
robbing	O
the	O
boats	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
ten	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
slack	O
water	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
rowing	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
bowed	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
comes	O
a	O
towing	O
match	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
towing	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
chucked	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
wherry	O
;	O
we	O
carriedthe	O
hemp	O
into	O
Mr	O
.	O
Climber	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
six	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
hemp	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
boat	O
at	O
our	O
boat-builder	O
's	O
;	O
Eliza	O
was	O
wrote	O
on	O
the	O
stem	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
that	O
were	O
towing	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLIMBER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
rowing	O
up	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
towing	O
match	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
boat	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
drawing	O
a	O
ship	O
's	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Willis	O
had	O
the	O
rope	O
over	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
Bailey	O
was	O
pulling	O
the	O
sculls	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
so	O
close	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
chuck	O
the	O
rope	O
from	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
rowed	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
wind	O
the	O
boat	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
shot	O
round	O
the	O
tier	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Willis	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
pursued	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boat	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
conscious	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
brought	O
Willis	O
all	O
over	O
wet	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
sixty	O
odd	O
heads	O
of	O
hemp	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
six	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
boat	O
had	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Eliza	O
on	O
the	O
stern	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Has	O
Comyn	O
seen	O
that	O
boat	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Comyn	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
boat	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
boat	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
prisoner	O
Willis	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
long	O
used	O
to	O
the	O
river	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
you	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
boat	O
on	O
drift	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
take	O
her	O
and	O
secure	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
nearest	O
place	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PIERCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Union-stairs	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boat	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
Union-stairs	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Bailey	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
stop	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
bloody	O
rogue	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LONGHURST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
somebody	O
splashing	O
in	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
under	O
the	O
ship	O
's	O
bottom	O
;	O
he	O
proceeded	O
on	O
;	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
chin	O
level	O
with	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
came	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
hauled	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
presently	O
;	O
we	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Comyn	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
rope	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
fastened	O
the	O
boat	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
tolerable	O
good	O
rope	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Willis	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
to	O
Willis	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
story	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
tell	O
it	O
yourself	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
WILLIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
this	O
man	O
as	O
a	O
waterman	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
fish-boat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boat	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
called	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
boat	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
,	O
pick	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
shore	O
;	O
so	O
immediately	O
the	O
waterman	O
gave	O
me	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
rope	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
till	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
halloo	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
then	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
immediately	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Willis	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Bailey	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
to	O
Comyn	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
hemp	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
CHIEF	O
BARON	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JAMES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
an	O
inside	O
case	O
and	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
61	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
Marshall-street	B-place
,	I-place
Carnaby-market	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
pass	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
daddy	O
?	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
slight	O
push	O
on	O
the	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
hardly	O
knew	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
meant	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
lean	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
person	O
in	O
view	O
till	O
the	O
turning	O
of	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
crowd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
lamps	O
near	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
voice	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
daddy	O
?	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
supposed	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
somebody	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
:	O
I	O
leave	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clemency	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
61	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
part	O
of	O
five	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
that	O
afternoon	O
with	O
others	O
.	O
-	O
GOREING	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
considerably	O
a-head	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
down	O
Broad-street	O
;	O
Marshall-street	O
crosses	O
Broad-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
might	O
be	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
making	O
up	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
following	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
foremost	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
running	O
into	O
my	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
says	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Between	O
that	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
described	O
this	O
to	O
have	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
how	O
many	O
streets	O
were	O
there	O
that	O
branched	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Cambridge-street	O
and	O
Poland-street	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARTLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
crossing	O
leading	O
from	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Poland-street	O
to	O
Cambridge-street	O
;	O
Marshall-street	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
Supposing	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Marshall-street	O
into	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
could	O
he	O
have	O
dropt	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
that	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
when	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
having	O
had	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
name	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Cofield	I-pers
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
Marshall-street	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Goreing	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
goes	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
cabinet-maker	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
CHIEF	O
BARON	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
attend	O
to	O
that	O
recommendation	O
;	O
for	O
though	O
this	O
slight	O
of	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
these	O
people	O
have	O
acquired	O
,	O
is	O
become	O
extremely	O
dangerous	O
to	O
the	O
community	O
,	O
yet	O
there	O
certainly	O
is	O
a	O
difference	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
open	O
and	O
direct	O
violence	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
certainly	O
a	O
fair	O
ground	O
for	O
your	O
recommendation	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
mercy	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
mercy	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
his	O
poor	O
distressed	O
mother	O
;	O
and	O
sorry	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
56.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
three	O
cotton	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cosmo	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
COSMO	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
cotton	O
shawls	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-court	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
CHARLOTTE	B-pers
COSMO	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
turned	O
thirteen	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
ever	O
prospering	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
devil	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Detcry	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
lap	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
rope-walk	O
,	O
Queen	B-place
Anne-street	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lap	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
her	O
uncle	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
she	O
in	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
ran	O
off	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
uncle	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
knock	O
at	O
any	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
off	O
rather	O
quick	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
three	O
shawls	O
have	O
been	O
recovered	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
DETCRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shop-woman	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
goods	O
myself	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
some	O
shawls	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
mistress	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
else	O
to	O
send	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
shawls	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
and	O
constable	O
.	O
-	O
CHAFFINCH	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
shawl	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
one	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
8	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
girl	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
two	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
stopt	O
her	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
;	O
this	O
happened	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Friday	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cosmo	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shawls	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
private	O
mark	O
,	O
one	O
R	O
U	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
A	O
U	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Cosmo	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
one	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
57.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Horwood	I-pers
;	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
half	O
pint	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HORWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Horns	I-place
,	I-place
Upper	I-place
Thames-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
pint	O
he	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
;	O
having	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
searched	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
detained	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
one	O
pint	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
each	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half-pint	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
all	O
into	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
who	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
hand	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
quart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cypher	O
on	O
the	O
pint	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
bar	O
pint	O
;	O
we	O
particularly	O
missed	O
the	O
cypher	O
pot	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
pint	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
Mr.	O
Horwood	O
in	O
taking	O
these	O
pots	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
one	O
quart	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
here	O
now	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
saw	O
taken	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Horwood	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Morton	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
MORTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	B-place
Queen's-head	I-place
,	I-place
Darkhouse-lane	I-place
;	O
apparently	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
times	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
sign	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Monument	I-place
,	I-place
Little	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
pint	O
and	O
half-pint	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
any	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
sick	O
wife	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
66	O
.	O
)	O
Publicly	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
3	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
58.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NORMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Mark	B-pers
Small	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Small	I-pers
.	O
MARK	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
next	O
July	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
I	O
should	O
swear	O
false	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
punishment	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
bundles	O
I	O
carried	O
from	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
White-horse	O
yard	O
,	O
Wells-street	O
,	O
East-Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Catharine-street	O
,	O
Strand	O
,	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Crutched-friars	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
lad	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
Lombard-street	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Post-office	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
directions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
show	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
Post-office	O
;	O
never	O
mind	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
as	O
I	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
church	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
sixpence	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Ely-place	B-place
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
which	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
snatched	O
my	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
bundles	O
,	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
hat	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
my	O
hat	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
bottomof	O
Ely-place	O
;	O
I	O
halloo	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
picked	O
my	O
hat	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
lighted	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
lighted	O
when	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
voice	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Public-office	O
,	O
East-Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
mother	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
exactly	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
my	O
wife	O
washes	O
for	O
the	O
young	O
men	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Small	I-pers
:	O
on	O
Christmas-eve	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
son	O
with	O
three	O
bundles	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
blue	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
with	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
was	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
bundle	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chappell	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
in	O
Middle-row	O
,	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
place	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
's	O
,	O
Catharine-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
from	O
an	O
hundred	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
30	O
s.	O
altogether	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
the	O
father	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
as	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
,	O
black	O
coat	O
,	O
black	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
corduroy	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
particular	O
in	O
his	O
walk	O
,	O
with	O
straight	O
light	O
hair	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
,	O
East-Smithfield	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
then	O
a	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
buttoned	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
to	O
bottom	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
amongst	O
not	O
less	O
than	O
twenty	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
dress	O
again	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
appeared	O
the	O
clothes	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
him	O
that	O
concerned	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
pointed	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
parlour	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
VANNEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
Christmas-eve	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Gardens	O
,	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
often	O
comes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine's-lane	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
at	O
sea	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
the	O
bellman	O
went	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
compute	O
to	O
be	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
relation	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
get	O
his	O
dinner	O
often	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
might	O
he	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
.	O
What	O
relation	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
so	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Christmas-eve	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Christmas-day	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Might	O
it	O
not	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
dined	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
else	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
STACK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
From	O
one	O
till	O
six	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Vannest	O
,	O
and	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
both	O
(	O
I	O
wentby	O
invitation	O
)	O
on	O
Christmas-eve	O
;	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
would	O
meet	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
particular	O
reason	O
for	O
dining	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Vannest	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
I	O
always	O
do	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
she	O
washes	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
dined	O
with	O
her	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
dine	O
by	O
invitation	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
your	O
dinner	O
?	O
-	O
Always	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
dinner	O
.	O
Always	O
paid	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
always	O
paid	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
paid	O
somehow	O
or	O
somehow	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
pay	O
Vannest	O
for	O
your	O
dinner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
charged	O
me	O
nothing	O
for	O
my	O
dinner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
your	O
dinner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
lately	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
your	O
dinner	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Plymouth	O
Dock	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
dinner	O
on	O
Saturday	O
?	O
-	O
Beef	O
and	O
pudding	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
pudding	O
?	O
-	O
Plumb-pudding	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
beef	O
roasted	O
or	O
boiled	O
?	O
-	O
Roasted	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
on	O
Sunday	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
leg	O
of	O
mutton	O
roasted	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
potatoes	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
on	O
Monday	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
remains	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
after	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
nothing	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
else	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
twopenny	O
loaf	O
.	O
Who	O
dined	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Saturday	O
?	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Vannest	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dennis	B-pers
Stack	I-pers
.	O
Who	O
dined	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Sunday	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Who	O
dined	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Monday	O
?	O
-	O
Catherine	B-pers
Vannest	I-pers
and	O
me	O
alone	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Vannest	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
dined	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Saturday	O
but	O
yourself	O
and	O
your	O
brother	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
:	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
dinner	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
wash	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
every	O
day	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
often	O
calls	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
victuals	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
cupboard	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
frequently	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
always	O
,	O
only	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
pay	O
you	O
for	O
his	O
dinners	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
pays	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
victuals	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
victuals	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
you	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
-	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
Saturday	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
brother	O
dined	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
brother	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
besides	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
brother	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Monday	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
dinner	O
on	O
Saturday	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
Irish	O
stew	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
mutton	O
and	O
potatoes	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
your	O
Saturday	O
's	O
dinner	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-eve	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
on	O
Sunday	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
bit	O
of	O
roast	O
beef	O
and	O
a	O
plumb-pudding	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
this	O
Stack	O
did	O
not	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
on	O
Monday	O
?	O
-	O
Some	O
of	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
roast	O
beef	O
and	O
pudding	O
,	O
not	O
mutton	O
and	O
potatoes	O
?	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
Dawson	O
told	O
the	O
boy	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
naturally	O
pitched	O
upon	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mark	B-pers
Small	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
Dawson	O
tell	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
only	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
me	O
and	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
highway	O
robbery	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
59.	O
JAMES	B-pers
STACEY	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
STACEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
three	O
pint	O
and	O
two	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Masons-arms	B-place
,	I-place
Upper	I-place
Berkley-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
pots	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
Leech	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
pots	O
we	O
never	O
send	O
out	O
,	O
only	O
use	O
them	O
for	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEECH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Lord	O
Clive	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
Cavendish-square	O
;	O
these	O
pots	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoners	O
'	O
apartments	O
in	O
seeking	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
'	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
Berwick-court	O
,	O
nearly	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Thursday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
under	O
some	O
clothes	O
,	O
two	O
bar	O
pots	O
under	O
a	O
hod	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
pots	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
lodgings	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
drinking	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
pot	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
tumbled	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
many	O
people	O
came	O
round	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
extricate	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
dared	O
say	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
was	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
PEEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
chare	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
'	O
lodgings	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
;	O
they	O
live	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
;	O
the	O
pots	O
produced	O
are	O
the	O
pots	O
we	O
took	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
cupboard	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
by	O
having	O
them	O
in	O
use	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
having	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
quitted	O
without	O
paying	O
his	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Leech	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
the	O
pot	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
together	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
STACEY	O
.	O
This	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
frosty	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
towards	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
liquor	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
off	O
towards	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
company	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
night	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
three-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
different	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pots	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
's	O
maid	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
wife	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
pots	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
here	O
,	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
and	O
his	O
maid	O
came	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pots	O
,	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
home	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
Marybone	O
parish	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
knows	O
that	O
I	O
work	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
get	O
money	O
I	O
spend	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Leech	O
knows	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Palmer	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
pots	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
building	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
expected	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
STACEY	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
Aged	O
40	O
.	O
)	O
Publicly	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
3	O
months	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
STACEY	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
60.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
READ	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
bridle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
carpetting	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
'	O
desire	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THACKWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
lost	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
the	O
coach-house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
the	O
Christmas-day	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
week	O
following	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Dick	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bridle	O
and	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
carpet	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glasses	O
fitted	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
frames	O
on	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
colour	O
that	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
quite	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Dick	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
four	O
glasses	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
two	O
front	O
glasses	O
.	O
ELIAS	B-pers
MORDECAI	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
first	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
glasses	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
these	O
glasses	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
another	O
room	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
pulled	O
out	O
three	O
glasses	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
lap	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
carpet	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
saw	O
me	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
brother	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
understood	O
them	O
better	O
than	O
me	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
glass	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
gets	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
shoes	O
were	O
all	O
mouldy	O
with	O
country	O
dirt	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
109	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
rag	O
line	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Thackway	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
?	O
-	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
292	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
.	O
LEVY	B-pers
LEVY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
rags	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
sorting	O
rags	O
in	O
Mordecai	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
themorning	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
first	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
carpet	O
,	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
followed	O
her	O
with	O
three	O
coach	O
glasses	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
the	O
man	O
any	O
questions	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-joiner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
cross	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
and	O
Mordecai	O
the	O
Jew	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
glasses	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
glass	O
for	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
27	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
brother	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
good	O
bargain	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
front	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
broken	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
little	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
some	O
glasses	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
them	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edward	O
's	O
and	O
tried	O
the	O
frames	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fitted	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
that	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
glass	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
without	O
the	O
frames	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
frames	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Kinsey	O
,	O
New-Road	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
glasses	O
of	O
Mordecai	O
's	O
brother	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
stop	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
Thackway	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
glasses	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
frames	O
left	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
front	O
glasses	O
.	O
To	O
Dick	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
the	O
third	O
glass	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
frame	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
frame	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observations	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
the	O
brother	O
brought	O
you	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
glass	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
measured	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
diamond-cut	O
glass	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mordecai	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
bridle	O
,	O
carpet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
the	O
coat	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
guinea	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
one	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
carpetting	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mordecai	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
a	O
brother	O
of	O
his	O
to	O
East-Smithfield	O
office	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
information	O
last	O
Monday	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoners	O
'	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bridle	O
and	O
the	O
carpet	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Thackway	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
'	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
butter	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
here	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
named	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mayne	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
lock-up	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Moses	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
for	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
bring	O
you	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
so	O
false	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
swear	O
that	O
your	O
husband	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
sware	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
God	O
may	O
judge	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
judgement	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mayne	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
her	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
these	O
prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
do	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
Read	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
;	O
they	O
always	O
passed	O
so	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Readthese	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Jacobs	O
to	O
Mayne	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
Moushe	O
Pop	O
;	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
mean	O
that	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
DE	I-pers
BURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Prussian	O
blue	O
manufactory	O
,	O
in	O
No	O
.	O
27	O
,	O
Jacks's-row	O
,	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
till	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
and	O
Friday	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
quay	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
London-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
some	O
Turkey	O
from	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Turkey	O
was	O
entered	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
this	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
remained	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
on	O
Saturday	O
he	O
came	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
remained	O
till	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
works	O
on	O
the	O
quays	O
;	O
I	O
employ	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Thackway	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
stable-house	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
double-locked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
single	O
lock	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoners	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
further	O
to	O
their	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
proved	O
they	O
lived	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
READ	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
61.	O
MARY	B-pers
COLLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hetely	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HETELY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
49	I-place
,	I-place
Old	I-place
Compton-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
from	O
a	O
small	O
room	O
over	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
last	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
past	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
shop-door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MARISS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
66	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
one	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
62.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
containing	O
126	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
their	O
property	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
only	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
FENN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Richard	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
only	O
partner	O
;	O
I	O
pay	O
the	O
expences	O
of	O
housekeeping	O
myself	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
or	O
31st	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shutter	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
intirely	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
screws	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
nuts	O
;	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
have	O
free	O
access	O
into	O
my	O
warehouse	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Fenn	O
and	O
Rothwell	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
place	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
shop	O
shut	O
up	O
so	O
early	O
as	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
wholesale	O
dealer	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RHODES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Fenn	O
and	O
Rothwell	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
go	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
secure	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
at	O
eight	O
,	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
break	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
watchman	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
place	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
was	O
safe	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
pieces	O
gone	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
level	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
pile	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
another	O
of	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
At	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
you	O
saw	O
all	O
safe	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
With	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
pieces	O
themselves	O
you	O
made	O
no	O
observations	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
right	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
you	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
parcels	O
lay	O
level	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SERGEANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
ward	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
observed	O
something	O
at	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Fenn	O
and	O
Rothwell	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Newman's-court	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
pannel	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
very	O
busy	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stretch	O
his	O
arms	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
pannel	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
covered	O
with	O
this	O
pannel	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
stoop	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
stretch	O
his	O
arms	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
something	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
having	O
been	O
cut	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
cut	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hackney-coach	O
on	O
the	O
rank	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
fronting	O
the	O
place	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
immediately	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
going	O
cross	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
slipt	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
left-hand	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
turn	O
after	O
these	O
two	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
pursuing	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
my	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
more	O
than	O
five	O
yards	O
distance	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
flag-stones	O
before	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
walked	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
took	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
ever	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sight	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
those	O
three	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
is	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
alarm	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
rung	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
only	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
only	O
suppose	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
crow	O
;	O
Rhodes	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
opposite	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
nothing	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
coach	O
was	O
not	O
open	O
,	O
nor	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
open	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
I	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
You	O
paid	O
no	O
attention	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
minded	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
your	O
watch-box	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
no	O
boxes	O
in	O
the	O
ward	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
was	O
this	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
North	O
side	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
stand	O
of	O
coaches	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
try	O
the	O
fastenings	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
beat	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
twelve	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
go	O
round	O
the	O
ward	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
said	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
your	O
beat	O
;	O
what	O
brought	O
you	O
to	O
this	O
spot	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
try	O
the	O
pins	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
my	O
beat	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
all	O
round	O
the	O
whole	O
ward	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
twelve	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
go	O
round	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
ward	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
fastenings	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
try	O
them	O
I	O
call	O
my	O
own	O
beat	O
;	O
this	O
part	O
happens	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
beat	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
try	O
the	O
fastenings	O
.	O
-	O
RHODES	O
sworn	O
.	O
Of	O
whom	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
that	O
crow	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Sergeant	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
OSSINGBROKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
crow	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
)	O
house	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
door	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fenn	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Finch-lane	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
groove	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
for	O
shutters	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
last	O
year	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
by	O
John	O
Sergeant	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
questions	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
what	O
could	O
bring	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
hour	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
into	O
that	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
drinking-club	O
in	O
Shoemaker-row	O
,	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
then	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Fenn	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Townsend	O
and	O
Jealous	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
finding	O
Jealous	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
finding	O
Jealous	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
fellow	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
living	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
keeps	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
public-house	O
,	O
Half-moon	O
alley	O
,	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
Jealous	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
people	O
,	O
mentioning	O
two	O
names	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
that	O
morning	O
fast	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
of	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
assertion	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
living	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
public-house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
Shoemaker-row	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
person	O
had	O
been	O
inclined	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
Shoemaker-row	O
to	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
way	O
,	O
although	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
nearest	O
way	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
happen	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Undoubtedly	O
if	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
Shoemaker-row	O
to	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
his	O
way	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
tothe	O
monument	O
;	O
but	O
would	O
it	O
not	O
be	O
coming	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
Aldgate	O
to	O
Half-moon	O
alley	O
,	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
through	O
Cornhill	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
almost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
should	O
you	O
think	O
Cornhill	O
the	O
safer	O
road	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
thought	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
danger	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
certainly	O
taken	O
the	O
