TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1793	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
SANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
MANOAH	O
SIBLY	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Goswell-Street	O
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
HENRY	B-pers
FENWICK	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
63	O
,	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
.	O
PRICE	O
ONE	O
SHILLING	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JAMES	B-pers
SANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
:	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
:	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bracey	I-pers
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Meymott	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Leggatt	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Kerrington	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
William	B-pers
Shrub	I-pers
James	B-pers
Pateman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
William	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gerald	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Shurman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
George	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Dorrell	I-pers
James	B-pers
Collingsbridge	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cheek	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
William	B-pers
Burdon	I-pers
673.	O
MARY	B-pers
JENNINGS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Joel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
of	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
and	O
a	O
check	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Joel	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
JOEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cordwainer	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
4	B-place
,	I-place
East	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Lewis	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
when	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
they	O
wrenched	O
off	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
door	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
girl	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
alarm	O
?	O
-	O
Lewis	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
came	O
on	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
before	O
six	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Mary	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
with	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
when	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
half	O
the	O
property	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
past	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
back	O
kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
wrenched	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
this	O
yard	O
lead	O
to	O
?	O
is	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
or	O
how	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
thorough	O
fare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
wife	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
altogether	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
apron	O
loose	O
,	O
Haris	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
slippers	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
making	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
name	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
muslin	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
worn	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
JOEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
this	O
night	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
layed	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
girl	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
very	O
fast	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
tookhold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
?	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
locked	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
left	O
open	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
locked	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
girl	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
edging	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
here	O
apron	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
lap	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
property	O
here	O
,	O
directly	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
off	O
but	O
loose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
without	O
going	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
how	O
could	O
I	O
get	O
in	O
without	O
the	O
key	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
this	O
kitchen	O
door	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
or	O
is	O
it	O
an	O
inside	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
passage	O
locked	O
or	O
unlocked	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
was	O
an	O
inner	O
kitchen	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
kitchen	O
door	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
articles	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
girl	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
shoes	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
apron	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
washed	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
apron	O
has	O
aquasortis	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
down	O
that	O
morning	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
that	O
door	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
how	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
street	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Joel	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Joel	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
day	O
light	O
when	O
you	O
locked	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
O	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
day	O
light	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Joel	B-pers
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
with	O
some	O
edging	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
articles	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
lock	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
half	O
a	O
glass	O
window	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
sell	O
these	O
clothes	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
thiswoman	O
came	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
674.	O
ANN	B-pers
LOWMAN	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LANE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
STEPHEN	O
RIDDINGTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
675.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DELLEMOTTE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
soles	O
for	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dizney	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DIZNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
he	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
more	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Dizney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Duke's-court	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
employ	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
militia	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
that	O
he	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
these	O
boots	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
till	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
putting	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
post	O
office	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
boots	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
frequently	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
boots	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Simpson	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
boots	O
.	O
Dizney	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
boots	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
sold	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Twelve	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
perfectly	O
well	O
knows	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
offence	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
mere	O
want	O
;	O
he	O
knows	O
meperfectly	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
children	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
wife	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Dizney	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
understand	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
children	O
in	O
the	O
workhouse	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
defrauded	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
out	O
of	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
42	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
676.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
spade	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hay	O
steel	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
halter	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
cropper	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
leather	O
belly	O
band	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
leather	O
wanty	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plough	O
chains	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
tame	O
live	O
hen	O
fowl	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
live	O
cock	O
fowl	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevenit	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
STEVENIT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevenit	I-pers
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
farming	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
stable	O
up	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
first	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
harness	O
,	O
a	O
spade	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
steel	O
yard	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
work	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
things	O
here	O
?	O
just	O
produce	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
weight	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
spade	O
by	O
this	O
mending	O
here	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
eighteen-pence	O
mending	O
.	O
RICHARD	O
GASS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
and	O
headborough	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
just	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Acton	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
property	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
spade	O
,	O
steel	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
the	O
fowls	O
hung	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spade	O
and	O
bundle	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
for	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drove	O
out	O
for	O
hunger	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
28	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
677.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GILBERT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FLINT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BEDNELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
slop	O
seller	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
362	B-place
,	I-place
Armitage-street	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
;	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
had	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
attending	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
till	O
night	O
when	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
settled	O
with	O
his	O
captain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
packed	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
whity	O
brown	O
and	O
brown	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
wanting	O
toput	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
another	O
parcel	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WEAVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
KNIGHTLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
the	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
on	O
the	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
plated	O
buckles	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
a	O
very	O
right	O
thing	O
,	O
the	O
public	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Flint	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
greek	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
lost	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Knightly	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
50	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
678.	O
ANN	B-pers
ANDREWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
check	O
linen	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Beston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BESTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
43	B-place
,	I-place
Fort-street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
let	O
lodgings	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
this	O
Ann	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
at	O
three	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
forwards	O
;	O
they	O
stayed	O
one	O
week	O
,	O
they	O
paid	O
me	O
that	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
they	O
robbed	O
the	O
lodgings	O
and	O
set	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
both	O
came	O
and	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
took	O
it	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Susannah	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Michaelmas	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
from	O
your	O
lodgings	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
curtains	O
,	O
a	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coverlid	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
you	O
recover	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
has	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
giving	O
earnest	O
,	O
or	O
paying	O
the	O
rent	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
both	O
took	O
it	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
.	O
LYDIA	B-pers
BESTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
locking	O
herself	O
in	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
an	O
iron	O
and	O
a	O
frying	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
gentleman	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
justly	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
woman	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
duplicates	O
for	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
two	O
sheets	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
she	O
rented	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
apartment	O
.	O
-	O
TURNER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
sheets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
sheets	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
when	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
pawn	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Evans	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
but	O
these	O
two	O
sheets	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Beston	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
sheets	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
was	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
mistress	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
learning	O
her	O
business	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
pledged	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Friday	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
the	O
woman	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
tickets	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
them	O
till	O
she	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
32	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
679.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BURLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
globe	O
glass	O
lamp	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HUDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
in	O
law	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
boot	O
closer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
returning	O
again	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
wanted	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
lodgers	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
lodgers	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
one	O
arm	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
under	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
trying	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
back	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
down	O
this	O
globe	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
religious	O
society	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
has	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fixed	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
round	O
brass	O
plate	O
where	O
the	O
beam	O
of	O
it	O
goes	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
take	O
out	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
ease	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
the	O
lamp	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
stands	O
loose	O
in	O
a	O
socket	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
no	O
screw	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
lamp	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Promiscuously	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hudson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Hudson	O
take	O
the	O
lamp	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
with	O
this	O
lamp	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
backward	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
ease	O
herself	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
stands	O
there	O
beat	O
me	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
there	O
is	O
justice	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
at	O
all	O
but	O
God	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
30	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
680.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
BARNETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
frying	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
in	O
a	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
RING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cable-street	B-place
,	I-place
Wellclose-square	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
east	I-place
;	O
I	O
let	O
lodgings	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
shillingsweek	O
;	O
she	O
stayed	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
paid	O
one	O
week	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
key	O
by	O
a	O
stranger	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
frying	O
pan	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
got	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
use	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
married	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
put	O
both	O
their	O
names	O
down	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
accustom	O
yourself	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
lodgings	O
to	O
girls	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
gentlemen	O
he	O
does	O
himself	O
no	O
credit	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAPLIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
frying	O
pan	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
find	O
this	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Ring	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
frying	O
pan	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
mark	O
S.	O
E.	O
K.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
here	O
young	O
man	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ring	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
keeping	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ill	O
used	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
and	O
turned	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ring	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Ring	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
promise	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
681.	O
MARY	B-pers
COOLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sweatman	I-pers
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
SWEATMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sweatman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Earl-street	I-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
entered	O
our	O
shop	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
shoes	O
there	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
shoes	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
gets	O
my	O
livelyhood	O
by	O
shoe	O
blacking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happened	O
that	O
morning	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
drop	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mistook	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
use	O
to	O
black	O
shoes	O
for	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
57	O
.	O
)	O
Fined	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
682.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
three	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sherbone	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SHERBONE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
my	O
pewter	O
pots	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Spread	B-place
Eagle	I-place
in	I-place
Old	I-place
North-street	I-place
,	I-place
Red	I-place
Lion-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
opposite	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
rather	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
the	O
square	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
suspect	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
three	O
pots	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
pockets	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
supply	O
that	O
house	O
with	O
pots	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
gentlewoman	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
pots	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
got	O
more	O
than	O
sixty	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
23	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
683.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MACARTHY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
fustian	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
with	O
capes	O
,	O
trimmed	O
with	O
narrow	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
cotton	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
dimity	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
binder	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
tucker	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Almeria	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
.	O
JANE	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
lives	O
in	O
Hawnorth-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bedford-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
painting	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
Almira	O
Giles	O
is	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
property	O
here	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
playhouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fetched	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
gown	O
by	O
its	O
being	O
pieced	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
that	O
is	O
alledge	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
witnesses	O
.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
DAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
bed	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
charged	O
with	O
any	O
particular	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
girl	O
's	O
room	O
that	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Miller	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
that	O
you	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Church-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
rented	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
girl	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
witness	O
that	O
see	O
another	O
man	O
carry	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Had	O
any	O
strange	O
woman	O
any	O
access	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
684.	O
MARY	B-pers
ODDY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
muslin	O
apron	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
black	O
cloak	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
keep	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
black	O
cloak	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
she	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
absconded	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
accused	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
apron	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
absconded	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
apron	O
out	O
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
Mary	B-pers
Oddy	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
apron	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
fetch	O
both	O
apron	O
and	O
cloak	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
brother	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
great	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
allows	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
every	O
month	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
generally	O
paid	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
makes	O
sailors	O
jackets	O
,	O
and	O
slops	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAPLIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
I	O
paid	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
I	O
owed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
son	O
that	O
is	O
transported	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
forty	O
shillings	O
by	O
me	O
likewise	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
Newgate	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
got	O
two	O
children	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
685.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willymott	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLYMOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
come	O
to	O
prove	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
wife	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
spoon	O
being	O
defaced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
arms	O
being	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
from	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
carriage	O
come	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
arms	O
on	O
the	O
carriage	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
was	O
defaced	O
.	O
Willymott	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
spoon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wentworth	O
to	O
Davis	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
article	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
doubled	O
together	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
arms	O
was	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
suspicion	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
this	O
being	O
defaced	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
bruised	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
bowl	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
produced	O
the	O
bowl	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
only	O
what	O
the	O
man	O
brought	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
find	O
a	O
bowl	O
to	O
that	O
then	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
bowl	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
put	O
any	O
questions	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
Treadway	O
came	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
cess	O
pool	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
arms	O
out	O
?	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
any	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wentworth	O
to	O
Willymott	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
being	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
DINAH	B-pers
KITCHEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
carpenter	O
at	O
work	O
repairing	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
52	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
686.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
STEPHENS	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CHINNERY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whealey	I-pers
.	O
HANNAH	O
WHEALEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whealey	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
during	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
their	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
their	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
we	O
shut	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
only	O
a	O
coarse	O
apron	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
belonged	O
to	O
Catharine	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
my	O
servant	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAPLIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
shed	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
concealed	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
shed	O
belonged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
took	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
or	O
did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
in	O
a	O
shed	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Chinnery	O
present	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Chinnery	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
only	O
what	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
told	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Whealey	O
.	O
This	O
apron	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Stephens	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
parcel	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whealey	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
Stephens	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
nobody	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
Chinnery	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
55	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chinnery	I-pers
,	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
687.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STOLLARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty-four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
called	O
bandanno	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Legrew	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Peltrau	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
KIRBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
PELTRAU	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Legrew	I-pers
,	O
we	O
are	O
silk	O
manufacturers	O
in	O
Stewart-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Stollard	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Kirby	O
was	O
apprehended	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
any	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
her	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
any	O
favour	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
first	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
apartment	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
patience	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
crying	O
and	O
frightened	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
bandanno	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
taken	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
remainder	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
woman	O
or	O
the	O
man	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
lodgings	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
your	O
warehouse	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
Before	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
our	O
number	O
book	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
what	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
but	O
the	O
marks	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
other	O
partner	O
except	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Legrew	I-pers
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
mention	O
a	O
syllable	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
having	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
twodepositions	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Floud	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sign	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
examination	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
your	O
signature	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q.There	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
that	O
circumstance	O
of	O
his	O
confession	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
magistrate	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Floud	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Floud	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Colquohon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
living	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
at	O
this	O
very	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
to	O
an	O
inn	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
then	O
say	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Peltrau	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
property	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
stock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
taken	O
stock	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
those	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
missing	O
that	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
sold	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
every	O
number	O
and	O
these	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Armstrong	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
your	O
partner	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Legrew	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
her	O
apartment	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Legrew	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
examined	O
twice	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
same	O
magistrate	O
or	O
different	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
before	O
different	O
magistrates	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
conversation	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
stated	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
or	O
the	O
second	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
here	O
in	O
this	O
deposition	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
mentioned	O
it	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
son	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
121	O
,	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
one	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
of	O
whom	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
Harriot	O
Bole	O
or	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
.	O
HARRIOT	O
BOLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Kirby	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
bring	O
some	O
bandanno	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
whom	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
continue	O
bringing	O
handkerchiefs	O
?	O
-	O
All	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
there	O
sometimes	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
few	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
sometimes	O
twelve	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
or	O
seven	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
travelled	O
the	O
country	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ruined	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
chocolate	O
colour	O
and	O
blue	O
birds	O
eyes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
information	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
all	O
this	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
mention	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
I	O
recollect	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
mistress	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
first	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
see	O
her	O
sometimes	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
fag	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
cut	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
burn	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fire	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
chuck	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
necessary	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
some	O
butter	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
never	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
felony	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
once	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
this	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
turned	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
being	O
turned	O
up	O
?	O
how	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
these	O
terms	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
gentlemen	O
discharged	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
accused	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
we	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
butter	O
firkin	O
again	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
they	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
discovery	O
till	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White-row	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
one	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
Harriot	O
Bole	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Harriot	O
Bole	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
LACEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
of	O
who	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Harriot	O
Bole	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
French	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
now	O
examined	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
pawning	O
it	O
with	O
French	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
your	O
mistress	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
police	O
office	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Kirby	O
in	O
Dillon's-court	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
conversation	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Kirby	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hold	O
out	O
any	O
promises	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
must	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
?	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Stollard	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
's	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
his	O
master	O
knew	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
some	O
fag	O
ends	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
privy	O
joining	O
her	O
door	O
almost	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Armstrong	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
that	O
profession	O
to	O
drag	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
these	O
fag	O
ends	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
This	O
privy	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
common	O
use	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
common	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
hinder	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
Stollard	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
better	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
Stollard	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
woman	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Stollard	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
her	O
before	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
printer	O
;	O
I	O
print	O
handkerchiefs	O
for	O
Messrs.	O
Peltrau	O
and	O
Legrew	O
;	O
I	O
generally	O
puts	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
every	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
for	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
fag	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
these	O
fag	O
ends	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
work	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
Here	O
is	O
one	O
done	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
L.	O
P.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
put	O
L.	O
P.	O
on	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
denote	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Peltrau	O
and	O
Legrew	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
that	O
appears	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
name	O
is	O
defaced	O
nearly	O
;	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
done	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
these	O
would	O
match	O
the	O
pattern	O
of	O
any	O
handkerchief	O
here	O
produced	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
nor	O
no	O
man	O
living	O
can	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
marked	O
with	O
?	O
-	O
With	O
a	O
type	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
prepared	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
patent	O
.	O
-	O
READ	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
excise	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
fag	O
ends	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
was	O
stamped	O
by	O
me	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
You	O
as	O
an	O
excise	O
officer	O
,	O
stamp	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
stamped	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
without	O
being	O
stamped	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
legally	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
stamp	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Stollard	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Kirby	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
that	O
girl	O
Bole	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
false	O
oath	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
witness	O
against	O
her	O
own	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
five	O
guineas	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
privy	O
it	O
is	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
by	O
a	O
dozen	O
misfortunate	O
girls	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Stollard	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Peltrau	O
.	O
Had	O
William	B-pers
Stollard	I-pers
access	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
where	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
deposited	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
always	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stollard	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
27	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
688.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SIMMONS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
lost	O
two	O
spoons	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
kitchen	O
abouteleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pantry	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
James	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
take	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
and	O
conceal	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
doing	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
down	O
as	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
we	O
wanted	O
any	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
fishmongers	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
out	O
of	O
Clare-market	O
that	O
supplied	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
with	O
fish	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
spoons	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
none	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apron	O
with	O
the	O
right	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
spoons	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
marked	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
they	O
formerly	O
belonged	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hender	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
bought	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
on	O
them	O
A.	O
T.	O
H.	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
these	O
letters	O
on	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
Wightman	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
-	O
WIGHTMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
spoons	O
that	O
Watson	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
spoons	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
very	O
minute	O
before	O
the	O
footman	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
nobody	O
here	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
689.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Esau	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
,	O
Jane	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
check	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Esau	O
Alfred	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
ALFRED	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Esau	O
Alfred	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Castle-lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
backward	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
front	O
parlour	O
door	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Duck	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
very	O
seldom	O
goes	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
my	O
front	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
through	O
my	O
front	O
room	O
into	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
through	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shut	O
it	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
positively	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
so	O
positive	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
latched	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
hallooed	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
not	O
more	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
followed	O
him	O
directly	O
on	O
my	O
calling	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
try	O
to	O
fling	O
some	O
things	O
over	O
some	O
pales	O
into	O
a	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
hitched	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
pales	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
JACOB	B-pers
ALFRED	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
facing	O
my	O
house	O
my	O
mother	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
things	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
hitched	O
on	O
the	O
pales	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
bundle	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
when	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
man	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Jane	O
Alfred	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
check	O
apron	O
it	O
rolled	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
gown	O
by	O
a	O
piece	O
that	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
under	O
the	O
arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
my	O
defence	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
let	O
my	O
friends	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
690.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BARNES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
last	O
Friday	O
evening	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
rather	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
just	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-court	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
City	O
home	O
to	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
more	O
than	O
five	O
yards	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
takes	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seized	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
off	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
and	O
seals	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
indeed	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-court	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
people	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
villain	O
that	O
snatched	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
positive	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
St.	O
Martin's-court	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
gentleman	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
comes	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
cane	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
ill	O
use	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
people	O
surrounding	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
call	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
look	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
played	O
a	O
slight	O
of	O
hand	O
trick	O
,	O
accordingly	O
he	O
felt	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
691	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
woollen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
kerseymire	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thickset	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
leather	O
powder	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
powder	O
puffs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
razor	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
steel	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Vallans	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
VALLANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
property	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Lukener's-lane	B-place
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
whose	O
house	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
your	O
lordship	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
relate	O
the	O
story	O
I	O
will	O
relate	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
named	O
herself	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
?	O
which	O
I	O
complied	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Lukener's-lane	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
sleep	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
withdrew	O
from	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
agreed	O
to	O
sleep	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
bundle	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
was	O
left	O
hanging	O
over	O
the	O
chair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
merry	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
spirits	O
;	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
awoke	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
me	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
bundle	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
property	O
on	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
she	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
down	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
catched	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
for	O
a	O
certain	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
was	O
discharged	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
a	O
duplicate	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
bundle	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
692.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KNIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
O'Brian	I-pers
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	O
O'BRIAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
happened	O
in	O
Oxford-road	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
on	O
pretty	O
close	O
,	O
I	O
drew	O
mywife	O
in	O
towards	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
for	O
to	O
make	O
way	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
pass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
pass	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
pass	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
hurry	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Joet	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
any	O
handkerchief	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
past	O
you	O
have	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
will	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
from	O
Wardour-street	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
on	O
very	O
smart	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
we	O
walked	O
on	O
smart	O
after	O
them	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
Noel-street	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bawled	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
building	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
this	O
man	O
you	O
knocked	O
down	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
on	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
forcibly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
cotton	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
darns	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
he	O
tore	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
miss	O
such	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
the	O
very	O
minute	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
last	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamp	O
I	O
see	O
he	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
spring	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
across	O
the	O
wrist	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
street	O
was	O
this	O
he	O
cut	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Wardour-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
you	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
near	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
many	O
more	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
heard	O
the	O
word	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
knife	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
runners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
O'Conner	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
apothecary	O
,	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
hand	O
dressed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
and	O
make	O
my	O
appearance	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
the	O
runners	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
run	O
through	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
runners	O
point	O
him	O
out	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
and	O
appearance	O
and	O
being	O
pock	O
marked	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
lamp	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
plain	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
cut	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
my	O
hand	O
dressed	O
and	O
stitched	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
lame	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
wrist	O
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
JOET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
behind	O
O'Brian	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
O'Brian	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
felt	O
nothing	O
about	O
you	O
to	O
induce	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
be	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
three	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
three	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
halfpenny	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Joet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
escaped	O
,	O
just	O
coming	O
behind	O
O'Brian	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
keep	O
looking	O
back	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
O'Brian	O
noticed	O
their	O
having	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
their	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
making	O
belief	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
notice	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
crossed	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
asked	O
O'Brain	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Berwick-street	O
and	O
turned	O
down	O
Noel-street	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
another	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
they	O
set	O
off	O
running	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
into	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
we	O
caught	O
this	O
one	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
O'Brian	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sight	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
while	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
tell	O
O'Brian	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Noel-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
passing	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
Wardour-street	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
knocked	O
down	O
by	O
O'Brian	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
O'Brian	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
O'Brian	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
cut	O
his	O
wrist	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
two	O
attempts	O
,	O
he	O
first	O
cut	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
kept	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
O'Brian	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
away	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
cut	O
him	O
and	O
then	O
O'Brian	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
pursued	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
witness	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
pocket	O
that	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
robbery	O
committed	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
banking	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Wardour-street	O
towards	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chapel-street	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
seizing	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
people	O
say	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
towards	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
my	O
knee	O
upon	O
him	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
knife	O
from	O
under	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
suffered	O
him	O
to	O
rise	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
patrole	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
patrole	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
search	O
might	O
bemade	O
after	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
between	O
Wardour-street	O
and	O
Chapel-street	O
.	O
Joet	O
joined	O
the	O
pursuit	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
so	O
cut	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SKEATE	I-pers
sworn	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
myself	O
,	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
beat	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
had	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
person	O
has	O
been	O
cutting	O
with	O
this	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
patroles	O
had	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
come	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
MACLARIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
first	O
between	O
Wardour-street	O
and	O
Chapel-street	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
custody	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
tumbled	O
down	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
happened	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
throw	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
knife	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
to	O
raise	O
him	O
up	O
one	O
Clark	O
,	O
a	O
patrole	O
,	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
laying	O
just	O
under	O
his	O
belly	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
?	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
Maclarin	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Swallow-street	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
aunt	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eight	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
runs	O
past	O
me	O
and	O
heaves	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
walked	O
on	O
;	O
this	O
here	O
gentleman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
O'Brian	O
,	O
immediately	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
how	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
another	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
stole	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
was	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
open	O
or	O
wrapt	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
put	O
outside	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
;	O
another	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
In	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
below	O
Wardour-street	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
693.	O
DAVID	B-pers
DONNOUCHTY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coal	O
merchant	O
.	O
My	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
touch	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
was	O
next	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
immediately	O
crossed	O
over	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
New-street	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rising	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
care	O
and	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
the	O
mark	O
T.	O
S	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
direction	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
within	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
collared	O
by	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
you	O
see	O
cross	O
over	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
robbing	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LANGLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopped	O
him	O
was	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
knocked	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
crossing	O
from	O
the	O
India	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
to	O
Langley	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
man	O
use	O
you	O
ill	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
He	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
if	O
he	O
once	O
got	O
clear	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
694.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TATE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
medical	O
profession	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
walking	O
along	O
,	O
going	O
eastward	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
person	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
held	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
till	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
On	O
searching	O
my	O
pocket	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
previous	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
missed	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
till	O
you	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
another	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
?	O
After	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
continued	O
having	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
knife	O
andsaid	O
damn	O
me	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
after	O
this	O
circumstance	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
being	O
mine	O
by	O
having	O
two	O
I	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
it	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
Out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
knife	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
cut	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
cut	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
jumped	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
LESBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine	O
merchant	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
this	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
look	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
detained	O
there	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
down	O
Cheapside	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
King-street	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
knife	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
he	O
requested	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
holding	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
walk	O
along	O
peaceably	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
let	O
go	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
use	O
this	O
knife	O
had	O
any	O
body	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
or	O
had	O
they	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
part	O
did	O
he	O
attempt	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
see	O
Mr.	O
