TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1793	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
SANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
MANOAH	O
SIBLY	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Goswell-Street	O
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
HENRY	B-pers
FENWICK	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
63	O
,	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
ONE	O
SHILLING	O
and	O
FOUR-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JAMES	B-pers
SANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
LLOYD	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
KENYON	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
:	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
:	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
CITY	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shuffry	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Tree	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
William	B-pers
Leathwick	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Humpleby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ivy	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
Raham	B-pers
Reepe	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
David	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
Bear	I-pers
George	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Stenson	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chancellor	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Hamston	I-pers
Jampion	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
John	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
Porteus	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Leake	I-pers
David	B-pers
Egleton	I-pers
285.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MANSFIELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
three	O
woollen	O
coats	O
,	O
called	O
flushing	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
and	O
bands	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
Redcross-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
one	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
I	O
believe	O
above	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
below	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
lodges	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
landlord	O
lives	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
way	O
connected	O
with	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
padlocked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
,	O
my	O
neighbours	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
my	O
place	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
immediately	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
clothes	O
were	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
drawn	O
and	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
padlock	O
remained	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
not	O
touched	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
locks	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
entirely	O
and	O
thrown	O
on	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
is	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
box	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
justice	O
Davis	O
,	O
in	O
Lambert-street	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
articles	O
now	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
never	O
returned	O
till	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
from	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
myself	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
coarse	O
aprons	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GRAYFLOWER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
pork	O
shop	O
,	O
buying	O
some	O
sausages	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Robert	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
running	O
for	O
a	O
wager	O
?	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
William	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
running	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Maypole	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
from	O
underneath	O
his	O
jacket	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
has	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TUCKER	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
go	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
's	O
stairs	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
;	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
three	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
William	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
nothing	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
neighbours	O
seeing	O
these	O
two	O
,	O
made	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
directly	O
pursued	O
after	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	O
Grayflower	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
William	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
come	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
JOSEPH	O
NASH	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
office	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
office	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
articles	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
The	O
three	O
flushing	O
coats	O
cost	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
worth	O
what	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Grayflower	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
account	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
286.	O
PENRY	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
spring	O
table	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Ann	B-pers
Baroness	I-pers
Godolphin	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
Case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
AXFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
lady	O
Godolphin	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
her	O
ladyship	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
service	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
four	O
months	O
from	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
service	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
this	O
loss	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
committed	O
to	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
NETTLETON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
clock	O
that	O
evening	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
windows	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
stable	O
yard	O
communicates	O
to	O
Lady	O
Godolphin	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
yard	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
access	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
being	O
missed	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
clock	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
step	O
taken	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
near	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
clock	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
describe	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
case	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
table	O
clock	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Axford	O
.	O
The	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Knibb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
clock	O
ever	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
found	O
yet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
service	O
was	O
this	O
boy	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
foot	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
's	O
service	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
twelve	O
month	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRAMBLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
107	O
,	O
Oxford-street	O
;	O
a	O
clock-maker	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
lad	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
work	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
we	O
want	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
direct	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
39	O
,	O
Rathbone-Place	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
placed	O
this	O
clock	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
placed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
family	O
piece	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Penry	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
this	O
clock	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
never	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
eight	O
day	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
winder	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Penry	O
Jones	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
clock	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
laughed	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
would	O
I	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
winder	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
further	O
discourse	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
This	O
clock	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
ebony	O
case	O
.	O
The	O
name	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Knibb	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
name	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
circle	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
was	O
pierced	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
there	O
about	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
perfect	O
recollection	O
what	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
told	O
the	O
magistrate	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
mistress	O
our	O
Lady	O
Godolphin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
coachman	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Nettleton	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
clock	O
was	O
it	O
-	O
The	O
clock	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
ebony	O
case	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Carmarthen	O
in	O
South	O
Wales	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
287.	O
PENRY	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Axford	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
AXFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bramble	I-pers
has	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRAMBLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
Loaded	O
with	O
Mischief	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
to	O
dispose	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
an	O
alamode	O
beef	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
also	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
the	O
duplicate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
Edward	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
with	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
seven-pence	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
these	O
breeches	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAVENDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
two	O
examinations	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
all	O
these	O
times	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
taking	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
duplicate	O
to	O
Bramble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
or	O
threat	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
free	O
confession	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
288.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Yendole	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
YENDOLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James's-street	I-place
,	O
with	O
my	O
coach	O
and	O
horses	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
six-pence	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
where	O
the	O
eight	O
shillings	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
almost	O
facing	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
asleep	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
awoke	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
shilling	O
on	O
this	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
six	O
shillings	O
besides	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BAINBRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
or	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
hecould	O
describe	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
shilling	O
almost	O
square	O
,	O
and	O
rubbed	O
at	O
the	O
edge	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
save	O
myself	O
the	O
trouble	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
money	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
picked	O
one	O
shilling	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shilling	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
edge	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
shilling	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
298.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
GOODALL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PEARCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
to	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Drury-lane	B-place
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
new	O
hat	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
who	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
there	O
bleeding	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
senses	O
till	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
woman	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
green	O
coat	O
on	O
and	O
a	O
crape	O
on	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
these	O
two	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Charles	O
Allen	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
nothing	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
coat	O
and	O
black	O
crape	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
stood	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
senseless	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
rifled	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
it	O
by	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behind	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
could	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Brownlow-street	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
public	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
Brownlow-street	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
at	O
all	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
dressed	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
behind	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
persons	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
animosity	O
to	O
me	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
under	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
place	O
for	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1782	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
brother	O
died	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
how	O
many	O
times	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
nobody	O
near	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
was	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
information	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
where	O
that	O
robbed	O
this	O
Pearce	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Golden	O
Hart	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
playing	O
at	O
shove	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Pearce	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
put	O
his	O
name	O
inside	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Jury	O
to	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
own	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
wrote	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
lay	O
under	O
a	O
predicament	O
by	O
being	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
know	O
my	O
hat	O
again	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DICKEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
draw	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Brownlow-street	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
this	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
coat	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
crape	O
about	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
patrole	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
laying	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pick	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
laying	O
down	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
his	O
hat	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
about	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
called	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
answer	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
damn	O
him	O
let	O
him	O
lay	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Goodall	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
deny	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
nigh	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
leave	O
you	O
to	O
judge	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
rob	O
this	O
man	O
knowing	O
him	O
so	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
towards	O
my	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
hat	O
lay	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
290	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TURNBULL	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
SOMERVILLE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
tea	O
caddy	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
with	O
silver	O
clasps	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
metal	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
powderhorn	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
knife	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plated	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
five	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
nankeen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Upstone	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROOKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
chambers	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clement's-Inn	I-place
,	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
chambers	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Upstone	I-pers
,	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
clerk	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Oxford-shire	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
my	O
chambers	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
secure	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
shutters	O
were	O
not	O
shut	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
myself	O
till	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
a	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
my	O
clerk	O
was	O
returned	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
Bow-street	O
people	O
and	O
the	O
porter	O
there	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
chambers	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
shutters	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
by	O
means	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
chissel	O
;	O
they	O
also	O
forced	O
several	O
drawers	O
of	O
a	O
book	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
UPSTONE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Westminster	O
Hall	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Messrs.	O
Hayman	O
and	O
Cobb	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
clerks	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chambers	O
looking	O
about	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
directly	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
the	O
chambers	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
listed	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
nankeen	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
confusion	O
,	O
my	O
trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
thrown	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
bureau	O
and	O
drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
paper	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
wrote	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
tumbled	O
down	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
wet	O
foot	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wet	O
night	O
.	O
BENNET	O
ALLEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Hayman	O
and	O
Cobb	O
,	O
their	O
chambers	O
are	O
directly	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
passing	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
chambers	O
a	O
man	O
immediately	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
looked	O
me	O
very	O
hard	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
chambers	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
clerk	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
dark	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
past	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
there	O
calling	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
box	O
he	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
chambers	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
passing	O
his	O
box	O
the	O
man	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
candles	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
candlesticks	O
upright	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
alight	O
;	O
all	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
heap	O
of	O
confusion	O
;	O
the	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
windows	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observations	O
how	O
the	O
persons	O
might	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
all	O
the	O
drawers	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
locked	O
were	O
forced	O
open	O
;	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
Mr.Upstone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
chambers	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DE	I-pers
La	I-pers
FONTAINE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Turnbull	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
World	O
's	O
End	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Turnbull	O
was	O
quartered	O
at	O
,	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
militia	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
quartered	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
a	O
powder	O
flask	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
present	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
Wells	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
trembling	O
on	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
dream	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
that	O
his	O
mother	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
expected	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
came	O
for	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
box	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
giving	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
to	O
a	O
comrade	O
,	O
the	O
comrade	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
powder	O
horn	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
powder	O
horn	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
powder	O
horn	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
this	O
Turnbull	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tie	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
bad	O
and	O
sick	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
cast	O
up	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
head	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
when	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
horn	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
dare	O
say	O
I	O
had	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
I	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
the	O
furrier	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Turnbull	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
servant	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
instant	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
faint	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
what	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
;	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
requested	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
therein	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
produce	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
man	O
has	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
has	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
articles	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Somerville	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Crown-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
Miller	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
his	O
name	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
playing	O
at	O
knock	O
up	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
pray	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
name	O
Somerville	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hair	O
was	O
dressed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
form	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
your	O
name	O
is	O
Somerville	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
militia	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
feign	O
their	O
dress	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
your	O
name	O
is	O
Somerville	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Treadway	O
had	O
searched	O
Somerville	O
's	O
lodgings	O
before	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Somerville	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
Somerville	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
by	O
Stone	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
in	O
Shaw's-Gardens	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
property	O
there	O
;	O
some	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brooke	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
belonging	O
to	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
chambers	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boot	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
the	O
top	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
piece	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chambersof	O
Mr.	O
Brooke	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
correspond	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
PULLEIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Shaw's-Garden	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Somerville	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Treadway	O
came	O
.	O
Treadway	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
searched	O
(	O
The	O
articles	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Somerville	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Smith	O
that	O
boarded	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
washed	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
absence	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
boarded	O
with	O
me	O
very	O
near	O
a	O
twelve	O
month	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Somerville	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Turnbull	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turnbull	I-pers
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Somerville	I-pers
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
291.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARNOLD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sampson	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
Indicted	O
in	O
a	O
SECOND	O
COUNT	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sampson	O
Hanbury	O
only	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
HOPTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Messrs.	O
Hanbury	O
and	O
Reed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
in	O
the	O
brew-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
store-house	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
drink	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
cock	O
lay	O
,	O
the	O
cock	O
was	O
laying	O
in	O
a	O
barrel	O
that	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulls	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
looks	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
puts	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
looked	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
pulls	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
lays	O
it	O
across	O
his	O
knee	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
leather	O
off	O
that	O
was	O
fastened	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
fixed	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
leather	O
under	O
the	O
steering	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
barrel	O
was	O
fixed	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
cock	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
cock	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
cock	O
was	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
cut	O
away	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
cut	O
off	O
no	O
cock	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
taking	O
a	O
drink	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cock	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
cock	O
at	O
this	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
breast	O
with	O
this	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
not	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
cock	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
off	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
store	O
house	O
,	O
just	O
opposite	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
very	O
perfectly	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KETTLEBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
brew-house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
assisted	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
brass	O
cock	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
using	O
of	O
it	O
not	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
our	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
downed	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RUSSELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
their	O
names	O
are	O
Henry	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
and	O
Sampson	O
Hanbury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
brass	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
laid	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
at	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
turned	O
of	O
sixty	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
63	O
.	O
)	O
Publickly	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
292.	O
JANE	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
five	O
case	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
case	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Man	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Moon	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
conveyed	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
woman	O
given	O
to	O
liquor	O
nor	O
never	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
judge	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
till	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
51	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
293.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROMFIELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
hogs	O
bristles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Faith	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
Case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
FAITH	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Henrietta-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brush	O
maker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
hogs	O
bristles	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
broom	O
which	O
he	O
enveigled	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
apprentices	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
hair	O
to	O
make	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
black	O
and	O
white	O
hair	O
there	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
taken	O
an	O
oath	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
What	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
false	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
learned	O
your	O
catechism	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
learned	O
where	O
lyars	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
go	O
to	O
Hell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
expect	O
punishment	O
in	O
another	O
world	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Now	O
mind	O
and	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
Bromfield	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
hair	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
brush	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Bromfeild	O
had	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
hairs	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
about	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
a	O
pound	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
He	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
penny	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
for	O
giving	O
him	O
these	O
hairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
at	O
them	O
cleverly	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
little	O
lilly	O
white	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
This	O
boy	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
your	O
care	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
extremely	O
wanting	O
in	O
the	O
duty	O
you	O
owe	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
public	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
taught	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
rudiments	O
of	O
religion	O
.	O
If	O
this	O
boy	O
should	O
fail	O
in	O
his	O
future	O
passages	O
through	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
will	O
be	O
imputable	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
294.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
CAMPBELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Waithman	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PARRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Waithman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bow	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
check	O
,	O
they	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
yards	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
paid	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
;	O
then	O
Margaret	O
Campbell	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
muslin	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
difficult	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
their	O
design	O
;	O
one	O
woman	O
kept	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
asking	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
several	O
articles	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
fixed	O
on	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
I	O
asked	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
how	O
much	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
half	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
shillings	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
asked	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
enough	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
something	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
this	O
boy	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
long	O
cloak	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
her	O
before	O
stoop	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
muslin	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
money	O
for	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
returned	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
towards	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
muslin	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
muslins	O
to	O
see	O
which	O
piece	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
before	O
I	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
muslin	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
muslin	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
from	O
where	O
she	O
stood	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nine	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ARMSTEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
on	O
fifteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
bind	O
me	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
muslin	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
dropped	O
an	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
picking	O
up	O
the	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
she	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
muslin	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
SLACK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
her	O
hand	O
within	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
muslin	O
down	O
from	O
within	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
muslin	O
fall	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
see	O
her	O
kick	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
foot	O
(	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
foot	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
)	O
when	O
she	O
dropped	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
that	O
gentleman	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
he	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
oranges	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
poor	O
fatherless	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
to	O
buy	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
he	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
30	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
295.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
and	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
BRUCE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Simeon	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
SIMEON	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
come	O
to	O
prove	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CRISP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Be	O
sure	O
you	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
's	O
house	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
cloths	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Bruce	O
cut	O
down	O
the	O
coat	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Davis	B-pers
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
nigh	O
him	O
,	O
Bruce	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
Davies	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
Bruce	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
pretty	O
fast	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
very	O
plainly	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
shopman	O
of	O
it	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
office	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shopman	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
immediately	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Davis	O
in	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
street	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
fresh	O
pursuit	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
Bruce	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Davis	O
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
Whitechapel	O
Church	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
very	O
fast	O
and	O
dropped	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
calls	O
out	O
master	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Bruce	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Red	O
Lyon-street	O
and	O
this	O
little	O
boy	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
sky	O
larking	O
,	O
throwing	O
turnip	O
tops	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
heaved	O
one	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threatened	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
see	O
me	O
cut	O
down	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
33	O
.	O
)	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
296.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HARDY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
linendiaper	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
vicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bromwick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Medlicot	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BROMWICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spa-fields	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
linen	O
aprons	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
three	O
table	O
cloths	O
and	O
one	O
napkin	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
was	O
he	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
my	O
clothes	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
whether	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
MEDLICOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Bromwick	O
;	O
these	O
clothes	O
were	O
lost	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
line	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drying	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ELISHA	I-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
linen	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
narrow	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
flung	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
so	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
JOSIAH	B-pers
HON	I-pers
BORNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
table	O
cloths	O
and	O
aprons	O
which	O
Turner	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Bromwick	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Medlicot	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Turner	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
person	O
nigh	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
your	O
apron	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
297.	O
AMBROSE	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
hamper	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
ninety	O
five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
spun	O
cotton	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BETTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
porter	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
waggoner	O
has	O
no	O
book	O
keeper	O
or	O
warehouse	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Stanbridge	O
,	O
these	O
hampers	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stanbridge	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
from	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
to	O
Brick	B-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
truck	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
myself	O
;	O
this	O
truck	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
third	O
and	O
fourth	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
truck	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
Smithfield	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
passing	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
into	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Spitalfields	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
lift	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Spitalfields	O
church	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
stopped	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
any	O
time	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
coming	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
mind	O
the	O
truck	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
delivering	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
fourth	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
warehouse	O
at	O
the	O
gateway	O
;	O
I	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hamper	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUNCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joiner	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
298.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
JUGGINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
instigated	O
by	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
,	O
feigned	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
,	O
made	O
and	O
coined	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
an	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
falsely	O
,	O
deceitfully	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
traiterously	O
did	O
coin	O
against	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
his	O
allegiance	O
,	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Peace	O
and	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
Indicted	O
in	O
a	O
second	O
COUNT	O
in	O
like	O
manner	O
for	O
coining	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Indicted	O
in	O
a	O
third	O
COUNT	O
for	O
coining	O
a	O
six-pence	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Schoen	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
some	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
strong	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lawrance	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carpmeal	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Harper	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Bryan	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
these	O
people	O
all	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
strong	O
room	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
did	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
silver	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
his	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
box	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lawrance	O
took	O
the	O
base	O
metal	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
box	O
open	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lawrance	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
broken	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
these	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
or	O
bad	O
?	O
-	O
Bad	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
strong	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
persons	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
only	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
was	O
chum	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
prisoner	O
likewise	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
understand	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
talk	O
about	O
a	O
box	O
which	O
you	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
you	O
only	O
talk	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
him	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
that	O
room	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lawrance	O
produced	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
which	O
you	O
took	O
this	O
money	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
to	O
that	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
box	O
opened	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
or	O
without	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
appeared	O
bad	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
No	O
man	O
living	O
who	O
saw	O
it	O
could	O
doubt	O
it	O
was	O
bad	O
?	O
A	O
man	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
fool	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Schoen	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
asked	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
right	O
,	O
you	O
took	O
this	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
box	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Lawrance	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LAWRANCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
officers	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
into	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Strong	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
papers	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
into	O
another	O
apartment	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
was	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
box	O
I	O
opened	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
apartment	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
bench	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
a	O
flask	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
bench	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
files	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
;	O
the	O
bench	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
front	O
before	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
or	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
some	O
galley	O
pots	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
some	O
broken	O
crucibles	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
a	O
hand	O
vise	O
,	O
several	O
files	O
,	O
a	O
vial	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
with	O
liquor	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
four	O
galley	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
stone	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
bureau	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
base	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
six-pence	O
;	O
five	O
incomplete	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
six-pences	O
,	O
incomplete	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
get	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
paper	O
was	O
likewise	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
spoons	O
found	O
which	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
spoons	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
Carpmeal	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
,	O
and	O
Bryan	O
,	O
and	O
Harper	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
after	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
examination	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
examination	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
box	O
did	O
you	O
describe	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
presence	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
box	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
Now	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
public	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
inspection	O
,	O
perhaps	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Chum	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
Chum	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Chum	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
that	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
public	O
?	O
-	O
Except	O
that	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
described	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
key	O
that	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Let	O
us	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
common	O
key	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
some	O
difficalty	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
it	O
I	O
assure	O
you	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KEENE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
occupies	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
officers	O
went	O
;	O
his	O
Chum	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Hunt	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
chummed	O
on	O
him	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1793	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
occupied	O
that	O
room	O
before	O
February	O
?	O
-	O
Some	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
moved	O
to	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
back	O
to	O
that	O
room	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
confined	O
in	O
the	O
Strong	O
Room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Frequently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
February	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
charge	O
my	O
memory	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
see	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
boxes	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
searched	O
several	O
boxes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
say	O
Hunt	O
was	O
the	O
Chum	O
then	O
;	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Chum	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
Rushton	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
rich	O
enough	O
to	O
buy	O
off	O
his	O
Chum	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
ever	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Chum	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
charge	O
my	O
memory	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
paid	O
his	O
Chum	O
out	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
fellow	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
his	O
Chum	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
believe	O
very	O
shortly	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
complaint	O
put	O
in	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
some	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Tracy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
man	O
is	O
disliked	O
by	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
quarrel	O
with	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
chummed	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
bail	O
.	O
Tracey	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Chum	O
.	O
Hunt	O
introduced	O
Tracey	O
as	O
his	O
Chum	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
slept	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
during	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Strong	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Hunt	O
then	O
introduced	O
Tracey	O
into	O
this	O
room	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
indicted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
.	O
Now	O
Mr.	O
Keene	O
how	O
long	O
before	O
this	O
discovery	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
man	O
confined	O
in	O
the	O
Strong	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
unable	O
to	O
visit	O
this	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
exactly	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
this	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
whatever	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
completely	O
at	O
the	O
disposal	O
of	O
Tracey	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
Tracey	O
who	O
has	O
an	O
ill	O
will	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
indicted	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
has	O
slept	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
Now	O
we	O
find	O
how	O
very	O
easily	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
;	O
if	O
that	O
box	O
which	O
was	O
opened	O
was	O
his	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
more	O
easy	O
on	O
earth	O
to	O
open	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
this	O
man	O
make	O
pewter	O
spoons	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
prison	O
?	O
You	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
indeed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
rasping	O
and	O
filing	O
spoons	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
gather	O
the	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
sold	O
several	O
in	O
the	O
prison	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Tracey	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
raising	O
the	O
Royal	O
George	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
Tracey	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
us	O
you	O
saw	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
described	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
described	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
directedto	O
that	O
room	O
as	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
his	O
that	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
shewn	O
it	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
SCOOL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
resided	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
Dublin	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
barrister	O
at	O
law	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
perjury	O
preferred	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
tried	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Dillon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Answer	O
the	O
plain	O
question	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
tried	O
on	O
that	O
indictment	O
for	O
perjury	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
only	O
that	O
you	O
believe	O
?	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
struck	O
off	O
the	O
list	O
from	O
practising	O
at	O
the	O
English	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
hindered	O
from	O
proceeding	O
in	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
heard	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
reason	O
for	O
striking	O
me	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
heard	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
oath	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
ground	O
for	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
competent	O
witness	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
two	O
apartments	O
that	O
he	O
occupied	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
apartment	O
was	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
him	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
wall	O
between	O
his	O
apartment	O
and	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
apartment	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
gallery	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
him	O
only	O
once	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
recollection	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
and	O
doing	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
In	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
report	O
of	O
this	O
business	O
from	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
waked	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
the	O
noise	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
curious	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
299.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARNES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
eight	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
East	B-pers
India	I-pers
Company	I-pers
.	O
Indicted	O
in	O
second	O
COUNT	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
,	O
laying	O
the	O
property	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
;	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
is	O
this	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
look	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
by	O
Aaron	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	O
James	O
Rickman	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
officer	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
lockers	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
tea	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
tea	O
of	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
in	O
your	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
have	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
and	O
quality	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
and	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
tea	O
department	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
tea	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
chests	O
nearly	O
empty	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
labourers	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
pull	O
off	O
their	O
coats	O
when	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
those	O
that	O
come	O
in	O
a	O
working	O
dress	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
tea	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
take	O
his	O
coat	O
off	O
to	O
work	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
weighing	O
gang	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
there	O
three	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
In	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
covering	O
another	O
coat	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
covering	O
another	O
coat	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
missing	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
this	O
by	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
warehouses	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
saw	O
the	O
chests	O
plugged	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
missing	O
several	O
months	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
daily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
some	O
hundred	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
hundred	O
.	O
AARON	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gate	O
keeper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
gate	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
leading	O
into	O
Crutched	B-place
Friars	I-place
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
before	O
his	O
time	O
of	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
his	O
usual	O
time	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
before	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
wanting	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
it	O
makes	O
no	O
difference	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
but	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
then	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
rub	O
you	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hands	O
down	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
tea	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
wrenched	O
himself	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
by	O
force	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Rickman	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
stepped	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
Barnes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
now	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
immediately	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
before	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
that	O
way	O
was	O
his	O
nearest	O
way	O
home	O
was	O
true	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RICKMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
and	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
there	O
by	O
Noble	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
tea	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
RICHARD	B-pers
NOBLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
this	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
27	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
300.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BOWDEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reece	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
REECE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
Rickman-street	B-place
,	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
sometimes	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
day	O
job	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
duplicates	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MULCASTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
near	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
the	O
sleeve	O
being	O
mended	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
yard	O
I	O
owed	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
to	O
my	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
where	O
the	O
horses	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
owing	O
my	O
washerwoman	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
here	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
brought	O
here	O
only	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Reece	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
his	O
horses	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
stable	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
horses	O
in	O
that	O
stable	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
301.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
STAPLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
HULL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
an	O
horse	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
was	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
saddle	O
to	O
use	O
with	O
that	O
horse	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
did	O
not	O
fit	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
continued	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
saddle	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
saddle	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Catley	O
's	O
livery	O
stable	O
,	O
Gray	B-place
's	I-place
Inn-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
with	O
the	O
saddle	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
saddle	O
from	O
about	O
his	O
shoulder	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
saddle	O
?	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hull	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Hatton-garden	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
saddle	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
saddle	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hull	O
's	O
name	O
in	O
the	O
saddle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
name	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
saddle	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
the	O
saddle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
exactly	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
302.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
LESTER	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
IBBETT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PATRICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ibbett	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
called	O
on	O
their	O
recognizances	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
303.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MACARTHY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
seventy-seven	O
copper	O
halfpenc	O
e	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
chattels	O
,	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slany	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SLANY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	B-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
Roach-street	I-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
highway	I-place
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HENLY	I-pers
BLACK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
last	O
Saturday	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Slany	O
attack	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
looking	O
to	O
see	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
a	O
bason	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
attacked	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
way	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
us	O
of	O
the	O
bason	O
and	O
the	O
halfpence	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
he	O
immediately	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
and	O
throws	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
mud	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
scuffle	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
a	O
maid	O
servant	O
about	O
a	O
bason	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
had	O
this	O
scuffle	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Slany	O
,	O
I	O
acted	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
soldiers	O
quartered	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
?	O
I	O
made	O
answer	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
bason	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
the	O
soldier	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
bason	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
I	O
turns	O
round	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
bason	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
mud	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pattern	O
of	O
the	O
bason	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
to	O
the	O
pieces	O
;	O
the	O
bason	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
on	O
a	O
barrel	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
moved	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
while	O
the	O
soldier	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
scuffle	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
doors	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
pieces	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
of	O
halfpence	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUMPHRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Ratcliff	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
bason	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
halfpence	O
in	O
the	O
bason	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
halfpence	O
there	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
304.	O
HARRIOTT	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
satin	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
fur	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
chattels	O
,	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Billan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BILLAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Billan	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
was	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-court	O
,	O
enquiring	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
;	O
she	O
accosted	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
plausible	O
and	O
pitiful	O
story	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
decoyed	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
from	O
the	O
boarding	O
school	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
pawned	O
her	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
what	O
directions	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
directions	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
event	O
of	O
finding	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
employed	O
her	O
from	O
Monday	O
to	O
Thursday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
out	O
on	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cloak	O
about	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
with	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
against	O
the	O
mantle	O
piece	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
declaration	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
then	O
at	O
Bow	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
cloak	O
on	O
then	O
because	O
Mr.	O
Delafontaine	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DELAFONTAINE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
Wright	O
's	O
;	O
this	O
lady	O
saw	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
cloak	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
at	O
gravesend	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
stolen	O
thing	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
cloak	O
only	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
305.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KATES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Brentford	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
odd	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
odd	O
leather	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
hit	O
against	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
she	O
looked	O
where	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
that	O
we	O
make	O
a	O
show	O
