TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1793	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
:	O
Being	O
the	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
SANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
MANOAH	B-pers
SIBLY	I-pers
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Goswell-Street	O
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
HENRY	B-pers
FENWICK	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
63	O
,	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
.	O
PRICE	O
ONE	O
SHILLING	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JAMES	B-pers
SANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
one	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
NASH	B-pers
GROSE	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
:	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
:	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beverly	I-pers
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
Gabriel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
Aaron	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
John	B-pers
Draycott	I-pers
Frederick	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
William	B-pers
Mortlock	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Vineing	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Whippy	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Tibbott	I-pers
Gabriel	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Rubard	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Willymot	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Gabriel	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sangster	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Bamford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
John	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
Mark	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chadsey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
548.	O
MARY	B-pers
CRAMMANT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
SPARROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Giles	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
Two	O
tea	O
spoons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dundas	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
articles	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
at	O
tea	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
two	O
tea	O
spoons	O
since	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hambury	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KIMBER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
pawned	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WOODYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
lady	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
relation	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sparrow	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
afternoon	O
she	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
company	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
we	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
these	O
spoons	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hambury	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
produced	O
two	O
spoons	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Sparrow	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
since	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
about	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
spoons	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
Somersetshire	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
marked	O
in	O
my	O
maiden	O
name	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
marked	O
in	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
mother	O
and	O
father-in-law	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
cypher	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
in	O
initials	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
this	O
woman	O
any	O
children	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
distressed	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owed	O
me	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
triffle	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
short	O
of	O
cash	O
,	O
take	O
these	O
spoons	O
and	O
pledge	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
pledged	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pledged	O
these	O
spoons	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Sparrow	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sparrow	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
oath	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
these	O
spoons	O
to	O
pledge	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
pawned	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
name	O
were	O
they	O
pawned	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
;	O
the	O
name	O
she	O
always	O
went	O
by	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
maiden	O
name	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
549.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOLROYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
no	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Articles	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
20	I-place
,	I-place
Gerrard-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
left	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
wet	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
spot	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
naturally	O
asked	O
where	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
was	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
must	O
have	O
had	O
improper	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
must	O
have	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
duplicates	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
articles	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
but	O
two	O
great	O
coats	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
empty	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
doubtful	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
other	O
duplicates	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
her	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
near	O
twenty-five	O
or	O
thirty	O
duplicates	O
,	O
five	O
of	O
which	O
referred	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
these	O
duplicates	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
examine	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
duplicates	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
promised	O
me	O
pardon	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
duplicates	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
two	O
great	O
coats	O
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
HOLROYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
one	O
article	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FARMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
pledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hart	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Bailey	O
;	O
all	O
four	O
were	O
pledged	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
were	O
pawned	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
;	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holroyd	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
articles	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
W.	O
B.	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
the	O
sheetsare	O
marked	O
T.	O
A.	O
H.	O
My	O
daughter	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
stockings	O
by	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
put	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
heel	O
;	O
I	O
footed	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
tickets	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
promised	O
me	O
pardon	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
witnesses	O
here	O
for	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
day	O
my	O
trial	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
550.	O
JESSEY	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
and	O
HENRY	B-pers
BOCOCK	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
hammer	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
;	O
and	O
HANNAH	B-pers
HAWKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
months	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
your	O
dwelling	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
still	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
messenger	O
in	O
possession	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
possession	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
He	O
in	O
possession	O
under	O
the	O
commission	O
of	O
bankruptcy	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
partly	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
the	O
rent	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
assignees	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
before	O
this	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
assignment	O
made	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
sale	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
bought	O
in	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
tenant	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
tenant	O
but	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
not	O
tenant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Under	O
whose	O
right	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
possession	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
clerk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
possession	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
kept	O
possession	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
persons	O
for	O
whom	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
sale	O
was	O
made	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
assignees	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
they	O
sent	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
possession	O
long	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
employed	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
keep	O
possession	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
when	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
examinations	O
had	O
you	O
passed	O
before	O
the	O
commissioners	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
certificate	O
signed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
ceased	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pay	O
your	O
rent	O
yourself	O
for	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
look	O
to	O
for	O
the	O
rent	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
looked	O
to	O
the	O
assignees	O
for	O
the	O
twelve	O
months	O
rent	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
look	O
to	O
for	O
the	O
growing	O
rent	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
there	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DENNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
and	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
punished	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
Bryant	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Bryant	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
parish	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
,	O
without	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Dennis	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
that	O
adjoins	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
near	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Henry	B-pers
Bocock	I-pers
shove	O
the	O
boards	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
he	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
without	O
shoving	O
the	O
boards	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
necessary	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
adjoins	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
so	O
light	O
as	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
features	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
countenance	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
from	O
him	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
often	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
shoving	O
these	O
boards	O
with	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
Jessy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jessy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Young	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
our	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
rightly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
come	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Jessy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
bring	O
a	O
bed	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
Bocock	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
fire	O
shovel	O
and	O
the	O
hammer	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
iron	O
hammer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
business	O
;	O
-	O
They	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
SHURLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
;	O
I	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
but	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
boards	O
of	O
the	O
necessary	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
boards	O
up	O
myself	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
string	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
they	O
were	O
separated	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
hammer	O
and	O
a	O
shovel	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Bryant	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
opening	O
made	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
some	O
boards	O
broke	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
any	O
body	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
an	O
opening	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
your	O
necessary	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
MOWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hawkins	O
had	O
this	O
bed	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
six	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Hawkins	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
bed	O
was	O
exposed	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
her	O
other	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
deal	O
for	O
beds	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
that	O
bed	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
a	O
fair	O
price	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
distress	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
without	O
any	O
abatement	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
kept	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
bought	O
some	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
that	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
many	O
things	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
pounds	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
bed	O
again	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Shurland	I-pers
and	O
two	O
others	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
Young	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hawkins	O
both	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Hawkins	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
bed	O
?	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
of	O
a	O
shovel	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hammer	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
shovel	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
possession	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
beds	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
beds	O
was	O
the	O
bed	O
they	O
bought	O
of	O
Young	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
proceeding	O
to	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
purchased	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
this	O
shovel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hammer	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
wharf	O
where	O
her	O
husband	O
worked	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
their	O
names	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
husband	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
that	O
wharf	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
wharf	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
Kendall	O
's	O
Wharf	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
worked	O
at	O
that	O
Wharf	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Dennis	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Wharf	O
where	O
Hawkins	O
worked	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mowen	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
The	O
husband	O
was	O
by	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
speaking	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprehended	O
on	O
this	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
work	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
other	O
conversation	O
with	O
Hawkins	O
besides	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
nothing	O
said	O
by	O
him	O
upon	O
this	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
urging	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
held	O
out	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
prisoners	O
,	O
to	O
induce	O
them	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
Mrs.	O
Hawkins	O
was	O
told	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
confessed	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Knapp	O
to	O
Bryant	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
by	O
any	O
particular	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
necessary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
Bryant	O
has	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
lad	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Bryant	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
say	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
shovel	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Young	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
said	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
afterwards	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
his	O
supper	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Dennis	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
while	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
supper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
bring	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
beer	O
before	O
I	O
see	O
them	O
bring	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
tumbled	O
over	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
just	O
now	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Young	O
bring	O
the	O
bed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
saw	O
Bocock	O
bring	O
out	O
a	O
shovel	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
hammer	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
bring	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
Hawkins	O
and	O
Bocock	O
each	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Jessy	O
Young	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Bocock	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
23	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
To	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
Soldiers	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
551.	O
MARY	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
glass	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Felix	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
MAC	I-pers
DENNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
two	O
rooms	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
house	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
lodgings	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
rent	O
your	O
rooms	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
Mrs.	O
Donaldson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Donaldson	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
child	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
my	O
child	O
cried	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
child	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
then	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
rightly	O
tell	O
;	O
not	O
long	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
that	O
watch	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
nail	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
immediately	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
in	O
backward	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
to	O
frighten	O
me	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
her	O
words	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
on	O
that	O
she	O
cameto	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
mislaid	O
it	O
or	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
fortune	O
teller	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
herself	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
She	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
some	O
old	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
sun	O
set	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Whiteway	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
runner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
search	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
seen	O
since	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
552.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RICHARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
marked	O
No	O
.	O
4,881	O
,	O
dated	O
London	O
,	O
July	O
12	O
,	O
1793	O
;	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
marked	O
No	O
.	O
2,899	O
,	O
dated	O
London	O
,	O
July	O
16	O
,	O
1793	O
;	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
marked	O
No	O
.	O
6,371	O
,	O
dated	O
London	O
,	O
July	O
18	O
,	O
1793	O
;	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
marked	O
No	O
.	O
8,423	O
,	O
dated	O
London	O
,	O
March	O
22	O
,	O
1793	O
;	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
marked	O
No	O
.	O
8,690	O
,	O
dated	O
London	O
,	O
June	O
29	O
,	O
1793	O
;	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
marked	O
No	O
.	O
7,278	O
,	O
dated	O
London	O
,	O
July	O
18	O
,	O
1793	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
committing	O
the	O
felony	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
gentleman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
-	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
drew	O
a	O
draft	O
on	O
my	O
bankers	O
,	O
Messrs.	O
Child	O
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
William	O
Vizard	O
,	O
a	O
confidential	O
clerk	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
receive	O
that	O
sum	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
that	O
sum	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Vizard	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
banker	O
has	O
debited	O
my	O
account	O
in	O
that	O
sum	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
VIZARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
draft	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
six	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
another	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
took	O
a	O
memorandum	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
notes	O
with	O
the	O
memorandum	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
memorandum	O
read	O
)	O
after	O
the	O
memorandum	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
notes	O
on	O
my	O
desk	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
the	O
bankers	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
clerk	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
copying	O
clerk	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
evening	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
hardly	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
what	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
officer	O
took	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
notes	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
possession	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
marked	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
possession	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
own	O
seal	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
notes	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
and	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
dinner	O
I	O
drank	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
in	O
common	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
true	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
chambers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
notes	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Vizard	O
's	O
desk	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
perfectly	O
well	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
warm	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
chamber	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
these	O
notes	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
for	O
fear	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
slip	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
glasses	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
threw	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
business	O
was	O
merely	O
through	O
intemperance	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
guilt	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
finding	O
myself	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
thinking	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
to	O
have	O
returned	O
him	O
this	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
intention	O
of	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
other	O
methods	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
pursued	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
that	O
afternoon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
face	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
being	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
committed	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
before	O
.	O
One	O
favour	O
I	O
beg	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
has	O
received	O
letters	O
from	O
some	O
people	O
at	O
Guildford	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
read	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
particular	O
indulgence	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
submit	O
myself	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
an	O
extreme	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sibhorpe	O
,	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
who	O
has	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
44	O
.	O
)	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
553.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
MACARTHY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
tick	O
pocket	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
ticken	O
pocket	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
six	O
halfpence	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
chattles	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
JUDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
parish	I-place
,	O
I	O
follow	O
my	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
fruit	O
,	O
and	O
fish	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
bed	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
woman	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
happening	O
from	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
nobody	O
made	O
me	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shadow	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
nobody	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
just	O
her	O
apparition	O
like	O
,	O
just	O
the	O
shadow	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
went	O
right	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
slept	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swan-alley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Sunday	O
week	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
my	O
bed	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
whether	O
they	O
could	O
tell	O
mewhere	O
an	O
officer	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Fonseca	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Bank	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Black	O
Lyon	O
,	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
or	O
better	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
her	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pocket	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
she	O
would	O
find	O
the	O
rest	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Fonseca	O
took	O
custody	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
pocket	O
apron	O
was	O
tied	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
fasten	O
your	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nobody	O
else	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
FONSECA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
pocket	O
apron	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
myself	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
bed	O
gown	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
it	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
apron	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
making	O
;	O
the	O
pocket	O
apron	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
three-pence	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
three-pence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
way	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
pocket	O
apron	O
and	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
looking	O
after	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Holborn	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
man	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
apron	O
and	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
stop	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
five	O
duplicates	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Fonseca	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
duplicates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
554.	O
VALENTINE	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Harrison	B-pers
Phillip	I-pers
Hinslie	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
-	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
three	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
uncle	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
halfpence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
apron	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
any	O
more	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
contained	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
speaking	O
to	O
this	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
another	O
house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Osborne	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Osborne	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
after	O
you	O
are	O
are	O
dead	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
go	O
to	O
God	O
Almighty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Be	O
sure	O
you	O
say	O
what	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Brompton-row	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
?	O
Was	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hinslies	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Osborne	O
's	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
TIMMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
four	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Osborne	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
message	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
message	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
many	O
pheasants	O
and	O
partridges	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
compliments	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
about	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jones	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
the	O
tin	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
A	O
CONSTABLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
four-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
drinking	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
that	O
is	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friends	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
brothers	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
in	O
America	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
60	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
555.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
SHEILDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
feather	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
feather	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
mahogany	O
pot	O
stands	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
stew	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
thirteen	O
table	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
eleven	O
table	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
damask	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
stuff	O
window	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
seven	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Square	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
SQUARE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
George's-court	B-place
,	I-place
York-buildings	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
On	O
the24th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
anonymous	O
letter	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
that	O
anonymous	O
letter	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
justice	O
Bond	O
;	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
place	O
pointed	O
out	O
in	O
that	O
letter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
sent	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
in	O
Lumley-court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
landlord	O
or	O
landlady	O
,	O
rather	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Southampton-street	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
owned	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
occupied	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
custody	O
with	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
by	O
her	O
appearance	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
frequently	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
considerable	O
deal	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
to	O
about	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Square	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baythorne	O
the	O
beadles	O
,	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Mrs.	O
Hardy	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
where	O
this	O
gentleman	O
tells	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Square	O
owned	O
the	O
property	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
556.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GLOVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
eleven	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
strainers	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
jug	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
SNELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
,	O
leading	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
employ	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
maid	O
halloo	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
we	O
are	O
robbed	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
robbed	O
;	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hallooed	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
blue	O
coat	O
!	O
He	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
property	O
myself	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
bureau	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
my	O
china	O
closet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
parlour	O
;	O
we	O
seldom	O
use	O
them	O
unles	O
we	O
have	O
company	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
common	O
things	O
besides	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
china	O
closet	O
;	O
the	O
cream	O
jug	O
has	O
a	O
cypher	O
three	O
letters	O
,	O
F.	O
R.	O
S.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
weighed	O
theday	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
three	O
pounds	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
at	O
five	O
shillings	O
per	O
ounce	O
.	O
DIANA	B-pers
BLACKBURN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
down	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
brandy	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
young	O
mistress	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
he	O
walked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
stones	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
turned	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
gate	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
chuck	O
these	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
a	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
alarm	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
the	O
owners	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
557.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GABRIEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OAKLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
's	O
area	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
one	O
candlestick	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Chesterfield-street	B-place
,	I-place
May	I-place
Fair	I-place
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
pursued	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
run	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
was	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
,	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
,	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hands	O
behind	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
see	O
his	O
hands	O
before	O
him	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
in	O
the	O
grass	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
Army	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BURCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chesterfield-street	O
,	O
May	O
Fair	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
OAKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Oakley	O
when	O
the	O
alarm	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
a	O
boy	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
's	O
servant	O
maid	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
go	O
past	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
Park	O
into	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
Piccadilly	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
coachman	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
just	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
another	O
witness	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
guards	O
that	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
something	O
concealed	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Oakley	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
lad	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
Oakley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
SEARLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
,	O
opposite	O
Claridges-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
on	O
guard	O
took	O
these	O
candlesticks	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
from	O
Saturday	O
one	O
o'clock	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
's	O
charge	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
respecting	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
this	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
speak	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
only	O
what	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Ann	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
property	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
say	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baynes	I-pers
my	O
butler	O
can	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
butler	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
these	O
candlesticks	O
were	O
missing	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
Deposes	O
to	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
number	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
search	O
made	O
on	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
being	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
directly	O
;	O
this	O
Oakley	O
met	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
immediately	O
a	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
made	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Oakley	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
country	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
keeping	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
theft	O
was	O
discovered	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Oakley	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
house-keeper	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
iron	O
steps	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
iron	O
steps	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JACQUES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Branham	O
the	O
patent	O
locksmith	O
,	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
dinner	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
attempting	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
gate	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
strong	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
till	O
other	O
assistance	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
an	O
officer	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
's	O
servant	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
Oakley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
one	O
candlestick	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
any	O
property	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
that	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
hands	O
were	O
behind	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
you	O
and	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
find	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
Oakley	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
an	O
hedge	O
,	O
among	O
some	O
nettles	O
in	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
some	O
intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
hide	O
them	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
never	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
you	O
hide	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
lad	O
that	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tattersall	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Grosvenor-place	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
across	O
the	O
Park	O
they	O
pursued	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
558.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HAMMETT	I-pers
or	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hemmett	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
purse	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRANDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
grocer	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Witham	O
Common	O
,	O
in	O
Linconshire	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
in	O
Moore-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
seven	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
any	O
where	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
or	O
an	O
unmarried	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Unmarried	O
.	O
She	O
accosted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
proposed	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Dyott-street	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Quite	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
Quite	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
purse	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
one	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
seven	O
,	O
the	O
silver	O
I	O
put	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
purse	O
likewise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
drop	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
the	O
last	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
buttoned	O
my	O
pocket	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
sight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
buttoned	O
my	O
pocket	O
up	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
dropped	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Instantly	O
she	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
feltand	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
money	O
go	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
from	O
him	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
immediately	O
as	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
SANDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
office	O
,	O
Marlborough-street	O
;	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
giving	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
that	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
purse	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
559.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HITCHCOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
pudding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
geneva	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
first	O
into	O
a	O
pig	O
sty	O
twice	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
boards	O
down	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
promise	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Pinner	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
lived	O
at	O
Pinner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
pudding	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
chest	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
the	O
gin	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bottle	O
that	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
hours	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
the	O
bacon	O
and	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
hearing	O
tell	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
you	O
have	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
bacon	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
penknife	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
me	O
that	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
then	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
officer	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
knife	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
the	O
bacon	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
half	O
witted	O
man	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
bacon	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
wit	O
enough	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
your	O
clothes	O
of	O
more	O
value	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Gaol	O
a	O
month	O
for	O
this	O
already	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
SIMON	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
headborough	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
penknifefrom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
by	O
a	O
crumb	O
off	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
560.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
hundred	O
and	O
thirty-four	O
halfpence	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
and	O
costermonger	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Harlow	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Covent-garden-market	B-place
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
near	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
against	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
halfpence	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
directly	O
,	O
your	O
halfpence	O
has	O
dropped	O
from	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
17	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
561.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WIGHTMAN	I-pers
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MACKAY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Granville	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
GRANVILLE	B-pers
SHARP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Chancery-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
for	O
a	O
memorandum	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
little	O
noise	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
constable	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
way	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silk	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
fellow	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
tallest	O
one	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Wightman	I-pers
,	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
that	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
Mackay	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
corner	O
into	O
Chancery-lane	O
very	O
sharp	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
belief	O
that	O
chap	O
is	O
at	O
somebody	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wightman	O
close	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
then	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
Wightman	O
and	O
Mackay	O
both	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
them	O
talking	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
close	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
Mackay	O
close	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
passing	O
,	O
directly	O
as	O
the	O
coach	O
passed	O
,	O
Wightman	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
Wightman	O
he	O
ran	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
Wightman	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
ran	O
I	O
past	O
Mackay	O
;	O
Mackay	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
halloos	O
out	O
brush	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wightman	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
up	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
very	O
near	O
went	O
down	O
an	O
area	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
just	O
catched	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
I	O
crossedover	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
there	O
was	O
G.	O
S.	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
G.	O
S.	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Wightman	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
soldier	O
or	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
JANES	B-pers
VAUGHAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
Mackay	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Wightman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Chancery-lane	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Mackay	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
theft	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
this	O
young	O
lad	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wightman	I-pers
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Mackay	I-pers
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
14	O
.	O
)	O
Sent	O
to	O
Sea	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
562.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CONNOLLY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
an	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Lettice	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
MARSHALL	B-pers
SPINK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
watch	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
August	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
five	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
property	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
enquired	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
uncle	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
abroad	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
use	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
stop	O
it	O
and	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
he	O
persisted	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
here	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
inside	O
case	O
gold	O
and	O
outside	O
case	O
base	O
metal	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Windsor	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
watch	O
maker	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
repair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
observation	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
immediately	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
saw	O
before	O
at	O
Windsor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
Windsor	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
widow	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Wynn	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
there	O
remarkable	O
about	O
this	O
watch	O
that	O
you	O
knew	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
WYNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch	O
maker	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
that	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
for	O
to	O
repair	O
it	O
between	O
a	O
fortnight	O
andthree	O
weeks	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
because	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
every	O
night	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
SMALLMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wynn	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
a	O
second	O
hand	O
seal	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
down	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
hung	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
near	O
that	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
ranks	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
regiment	O
over	O
hauled	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
laughed	O
and	O
made	O
such	O
jeer	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pick	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wynn	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Letitia	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
how	O
came	O
it	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
to	O
be	O
repaired	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
repair	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
take	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Spink	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spink	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
LETITIA	B-pers
SHELTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
it	O
being	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Wynn	O
's	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
serjeant	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
his	O
comrades	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
.	O
)	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
regiment	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
563.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MEARS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
iron	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
pig	O
iron	O
,	O
weight	O
187	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
merchandise	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Crawshaw	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Crawshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
barge	O
called	O
the	O
Joseph	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
navigable	O
river	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PHELPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
stone	O
mason	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
market	O
boats	O
that	O
come	O
to	O
Paul	B-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
when	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
move	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
move	O
his	O
boat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
causeway	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stow	O
it	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Crawshaw	O
's	O
Dock	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
market	O
boats	O
were	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
fast	O
there	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
boat	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
iron	O
in	O
her	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Phelps	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
either	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barge	O
master	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
my	O
barge	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Hamborough	O
Wharf	O
,	O
her	O
head	O
tied	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crawshaw	O
's	O
craft	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
come	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
crafts	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
somebody	O
coming	O
to	O
steal	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
barge	O
,	O
so	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
boat	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
hearing	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
man	O
move	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
iron	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
first	O
the	O
upper	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
lower	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
craft	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
the	O
craft	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hallooed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
loosened	O
his	O
boat	O
to	O
get	O
nearer	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
craft	O
where	O
the	O
iron	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
shoved	O
his	O
boat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
rowed	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
stopped	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
catched	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
bars	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
called	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
to	O
help	O
him	O
come	O
and	O
row	O
the	O
boat	O
after	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
Paul	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
barge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
iron	O
brought	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
seven	O
pigs	O
and	O
two	O
bits	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
craft	O
as	O
the	O
iron	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
iron	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
on	O
shore	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
skiff	O
as	O
the	O
iron	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sculler	O
when	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
.	O
Thursday	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
my	O
business	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
two	O
craft	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
driving	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
iron	O
grappling	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
crafts	O
and	O
a	O
boat	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
width	O
of	O
the	O
pile	O
from	O
the	O
stairs	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Crawshaw	O
's	O
Dock	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
supposed	O
somebody	O
was	O
moving	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
craft	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Crawshaw	O
's	O
Wharf	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
one	O
Bensley	O
who	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
Bensley	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
very	O
possibly	O
have	O
stepped	O
in	O
the	O
craft	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
boat	O
row	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
craft	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
say	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
distinctly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
boat	O
that	O
rowed	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
craft	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
only	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
dropped	O
my	O
barge	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
some	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
or	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
this	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
we	O
rowed	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
he	O
wished	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
iron	O
overboard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
man	O
you	O
rowed	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
we	O
might	O
dispose	O
of	O
his	O
boat	O
as	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
Paul	O
's	O
Wharf	O
stairs	O
,	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
iron	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Crawshaw	O
's	O
watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
iron	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
?	O
-	O
Seven	O
iron	O
pigs	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
observation	O
enough	O
of	O
that	O
iron	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
court	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
with	O
the	O
iron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
several	O
times	O
of	O
his	O
doing	O
very	O
bad	O
things	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bargeman	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
step	O
into	O
the	O
skiff	O
,	O
and	O
row	O
after	O
somebody	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
just	O
after	O
we	O
past	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Paul	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
seven	O
pigs	O
of	O
iron	O
in	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
and	O
prayed	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
the	O
iron	O
overboard	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
we	O
would	O
with	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
iron	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Causeway	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
iron	O
again	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
rowing	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hands	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
done	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
he	O
bears	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
middling	O
one	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Ball	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
craft	O
a	O
float	O
or	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
dock	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
float	O
in	O
the	O
dock	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PELHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Crawshaw	O
,	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
Thompson	O
,	O
the	O
firm	O
is	O
Richard	B-pers
Crawshaw	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Crawshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
happened	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
yourself	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
Mears	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
parts	O
undressed	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
iron	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
any	O
iron	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
know	O
out	O
of	O
about	O
forty	O
ton	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
our	O
porter	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
and	O
have	O
them	O
weighed	O
,	O
the	O
pig	O
iron	O
found	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
iron	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Joseph	O
barge	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
iron	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
public	O
stairs	O
,	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Causeway	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
iron	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
mark	O
,	O
Donnington	O
,	O
on	O
five	O
whole	O
pigs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
mark	O
Ketley	O
on	O
two	O
whole	O
pigs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
Joseph	O
barge	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Queenhithe	O
;	O
this	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
works	O
for	O
him	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
stair	O
head	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
fresh	O
craft	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
watchman	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
rubbing	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
almost	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
this	O
Joseph	O
barge	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
tier	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Williams	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
you	O
examine	O
what	O
was	O
written	O
on	O
the	O
barge	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
Donnington	O
and	O
Ketley	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
Donnington	O
and	O
Ketley	O
on	O
it	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Hall	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
same	O
observation	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
boat	O
away	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
iron	O
in	O
my	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
the	O
iron	O
coming	O
intothe	O
boat	O
than	O
the	O
greatest	O
stranger	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
only	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
put	O
me	O
on	O
shore	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
me	O
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
CRAWLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
cordwainer	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
wanting	O
one	O
week	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
going	O
on	O
of	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Pelham	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
this	O
iron	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
seven	O
hundred	O
weight	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
twenty	O
one	O
pounds	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
eight	O
shillings	O
a	O
hundred	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
exceedingly	O
undervalued	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
(	O
Aged	O
29	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
564.	O
ALICE	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
nutmeg	O
grater	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Mahony	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Selway	I-pers
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
MAHONY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Mahony	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
toys	O
at	O
Bartholomew	O
fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
landlady	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
mother	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Mary	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
fair	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
toys	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
here	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
fair	O
she	O
came	O
