TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
1794	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
PAUL	O
LE	O
MESURIER	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
MANOAH	B-pers
SIBLY	I-pers
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Goswell-Street	O
,	O
and	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
HENRY	B-pers
FENWICK	I-pers
,	O
No.63	O
,	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
.	O
PRICE	O
ONE	O
SHILLING	O
and	O
FOUR-PENCE	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
PAUL	B-pers
LE	I-pers
MESURIER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
LORD	O
LLOYD	B-pers
KENYON	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
:	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
one	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
:	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
:	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
CITY	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justces	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barnfield	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Brass	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Winkworth	I-pers
William	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Curl	I-pers
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
Launcelot	B-pers
Hoggat	I-pers
John	B-pers
Vevan	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
George	B-pers
Weatherston	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
Nathan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chaston	I-pers
George	B-pers
Dotson	I-pers
^	O
Abel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sitch	I-pers
John	B-pers
Moffatt	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
James	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tongue	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sandiford	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Mark	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
.	O
^	O
Anthony	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
served	O
on	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
230.	O
ABIGAIL	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
SAMUEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
second	O
hand	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
rent	O
a	O
lower	O
apartment	O
in	O
Mansfield-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
sold	O
second	O
hand	O
silk	O
stockings	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
shop	O
after	O
our	O
Sabbath	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
hung	O
up	O
my	O
stockings	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
ten	O
dozen	O
of	O
stockings	O
there	O
,	O
dirty	O
and	O
clean	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
hung	O
them	O
up	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
on	O
two	O
lines	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
gimblet	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
wife	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
wife	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
till	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
some	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
offered	O
me	O
first	O
one	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
two	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
then	O
,	O
good	O
woman	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
you	O
with	O
these	O
,	O
because	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
this	O
woman	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
other	O
goods	O
to	O
sell	O
besides	O
these	O
stockings	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
goods	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
such	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
rightly	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
in	O
Winfield-street	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Winfield-street	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
again	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
apron	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
all	O
these	O
women	O
have	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
she	O
whispered	O
something	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
throw	O
seven	O
pair	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
a	O
wicked	O
woman	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
had	O
more	O
concealed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
and	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
them	O
into	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
the	O
same	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
wife	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
that	O
woman	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
learned	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
her	O
father	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
eleven	O
pairand	O
one	O
odd	O
stocking	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
opened	O
them	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
some	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
some	O
only	O
half	O
stockings	O
,	O
legs	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
thing	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
Samuel	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Stone-lane	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Samuel	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
pair	O
,	O
this	O
dark	O
brown	O
pair	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
such	O
a	O
remarkable	O
pair	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
mended	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
leg	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
nine	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
some	O
new	O
and	O
some	O
old	O
stockings	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
had	O
them	O
old	O
pair	O
that	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
ribbed	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
mended	O
with	O
yellow	O
silk	O
in	O
the	O
leg	O
.	O
Box	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
deals	O
in	O
the	O
fair	O
with	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
agreement	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
word	O
,	O
till	O
next	O
day	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
delivered	O
herself	O
up	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
word	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
my	O
witnesses	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
in	O
that	O
see	O
me	O
buy	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
these	O
old	O
silk	O
stockings	O
buying	O
of	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
fair	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
last	O
sessions	O
began	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
give	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
I	O
see	O
her	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
not	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
shillings	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
only	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
this	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
bought	O
and	O
sold	O
stockings	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
her	O
business	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Samuel	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
?	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
fair	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
you	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
that	O
by	O
Petticoat-lane	O
?	O
-	O
Just	O
by	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
other	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
231.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
LORAINE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Salts	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
WALTER	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
SALTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Crown-court	B-place
,	I-place
it	I-place
is	I-place
facing	I-place
of	I-place
Compton-street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Little	I-place
Pultney-street	I-place
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
largeconfectioner	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
cast	O
a	O
great	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
cleverly	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stepped	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stepped	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
pushed	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
punch	O
of	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
coat	O
,	O
buttoned	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
rapped	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
felt	O
it	O
pulled	O
out	O
instead	O
of	O
dropping	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
O	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
pocket	O
;	O
O	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
is	O
gone	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
boy	O
s	O
standing	O
by	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
turning	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hear	O
what	O
the	O
boys	O
said	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
says	O
the	O
boys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
spoke	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
both	O
spoke	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
words	O
,	O
says	O
they	O
,	O
follow	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
right	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
running	O
rather	O
faster	O
than	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
over	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
than	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
boys	O
kept	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
Four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
besides	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
black	O
ribbon	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
that	O
watch	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Your	O
name	O
is	O
Walter	B-pers
William	I-pers
Bates	I-pers
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
to	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
alledged	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
232.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CHALK	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WALLING	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMART	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
price	O
10l	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MOSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
ascertain	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
Kilburn	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
sixteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
three	O
inches	O
high	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
recovered	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
I	O
recovered	O
it	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
or	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
livery	O
stable	O
near	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
advertisement	O
I	O
observed	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
never	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
identify	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
horse	O
dealer	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
mentioned	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
horse	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
October	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
advertised	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
from	O
October	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
at	O
large	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
SURETY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
to	O
Kilburn	O
,	O
to	O
grass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
taken	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
when	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
grass	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
lately	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
enquiry	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
mistress	O
making	O
any	O
enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
out	O
hand	O
bills	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
high	O
,	O
a	O
swiss	O
tail	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
blaze	O
down	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
livery	O
stables	O
in	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
sometime	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
horse	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
livery	O
stables	O
were	O
it	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
turnpike	O
in	O
Back-lane	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DEWER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Chalk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
lad	O
,	O
Smart	O
,	O
brought	O
four	O
horses	O
to	O
my	O
stable	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
Arms	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
London-street	O
,	O
Ratcliff	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
exposed	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
in	O
public	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
accommodate	O
him	O
with	O
stabling	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
horses	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
's	O
horse	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
horse	O
dealer	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
the	O
horses	O
into	O
your	O
yard	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
publickly	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
secret	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
and	O
Mayne	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
City	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
London-street	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Both	O
not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
233.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CHALK	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WALLIN	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMART	I-pers
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
price	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
sign	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DEWER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
horse	O
was	O
brought	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
234.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
falsly	O
made	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
willingly	O
act	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
falsly	O
making	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
1792	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
deed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
Clapue	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
sealed	O
and	O
delivered	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
Indicted	O
in	O
a	O
second	O
COUNT	O
,	O
with	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
Indicted	O
in	O
a	O
third	O
and	O
fourth	O
COUNTS	O
,	O
with	O
forging	O
and	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Joseph	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
Carpue	I-pers
.	O
In	O
a	O
fifth	O
and	O
sixth	O
COUNTS	O
with	O
forging	O
and	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Gosden	I-pers
in	O
his	O
life	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Raine	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
steward	O
of	O
the	O
Manor	O
of	O
Barnsbury	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
Mr.	O
Carpue	O
being	O
admitted	O
to	O
certain	O
copy	O
hold	O
premises	O
in	O
that	O
Manor	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ground	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
trustee	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
admission	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
from	O
the	O
court	O
roll	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
the	O
surrender	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
dated	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
twenty-ninth	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
surrender	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
Reverend	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
being	O
afterwards	O
produced	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
produced	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
1792	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
what	O
purpose	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
remainder	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
little	O
field	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
empower	O
him	O
to	O
transfer	O
them	O
premises	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Carpue	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
homage	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
surrender	O
accordingly	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
surrender	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
surrender	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
1793	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
surrender	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
court	O
roll	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
The	O
surrender	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
appeared	O
with	O
that	O
surrender	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
with	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
as	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
Carpue	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
was	O
admitted	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
surrender	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
1792	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
admission	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
notice	O
not	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whom	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
Mr.	O
Gosden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
notice	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Gosden	O
's	O
attorney	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
estate	O
lay	O
open	O
and	O
my	O
lord	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
tenant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carpue	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
estate	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
did	O
admit	O
him	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
notice	O
,	O
I	O
admitted	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
on	O
the9th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Golden	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
records	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
continues	O
the	O
tenant	O
to	O
this	O
estate	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
hour	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
does	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Gosden	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
time	O
,	O
ever	O
venture	O
to	O
file	O
a	O
bill	O
against	O
my	O
lord	O
for	O
admitting	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
nothing	O
,	O
only	O
this	O
notice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Gosden	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
this	O
surrender	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
on	O
this	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
come	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Gosden	O
says	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
notice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Gosden	O
wished	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
joy	O
of	O
his	O
purchase	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
Maynard	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
's	O
Clerk	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CONSTANTINE	I-pers
CARPUE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
objected	O
to	O
his	O
evidence	O
being	O
received	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
alledged	O
to	O
be	O
defrauded	O
by	O
this	O
transaction	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
court	O
allowed	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
GOSDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
Shewn	O
a	O
deed	O
executed	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gosden	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
hand	O
writing	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
defaced	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
,	O
but	O
hardly	O
any	O
one	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
your	O
recollection	O
and	O
belief	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
that	O
point	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
much	O
as	O
you	O
do	O
see	O
of	O
it	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
As	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
hardly	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
you	O
also	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
defaced	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
in	O
this	O
present	O
defaced	O
state	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
appears	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
state	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
form	O
a	O
belief	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
GOSDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
your	O
knowledge	O
?	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
defaced	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
writes	O
rather	O
a	O
remarkable	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
in	O
this	O
defaced	O
state	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
deed	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1789	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
surrender	O
of	O
Powell	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1789.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
Shewn	O
the	O
deed	O
)	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
hand	O
writing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MAYNARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
business	O
as	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
he	O
hand	O
writing	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	O
Gosden	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Carpue	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
instrument	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
purports	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
your	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
say	O
whose	O
writing	O
it	O
is	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
looks	O
like	O
the	O
writing	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
writing	O
is	O
that	O
.	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
about	O
these	O
words	O
being	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
Carpue	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
that	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
executed	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BALLAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
executor	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gosden	O
deceased	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ralne	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Carpue	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
234.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
in	O
six	O
COUNTS	O
for	O
a	O
similar	O
forgery	O
and	O
uttering	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Richard	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
Carpue	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gosden	I-pers
in	O
his	O
life	O
time	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
235.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PEALING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
10s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Drabwell	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DRABWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	B-place
Red	I-place
Lion	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Charles-street	I-place
,	I-place
Long-acre	I-place
.	O
This	O
here	O
James	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
wants	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
?	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
turning	O
my	O
back	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
change	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
says	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
that	O
half	O
guinea	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
silver	O
for	O
every	O
body	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
makes	O
answer	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
says	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
joking	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
Gilbert	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
worth	O
of	O
silver	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
says	O
to	O
Peeling	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
?	O
you	O
be	O
satisfied	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
pulls	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
lays	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
says	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
about	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
future	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
pass	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
another	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Peeling	O
,	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
half	O
guinea	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
half	O
guinea	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
you	O
;	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
indeed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wentout	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
your	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
people	O
saw	O
me	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
sawyer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
charged	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
236.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STUNNELL	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
STONEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
saddle	O
bags	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
kerseymere	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
value	O
8d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
9d	O
.	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
last	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Little	O
George-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Wales	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
coming	O
from	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
abroad	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
between	O
Brentford	B-place
Bridge	I-place
and	O
the	B-place
Magpye	I-place
near	I-place
Longfoot-lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
chaise	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
five	O
footpads	O
together	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
opened	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
their	O
pistols	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
struck	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
and	O
they	O
struck	O
me	O
against	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
afterwards	O
searched	O
my	O
pockets	O
and	O
took	O
five	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
saddle	O
bags	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
underneath	O
the	O
seat	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
strait	O
up	O
and	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
grey	O
frock	O
coat	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
kerseymere	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
jean	O
breeches	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
they	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
disguised	O
?	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
over	O
their	O
faces	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
haze	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
countenances	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
recover	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wentworth	O
You	O
say	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
together	O
who	O
attacked	O
your	O
post	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
Five	O
together	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
FOSBROOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
this	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
linen	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JEALOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
previous	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
an	O
information	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
should	O
light	O
of	O
ten	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Hope	O
,	O
White	O
Lion-street	O
,	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
six	O
more	O
together	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
eight	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mac	B-pers
Manus	I-pers
Townsend	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
rather	O
saucy	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mac	O
Manus	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
cut	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
chin	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
watched	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
son	O
lived	O
in	O
New	O
Court	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
place	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
produce	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
vast	O
quantity	O
of	O
other	O
linen	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
pistols	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
mantle	O
piece	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
key	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fosbrooke	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
stockings	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Lawson	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
in	O
mending	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
picked	O
out	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BACCHUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
from	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Lawson	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
stockings	O
in	O
your	O
saddle	O
bags	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
certainly	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
certain	O
.	O
Mr	O
Wentworth	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
had	O
the	O
saddle	O
bags	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
in	O
them	O
than	O
the	O
stockings	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
possible	O
that	O
these	O
stockings	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
mislaid	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
very	O
possible	O
case	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
journey	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wentworth	O
to	O
Jealous	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
to	O
Stannell	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
saddle	O
bags	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
saddle	O
bags	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
stockings	O
last	O
May	O
in	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
mended	O
them	O
but	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
mending	O
on	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
337.	O
WALTER	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Duberley	I-pers
privately	O
in	O
his	O
warehouse	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by-	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PARIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Duberley	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
army	O
clothier	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Soho	O
square	O
,	O
his	O
warehouse	O
is	O
in	O
Dean	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
clerk	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Walter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
cutter	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Walter	O
Smith	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cutting	O
room	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Smith	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
other	O
reply	O
than	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
trouble	O
yourself	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
myself	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
G.P	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
belongs	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Duberley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
any	O
marks	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
reason	O
than	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cutting	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
or	O
threats	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
any	O
kind	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
voluntary	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
taken	O
any	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
taken	O
any	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wentworth	O
.	O
Has	O
there	O
not	O
been	O
some	O
difference	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
malicious	O
report	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
report	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
report	O
by	O
your	O
speaking	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
that	O
cloth	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
board	O
he	O
cuts	O
out	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
hesitate	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
when	O
you	O
told	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Duberley	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
board	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
cutting	O
out	O
on	O
without	O
my	O
keeping	O
my	O
eye	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
,	O
on	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
valued	O
at	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
intrinsically	O
worth	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
-	O
Out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
broad	O
way	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
However	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
hesitation	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
ever	O
recollect	O
refusing	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
his	O
beer	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
recollect	O
that	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
beer	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
impeded	O
the	O
business	O
very	O
much	O
continually	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duberley	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
brought	O
in	O
at	O
stated	O
hours	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
particularly	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
cloth	O
at	O
all	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
miss	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
like	O
this	O
in	O
our	O
warehouse	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
there	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DUBERLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Army	O
Clothier	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
cutter	O
.	O
Among	O
the	O
thousand	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
we	O
have	O
it	O
is	O
almost	O
impossible	O
to	O
identify	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
particular	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
scarcity	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
cloth	O
dyed	O
in	O
town	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
seldom	O
that	O
I	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
or	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
piece	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Dyer	O
's	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
colour	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
examine	O
the	O
cloth	O
very	O
minutely	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
fag	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
particularly	O
torn	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
circumstance	O
in	O
the	O
dye	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
itself	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
minute	O
inspection	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
found	O
full	O
of	O
littleblack	O
dots	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
almost	O
imperceptible	O
unless	O
closely	O
looked	O
into	O
,	O
which	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
dye	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
Jury	O
Is	O
it	O
customary	O
for	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
cut	O
so	O
many	O
garments	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
they	O
employed	O
as	O
cutters	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
cut	O
all	O
by	O
patterns	O
which	O
they	O
have	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
superintends	O
that	O
branch	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
cutting	O
this	O
species	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
as	O
this	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wentworth	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
usually	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
cutters	O
a	O
whole	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
cut	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
deliver	O
nothing	O
myself	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
hardly	O
any	O
thing	O
delivered	O
but	O
a	O
whole	O
piece	O
,	O
except	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
might	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
cut	O
out	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
its	O
being	O
a	O
whole	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
cutter	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
cutting	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
going	O
in	O
by	O
accident	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
not	O
liking	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
other	O
Army	O
Clothiers	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
?	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
possible	O
to	O
find	O
cloth	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
and	O
dye	O
in	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
these	O
marks	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
during	O
the	O
American	O
War	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
worked	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Three	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
52	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
eighteen	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
238.	O
JANE	B-pers
WARNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
stone	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Sugar	I-place
Loaf	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
a	O
walking	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
was	O
standing	O
on	O
a	O
step	O
of	O
a	O
passage	O
in	O
Parker's-buildings	O
I	O
came	O
along	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
gin	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
come	O
along	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Sugar	O
loaf	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
five	O
minutes	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
an	O
agreement	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopped	O
there	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
shilling	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
only	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
hold	O
my	O
watch	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
got	O
change	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
one	O
shilling	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
watch	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
again	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
company	O
that	O
I	O
at	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
more	O
,	O
some	O
beer	O
and	O
some	O
gin	O
;	O
we	O
stayed	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
my	O
uncle	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
watch	O
outof	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
I	O
chanced	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
wrong	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
afterwards	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
since	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BIBBIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
uncle	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
table	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
table	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JENNINGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Sugar	O
Loaf	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
immediately	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Sugar	O
Loaf	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
was	O
very	O
acceptable	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
child	O
to	O
keep	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
before	O
any	O
thing	O
passed	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
hold	O
while	O
he	O
got	O
change	O
for	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
so	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
change	O
for	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
treat	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
companions	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
about	O
six	O
half	O
pints	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
pots	O
of	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
being	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ash	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
239.	O
MARY	B-pers
VALLENCE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Good	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Good	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
in	O
Newport-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-square	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
lost	O
any	O
printed	O
callico	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
he	O
lost	O
somewhere	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
callico	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
callico	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
on	O
yourself	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
that	O
callico	O
had	O
been	O
hanging	O
at	O
thedoor	O
just	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
HAMILTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
linen	O
has	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
selling	O
brockery	O
and	O
asparagus	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
young	O
child	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
market	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
meat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
this	O
linen	O
for	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
halfpence	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
few	O
halfpence	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
my	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
holding	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
strange	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
240.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
RHODES	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
RHODES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
20s	O
.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
last	O
see	O
this	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
George-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
some	O
girls	O
and	O
pushed	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
pushed	O
by	O
force	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
voluntary	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
force	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
down	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
robbed	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
being	O
pushed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
any	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
watch	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
the	O
girls	O
that	O
shoved	O
me	O
in	O
I	O
suppose	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
further	O
than	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
I	O
struggled	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
all	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
second	O
evidence	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
respecting	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
masterof	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
any	O
thing	O
hardly	O
of	O
any	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
home	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
spot	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
fix	O
upon	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRAYDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
near	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
stupified	O
condition	O
indeed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
never	O
found	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
THOMPSON	O
.	O
241.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
cotton	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velverett	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
Harmsworth	I-place
near	I-place
Colnbrooke	I-place
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
some	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
mother	O
and	O
brother	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
at	O
my	O
labour	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
mother	O
or	O
brother	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
returned	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
riffled	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarries	O
of	O
glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
frock	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
or	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
value	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
over	O
rated	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
this	O
value	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
acquire	O
the	O
knowledge	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
fact	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
recovered	O
the	O
property	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
now	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
seventeenth	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
follow	O
his	O
daily	O
labour	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
too	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
all	O
my	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
shut	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
return	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
eleven	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
son	O
James	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lower	O
window	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
window	O
,	O
three	O
quarries	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
returned	O
home	O
at	O
eleven	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
stood	O
just	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
son	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
this	O
violence	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
was	O
it	O
afterwards	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
alarm	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HIBBERT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
barn	O
door	O
stood	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
rather	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
answer	O
made	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
when	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
being	O
nigh	O
at	O
hand	O
joined	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
follow	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barn	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
he	O
throwed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
of	O
water	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
seizing	O
the	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harman	O
went	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
assisted	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
this	O
frock	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
or	O
breeches	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
there	O
among	O
them	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
RIMINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
own	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
made	O
a	O
change	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velverett	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
claims	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
hat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
your	O
Lordship	O
and	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
28	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
242.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SWINDEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
person	O
employed	O
in	O
sorting	O
letters	O
in	O
the	O
General	O
Post-office	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
General	O
Post-office	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
letter	O
sent	O
to	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
General	B-place
Post-office	I-place
,	O
then	O
lately	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Wedd	I-pers
of	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Wedd	I-pers
of	O
Gerard-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
Westminster	O
;	O
containing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3461	O
,	O
dated	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
1793	O
,	O
signed	O
and	O
subscribed	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Woolnoth	O
.	O
being	O
so	O
employed	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
having	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
banknote	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
he	O
feloniously	O
did	O
secret	O
the	O
said	O
letter	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
containing	O
the	O
said	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	O
Wedd	O
.	O
Indicted	O
in	O
three	O
other	O
COUNTS	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
offence	O
,	O
only	O
varying	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
charging	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
PETER	B-pers
WEDD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1793	O
,	O
I	O
inclosed	O
a	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3461	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
memorandum	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
enclosed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
whom	O
did	O
you	O
direct	O
the	O
letter	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
Robert	B-pers
Wedd	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Gerard-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
sealed	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
post	O
office	O
myself	O
,	O
the	O
memorandum	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Giber	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Therefore	O
you	O
rely	O
on	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
number	O
only	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
GIBER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wedd	O
,	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
of	O
him	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
presence	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
down	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
back	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
inclosed	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
book	O
or	O
paper	O
did	O
you	O
enter	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
this	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
this	O
book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
book	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
book	O
where	O
we	O
enter	O
all	O
notes	O
,	O
our	O
bill	O
book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
entry	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
copied	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
number	O
?	O
-	O
3461	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Oakly	I-pers
,	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
payable	O
to	O
Abraham	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
by	O
whom	O
drawn	O
,	O
April	O
6	O
,	O
1793	O
,	O
entered	O
William	B-pers
Garratt	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Wedd	I-pers
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wedd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
entry	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROLFE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
office	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
the	O
letters	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
which	O
were	O
addressed	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
forwarded	O
to	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
bag	O
sealed	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
mail	O
coach	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
never	O
sent	O
unsealed	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
sealed	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
guard	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
when	O
would	O
that	O
mail	O
arrive	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
Early	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SPRINE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
General	O
Post-office	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
bag	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
received	O
safe	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Sealed	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
manner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
sealed	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
struck	O
me	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
course	O
is	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
arrive	O
sealed	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WEDD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
in	O
Gerard-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
brother	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wedd	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
either	O
the	O
letter	O
or	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
Neither	O
,	O
it	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
-	O
FERGUSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
inspector	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
so	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
employment	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
?	O
-	O
As	O
a	O
letter	O
carrier	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
assisted	O
in	O
subsorting	O
of	O
the	O
letters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
duty	O
in	O
that	O
character	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
letters	O
are	O
sorted	O
first	O
by	O
twelve	O
sorters	O
in	O
twelve	O
divisions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
are	O
sorted	O
by	O
the	O
twelve	O
sorters	O
to	O
whom	O
are	O
they	O
delivered	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
,	O
who	O
subsort	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
different	O
districts	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
duty	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
letters	O
directed	O
for	O
Gerard-street	O
fall	O
among	O
those	O
that	O
he	O
sorted	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
might	O
or	O
might	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
his	O
walk	O
to	O
carry	O
letters	O
in	O
Gerard	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
ten	O
districts	O
and	O
twelve	O
divisions	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
districts	O
in	O
this	O
division	O
that	O
he	O
forted	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
sorters	O
make	O
them	O
into	O
twelve	O
divisions	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
postage	O
is	O
tolled	O
and	O
the	O
letters	O
are	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
carriers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
subsorted	O
by	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
of	O
that	O
division	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
subsorted	O
by	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
of	O
that	O
division	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
subsort	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
one	O
take	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
district	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
divisions	O
are	O
delivered	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
,	O
who	O
subsort	O
the	O
letters	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
districts	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
in	O
this	O
division	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Gerard-street	O
in	O
that	O
division	O
in	O
which	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ten	O
to	O
sort	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
Gerard-street	O
must	O
be	O
among	O
them	O
sorters	O
?	O
-	O
Naturally	O
speaking	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
others	O
,	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
wrong	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
sorters	O
under	O
a	O
mistake	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
particular	O
period	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
make	O
their	O
payment	O
at	O
the	O
Post-office	O
?	O
-	O
Every	O
other	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
days	O
?	O
-	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
and	O
Fridays	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
week	O
in	O
which	O
this	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
fell	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
regular	O
in	O
making	O
his	O
payments	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday-	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
memorandum	O
book	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
entries	O
in	O
that	O
memorandum	O
book	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
he	O
was	O
deficient	O
eight	O
pounds	O
and	O
four-pence	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
in	O
fact	O
pay	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
paid	O
into	O
the	O
revenue	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
paid	O
it	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
consequence	O
if	O
a	O
letter	O
carrier	O
does	O
not	O
make	O
good	O
his	O
payments	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
post	O
master	O
's	O
order	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
be	O
suspended	O
till	O
such	O
times	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
paid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
the	O
rules	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
when	O
would	O
he	O
have	O
been	O
reported	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
paid	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
right	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
others	O
into	O
whose	O
hands	O
these	O
letters	O
might	O
have	O
fell	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
persons	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
this	O
process	O
takes	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
strangers	O
admitted	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
sometimes	O
they	O
come	O
in	O
enquiring	O
for	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
gates	O
are	O
opened	O
they	O
will	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
letters	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
general	O
till	O
the	O
sorting	O
is	O
all	O
over	O
,	O
except	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
supplies	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
sorters	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
these	O
ten	O
sorters	O
of	O
this	O
division	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
sorted	O
by	O
the	O
letter	O
carriers	O
?	O
-	O
All	O
the	O
divisions	O
are	O
sorted	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
three	O
rooms	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
connected	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
sorters	O
have	O
access	O
to	O
all	O
these	O
rooms	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
understand	O
your	O
description	O
right	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
class	O
of	O
sorters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
class	O
of	O
subsorters	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
subsorter	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
a	O
sorter	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
these	O
twelve	O
divisions	O
it	O
sometimes	O
happens	O
that	O
a	O
mistake	O
happens	O
,	O
a	O
letter	O
gets	O
into	O
a	O
wrong	O
division	O
frequently	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
avoid	O
that	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
When	O
a	O
mistake	O
happens	O
what	O
is	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
boxes	O
for	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
twelve	O
divisions	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
thrown	O
off	O
to	O
the	O
division	O
it	O
belong	O
to	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SHILLCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sworn	O
Mr.	O
Shillcock	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
employment	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
or	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Southampton	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
leads	O
from	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
being	O
examined	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
bank	O
note	O
being	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
whom	O
had	O
you	O
received	O
that	O
bank	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
state	O
the	O
time	O
correctly	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
us	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
examined	O
at	O
Bow	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
Southampton	O
Arms	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Swinden	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
twenty-seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
changed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
return	O
him	O
the	O
difference	O
after	O
taking	O
what	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Bailey	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Terrace	O
,	O
on	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
came	O
but	O
once	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
twice	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
the	O
change	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
note	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
which	O
note	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
debt	O
of	O
twenty-seven	O
shillings	O
been	O
due	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
fortnight	O
,	O
or	O
there	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
your	O
recollection	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
you	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
any	O
certainty	O
about	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
you	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
business	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
LYDIA	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Terrace	O
,	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
change	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
Shillcock	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
month	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
examined	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
changed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
Shillcock	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
changed	O
it	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
?	O
-	O
Within	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
change	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shillcock	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rains	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
imperfect	O
recollection	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
in	O
which	O
this	O
transaction	O
took	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
either	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Or	O
a	O
Thursday	O
perhaps	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
Recollect	O
yourself	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
recent	O
in	O
your	O
recollection	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
more	O
doubtful	O
concerning	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q.	O
Recollect	O
yourself	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
remember	O
precisely	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
you	O
changed	O
it	O
with	O
Underwood	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
UNDERWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
cash	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
or	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
possession	O
?	O
-	O
Till	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
then	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Hill	O
and	O
Rickards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
that	O
you	O
paid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rickards	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
you	O
received	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
accurate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
19th	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
days	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
you	O
possession	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
RICKARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
that	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
cashiers	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
so	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
whom	O
is	O
that	O
bank	O
note	O
signed	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
note	O
out	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WEDD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
on	O
this	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Miller	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
this	O
note	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
memorandum	O
making	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
own	O
lodgings	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
did	O
any	O
body	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
give	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
that	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
either	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
threaten	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Shillcock	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
Miller	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
Miller	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
?	O
he	O
hesitated	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
by	O
interrogating	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
degree	O
of	O
spirit	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
different	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
very	O
little	O
more	O
passed	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
At	O
Bow-street	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
memorandum	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
positively	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
writing	O
taken	O
down	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
attend	O
to	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAVENDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
office	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
original	O
minute	O
book	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
words	O
,	O
a	O
sentence	O
begun	O
but	O
not	O
finished	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
it	O
begins	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saith	O
that	O
.	O
''	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
question	O
was	O
not	O
what	O
the	O
clerk	O
had	O
writ	O
on	O
any	O
subject	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
your	O
search	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
one	O
syllable	O
which	O
imported	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nothing	O
only	O
,	O
''	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saith	O
that	O
.	O
''	O
Court	O
to	O
Wedd	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
myself	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rolse	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
assists	O
you	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
occasionally	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
memory	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
letter	O
as	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
your	O
office	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
impossible	O
;	O
I	O
generally	O
keep	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
sometimes	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Monday	O
evening	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
lately	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
had	O
you	O
sealed	O
that	O
bag	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Wisbich	O
Mail	O
comes	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
commonly	O
comes	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
sometimes	O
sooner	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
later	O
,	O
I	O
delivers	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
guard	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
letters	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
box	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bag	O
sealed	O
for	O
London	O
only	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Peter	O
Wedd	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
pay	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Into	O
the	O
letter	O
box	O
.	O
Rolfe	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wedd	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
particular	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Wedd	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
you	O
are	O
absolutely	O
certain	O
you	O
forwarded	O
it	O
in	O
proper	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
conscious	O
of	O
my	O
innocence	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
nine	O
weeks	O
on	O
bail	O
,	O
andtwice	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
bail	O
even	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
absent	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
bail	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
trial	O
like	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
certainly	O
true	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
did	O
twice	O
surrender	O
himself	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
twice	O
upon	O
bail	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
trial	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
twenty-one	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
36	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
general	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wedd	O
.	O
243.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STOUT	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Dowel	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Twenlowe	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
India	O
merchants	O
;	O
Captain	O
Hamilton	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
he	O
can	O
appear	O
before	O
next	O
sessions	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
244.	O
MARY	B-pers
THORPE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
another	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
mourning	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
tea	O
caddy	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
with	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
muslin	O
dimity	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
a	O
worked	O
muslin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
astuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
white	O
marseilles	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
dimity	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
muslin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
three	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
dimity	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
five	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
six	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
six	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
a	O
muslin	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
muslin	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
two	O
shawl	O
handkerchiefs	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
wax	O
bead	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
muslin	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
linen	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
only	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
were	O
deficient	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
so	O
soon	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
either	O
I	O
or	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
waited	O
some	O
time	O
and	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
short	O
interval	O
of	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
her	O
mistress	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
hearing	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
box	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
property	O
missing	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
week	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
King	O
's	O
Langley	O
,	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
having	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
dated	O
from	O
that	O
piece	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
subsequent	O
to	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
traced	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
Watford	O
,	O
she	O
there	O
took	O
another	O
post	O
chaise	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
tell	O
your	O
lordship	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
Watford	O
that	O
drove	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
here	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
some	O
days	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
brought	O
forward	O
by	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
is	O
James	O
Thomas	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
understand	O
this	O
woman	O
quitted	O
your	O
service	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
then	O
miss	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
property	O
that	O
you	O
missed	O
from	O
any	O
one	O
particular	O
place	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
different	O
rooms	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
different	O
places	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MILES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
place	O
at	O
our	O
coach	O
office	O
for	O
Kingston	O
,	O
from	O
Kingston	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
she	O
booked	O
the	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
outside	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
the	O
bundle	O
with	O
her	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
large	O
bundle	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
bundle	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Stones	O
End	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
the	O
