TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1796	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MATORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	O
CURTIS	O
,	O
ESQ	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
MARSOM	O
&	O
RAMSEY	O
,	O
AND	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1796	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CURTIS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
LLOYD	O
,	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	O
HOTHAM	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
and	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BULLER	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Erwood	I-pers
James	B-pers
Winwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whitbread	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bellis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Linford	I-pers
James	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cobbett	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Toseland	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Essex	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
Emanuel	B-pers
Freethig	I-pers
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Beauchamp	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Horcomb	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkie	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Newham	I-pers
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
227.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CRAYFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thickset	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sandall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SANDALL	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
silk	O
dyer	O
and	O
scowerer	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
Wych-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
my	O
mother	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Arrundel-street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stcoking	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buff	O
thickset	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
not	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
our	O
shop	O
marks	O
in	O
the	O
waistband	O
.	O
-	O
TALBOYS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
area	O
rails	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
a	O
boy	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
228.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PINK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
two	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
17s	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Aldred	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tapp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Aldred	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TAPP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
96	O
,	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
James	O
Aldred	O
;	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
keep	O
house	O
together	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Aldred	I-pers
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
belongs	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
:	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
from	O
a	O
shelf	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
any	O
from	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Aldred	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linen	O
;	O
by	O
its	O
appearance	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
linen	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Police-office	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
against	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
articles	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
aticles	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
were	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
having	O
our	O
private	O
marks	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Tapp	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
this	O
room	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Her	O
mistress	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
slept	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
by	O
her	O
about	O
this	O
being	O
her	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
where	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
,	O
from	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
promises	O
or	O
threats	O
,	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Certainly	O
not	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Trebeck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Herself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
servants	O
are	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
sleeps	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
is	O
generally	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
may	O
have	O
access	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Every	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
might	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
(	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FLAMSTONE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
first	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three-quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
while	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
an	O
hundred	O
times	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
Privately	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
229.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CROSSBY	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
live	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hezekiah	B-pers
Denby	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Denby	O
,	O
in	O
Enfield	B-place
Town	I-place
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
a	O
pig	O
,	O
or	O
pigs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
back	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
still	O
heard	O
the	O
squeaking	O
of	O
the	O
pigs	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Bradshaw	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
meet	O
me	O
in	O
Bloomfield-lane	O
,	O
which	O
adjoins	O
Mr.	O
Denby	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
and	O
slaughter-house	O
,	O
and	O
pig	O
stye	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
yard	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
facing	O
Bloomfield-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
very	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Denby	O
's	O
pig-stye	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
distinguish	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
hesitating	O
about	O
taking	O
a	O
stick	O
a-piece	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
instantly	O
back	O
into	O
Bloomfield-lane	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Crossby	O
's	O
gate	O
,	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
carts	O
standing	O
in	O
Crossby	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Crossby	O
standing	O
between	O
the	O
shafts	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
ah	O
!	O
Jack	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
it	O
is	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
answer	O
;	O
immediately	O
upon	O
that	O
out	O
ran	O
a	O
pig	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
sack	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
sacks	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
something	O
heavy	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
pig	O
hardly	O
dead	O
,	O
quite	O
warm	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
Morris	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Bradshaw	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
no	O
further	O
notice	O
of	O
Crossby	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
hearing	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
Morris	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Denby	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pigs	O
were	O
left	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
live	O
pigs	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
slaughtered	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRADSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
our	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
into	O
Crosby	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
between	O
the	O
shafts	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sack	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
live	O
pig	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dead	O
pig	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
warm	O
;	O
Morris	O
stood	O
behind	O
another	O
cart	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
HEZEKIAH	O
DENBY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pigs	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
stye	O
in	O
my	O
premises	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
;	O
Crosby	O
's	O
yard	O
is	O
fifty	O
or	O
60	O
yards	O
from	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
bring	O
you	O
any	O
pigs	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
one	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
alive	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
pigs	O
;	O
the	O
dead	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
boar-pig	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
string	O
was	O
so	O
swelled	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
proper	O
;	O
the	O
live	O
pig	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
size	O
and	O
age	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
mother	O
took	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoners	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
)	O
.	O
Crosby	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
34	O
.	O
)	O
Morris	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
35	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
LORD	O
KENYON	O
.	O
230.	O
HENRY	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
twelve	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pepwell	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PEPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
and	O
ironmonger	O
,	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
pockets	O
filled	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
nails	O
,	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
them	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
nails	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
pockets	O
.	O
Pepwell	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
loose	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
others	O
nails	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
mould	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
correspond	O
with	O
these	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
231.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FAIRBROTHER	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
CORNWALL	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
gravy	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
ALDRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Russel-street	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
live	O
together	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
she	O
rent	O
the	O
house	O
too	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
only	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Myself	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
only	O
tenant	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gravy	O
spoon	O
,	O
four	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
six	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
drawing-room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mustard	O
pot	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
gravy	O
spoon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
silversmith	O
that	O
bought	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
valued	O
them	O
yesterday	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
3l	O
.	O
5s	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
lodgings	O
of	O
my	O
sister	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
footman	O
to	O
a	O
family	O
that	O
visued	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Coles	O
of	O
Highgate	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
come	O
with	O
his	O
mistress	O
very	O
frequently	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
dined	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
late	O
did	O
he	O
continue	O
after	O
dinner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
;	O
our	O
servants	O
set	O
up	O
for	O
them	O
till	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
have	O
before-named	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
information	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
he	O
robbed	O
in	O
London-street	O
.	O
-	O
DONALDSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-inn-fields	O
;	O
upon	O
going	O
to	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Williams	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
,	O
twelve	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
8s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
4d	O
.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Aldridge	O
.	O
The	O
spoon	O
do	O
n't	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
tongs	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
tea	O
belongs	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
from	O
my	O
grocer	O
's	O
having	O
sworn	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
WALTER	B-pers
BRIDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
four	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Aldridge	O
.	O
The	O
four	O
table	O
spoons	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
gravy	O
spoon	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
68	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
232.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
STUART	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Court	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eden	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
Welbore	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
Agar	I-pers
,	O
Joah	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
Alexander	B-pers
Munro	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Frewin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Fownes	I-pers
Luttrell	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
Fourth	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
)	O
.	O
RANDAL	O
SUTTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
appointer	O
of	O
the	O
weighers	O
in	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
warehouse	I-place
upon	I-place
Tower-Hill	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
taking	O
up	O
some	O
leaf	O
tobacco	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
is	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
beer	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
from	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
little	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
what	O
is	O
in	O
this	O
bag	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
unbuttoned	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
mention	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
superior	O
officer	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
very	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
certainly	O
should	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
my	O
superior	O
officer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
tobacco	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
proper	O
package	O
.	O
TIMOTHY	O
OSBURN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
controuling	O
surveyor	O
of	O
these	O
warehouses	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
acquainted	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
business	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
the	O
principal	O
surveyor	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
;	O
just	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
kept	O
within	O
the	O
gates	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
very	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
was	O
Stuart	O
's	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
how	O
we	O
can	O
connect	O
this	O
with	O
tobacco	O
taken	O
somewhere	O
else	O
.	O
Witness	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
ounce	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
65	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
KENYON	I-pers
.	O
233.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SHUTTLEWOOD	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SHUTTLEWORTH	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
having	O
feloniously	O
intermarried	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Ludgate	I-pers
,	O
onthe	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hough	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
)	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BIRD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
parish	O
clerk	O
of	O
Mary-le-bonne	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
register	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
banns	O
,	O
to	O
Catherine	O
Hough	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
witnessed	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
the	O
party	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
dated	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1788	O
.	O
MARGARET	O
ROBSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
married	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
marriage	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1788	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
attested	O
the	O
marriage	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hand-writing	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
sister	O
now	O
living	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
The	O
Reverend	O
GRIFFITH	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
curate	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
register	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
find	O
in	O
that	O
register	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Shuttleworth	O
with	O
Ann	O
Ludgate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
(	O
reads	O
,	O
)	O
Thomas	O
Shuttleworth	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
parish	O
,	O
a	O
widower	O
,	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Ludgate	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
married	O
at	O
this	O
church	O
,	O
by	O
banns	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1796	O
,	O
by	O
me	O
Griffith	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
curate	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
any	O
recollection	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
LUDGATE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
church	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
married	O
me	O
.	O
MARY	O
GREENWAY	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jucksan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
church	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
a	O
written	O
defence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
)	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Under	O
the	O
pressure	O
of	O
my	O
unfortunate	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
here	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
eyes	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
solemnly	O
assort	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
of	O
my	O
first	O
wife	O
being	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
her	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
crime	O
I	O
now	O
stand	O
unfortunately	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
felony	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
married	O
my	O
second	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
assure	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
in	O
marriage	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
exculpate	O
me	O
from	O
any	O
finister	O
views	O
;	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
hope	O
is	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
will	O
discriminate	O
the	O
intention	O
of	O
my	O
action	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
Aged	O
28	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
234.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIES	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hadley	O
,	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cheese	O
at	O
Holloway	B-place
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
flour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
loading	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seventeen	O
cheeses	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
taken	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
cart	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
the	O
cheese	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
G	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
cheeses	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ORTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
cheese	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
on	O
horseback	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robbing	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cheese	O
within	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
spot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
have	O
the	O
cheese	O
in	O
their	O
possession	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
innocent	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
had	O
the	O
prisoners	O
got	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
run	O
up	O
a	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
BANNISTER	O
sworn	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Davies	O
,	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
cheese	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
(	O
Davies	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
off	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
while	O
the	O
cheese	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cheese	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
presecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Davies	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
cheese	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
said	O
somebody	O
robbed	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
leg	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
set	O
my	O
foot	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Davies	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
.	O
)	O
Young	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
235.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PURCELL	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
fifty-four	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
27s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
SHORT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holywell-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher'sand	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
taken	O
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Crutchley	I-pers
;	O
the	O
boys	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stapleton	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
ribbons	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
boys	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
ribbons	O
are	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
shop	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
ANN	O
CRUTCHLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Short	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
tallest	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
boys	O
,	O
Purcell	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
ribbon	O
to	O
tie	O
on	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
galoon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
broader	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
coloured	O
ribbons	O
were	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
broader	O
ribbon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
eight	O
yards	O
,	O
would	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
pattern	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
reach	O
the	O
box	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
ribbons	O
that	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
till	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
those	O
ribbons	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
ribbons	O
that	O
laid	O
upon	O
your	O
counter	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
our	O
's	O
.	O
JOHN	O
STAPLETON	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
own	O
business	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Holywell-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
suspicious	O
characters	O
about	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
past	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
Bailey	O
;	O
I	O
passed	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Short	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
facing	O
where	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
was	O
standing	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
he	O
walked	O
slowly	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
facing	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
head	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
ribbons	O
;	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
ribbons	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Purcell	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
that	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
this	O
boy	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
ribbon	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
got	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
,	O
or	O
friends	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
soon	O
settle	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
few	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
poor	O
;	O
``	O
we	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
go	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
get	O
as	O
much	O
money	O
as	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
''	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Stapleton	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
pass	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
information	O
begged	O
somebody	O
to	O
stop	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
curiosity	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
about	O
compounding	O
it	O
for	O
felony	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Purcel	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
.	O
)	O
Bailey	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
KENYON	I-pers
.	O
236.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
60s	O
.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
13s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveteen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
velveteen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
glazed	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
sustian	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Denys	I-pers
;	O
a	O
leather	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Heeley	I-pers
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sherry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
)	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
DENYS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
my	O
livery	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
distribute	O
some	O
visiting	O
cards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
all	O
his	O
livery	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SHERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Denys	O
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
quitted	O
Mr.	O
Denys	O
'	O
service	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
distribute	O
some	O
cards	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
that	O
I	O
quitted	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
stayed	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
opera	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Palmer	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
returned	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
articles	O
specified	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
22d	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
that	O
description	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
the	O
Warren	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
regimentals	O
,	O
at	O
drill	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
light	O
artillery	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
situation	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sorry	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
if	O
youtake	O
me	O
to	O
London	O
I	O
shall	O
soon	O
return	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
fetched	O
the	O
plain	O
cloaths	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
least	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
he	O
signified	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
cloaths	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Denys	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Marlborough-street	O
office	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
those	O
cloaths	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
they	O
his	O
own	O
livery	O
cloaths	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
Captain	O
Palmer	B-pers
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Denys	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
given	O
those	O
cloaths	O
to	O
your	O
servant	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
By	O
no	O
means	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
worn	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
cloaths	O
that	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
can	O
amount	O
to	O
felony	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
237.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RANDALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
containing	O
eleven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Murray	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
Little	B-place
Windmill-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdashery	O
and	O
shoe	O
warehouse	O
:	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
eleven	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
understand	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
loitering	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
watched	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
we	O
observed	O
the	O
window	O
cracked	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
people	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hand	O
go	O
through	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
stood	O
together	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
witness	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
now	O
we	O
will	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
standing	O
here	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
buttoned	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
eight	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
glass	O
fly	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
shutters	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
they	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
COLES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
a	O
bit	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
some	O
chaps	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
shop	O
windows	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
looked	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
and	O
acquaint	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Randall	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
turned	O
back	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
watched	O
them	O
;	O
Williams	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
see	O
them	O
brake	O
the	O
glass	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
directly	O
;	O
accordingly	O
we	O
heard	O
them	O
break	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
Randall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
was	O
cracked	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
no	O
part	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
About	O
forty	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crown-court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
fight	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
DOWLING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
Williams	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
Williams	O
delivered	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
this	O
pattern	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
whole	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
by	O
persons	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
description	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Carnaby-market	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop-thief	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
bailed	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
238.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
16d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LILLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage-bridge	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
about	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
pots	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
carried	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Burr-street	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
fellow	O
servants	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
he	O
had	O
between	O
his	O
legs	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
run	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lilly	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Mr.	O
Lilly	O
's	O
pots	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Lilly	O
's	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
MITCHENER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
pots	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Glasgow	O
Whars	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
pots	O
standing	O
by	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
meant	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
the	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
60	O
.	O
)	O
Imprisoned	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
239.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LOVAT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
nankeen	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
pin-a-sore	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
nine	O
linen	O
clonts	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
calico	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GOODWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
;	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
kept	O
his	O
bed	O
these	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Castle-court	B-place
,	I-place
Fulwood's-rents	I-place
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
are	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
hanging	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
dog	O
barking	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
John	O
Runnington	O
;	O
the	O
lines	O
were	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
on	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
yard	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RUNNINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
moon-light	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
candle	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
linen	O
scattered	O
about	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
small	O
things	O
on	O
a	O
wall	O
beside	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
GOODWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
linen	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
pin-a-fores	O
,	O
a	O
nankeen	O
jacket	O
,	O
five	O
clouts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
roller	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
is	O
ill	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
)	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
different	O
parcels	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Goodwin	O
)	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
thoroughfare	O
in	O
this	O
yard	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
gate	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
240.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHN	I-pers
LANCASHIRE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
cambrick	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
25l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hounsom	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JOHN	O
HOUNSOM	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
wanted	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Lancashire	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
I	O
since	O
find	O
is	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
front	O
shop	O
;	O
Lancashire	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Newland	O
of	O
Clapham	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
friend	O
and	O
customer	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
patterns	O
of	O
striped	O
ginghams	O
,	O
and	O
striped	O
calicos	O
,	O
for	O
waistcoats	O
and	O
trowsers	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
them	O
what	O
few	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
get	O
,	O
them	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
called	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
message	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
compliments	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
some	O
cambricks	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
upon	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
iron	O
safe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
cambricks	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
my	O
two	O
shopmen	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
every	O
place	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Newland	O
's	O
,	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
must	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
your	O
servant	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Clapham	O
to	O
learn	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
their	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
such	O
persons	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Newland	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
persons	O
of	O
that	O
description	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
suspicion	O
immediately	O
sell	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
warrant	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
for	O
his	O
apprehension	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
traced	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Merlin's-cave	O
,	O
in	O
Spa-fields	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cambrick	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
obtain	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Newland	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
only	O
some	O
little	O
slips	O
for	O
patterns	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
friend	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Newland	O
's	O
of	O
Clapham	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
customer	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
patterns	O
of	O
ginghams	O
.	O
and	O
calicos	O
for	O
jackets	O
and	O
trowsers	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
abroad	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
sew	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
an	O
old	O
customer	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
some	O
patterns	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
that	O
evening	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
their	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
sent	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
to	O
procure	O
the	O
patterns	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Williams	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
for	O
the	O
patterns	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
price	O
and	O
his	O
compliments	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
Williams	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
write	O
your	O
letter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
writing-paper	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
while	O
he	O
wrote	O
some	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
waser	O
,	O
and	O
lest	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
twelve	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
carrying	O
the	O
letter	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
missed	O
his	O
cambricks	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
what	O
could	O
be	O
come	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
suspicion	O
fell	O
directly	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Williams	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
lest	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Merlin's-cave	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Cold-bath-fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
apartments	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cambrick	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apartment	O
at	O
my	O
peril	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
windows	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
glass	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
folded	O
up	O
without	O
any	O
paper	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
apartments	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
cambrick	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
dozen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Cold-bath-fields	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
my	O
putting	O
a	O
mark	O
upon	O
that	O
cambrick	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
C	O
D	O
A.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
that	O
that	O
property	O
belongs	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
this	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
feeing	O
the	O
shopman	O
find	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
cambrick	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
Merlin's-cave	O
;	O
Price	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Cold-bath-fields	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
marked	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
mark	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
marked	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
pencil	O
.	O
GEORGE	O
ALLEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
executing	O
the	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
)	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
My	O
mark	O
is	O
on	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
C	O
D	O
A	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
stroke	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
and	O
a-half	O
in	O
each	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
5l	O
.	O
15l	O
.	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
lowest	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
pieces	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
has	O
been	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
rubbed	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ticket	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
torn	O
off	O
and	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
permitted	O
to	O
read	O
my	O
defence	O
,	O
(	O
reads	O
)	O
;	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
on	O
the	O
Jury	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
being	O
engaged	O
in	O
the	O
East-India	O
service	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
patterns	O
of	O
ginghams	O
and	O
calices	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
Mrs.	O
Newland	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
being	O
used	O
better	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
we	O
saw	O
nobody	O
but	O
Price	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
Price	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
him	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Newland	O
,	O
of	O
Clapham	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
patterns	O
of	O
gingham	O
for	O
jackets	O
and	O
tsowsers	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
ginghams	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Price	O
informed	O
him	O
who	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
some	O
patterns	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Penny-post	O
latter	O
to	O
Clapham	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
them	O
ready	O
by	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
patterns	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
appointed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Price	O
informed	O
us	O
the	O
patterns	O
were	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
Price	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
patterns	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
's	O
compliments	O
;	O
Williams	O
asked	O
Price	O
for	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
loan	O
of	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
;	O
accordingly	O
the	O
paper	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
desired	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
proceeded	O
with	O
writing	O
his	O
letter	O
;	O
Price	O
was	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
cambrick	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
nor	O
could	O
be	O
taken	O
without	O
his	O
seeing	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
missed	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
;	O
can	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
the	O
11th	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
that	O
Williams	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
or	O
counting-house	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
besides	O
me	O
?	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
by	O
himself	O
?	O
or	O
can	O
Price	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
about	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
,	O
can	O
he	O
say	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
can	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
by	O
seeing	O
a	O
person	O
only	O
once	O
,	O
swear	O
that	O
Williams	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
after	O
?	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
may	O
this	O
impress	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
minds	O
of	O
the	O
merciful	O
Jury	O
;	O
we	O
parted	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
afternoon	O
Williams	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
by	O
Merlins'-cave	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cambrick	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
uncle	O
at	O
Copenhagen-house	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
Allen	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Merlin's-cave	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Allen	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
apartments	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
search	O
any	O
apartment	O
I	O
held	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cambrick	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
my	O
trunk	O
and	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
because	O
Price	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
objection	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
in	O
Cold-bath-fields	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cambrick	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
supposed	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
cambrick	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
ready	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
apartments	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
it	O
marked	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
Williams	O
?	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
to	O
the	O
determination	O
of	O
a	O
Jury	O
,	O
where	O
mercy	O
will	O
always	O
prevail	O
,	O
and	O
reason	O
is	O
always	O
studied	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
cambrick	O
,	O
Price	O
then	O
left	O
us	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
alone	O
with	O
the	O
cambrick	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
constable	O
(	O
Allen	O
)	O
and	O
myself	O
proceeded	O
towards	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
that	O
my	O
friends	O
were	O
all	O
disappointed	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
and	O
found	O
me	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
friends	O
to	O
have	O
bailed	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
ifthey	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
disappointed	O
me	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
every	O
information	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
constable	O
might	O
have	O
found	O
Williams	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
cambrick	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
Williams	O
could	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
the	O
way	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
could	O
then	O
find	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
cambrick	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
Williams	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
likelihood	O
of	O
obtaining	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
entire	O
stranger	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
at	O
some	O
other	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
fully	O
committed	O
for	O
trial	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
prosecute	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
promised	O
me	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
wife	O
for	O
it	O
any	O
time	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
call	O
every	O
Monday	O
;	O
he	O
allowed	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
weeks	O
running	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Thursday	O
Mr.	O
Hounsom	O
visited	O
me	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
Williams	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
suffer	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
upon	O
my	O
trial	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
my	O
advice	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
arraigned	O
,	O
plead	O
guilty	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
save	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
intercede	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
injuring	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
gratuity	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
allow	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
it	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
only	O
reason	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
plead	O
guilty	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
arraigned	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
may	O
have	O
some	O
pressure	O
upon	O
your	O
minds	O
,	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
one	O
young	O
in	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
heavy	O
losses	O
and	O
expences	O
that	O
have	O
attended	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
losing	O
my	O
former	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
disgrace	O
upon	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
have	O
turned	O
their	O
backs	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
unable	O
to	O
employ	O
counsel	O
;	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
where	O
mercy	O
abounds	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
that	O
Jury	O
,	O
where	O
mercy	O
is	O
ever	O
shewn	O
to	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Hounsom	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
allow	O
this	O
man	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
allowed	O
him	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
two	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
between	O
eighteen	O
and	O
nineteen	O
;	O
afterwards	O
another	O
wife	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
)	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
241.	O
ANN	B-pers
TROWBRIDGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
thirty-six	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
36s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
I	O
watched	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
the	O
constable	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
detected	O
her	O
with	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
gloves	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
gloves	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
gloves	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
particular	O
make	O
and	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
inserior	O
gloves	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
cheap	O
;	O
this	O
paper	O
of	O
gloves	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
prior	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
by	O
our	O
head	O
warehouseman	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
gloves	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
private	O
mark	O
of	O
my	O
warehouseman	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KITCHIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
porter	O
opened	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
bring	O
out	O
a	O
candlestick	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
porter	O
was	O
opening	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Swan-with-Two	O
Necks	O
tap	O
,	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
to	O
light	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
at	O
most	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
touched	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
bundle	O
of	O
gloves	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
at	O
Price	O
and	O
Cook	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
take	O
the	O
bundle	O
of	O
gloves	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
gloves	O
to	O
be	O
ours	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
inferior	O
gloves	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
cheap	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
private	O
mark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
knows	O
very	O
well	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
thewaste	O
paper	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
amongst	O
the	O
waste	O
paper	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
60	O
.	O
)	O
Fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
for	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
242.	O
JANE	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
nearly	O
opposite	O
Ely	O
Place	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
coppers	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
sudden	O
pull	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
myself	O
disengaged	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
rather	O
suspecting	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
that	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
far	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
nearer	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
led	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
up	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
wish	O
to	O
get	O
herself	O
disengaged	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
off	O
her	O
pattens	O
,	O
and	O
various	O
manoeuvres	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
searched	O
;	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half-guinea	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
on	O
bringing	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
toying	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
communication	O
with	O
her	O
)	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sleep	O
all	O
night	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
improper	O
communication	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
quite	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Perfectly	O
so	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
27	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
243.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BUCKTHORPE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
calico	O
,	O
containing	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
RUTTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Calico-glazer	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-close	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
calico	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
immediately	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
GREGORY	B-pers
HEELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
getting	O
my	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
kitchen	O
is	O
down	O
stairs	O
opposite	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
lay	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
from	O
my	O
breakfast	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
piece	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
-	O
ROSITER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Heeley	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ruller	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Ruller	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
there	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
has	O
not	O
your	O
son	O
some	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nobody	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
244.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
CROFTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
)	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
paid	O
his	O
wages	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
previous	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
hall-door	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
pounds	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
PHIPPS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
man	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
before	O
and	O
behind	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
stuff	O
in	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
three	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
wages	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
tobacco	O
of	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
or	O
guard	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
shilling	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
bread	O
for	O
my	O
children	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
)	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
245.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
239	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
snuffers	O
,	O
value	O
27l	O
.	O
120	O
brass	O
bed-caps	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
copper	O
tea	O
tongs	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LANCASTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
Craven-row	O
,	O
City-road	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
by	O
commission	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
nineteen	O
dozen	O
of	O
steel	O
inuffers	O
,	O
ten	O
dozen	O
of	O
bed-caps	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
tea-songs	O
;	O
Wood	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Gun	B-pers
Tavern	I-pers
at	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
a	O
captain	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
the	O
captain	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
him	O
captain	O
Riddle	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
captain	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Wood	O
and	O
the	O
mate	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
captain	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Gun	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
when	O
the	O
mate	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
captain	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occation	O
,	O
that	O
Wood	O
could	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
as	O
much	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
trusted	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
neither	O
brought	O
me	O
goods	O
or	O
money	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
upon	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	B-pers
Tavern	I-pers
;	O
Wood	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
all	O
looked	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
captain	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
approve	O
of	O
them	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
mate	O
and	O
captain	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
duty	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ruined	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
frightened	O
at	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
shew	O
you	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
both	O
captain	O
and	O
mate	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
over	O
Hermitage-bridge	O
,	O
into	O
Wapping	O
a	O
long	O
way	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
enquiring	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
looked	O
out	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
ready	O
by	O
six	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
captain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
ever	O
informed	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
captain	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
first	O
it	O
was	O
Grittle	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Little	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
Upper	O
Garlick-hill	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
merchant	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
every	O
thing	O
false	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Shows	O
him	O
a	O
paper	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
read	O
)	O
,	O
''	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lancaster	O
,	O
No.7	O
,	O
Craven-row	O
,	O
City-road	O
,	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
snussers	O
.	O
''	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
hardware	O
line	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
wanted	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
this	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
accept	O
a	O
bill	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
and	O
was	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Compter	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
knew	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
dealt	O
in	O
the	O
hardware	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
first	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
pocket	O
books	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
snussers	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
customer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
almost	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
amount	O
to	O
selony	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
obtaining	O
the	O
goods	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
idea	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
either	O
the	O
goods	O
or	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
state	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
selony	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
;	O
whether	O
they	O
chuse	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
obtaining	O
them	O
under	O
false	O
pretences	O
,	O
lies	O
with	O
themselves	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
The	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
246.	O
DIANA	B-pers
JANE	I-pers
CARNS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Loosely	I-pers
,	O
two	O
dimity	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
three	O
Banknotes	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20l	O
.	O
two	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10l	O
.	O
a	O
Promissory-note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
11s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
Promissry-note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
7s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
LOOSELY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
20l	O
.	O
Bank-notes	O
;	O
two	O
10l	O
.	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
twoPromissory-notes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
was	O
for	O
7l.11s.6d	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
12l.7s	O
.	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
access	O
to	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
alarmed	O
,	O
and	O
related	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
maid-servant	O
we	O
had	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
man-servant	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
assign	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
then	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
has	O
since	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
the	O
pockets	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
consetsed	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
ALICE	B-pers
LOOSELY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
pockets	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
after	O
the	O
loss	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
Miss	O
Alice	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
saw	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
canvass	O
bag	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
's	O
staff	O
for	O
her	O
father	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
to	O
several	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
what	O
your	O
daughter	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
denied	O
having	O
them	O
.	O
ALICE	B-pers
LOOSELY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
beating	O
a	O
child	O
facing	O
our	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
papa	O
,	O
that	O
woman	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
papa	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
his	O
staff	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
best	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
collar	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
look	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
ANN	O
STOBEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Goodman's-fields	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Allen	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
several	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
subpoened	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Loosely	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
friends	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
you	O
some	O
recompence	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
notes	O
that	O
are	O
charged	O
in	O
this	O
indictment	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
making	O
up	O
this	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
difference	O
of	O
your	O
loss	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Answer	O
my	O
question	O
,	O
sir	O
;	O
now	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
wish	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
mind	O
,	O
to	O
recover	O
the	O
loss	O
you	O
had	O
sustained	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
friends	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
recovering	O
your	O
loss	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
as	O
honest	O
people	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
committed	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
them	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
tell	O
those	O
honest	O
men	O
what	O
you	O
did	O
go	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
not	O
stone	O
unturned	O
to	O
recover	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
after	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
and	O
offer	O
to	O
lose	O
10l	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
recover	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Remember	O
,	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
's	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
life	O
,	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
recollect	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
restored	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
10l	O
.	O
short	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARRYMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
After	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
examined	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Loose-	O
ly	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
that	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PHILPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Loosely	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
theevening	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
notes	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Comp	O
ter	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
we	O
must	O
not	O
hear	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOOSELY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
loss	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
heard	O
what	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
247.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PATERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
eight	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
34s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bloomfield	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLOOMFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
wrapper	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
square	O
ones	O
,	O
or	O
corner	O
ones	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
coloured	O
silk	O
ones	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
brought	O
what	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
several	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
