TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1797	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BROOK	O
WATSON	O
,	O
ESQ	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RAMSEY	I-pers
,	O
AND	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
.	O
1797	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
BROOK	O
WATSON	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
HEATH	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	O
SILVESTER	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lightly	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wardell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Simeon	B-pers
Coley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Vincent	B-pers
Woodthorpe	I-pers
,	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hellen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollyman	I-pers
,	O
Aleph	B-pers
Buttle	I-pers
,	O
Stanton	B-pers
Rathbone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hallam	I-pers
,	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Lacey	B-pers
Punderson	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Steinmetz	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Leplaisterer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skirvin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mashiter	I-pers
,	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Albby	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Musgrove	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Nairne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
.	O
582.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Basnett	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	O
BASNETT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
hatter	O
,	O
in	O
Tothill-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
my	O
house	O
myself	O
;	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
pannel	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
cut	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
;	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
are	O
only	O
what	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
when	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
the	O
Police	O
Office	O
,	O
in	O
Queen-square	O
.	O
CHARLES	O
WHATMORE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Poet	O
's	O
Corner	O
,	O
Westminster-Abbey	O
,	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
property	O
)	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
my	O
suspecting	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
eight	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
pretended	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
get	O
somebody	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Grain	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
your	O
premisses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GRAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Having	O
some	O
business	O
at	O
the	O
Transport-office	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
I	O
heard	O
Whatmore	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Basnell	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
thread	O
upon	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
blue	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
stocking	O
dressers	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
make	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
of	O
mark	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
upon	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
stocking-dressers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
world	O
with	O
that	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
property	O
there	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
serjeant	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
583.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
DRUCE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
containing	O
fifty-six	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Waithman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
.	O
GABRIEL	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
consulting	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
break	O
Mr.	O
Waithman	O
's	O
windows	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
bring	O
out	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
holloaed	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
near	O
Green	O
Arbour-Court	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
cotton	O
)	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Waithman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Brislow	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
BRISTOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
cotton	O
is	O
our	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	O
Waithman	O
.	O
-	O
MARSHALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
)	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baran	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
584.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHUBBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
stove	O
,	O
value	O
11s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Noah	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
.	O
NOAH	B-pers
YARDLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
12	I-place
,	I-place
Church	I-place
lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
opposite	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
stoves	O
which	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
in	O
Church-court	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
stove	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
job	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Hungerford	O
Coffee-house	O
for	O
6d	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
Hungerford	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
23	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
585.	O
SARAH	B-pers
GROVES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
knowing	O
one	O
Esther	B-pers
Knightley	I-pers
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gearish	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
harbour	O
,	O
assist	O
,	O
comfort	O
,	O
and	O
maintain	O
her	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
peace	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
GEARISH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Christopher	O
Gearish	O
,	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
Esther	O
Knightley	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
left	O
Esther	B-pers
Knightley	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
the	O
dining-room	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
mat	O
,	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
202l	O
.	O
in	O
Banknotes	O
,	O
and	O
107l	O
.	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
gone	O
,	O
besides	O
my	O
table-linen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
cloth	O
apron	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
marked	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
for	O
Esther	B-pers
Knightley	I-pers
;	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
duplicate	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
pledged	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
gown	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
gown	O
was	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
quite	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
pledged	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gearish	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
gown	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WOODHOUSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
cloak	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
cloak	O
was	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gearish	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
cloak	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
586.	O
MARY	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SUSANNAH	I-pers
ROBERTSON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
four	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
19s	O
.	O
a	O
cotton	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
cotton	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
muslin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
muslin	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
;	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
Banknote	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BUTLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
last	O
June	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Windsor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
husband	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hindes	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
12l	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
a	O
10l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
2l	O
.	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
club-box	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
club	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
given	O
security	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
more	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
desk	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
,	O
at	O
Maidenhead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
13l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
1l	O
.	O
Bank-note	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
note	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
her	O
wages	O
,	O
except	O
about	O
12s	O
.	O
-	O
JONES	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Butler	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Butler	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
this	O
gown	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
washed	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
petticoat	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
mending	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
sewed	O
to	O
her	O
under-petticoat	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
two	O
muslin	O
petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
promised	O
to	O
forgive	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
587.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MANSELL	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RANTON	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
then	O
being	O
,	O
feloniously	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bedstead-maker	O
in	O
Portpool-lane	B-place
,	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
latch	O
at	O
the	O
private	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
seized	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Morris	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
broke	O
my	O
house	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
coachman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
devil	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wrested	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
gateway	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
spring	O
a	O
rattle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
patrole	O
and	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
hay-lost	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Ranton	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
loss	O
I	O
had	O
sustained	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
pigs	O
dead	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
brains	O
beat	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
third	O
man	O
stands	O
in	O
your	O
presence	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
swear	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
latch	O
been	O
broke	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
your	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
Mansell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
Morris	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
give	O
charge	O
of	O
Morris	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
Ranton	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
stable-yard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
moon-light	O
.	O
JONATHAN	O
KIRBY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Ranton	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
hay-lost	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
there	O
;	O
Davies	O
immediately	O
charged	O
him	O
as	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Ranton	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
yard	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
hay-lost	O
.	O
Morris	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
sooner	O
than	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
Davis	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
away	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
purl	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
.	O
Ranton	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
Morris	O
one	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Morris	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Mansell	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Ranton	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
588.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COPE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
iron	O
tinned	O
handles	O
for	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Maizeaux	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
ABRAHAM	O
WRIGHT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	O
Maizeaux	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
factory	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
them	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dozen	O
saucepan-handles	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
dozen	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
delivered	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
proved	O
the	O
partnership	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Hawker	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
these	O
handles	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
,	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
tin	O
or	O
pewter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Hawker	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
distress	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
earn	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
earn	O
at	O
least	O
25s	O
.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
diligent	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
37	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
589.	O
ANN	B-pers
SANMERT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowderoy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
sixpences	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
groats	O
,	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
half-crown	O
,	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
COWDEROY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
in	O
Broadway	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
last	O
,	O
atnear	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
settling	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
ledge	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back-room	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
something	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
purse	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
many	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
waistcoats	O
made	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
address	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
waited	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
between	O
her	O
things	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
string	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
2l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
including	O
a	O
French	O
half-crown	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
bad	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
eight	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Bank-notes	O
.	O
(	O
William	O
Messenger	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Cowderoy	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
four-penny	O
pieces	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Two	O
doors	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
dog	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
chink	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
57	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
590.	O
SARAH	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
check	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BALDWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Philip	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
SARAH	O
WORLIDGE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
stop	O
and	O
throw	O
the	O
things	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
did	O
throw	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
from	O
necessity	O
and	O
want	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
14	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
591.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MOSELY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
toilinet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveteen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Woods	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WOODS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	B-place
Old	I-place
Crown	I-place
,	I-place
Highgate-hill	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
property	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
cloaths	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MANN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
putting	O
them	O
on	O
while	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
own	O
mended	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
592.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
MURDOCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mulry	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
MULRY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
let	O
it	O
drop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
)	O
Mulry	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
paper	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
36	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
593.	O
SARAH	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Hack	I-pers
.	O
DIANA	B-pers
HACK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Francis	O
Hack	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
seeing	O
my	O
husband	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KNIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
594.	O
PETER	B-pers
MALONE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Spanish	O
wool	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bickham	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
looking	O
some	O
Spanish	O
wool	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
at	O
Galley	B-place
quay	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Spanish	O
wool	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
lighter	O
was	O
worked	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
secreted	O
partly	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
property	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
me	O
pilfering	O
or	O
skulking	O
about	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
must	O
speak	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
guilty	O
of	O
pilfering	O
on	O
the	O
quays	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q.Whose	O
lighter	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Salter	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bickham	O
are	O
Clothworkers	O
Porters	O
unshipping	O
merchants	O
'	O
property	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KNIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cloth-workers	O
'	O
Porter	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Bickham	O
is	O
my	O
partner	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
Tackle	O
Porters	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
jointly	O
liable	O
for	O
any	O
loss	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
sustained	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
do	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Green	O
take	O
the	O
wool	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
partly	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
of	O
Spanish	O
wool	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
wool	O
laid	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
scale	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
595.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SPARKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
six	O
pounds	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hould	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pinchin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hobbins	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOULD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gangsman	O
,	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
;	O
the	O
persons	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
are	O
my	O
partners	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
jointly	O
responsible	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
under	O
our	O
care	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Chesler	B-place
's	I-place
quay	I-place
with	O
some	O
raw	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
detected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
employed	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
body	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
;	O
the	O
only	O
excuse	O
he	O
made	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hogshead	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
loop-hole	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
head	O
broke	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
corresponded	O
with	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
upon	O
the	O
quays	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
sugar	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
property	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
596.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
coral	O
,	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
coal-shed	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GFARING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
:	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
two	O
children	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
child	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
;	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
followed	O
me	O
through	O
Ducke	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
keep	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
behind	O
whistled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Green-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
lose	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
was	O
duke	O
somebody	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
coral	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
string	O
was	O
cut	O
or	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
hewas	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
coral	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.Seventeen	O
.	O
Q.What	O
age	O
are	O
the	O
children	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
mistress	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
with	O
so	O
young	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
ever	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
?	O
-	O
A.With	O
Mrs.	O
Chilton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
walk	O
out	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
while	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
addressed	O
before	O
by	O
young	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
addressed	O
by	O
young	O
men	O
now	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
night	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
beautiful	O
moonlight	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
attempt	O
to	O
kiss	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
salute	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
attempted	O
to	O
touch	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
coral	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
young	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
other	O
ladies	O
besides	O
yourself	O
walking	O
the	O
streets	O
?	O
-	O
A.There	O
might	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
MERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
secretary	O
of	O
the	O
Imperial	O
Ambassador	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
screams	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
which	O
alarmed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
spot	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
very	O
swist	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
snatching	O
the	O
coral	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
coral	O
was	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
grass-plat	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
familiar	O
sort	O
of	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
coral	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
railing	O
of	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
coral	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
597.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
boiling	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Heaford	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
seventy	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
HEAFORD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
in	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
highway	I-place
:	O
Between	O
Thursday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
my	O
premisses	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
copper	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shadwell	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Myatt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
we	O
fitted	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
Myatt	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
proved	O
the	O
buying	O
it	O
of	O
John	O
Mills	O
,	O
accordingly	O
Mills	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
copper	O
ever	O
put	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
copper	O
has	O
been	O
fixed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BUCKLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Heaford	O
;	O
I	O
hit	O
the	O
copper	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
with	O
a	O
shovel	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
it	O
between	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
lead	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
nail-hole	O
that	O
corresponded	O
,	O
and	O
white-wash	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
copper	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
body	O
might	O
have	O
given	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
take	O
upon	O
yourself	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
copper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
bottom	O
was	O
not	O
cut	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
brickwork	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police	O
officer	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Heaford	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Myatt	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
copper	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
we	O
fitted	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
brick-work	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
corresponded	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
copper	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Myatt	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
old	O
lead	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
copper	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
cart	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
's	O
for	O
some	O
old	O
stuff	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
sale	O
if	O
I	O
liked	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fear	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
the	O
copper	O
and	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cut	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
officers	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
copper	O
was	O
not	O
cut	O
up	O
till	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Myatt	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
bent	O
double	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
most	O
used	O
,	O
was	O
less	O
worn	O
than	O
the	O
top	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
bottom	O
is	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
burnt	O
as	O
the	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
Myatt	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
himself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
cut	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
Myatt	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.That	O
poor	O
man	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
whole	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
concealment	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.Eight-pence	O
halfpenny	O
for	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
one-penny	O
farthing	O
for	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
fair	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
price	O
as	O
persons	O
that	O
have	O
stolen	O
things	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
stolen	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Myatt	O
never	O
charged	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Six	O
months	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Myatt	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mills	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MYATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
old	O
iron	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
goods	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
I	O
sent	O
Bailey	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
nine-pence	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
for	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
short	O
of	O
one-penny	O
halfpenny	O
for	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
came	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
usually	O
buy	O
lead	O
without	O
ever	O
having	O
seen	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
common	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
what	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
three-pence	O
a	O
pound	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
22d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
eight-pence	O
halfpenny	O
that	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
iron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
coal-yard	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
keep	O
an	O
honest	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
rags	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
it	O
happened	O
now	O
unluckily	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
happen	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
something	O
about	O
a	O
similar	O
job	O
with	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
got	O
through	O
that	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.And	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
through	O
this	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
six	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
little	O
accident	O
that	O
happened	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
about	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
iron	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
proved	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
fairly	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
HARVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
and	O
chair-woman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
employed	O
at	O
the	O
waterside	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
copper	O
and	O
some	O
lead	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Mills	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
lived	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
distress	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Mills	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
eight-pence	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
farthings	O
for	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
shed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
water-side	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
598.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRAMBLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
NORRIS	O
,	O
jun	O
:	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
father	O
keeps	O
a	O
carpet	O
and	O
upholstery	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
quilt	O
and	O
a	O
blanketfrom	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Redlion-square	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
within	O
the	O
rails	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
Henry	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Norris	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Gower-street	O
,	O
Bedford-square	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
599.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
serret	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
a	O
half-bound	O
small	O
printed	O
book	O
,	O
entitled	O
,	O
``	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Auld	O
Robin	O
Gray	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Jamie	O
and	O
Sandy	O
,	O
a	O
Scotch	O
Tale	O
,	O
''	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
another	O
printed	O
bound	O
book	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Prayer-book	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	O
CURTIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
,	O
in	O
Grice's-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Wellclose-square	I-place
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
eloped	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
my	O
enquiries	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
learned	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
situation	O
,	O
dreadfully	O
diseased	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
work-house	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
doctor	O
attended	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
discovered	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
CURTIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
an	O
old	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
a	O
prayer-book	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
-HOBART	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
she	O
herself	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Curtis	O
.	O
Habart	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
600.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LANDRITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
JAMES	I-pers
GALLOWAY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
dollars	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
.	O
ISABELLA	O
GALLOWAY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
James	O
Galloway	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
uncle	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Galloway	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
fortune	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
ship	O
loaded	O
with	O
bale	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
very	O
handsome	O
for	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Galloway	O
was	O
his	O
nephew	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
his	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
three	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
lit	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
fort	O
of	O
a	O
bed	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
lie	O
on	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
mean	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
somebody	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
two	O
dollars	O
,	O
he	O
snatched	O
the	O
two	O
dollars	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
brandy	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
dollars	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
CROCKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
dollars	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Galloway	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
dollars	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mark	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
present	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
d-d	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
believe	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
present	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
impostor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very-much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
overjoyed	O
at	O
seeing	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
insensible	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
passing	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
601.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
MOREY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	O
DYSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sine-drawer	O
:	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
Spital-square	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
step	O
,	O
and	O
stripping	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
child	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
brother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
clothes	O
off	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
comfortable	O
manner	O
.	O
SARAH	O
CASTLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spital-square	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
pinnafore	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
frock	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
that	O
,	O
andthan	O
she	O
doubled	O
up	O
the	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
over	O
the	O
frock	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Dyson	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
told	O
me	O
its	O
name	O
,	O
the	O
Bellman	O
was	O
crying	O
it	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
square	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Harrod-street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
Spital-square	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
missing	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
crying	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
it	O
where	O
its	O
mammy	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
pointed	O
strait	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
led	O
it	O
over	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Spital-square	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
petticoats	O
round	O
its	O
shoulders	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
warm	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
)	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
602.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PRYER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
turnings	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gooch	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GOOCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-case	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
vast	O
quantity	O
of	O
turnings	O
within	O
these	O
three	O
months	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
six	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
some	O
work	O
which	O
produced	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
turnings	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Hatton-garden	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
apartments	O
,	O
where	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
that	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
can	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
,	O
inside	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
some	O
silver	O
turnings	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Hatton-garden	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
taken	O
any	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
bad	O
parents	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
as	O
an	O
errand-boy	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
apprentice	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
TINK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
turnings	O
from	O
my	O
lathe	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Gooch	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
LONGDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
turnings	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
glove	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Gooch	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
turnings	O
that	O
are	O
produced	O
in	O
our	O
work	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
box	O
was	O
always	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
)	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
603.	O
MARK	B-pers
PEDDEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
sixty-three	O
pounds	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
39s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheese-monger	O
in	O
Spital-fields	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passing	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
bacon	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
laid	O
wait	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
hook	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
dark	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
bacon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q.What	O
coloured	O
coat	O
had	O
he	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
whitish	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
might	O
have	O
prevented	O
the	O
these	O
if	O
you	O
pleased	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
in	O
the	O
bacon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
bacon	O
off	O
the	O
hook	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BREWER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
other	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
27	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
604.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DODD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
hair-powder	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
John	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Saxton	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
Sarah	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examination	O
found	O
12lb	O
.	O
deficient	O
in	O
one	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
38lb	O
.	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
and	O
labelled	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pounds	O
of	O
powder	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A.Ten	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
powder	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.And	O
it	O
was	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
shipped	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	O
M'CARTY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
JOHN	O
PEACOCK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
put	O
twenty	O
boxes	O
of	O
powder	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
Sarah	O
.	O
EDWARD	O
ROGERS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
powder	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
noon-day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
concealed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
605.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half-pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
5d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Fifer	I-pers
.	O
JACOB	O
FIFER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
Leman-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pint	O
and	O
a	O
half-pint	O
pot	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
GRIFFITHS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
pots	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Timms	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pots	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
rent	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
pots	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
41	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
606.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
milled	O
money	O
,	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
milled	O
money	O
,	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
not	O
being	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
did	O
put	O
off	O
to	O
one	O
Israel	O
Mulberry	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
lower	O
rate	O
and	O
value	O
than	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
by	O
their	O
denomination	O
,	O
did	O
import	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
)	O
.	O
ISRAEL	O
MULBERRY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Colquhoun	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Bridge	B-place
water-gardens	I-place
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
we	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
shilling's-worth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
some	O
bad	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
two	O
shilling's-worth	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
six	O
sixpences	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
blacking	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
blacking	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
sixpence	O
that	O
I	O
objected	O
to	O
,	O
it	O
looked	O
very	O
yellow	O
,	O
he	O
changed	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officers	O
,	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
Ray	O
,	O
Ferris	O
,	O
and	O
Peach	O
;	O
we	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
the	O
officers	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
within	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
officers	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Armstrong	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
blacking	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Colquhoun	O
.	O
JOHN	O
ARMSTRONG	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Police	O
office	O
,	O
in	O
Worship	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Bridgewater-gardens	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Clark	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Marshalmen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
pushed	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolts	O
or	O
something	O
gave	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
This	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
blacking	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
good	O
money	O
or	O
bad	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
counterfeit	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
six	O
sixpences	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
what	O
particular	O
use	O
is	O
blacking	O
in	O
the	O
process	O
of	O
coining	O
?	O
-	O
A.This	O
blacking	O
is	O
used	O
upon	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
white	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
circulation	O
.	O
JOHN	O
CLARK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
City-Marshalmen	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Armstrong	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Armstrong	O
and	O
myself	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Brackley-street	O
,	O
Bridgwater-gardens	O
,	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Wooden-world	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
made	O
a	O
terrible	O
piece	O
of	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
bad	O
sixpences	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
breeches-pockets	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
good	O
or	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pot	O
with	O
some	O
blacking	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
common	O
blacking	O
for	O
shoes	O
,	O
or	O
blacking	O
for	O
any	O
particular	O
purpose	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Armstrong	O
)	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
blacking	O
that	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
blacking	O
shoes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
blacking	O
used	O
by	O
coiners	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
handcuffed	O
him	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
making	O
resistance	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
pocket	O
five	O
sixpences	O
all	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
kept	O
a	O
green-grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
five	O
sixpences	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
that	O
has	O
swore	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
days	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
607.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
RUSSELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
nineteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PARR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
a	O
waggoner	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
with	O
my	O
waggon	O
;	O
near	O
Maidenhead-Thicket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
hamper	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Colnbrook	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stop	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
forward	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
get	O
sixpennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
sixty-one	O
cheeses	O
to	O
leave	O
at	O
Oxbridge	O
.	O
Q.Where	O
was	O
the	O
waggon	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
left	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Colnbrook	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
upon	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
overtook	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Magpie	O
,	O
Hounslow-heath	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
squeezed	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
observed	O
before	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
cheese	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
money	O
to	O
his	O
daughter	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
head	O
to	O
be	O
entertained	O
with	O
a	O
boxing-match	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
your	O
waggon	O
on	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
miles	O
,	O
while	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
boxing-match	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.It	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
sack	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
it	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
sack	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
filled	O
with	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
apples	O
?	O
-	O
A.There	O
was	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
apples	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
might	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
sack	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
two	O
men	O
ride	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
to	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
were	O
driving	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
left	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
supposed	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
count	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
only	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
public-house	O
the	O
moment	O
the	O
charge	O
was	O
made	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LEDIARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
,	O
at	O
Colnbrook	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
waggoner	O
drinking	O
some	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
cheese	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
horse	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cheese	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
that	O
public-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
cheese	O
)	O
.	O
Parr	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
cheese	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
his	O
waggon	O
to	O
Maidenhead	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
breakfast	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
stopped	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
fight	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
overtook	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Colnbrook	O
;	O
how	O
the	O
cheese	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
36	O
)	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
608.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALMOND	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
POTTER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Mayor	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Commonalty	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Citizens	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
City	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
.	O
And	O
,	O
Three	O
other	O
Counts	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
cutting	O
the	O
same	O
lead	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WEBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Vaillant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
any	O
information	O
you	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
premisses	O
in	O
Butcher-row	B-place
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
those	O
which	O
are	O
now	O
standing	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
upon	O
the	O
house	O
getting	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Smith	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rattling	O
among	O
the	O
tiles	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
every	O
room	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
getting	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
lead	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
pieces	O
cut	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
being	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
through	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
;	O
they	O
begged	O
us	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
knives	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
cut	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
jar	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
house	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
boarded	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
quitted	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fence	O
round	O
the	O
two	O
houses	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
fence	O
open	O
;	O
what	O
lead	O
was	O
not	O
cut	O
up	O
was	O
marked	O
across	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
cut	O
up	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
two	O
knives	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
cutting	O
appeared	O
very	O
bright	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Joseph	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
JOSEPH	O
STEVENS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
this	O
house	O
safe	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
employed	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
keys	O
are	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Surveyor	O
's	O
office	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.And	O
any	O
body	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Surveyor	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
having	O
an	O
authority	O
from	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
might	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Who	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
has	O
the	O
key	O
but	O
the	O
Surveyor	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MONTAGUE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
Surveyor	O
's	O
office	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
house	O
in	O
Butcher-row	O
,	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
have	O
agreed	O
for	O
it	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
taken	O
any	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
pulled	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
house	O
surrounded	O
with	O
a	O
horde	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Behind	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
front	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
keys	O
you	O
took	O
no	O
trouble	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
hang	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
do	O
they	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
put	O
in	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
paid	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
we	O
ever	O
received	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
ought	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
no	O
keys	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
whose	O
custody	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Potter	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Almond	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
17	O
.	O
)	O
Potter	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
609.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
acting	O
lientenant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
passing	O
through	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
cart	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
person	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
has	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
beadle	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RHODES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
that	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Silver-street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
inhis	O
hand	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
upon	O
observing	O
me	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
conscious	O
of	O
his	O
guilt	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
holloaed	O
to	O
a	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
who	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
MARCH	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
two-pound	O
note	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
papers	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
in	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
name	O
written	O
in	O
that	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
only	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
like	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
eight	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Judgment	O
respited	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
610.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MACKEY	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
BOND	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
twenty-four	O
pounds	O
,	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
two	O
Bank-notes	O
of	O
20l	O
.	O
each	O
,	O
one	O
Bank-note	O
of	O
5l	O
.	O
another	O
Bank-note	O
of	O
2l	O
.	O
and	O
seven	O
Bank-notes	O
of	O
1l	O
.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Green	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
NORBURY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Skerrett	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Loudunsac	O
,	O
his	O
clerk	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Glynn	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
,	O
Birchin-lane	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bond	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
direct	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
house	O
but	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
jostled	O
up	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
money	O
go	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Bonner	O
stepped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
him	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
others	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
Bonner	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
bag	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cellar	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
,	O
counsel	O
for	O
Bond	B-pers
Q	O
.	O
Bond	O
you	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
in	O
Birchin-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
asked	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
direction	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
tremble	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
right	O
direction	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
first	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
house	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
money	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
impression	O
you	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
mercer	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
property	O
is	O
mine	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BONNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
warehouse-man	O
to	O
a	O
warehouse	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Birchin-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
following	O
Joseph	B-pers
Norbury	I-pers
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
beckoning	O
and	O
winking	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
Norbury	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
the	O
banking-house	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
Bond	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
shewing	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
all	O
before	O
about	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Mackey	O
came	O
close	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mackey	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
missed	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
returning	O
and	O
speaking	O
to	O
Bond	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
principal	O
ones	O
were	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
leads	O
through	O
into	O
St.	O
Michael's-court	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
St.	O
Michael's-court	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
ticket-porters	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
directed	O
us	O
into	O
Gracerhurch-street	O
,	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
informed	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
butter	O
passage	O
into	O
Leadenhall-market	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
up	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
very	O
soon	O
then	O
saw	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Mackey	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
passage	O
;	O
Bond	O
we	O
left	O
behind	O
in	O
Birchin	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mackey	O
threw	O
down	O
some	O
money	O
into	O
a	O
cellar	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
rebounded	O
from	O
the	O
bars	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
secured	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
has	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
applied	O
to	O
Bond	O
first	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
something	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Bond	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
,	O
counsel	O
for	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Q.When	O
Taylor	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
found	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
speak	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
Mackey	O
or	O
to	O
Bond	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
very	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
.	O
Q.Were	O
there	O
no	O
other	O
persons	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
in	O
Birchin-lane	O
,	O
besides	O
?	O
-	O
A.There	O
might	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
caught	O
together	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
LOUDUNSAC	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
porter	O
of	O
our	O
's	O
give	O
Norbury	O
78l	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
;	O
54l	O
.	O
in	O
Bank-notes	O
and	O
24l	O
.	O
8s	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Roberts	O
and	O
Green	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Carr	O
Glynn	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
a	O
20l	O
.	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
number	O
and	O
sum	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
Mackey	O
and	O
Taylor	O
pass	O
my	O
door	O
in	O
Leadenball-market	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
pick	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
canvas	O
bag	O
in	O
Mackey	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
passage	O
and	O
stopped	O
there	O
,	O
Mackey	O
was	O
counting	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
he	O
was	O
counting	O
19	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
beyond	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
making	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
one	O
by	O
each	O
arm	O
;	O
Mackey	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
a	O
cellar	O
;	O
the	O
notes	O
went	O
through	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
rebounded	O
back	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
.	O
Q.When	O
they	O
were	O
dividing	O
the	O
money	O
Bond	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mackey	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mackey	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
ship-mate	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Leadenhall	O
market	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
works	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Bond	O
.	O
Bond	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
rightly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
lower	O
down	O
.	O
Mackey	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
.	O
)	O
Taylor	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
24	O
.	O
)	O
Bond	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
32	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
611.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
carcase	O
of	O
lamb	O
,	O
weighing	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Newgate-market	B-place
;	O
I	O
killed	O
twenty	O
lambs	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
I	O
lost	O
one	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Rutter	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
a	O
carcase	O
of	O
lamb	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Three-tun-passage	O
,	O
leading	O
from	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
near	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
whether	O
accidently	O
or	O
purposely	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulders	O
again	O
and	O
pitched	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
bound	O
over	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
defect	O
of	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
must	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
612.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
MIDDLETON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
OSLAND	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
shooting	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
gun-powder	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
bullet	O
,	O
at	O
Daniel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
