TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1799	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIRST	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HARVEY	O
CHRISTIAN	O
COMBE	O
,	O
ESQ	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	O
RAMSEY	O
,	O
AND	O
published	O
by	O
authority	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1799	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
HARVEY	B-pers
CHRISTIAN	I-pers
COMBE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	O
GROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	O
HOTHAM	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALAN	O
CHAMBRE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAM	O
ROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burnby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Strahan	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Ferne	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Isleton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Galabin	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tregent	I-pers
William	B-pers
Nias	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lejeune	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Wallis	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Moorby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Glossop	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Noah	B-pers
Brocklesby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Aldy	I-pers
John	B-pers
Heron	I-pers
John	B-pers
Theobalds	I-pers
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
MARY	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
a	O
cambric	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
lawn	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
muslin	O
,	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
LEWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
at	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
sometime	O
in	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
we	O
desired	O
the	O
servants	O
to	O
open	O
their	O
boxes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
her	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
property	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
boxes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
in	O
both	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
Ray	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
she	O
pleaded	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
property	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
keys	O
lying	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
unlocked	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
ever	O
committed	O
any	O
crime	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
friends	O
live	O
at	O
Newcastle-upon-Tyne	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
30	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
two	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
2.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GANER	I-pers
and	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
GANER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
four	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elisha	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
ELISHA	B-pers
PEARCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
,	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
coal-porter	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
;	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
retail	O
coals	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
in	O
down	O
the	O
back	O
area	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
was	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
another	O
table-spoon	O
and	O
four	O
tea-spoons	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
work	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back-shop	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
drop	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
stable	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
among	O
the	O
dung	O
;	O
I	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
spoon	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
confessed	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
manger	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
another	O
spoon	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
teaspoons	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
at	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
among	O
some	O
girls	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAWTHORN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
servant	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
tablespoon	O
under	O
the	O
manger	O
,	O
another	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
had	O
slept	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
tea	O
spoons	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
tea-spoon	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm-pit	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
in	O
the	O
manger	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
no	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
confident	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
Rose-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
four	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
mother	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
30	O
,	O
Crown-street	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
baker	O
's	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
round	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
mother	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
spoon	O
which	O
her	O
son	O
had	O
brought	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Charlotte-street	O
,	O
Rathbone-place	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
mistres	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
if	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
provided	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
her	O
mistress	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
fellow	O
spoon	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
confident	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Ganen	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Ganen	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ganen	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Ganen	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
60	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
3.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NEWTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
three	O
gallons	O
of	O
anniseed	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Spackman	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Raine	O
.	O
)	O
ALEXANDER	O
GORDON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
distiller	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
Charles	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Spackman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
carman	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PEACH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police-officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Harper	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
presently	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
opened	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
and	O
staved	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
beat	O
the	O
head	O
in	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
anniseed	O
flew	O
over	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whose	O
servant	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
learned	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
a	O
distiller	O
's	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
on	O
Monday	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
cask	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
staved	O
the	O
cask	O
that	O
the	O
liquor	O
might	O
run	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
permit	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
liable	O
to	O
be	O
seized	O
as	O
a	O
smuggler	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
destroyed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
liquor	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
by	O
suffering	O
the	O
liquor	O
to	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Harper	O
produced	O
the	O
cask	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
frequently	O
send	O
out	O
casks	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
returned	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
lose	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
sell	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
other	O
partners	O
than	O
those	O
you	O
have	O
named	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
.	O
4.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
ASH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
three	O
time-pieces	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
accomplice	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
5.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LONGFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
carcase	O
of	O
a	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
21s	O
.	O
and	O
100	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
21s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lambley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
LAMBLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
my	O
shop	O
is	O
in	O
Tothill-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
carcase	O
of	O
a	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
beef	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
stated	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
guinea	O
each	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
carcase	O
of	O
a	O
sheep	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
two	O
shoulders	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
mangled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
beef	O
hanging	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
the	O
sheep	O
being	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
three	O
days	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
particular	O
scores	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GREENHILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
carcase	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hind	O
quarter	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
jack-ass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
right	O
shoulder	O
a	O
large	O
patch	O
of	O
grease	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
shouldering	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
very	O
ill	O
language	O
both	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Justices	O
.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
MUSTARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
jack-ass	O
go	O
pastmy	O
box	O
loaded	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lambley	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
upon	O
this	O
ass	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
jack-ass	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
DENHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
my	O
jackass	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
exchange	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half-a-guinea	O
to	O
boot	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
brown	O
jack-ass	O
,	O
cut	O
a	O
little	O
under	O
the	O
tail	O
with	O
the	O
crupper	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ass	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mustard	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
jack-ass	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Denham	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
ass	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
him	O
Rabbit	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
head	O
round	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Pye-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
jack-ass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Longford	O
's	O
own	O
jack-ass	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
riding	O
the	O
jack-ass	O
,	O
and	O
Longford	O
threatened	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
get	O
my	O
husband	O
transported	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
Fulham	O
to	O
sell	O
apples	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
my	O
stable	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
up	O
my	O
ass	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
hay	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
pannier	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
ass	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
my	O
ass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
meat	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
ass	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
.	O
6.	O
LETTICE	B-pers
FOWLER	I-pers
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
EMERY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
upon	O
Mary	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
COLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
7	I-place
,	I-place
Angel-court	I-place
,	I-place
Charing-cross	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
one-pair	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
drink	O
some	O
beer	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
unfortunately	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Emery	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
called	O
two	O
fellows	O
in	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
cut	O
my	O
pocket	O
off	O
;	O
my	O
nutmeg-grater	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
fellows	O
held	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
room	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
crept	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
watchman	O
,	O
loudly	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fellows	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
pistol	O
off	O
at	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
surgeon	O
attending	O
me	O
these	O
four	O
weeks	O
;	O
the	O
surgeon	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
powder	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
dead	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
I	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
their	O
long	O
brooms	O
and	O
candles	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
women	O
came	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
leave	O
me	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
wound	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
broom	O
?	O
-	O
A.They	O
beat	O
me	O
all	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
fingers	O
ends	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
black	O
all	O
over	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
duplicates	O
from	O
me	O
of	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
pawned	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
burn	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
DENTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
standing	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Fowler	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
tumbled	O
down	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
areas	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
intoxicated	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
was	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
nose	O
and	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
Fowler	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
broom	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Fowler	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
left	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
for	O
dead	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
beadle	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
Fowler	O
;	O
Donaldson	O
took	O
Emery	B-pers
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
BEATTIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
assist	O
Denton	O
in	O
Angel-court	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
jamb	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
word	O
she	O
spoke	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
two	O
fellows	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
row	O
in	O
Cockspur-street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
;	O
Fowler	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
broom	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
knocked	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
over	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
seized	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
broom	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
took	O
herto	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
searched	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DONALDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Emery	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
Angel-court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
whole	O
parcel	O
of	O
women	O
there	O
in	O
confusion	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
money	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
half	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bottom	O
drawer	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
but	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
those	O
the	O
words	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
work-bag	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Fowler	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Sally	O
Emery	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
wine	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
tipsey	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
porter	O
;	O
Sally	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Sally	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
with	O
a	O
knot	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
Sally	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
either	O
I	O
or	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
nobody	O
else	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
;	O
she	O
directly	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
stinking	O
bunter	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
dare	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
sighting	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
patten	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
besides	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Emery	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
some	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
half-guinea	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
into	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Lettice	O
Fowler	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
began	O
to	O
abuse	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
went	O
to	O
sight	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
,	O
tore	O
her	O
veil	O
off	O
her	O
bonnet	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
gown	O
was	O
tore	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
dress	O
on	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
things	O
to	O
rights	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
this	O
crown	O
piece	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
cohabits	O
with	O
any	O
man	O
but	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
landlady	O
what	O
was	O
best	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
advice	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
altogether	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
did	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
broom	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
patten	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
violence	O
used	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
public-house	O
with	O
Fowler	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q.Had	O
you	O
drank	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
the	O
porter	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
public-house	O
that	O
night	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
at	O
Wandsworth	O
,	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
City	O
Militia	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
got	O
liberty	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
liberty	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
going	O
forward	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
7.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rodwell	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
RODWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
Cannon-street	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
evening	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
tea	O
at	O
Garraway	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
seat	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
public	O
sale	O
at	O
Garraway	O
's	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
sale	O
was	O
announced	O
to	O
begin	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
my	O
coat	O
slide	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
somebody	O
was	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
joke	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
sale-room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
putting	O
on	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
lead	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Howell	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
Garraway	O
's	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
his	O
name	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
although	O
I	O
felt	O
disposed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
the	O
coat	O
remained	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
gloves	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
situation	O
was	O
the	O
seat	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Just	O
opposite	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
sale-room	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
many	O
people	O
attending	O
that	O
sale	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
any	O
persons	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
have	O
brushed	O
that	O
coat	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Impossible	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
at	O
my	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
waiter	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
you	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
mercy	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
confused	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
coat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
there	O
have	O
been	O
any	O
difficulty	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
coat	O
in	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A.None	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
situation	O
in	O
life	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Lieutenant	O
upon	O
half-pay	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
annuity	O
of	O
forty	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
Garraway	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
;	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
office	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Dublin	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
lest	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
many	O
things	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
pay	O
for	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
thief	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
many	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
you	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
and	O
patrole	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Garraway	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
taking	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Counsel	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
inadequate	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
before	O
;	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Barry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
submitted	O
that	O
very	O
question	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
whether	O
until	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Barry	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
necessary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
the	O
trial	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
word	O
this	O
morning	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Barry	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
shipmate	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lieutenant	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Crescent	O
frigate	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
war	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
situation	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
most	O
pleasant	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
an	O
appointment	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
Garraway	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
some	O
year	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
precisely	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
from	O
six	O
till	O
very	O
near	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sale-room	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
seeing	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
all	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
leaving	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
thinking	O
my	O
friend	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
suppose	O
there	O
were	O
one	O
hundred	O
persons	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
friend	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
holding	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
that	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
it	O
down	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
waiter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
add	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rodwell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
putting	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
34	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
.	O
8.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
,	O
wharfinger	O
and	O
lighterman	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Fresh	O
wharf	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
bat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
head	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
head	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
plunder	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bolt	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
upon	O
his	O
wharf	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
sometime	O
at	O
the	O
wharf	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
hurt	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
wheels	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
affected	O
his	O
hearing	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
honesty	O
before	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
upon	O
the	O
quays	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
taking	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
napkin	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
pressed	O
very	O
hard	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
sugar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
sugar	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
cooper	O
at	O
Wiggin	O
's	O
quay	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
two	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
.	O
9.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Crutched-Friars	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
from	O
Chester	B-place
's	I-place
quay	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
four	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
that	O
to	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
upon	O
Galley-quay	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
between	O
two	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
filled	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
a	O
City	O
constable	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
quays	O
,	O
from	O
within	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
slightly	O
intoxicated	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SEALLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
without	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
cotton	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
working	O
upon	O
the	O
quays	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
throw	O
myself	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
38	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
two	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
.	O
10.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
CROCKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
upon	O
the	O
quays	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Ralph's-quay	B-place
,	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
bags	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
act	O
of	O
plundering	O
the	O
bags	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
perceived	O
me	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
cotton	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
quite	O
frightened	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
cotton	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
30	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
11.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
John	I-pers
Arabin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William-John	O
.	O
WILLIAM-	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARABIN	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
last	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
town	O
for	O
the	O
winter	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
miles	O
from	O
town	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Uxbridge-road	B-place
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
horse-back	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
over	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
in	O
discourse	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
foot	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
my	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
jostled	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
my	O
coachman	O
might	O
have	O
driven	O
against	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
saw	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
very	O
violent	O
expressions	O
;	O
be	O
swore	O
very	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
t	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
directly	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
drew	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
d-n	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
neither	O
,	O
be	O
repeated	O
that	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
look	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
or	O
d-n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
do	O
n't	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
look	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
looked	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
look	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
y	O
rascal	O
,	O
b	O
-	O
t	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
look	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
turning	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
all	O
the	O
bottom	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Close	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
nearly	O
about	O
that	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
position	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
rode	O
away	O
a	O
full	O
gallop	O
;	O
I	O
handed	O
him	O
some	O
half-pence	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
walnuts	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
taking	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
snatched	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
containing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
recent	O
attack	O
near	O
the	O
same	O
spot	O
,	O
I	O
attended	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
to	O
identify	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
upon	O
earth	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
robbery	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Almost	O
twelve	O
months	O
ago	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Had	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
robbed	O
you	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
or	O
a	O
slapped	O
hat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
round	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
pretty	O
low	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
after	O
three	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
it	O
begins	O
to	O
be	O
duskish	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
frost	O
,	O
and	O
snow	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
sufficient	O
light	O
to	O
distinguish	O
his	O
features	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
has	O
been	O
no	O
property	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
persuasion	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
find	O
some	O
persons	O
there	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
some	O
persons	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
who	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
December	O
till	O
October	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
I	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
-	O
ARABIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
in	O
his	O
carriage	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
transaction	O
took	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
by	O
the	O
stopping	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
voice	O
,	O
exclaiming	O
,	O
b	O
-	O
st	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
almost	O
instantly	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
at	O
the	O
carriage-window	O
;	O
he	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
menacing	O
tone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
father	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
demanded	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
fixed	O
my	O
eye	O
and	O
my	O
attention	O
particularly	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
frequently	O
b	O
-	O
d	O
my	O
eyes	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
turn	O
my	O
head	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robbed	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
any	O
money	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
low	O
as	O
his	O
eye-brows	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
ostlers	O
usually	O
wear	O
,	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
snuff-colour	O
,	O
tied	O
over	O
his	O
chin	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
loosely	O
tied	O
,	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
motion	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
agitation	O
,	O
it	O
continually	O
dropped	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
strongly	O
imprinted	O
upon	O
my	O
recollection	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
alarmed	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sleep	O
by	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
napping	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
were	O
alarmed	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
used	O
to	O
these	O
kind	O
of	O
things	O
upon	O
that	O
road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
opportunity	O
of	O
observing	O
the	O
man	O
than	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
until	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
not	O
till	O
September	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
September	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WALTERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
coachman	O
to	O
General	O
Arabin	B-pers
,	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
Coming	O
from	O
Drayton	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
reins	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
look	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
over	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
round	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
carriage-door	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
or	O
your	O
life	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
;	O
whether	O
the	O
General	O
was	O
asleep	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
purse	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
.	O
Q.Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
if	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q.Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
forty	O
pounds	O
reward	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
now	O
in	O
General	O
Arabin	B-pers
's	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
innocent	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
12.	O
BARTHOLOMEW	B-pers
FOLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
PRETTY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3	I-place
,	I-place
Bow-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
daughter	O
to	O
my	O
desk	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
afterwards	O
missed	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
mother	O
one	O
guinea	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
n	O
w	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
mother	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lad	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
lad	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PRETTY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
desk	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
looked	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
accused	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
i	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
accused	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
newstockings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
promises	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
one	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
those	O
things	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
his	O
mother	O
the	O
change	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
HOLLIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pretty	O
is	O
my	O
uncle	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
accused	O
him	O
again	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
aunt	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
13	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
13.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PRACEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
sixty-nine	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
ferret	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
galloon	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
mitts	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
mitts	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
black	O
feather	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
black	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
persian	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
satin	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
barcelona	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
stock	O
stiffener	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
slippers	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
clogs	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
list	O
slippers	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
two	O
sans	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
lamb	O
's	O
wool	O
socks	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
diaper	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
31s	O
.	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
roses	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
straw	O
plat	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
pins	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
tape	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
eight	O
painted	O
medallions	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
china	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Comroux	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
)	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
CAMROUX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Camroux	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
9	I-place
,	I-place
Brinsley-place	I-place
,	I-place
Islington	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
various	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
boxes	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
articles	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
box	O
before	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
mitts	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
might	O
he	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
by	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
black	O
ferret	O
;	O
the	O
mitts	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
stockings	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
mark	O
has	O
been	O
picked	O
out	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
your	O
husband	O
any	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nobody	O
else	O
is	O
interested	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
TANNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
boxes	O
,	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Camroux	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
fan	O
manufactured	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
unfinished	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
in	O
which	O
fans	O
are	O
never	O
sold	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
darning	O
cotton	O
,	O
with	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
with	O
our	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
these	O
stockings	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
marks	O
have	O
been	O
picked	O
out	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
mark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
examined	O
all	O
these	O
articles	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
all	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
defence	O
to	O
her	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
Newbank	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
14.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BAYNE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
38s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
East	B-pers
India	I-pers
Company	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
15.	O
MARTIN	B-pers
BRYAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
21s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spokenburg	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SPOKENBURG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Prussian	O
:	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
my	O
ship	O
,	O
the	O
Isabella	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Towerhill	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
three	O
shillings	O
for	O
mybed	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
watch	O
underneath	O
the	O
pillow	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
property	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
waked	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
trowsers	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
these	O
trowsers	O
of	O
mine	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
hold	O
fast	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
hold	O
fast	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
trowsers	O
by	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
bit	O
put	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
ALBERT	O
FRANK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Hamburgh	O
man	O
:	O
Spokenburg	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
trowsers	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
trowsers	O
instead	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SANSUM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
parties	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
duplicate	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
wrong	O
trowsers	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
much	O
better	O
pair	O
behind	O
than	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
17	O
.	O
)	O
Publicly	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
16.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Woolwich	O
tender	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
fourpence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
quartern	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
trowsers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
end	O
and	O
she	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
pull	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
dressed	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
two	O
hours	O
looking	O
for	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
wrong	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
loose	O
brick	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
naked	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
watch-case	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
thrown	O
over	O
a	O
brick	O
wall	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
ROBERTS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Holt	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cliffe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
17.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JANE	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
sixty-six	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
14l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Green	O
,	O
milliner	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
in	O
Marybone-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
Smith	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
some	O
white	O
lace	O
,	O
she	O
purchased	O
three	O
yards	O
at	O
five	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
purchased	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
more	O
white	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
pretty	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
put	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
some	O
black	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
cut	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
thirty	O
cards	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
this	O
white	O
lace	O
and	O
black	O
lace	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
white	O
lace	O
to	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
black	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
consulted	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
patterns	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
laces	O
that	O
were	O
purchased	O
;	O
Jane	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
recommended	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
use	O
her	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
these	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
had	O
been	O
purchased	O
,	O
who	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
very	O
busy	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
that	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Jane	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
pardon	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
begged	O
her	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
to	O
satisfy	O
me	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
something	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
a	O
small	O
straw	O
basket	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
upimmediately	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
satisfy	O
myself	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
something	O
farther	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
stolen	O
some	O
lace	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
for	O
the	O
one	O
she	O
threw	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
here	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
detain	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
(	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Smith	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
bought	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
paid	O
likewise	O
for	O
a	O
remnant	O
that	O
was	O
purchased	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
altogether	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
purchasing	O
it	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
looking	O
over	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
a	O
person	O
asks	O
for	O
lace	O
,	O
we	O
always	O
shew	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
did	O
not	O
object	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
had	O
paid	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
turned	O
your	O
attention	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
do	O
nothing	O
but	O
bargain	O
for	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
told	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
people	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
been	O
asked	O
the	O
question	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
many	O
friends	O
of	O
your	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
who	O
have	O
heard	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
(	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Jane	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
Saturday	O
night	O
is	O
a	O
busy	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
fellow	O
shopmen	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Men	O
and	O
boys	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
all	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
upwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
partners	O
has	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
not	O
often	O
happen	O
that	O
lace	O
will	O
fall	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
it	O
will	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
to	O
slip	O
into	O
the	O
straw	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
DELIGHT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
seht	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
;	O
this	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
lace	O
that	O
I	O
picked	O
off	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
us	O
more	O
than	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
Jane	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
for	O
any	O
articles	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
refusal	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
bit	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	B-pers
that	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Smith	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Jane	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
49	O
.	O
)	O
Smith	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
45	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
18.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
MITCHELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
vice	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
:	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
tools	O
to	O
a	O
fresh	O
lodging	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
Gun-alley	O
:	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
the	O
tools	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
basket	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
vice	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
cupboard	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
.	O
EPHRAIM	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
vice	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
basket	O
of	O
tools	O
there	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
tools	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
19.	O
JOHN	B-pers
YOUD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
copper	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
threepence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tapper	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	O
TAPPER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
15	I-place
,	I-place
Bedford-square	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
articles	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
attempted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
detained	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
ninepence	O
in	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
20.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PROBART	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
King's-arms	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
sixpence	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
up	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
scream	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
bolted	O
the	O
back-door	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sheets	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
sheets	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
gardener	O
's	O
apron	O
tied	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
sheets	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sheets	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SLOPUM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
wet	O
the	O
sheets	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
maid-servant	O
to	O
dry	O
them	O
privately	O
.	O
Harper	O
.	O
The	O
sheets	O
were	O
dry	O
and	O
warm	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
42	O
.	O
)	O
confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
21.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PARR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
27s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
telescope	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Macleish	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MACLEISH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
brother	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
2	I-place
,	I-place
Bow-street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
in	O
the	O
bed-room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
a	O
maid-servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
foreman	O
;	O
we	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
our	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
then	O
missed	O
the	O
silver	O
one	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
wicked	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
watches	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
applied	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
detained	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watches	O
before	O
Justice	O
Floud	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
COLLIER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wharfinger	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Compton-street	O
,	O
Islington	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
privately	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back-parlour	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
violently	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
lost	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
sister	O
of	O
two	O
watches	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
duplicates	O
for	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
extremely	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
me	O
to	O
intercede	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Equitable	O
Assurance-office	O
for	O
Servants	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
sister	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
printer	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ACKLEM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bedford-street	O
:	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
belief	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
telescope	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
twelve	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MORRITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Acklem	O
.	O
)	O
In	O
what	O
name	O
was	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
pledged	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
DRUID	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sensible	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
22.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BATES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
servant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
his	O
employment	O
,	O
take	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
30l	O
.	O
for	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
employer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
fraudulently	O
did	O
embezzle	O
and	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
ten	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
fifteen	O
seven-shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
twenty	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
sixty	O
sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
hundred	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EMERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
conduct	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
entrusted	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
employed	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
above	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
near	O
three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
receiving	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
course	O
of	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
goods	O
sold	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
delivered	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
our	O
customers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
any	O
goods	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
out	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
's	O
servant	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
absolutely	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
course	O
of	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
this	O
money	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
entrusted	O
by	O
your	O
father	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.Constantly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
general	O
authority	O
from	O
your	O
father	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
customers	O
,	O
and	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Without	O
any	O
particular	O
order	O
from	O
your	O
father	O
to	O
receive	O
those	O
particular	O
sums	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
accounted	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
any	O
money	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
account	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
that	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
noon	O
upon	O
business	O
to	O
an	O
inn	O
in	O
Friday-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
return	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
before	O
five	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
Gloucester-place	O
,	O
Portman-square	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
from	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
begged	O
my	O
pardon	O
for	O
staying	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
then	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
truck	O
of	O
goods	O
that	O
stood	O
loaded	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
towards	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
go	O
out	O
towards	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
almost	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
truck	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
absconded	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
street	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
likely	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
take	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Crown-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
had	O
staid	O
out	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
watch	O
chain	O
hanging	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
that	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
up	O
his	O
accounts	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
general	O
conduct	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
get	O
any	O
account	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
either	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
accounts	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
to	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
muttered	O
something	O
about	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Bank	O
notes	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
apparently	O
quite	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
gave	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Bank	O
notes	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
embezzling	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Queen-square	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
writting	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
clerk	O
was	O
not	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
examination	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
magistrate	O
himself	O
took	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
contended	O
that	O
it	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
in	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
over-ruled	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
also	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
finally	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
subsequent	O
to	O
my	O
seeing	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
recollect	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
two	O
pound	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
one	O
pound	O
notes	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hired	O
by	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
tell	O
us	O
for	O
what	O
purpose	O
was	O
he	O
hired	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
carry	O
a	O
large	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
goods	O
out	O
to	O
different	O
customers	O
at	O
the	O
West	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
attend	O
occasionally	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q.Were	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
hiring	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
that	O
carrying	O
out	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
without	O
a	O
particular	O
direction	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
customers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
depended	O
on	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
customers	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
chose	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
returning	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
muttered	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
out	O
his	O
accounts	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
them	O
up	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
day	O
's	O
business	O
was	O
over	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
return	O
home	O
that	O
evening	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
watch	O
cost	O
,	O
from	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
passed	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
five	O
pounds	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
truck	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
attempted	O
o	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
sufficiency	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
growing	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
produce	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
tap-room	O
table	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
two	O
two	O
pound	O
notes	O
,	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
five	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
tore	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
observation	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
go	O
home	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
truck	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
him	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Emerson	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Emerson	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
note	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
being	O
drunk	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
truck	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
three	O
two	O
pound	O
Bank	O
notes	O
;	O
three	O
one	O
pound	O
Bank	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
watch	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
37	O
,	O
Gloucester-place	O
,	O
Portman-square	O
;	O
she	O
dealt	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Emerson	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
done	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Emerson	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
used	O
o	O
pay	O
him	O
once	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
from	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
to	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
amount	O
altogether	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
paid	O
him	O
any	O
bill	O
since	O
August	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
my	O
governor	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
23.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KALLAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Glazbrook	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Glazbrook	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
paper	O
with	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
paper	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
another	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
missed	O
two	O
pair	O
from	O
another	O
part	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
Iovertook	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
kirb-stone	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
