TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1799	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
RICHARD	O
CARR	O
GLYN	O
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RAMSEY	I-pers
,	O
AND	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1799	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CARR	I-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
LLOYD	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
KENYON	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Purse	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Norfolk	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pegrum	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gummer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
Hezekiah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Calcott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kensitt	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sawer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Venn	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchinson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Hezekiah	B-pers
Denby	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
202.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SEYMOUR	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
CHARLES	I-pers
SEYMOUR	I-pers
WILSHIRE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Isaac	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Counts	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
uttering	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
a	O
like	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Masterman	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Mildred	I-pers
,	O
Gerard	B-pers
Scorer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Coach	B-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
,	I-place
Haslewood-court	I-place
,	I-place
Blue-anchor-alley	I-place
,	I-place
Bunhill-row	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whitbread	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
note	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
forgery	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
)	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
1067	O
.	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
Messrs.	O
Masterman	O
,	O
Peters	O
,	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
bankers	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
1l	O
.	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1798	O
.	O
Entd	O
.	O
T.	O
Walker	O
.	O
Signed	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
you	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whitbread	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
returned	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DOCKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Whitbread	O
's	O
;	O
Strange	O
paid	O
me	O
this	O
note	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
Down	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
bankers	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
forgery	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
course	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Strange	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLOSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Masterman	O
and	O
Co.	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
such	O
an	O
account	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
some	O
enquiries	O
concerning	O
these	O
notes	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Strange	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
the	O
Public-office	O
,	O
Lambeth-street	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
six	O
of	O
these	O
notes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
necessaries	O
to	O
take	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
voyage	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
man	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Strange	O
)	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
pay	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
203.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SEYMOUR	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
CHARLES	I-pers
SEYMOUR	I-pers
WILSHIRE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
George	B-pers
Paulling	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Counts	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
uttering	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
a	O
like	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Masterman	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Mildred	I-pers
,	O
Gerard	B-pers
Scorer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PAULLING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
,	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Portsmouth	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
Admiral	O
Dunean	O
's	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
clerk	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
)	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
1063	O
.	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
Messrs.	O
Masterman	O
,	O
Peters	O
,	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
banker	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1798	O
.	O
Entd	O
.	O
T.	O
Walker	O
.	O
Signed	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLOSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Masterman	O
and	O
Co.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
account	O
with	O
John	O
Hart	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
know	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Lambeth-street	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
these	O
notes	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
52	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
uttering	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
204.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
and	O
MARIA	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
a	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
Privy-gardens	O
and	O
Parliament-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
standing	O
together	O
;	O
Green	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Burne	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
in	O
our	O
regiment	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
me	O
in	O
discourse	O
till	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
straight	O
towards	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Great	O
George-street	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
not	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
conduct	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
serjeant	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
back	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
prosecute	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
half-a-guinea	O
if	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
that	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
fight	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
opportunity	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
205.	O
HENRY	B-pers
PICKET	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Clarke	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
Tothillfields	B-place
Bridewell	I-place
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
hasty	O
word	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
demanded	O
what	O
they	O
called	O
garnish	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
;	O
Picket	O
then	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
covered	O
my	O
eyes	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
still	O
kept	O
ramshackling	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
face	O
was	O
uncovered	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
Brown	O
,	O
Picket	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
then	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
afterwards	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Brown	O
kicked	O
me	O
five	O
times	O
through	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
blinded	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
206.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
of	O
canvas	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COUTLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
sail-maker	O
,	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
We	O
lost	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
bolt	O
of	O
canvas	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
bolt	O
consists	O
of	O
from	O
forty	O
to	O
forty-three	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
this	O
piece	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BIGGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Near	O
upon	O
twenty-one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
nine	O
months	O
past	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
and	O
he	O
take	O
any	O
canvas	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
piece	O
of	O
canvas	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
then	O
;	O
very	O
near	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
canvas	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
shelf	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
measure	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
stand	O
to	O
measure	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
caught	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
canvas	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
himself	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
two	O
skains	O
of	O
twine	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
measured	O
the	O
canvas	O
by	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
measured	O
twelve	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
five	O
shillings	O
for	O
my	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
home	O
afterwards	O
-	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
your	O
master	O
taxed	O
you	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JENKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Biggs	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
that	O
occasioned	O
me	O
to	O
question	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
led	O
to	O
this	O
discovery	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
LADD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Marine	O
Police-office	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
at	O
our	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
promises	O
made	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
threats	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
William	O
West	O
,	O
acknowledges	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
taking	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
piece	O
of	O
canvas	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
paid	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
he	O
accompanied	O
Biggs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jenkins	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
where	O
Biggs	O
put	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
canvas	O
into	O
his	O
bag	O
,	O
but	O
says	O
,	O
Biggs	O
carried	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
canvas	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
Biggs	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
bag	O
;	O
while	O
Biggs	O
returned	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
measured	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
Biggs	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
39	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
207.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KIRK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
burglariously	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
men	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
16s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HARE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
431	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
hatter's-shop	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
half-a-dozen	O
hats	O
,	O
four	O
men	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
your	O
candles	O
lighted	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Corrock	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
hats	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
hats	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
running	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
path	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
run	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
him.	O
(	O
Mr	O
.	O
Corrock	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
hats	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
hats	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
the	O
hats	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
behind	O
me	O
till	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
14	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
208.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HERROD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
game	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
five	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gasquet	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GASQUET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hoxton	B-place
Town	I-place
:	O
Between	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
game	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
hens	O
from	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
they	O
been	O
found	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
produced	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Guest	O
,	O
another	O
officer	O
,	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
riot	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
quartered	O
,	O
in	O
sermon-time	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
called	O
me	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
stealing	O
some	O
fowls	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
bag	O
containing	O
five	O
hens	O
and	O
a	O
cock	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
New-prison	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
fowls	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
fowls	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Old	O
Ford	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
fowls	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
I	O
produced	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gasquet	O
in	O
their	O
feathers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Gasquet	O
)	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
fowls	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
fowls	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
I	O
described	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
full	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
209.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
gander	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
three	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dyson	I-pers
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
DYSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tottenham	B-place
High-cross	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
geese	O
and	O
a	O
gander	O
,	O
from	O
an	O
out-house	O
upon	O
my	O
premises	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
there	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Newington	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harper	O
's	O
at	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
mornings	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
upon	O
the	O
Stamford-hill	O
Trust	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
past	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
move	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
hare	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
brother	O
watchman	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
there	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
stupid	O
and	O
drunk	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
they	O
seem	O
like	O
geese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
this	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Dyson	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
miles	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Cheshunt	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
White-lion	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
old	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
should	O
send	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
coaches	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
liked	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HARPAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
belonging	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
inquiry	O
of	O
the	O
waggoners	O
that	O
went	O
that	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dyson	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
his	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
rather	O
too	O
much	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
48	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
210.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BEACHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
a	O
cotton	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Union-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
underneath	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
not	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
me	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
family	O
but	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
myself	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
14	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
211.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MAKWAY	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
MACKVOY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
seventy	O
pounds	O
of	O
ground	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Augustus	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gabell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
LOADER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
horse-keeper	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
Gabell	O
,	O
and	O
Lonsdale	O
,	O
sugar-baker	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
Spitalfields	B-place
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
guineas	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
to	O
myself	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
devulged	O
my	O
mind	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
appointed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
premises	O
;	O
he	O
met	O
methe	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
joins	O
the	O
sugar-house	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
then	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
mill-house	O
where	O
they	O
grind	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
emptied	O
two	O
baskets	O
of	O
sugar	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hold	O
the	O
bag	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
immediately	O
walked	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
stable-door	O
where	O
he	O
entered	O
in	O
at	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
get	O
above	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
given	O
a	O
hint	O
to	O
any	O
persons	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lonsdale	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
ground	O
sugar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
in	O
quantity	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LONSDALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Augustus	O
Stevens	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gabell	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
formerly	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
any	O
information	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
entered	O
the	O
premises	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pass	O
from	O
the	O
stables	O
towards	O
the	O
mill-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
about	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
of	O
ground	O
sugar	O
.	O
Q.	O
Whereabout	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
worth	O
about	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
32	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
212.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
VANDERPUMP	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
mould-frame	O
for	O
making	O
candles	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
twelve	O
candles	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Limbery	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LIMBERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tallowchandler	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Spital-square	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
mould	O
frame	O
full	O
of	O
candles	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
making	O
mould	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
using	O
the	O
frame	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rustling	O
;	O
I	O
went-out	O
and	O
caught	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
frame	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
frame	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
candles	O
sell	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
senseless	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Limbery	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
-	O
JARVIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Limbery	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
staggered	O
about	O
,	O
seemingly	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
make	O
sham	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
candles	O
were	O
then	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
frame	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
candles	O
and	O
the	O
frame	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
mud	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
charge	O
was	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
57	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
213.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SULLY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
38s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRATER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
William	O
Prater	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Prater	O
's	O
counter	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
small	O
man	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
linen	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
cloth	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Prater	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
another	O
person	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
took	O
Hanson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
-	O
HANSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Police	O
,	O
in	O
Hatton-garden	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
from	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Clarke	O
)	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
speak	O
with	O
certainty	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Hanson	O
)	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
that	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
cloth	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Clarke	O
)	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
Hanson	O
being	O
the	O
thief	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
214.	O
MARY	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
two	O
blue	O
jackets	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
two	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
trowsers	O
.	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
kerseymere	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
place	O
,	O
my	O
landlady	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chest	O
bottom	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
broke	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
my	O
chest	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
HOWES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
last	O
witness	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
chest	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Sullivan	O
's	O
chest	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
very	O
likely	O
Mrs.	O
Sullivan	O
has	O
taken	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
SMITH	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
property	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
1l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
8	O
1/2d	O
.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Sullivan	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
told	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
struck	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
43	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
215.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HART	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
tub	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
and	O
fifty-five	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
49s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Badman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BADMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-street	B-place
,	I-place
Finsbury-square	I-place
;	O
it	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
and	O
glazier	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
Long-alley	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
firkin	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
Broker-row	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Broad-street-buildings	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
patroles	O
and	O
one	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STOCKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-ward	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Harrison	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Long-alley	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
threw	O
the	O
firkin	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
New	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
firkin	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Badman	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
firkin	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
butter	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Forty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
216.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
and	O
assault	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
upon	O
Richard-Joseph	B-pers
Coltherup	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
paper	O
hatbox	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
five	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
.	O
RICHARD-JOSEPH	B-pers
COLTHERUP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
band	O
box	O
and	O
five	O
live	O
pigeons	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Chalk-farm	B-place
I	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
apparently	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
worse	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
shoved	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
pigeons	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
colour	O
for	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
robbery	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
217.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BUSHNELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
thirty-four	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
34s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dorey	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sibthorpe	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DOREY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
porter	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
man	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Absolom	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	B-place
Green	I-place
Man	I-place
and	I-place
Still	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Oxford-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
flat	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SIBTHORPE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
flat	O
of	O
butter	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dorey	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
till	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
flat	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
butter	O
would	O
not	O
keep	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
flat	O
)	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ABSOLOM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
flat	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
flats	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
flat	O
of	O
butter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Sibthorpe	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
butter	O
consigned	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
inside	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
sing	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
)	O
.	O
Publickly	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
218.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PILGRIM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
COPELAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
shawl	O
taken	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Richard	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
linen-draper	O
s.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SIMCOX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
box-maker	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Copeland	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
crossed	O
over	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Copeland	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
shawl	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
stood	O
within	O
side	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
across	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Copeland	O
's	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pattens	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Paul's-alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Copeland	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GALLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Copeland	O
and	O
Galley	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
shawl	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shawl	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
shawl	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
along	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
loose	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
shawl	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
brother	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
219.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HEBDEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thompson	B-pers
Bonar	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SEXTIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Cornhill	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
somewhere	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
print-shop	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
walked	O
away	O
towards	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
a	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Bonar	O
's	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
THOMPSON	B-pers
BONAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
print-shop	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
nearly	O
opposite	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
touched	O
upon	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
to	O
look	O
round	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
collared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
-	O
CHURCH	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bonar	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bonar	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
only	O
five	O
weeks	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
parts	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
220.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GABB	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
eleven	O
ounces	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
commodore	O
at	O
the	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
superintend	O
the	O
labourers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
employed	O
about	O
eight	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
tier	O
of	O
the	O
warehouses	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
door	O
go	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
wondered	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
search	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
concealing	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
turn	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
commodore	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
yet	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
heard	O
something	O
dropping	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
some	O
tea	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
plundering	O
some	O
chests	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
some	O
tea	O
upon	O
some	O
paper	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
and	O
prayed	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
tea	O
found	O
loose	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat-pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
quantity	O
found	O
underneath	O
him	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nine	O
ounces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
tea	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
.	O
-	O
NOBLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
locker	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
some	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
34	O
)	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
221.	O
JACOB	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
and	O
DAVID	B-pers
BELASCO	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
three	O
hides	O
of	O
tanned	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tanner	O
,	O
at	O
Ryegate	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
two	O
bundles	O
of	O
leather	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hickes	O
,	O
the	O
carrier	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
Leadenhall	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
hides	O
of	O
tanned	O
leather	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	O
Salloway	O
,	O
leather-factor	O
,	O
Leadenhall	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
delivered	O
them	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
your	O
men	O
here	O
who	O
delivered	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HICKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
tanned	O
leather	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Salloway	I-pers
,	O
leather-factor	O
,	O
Leadenhall	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
Leadenhall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
porter	O
read	O
the	O
direction	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
Leadenhall	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
two	O
bundles	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Salloway	I-pers
,	O
Leadenhall	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
the	B-place
Red-lion	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Leadenhall-market	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
some	O
more	O
leather	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
usually	O
put	O
leather	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
watchman	O
stands	O
;	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
that	O
spot	O
again	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
bundle	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
market	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
appointed	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
leather	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
master	O
is	O
answerable	O
for	O
leather	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
act	O
as	O
servant	O
to	O
Salloway	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hickes	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
Hickes	O
employ	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
FERRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
Isaacs	O
was	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
leather	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hat	O
on	O
;	O
Belasco	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
bag	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
hat	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
besides	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
leather	O
prevented	O
him	O
from	O
wearing	O
a	O
hat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
snatch	O
at	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
leather	O
almost	O
upon	O
my	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
;	O
Belasco	O
also	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Armstrong	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
Isaacs	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Peach	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
leather	O
was	O
dropped	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
that	O
Belasco	O
had	O
dropped	O
;	O
Isaacs	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
leather	O
publicly	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Without	O
any	O
concealment	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
sack	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observation	O
of	O
Belasco	O
's	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
tan	O
of	O
the	O
leather	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
leather	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
directed	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Salloway	I-pers
,	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
Belasco	O
's	O
back	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
carrying	O
the	O
leather	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
another	O
man	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
marked	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
leather	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
23	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Belasco	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
222.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SEDGLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
two	O
wooden	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
168	O
pieces	O
of	O
copper	O
money	O
,	O
called	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
474	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
farthings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
60	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
High-street	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
my	O
premises	O
were	O
then	O
all	O
safe	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
my	O
premises	O
were	O
then	O
all	O
safe	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
tiling	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
slaughter-house	O
;	O
the	O
slaughter-house	O
and	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
roof	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
farthings	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
lad	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
officers	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
neighbour	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
what	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
questions	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
want	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
for	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
from	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Arrow-alley	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
in	O
Alie-street	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
some	O
halfpence	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
count	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two-pence	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
expression	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
halfpence	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
altogether	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Somewhere	O
about	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
penny	O
pieces	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
halfpence	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
lad	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
old	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
lad	O
is	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
fifteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
apprehended	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
this	O
had	O
taken	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
minded	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
plenty	O
of	O
time	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
any	O
conversation	O
took	O
place	O
between	O
the	O
officers	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
forty	O
pounds	O
reward	O
for	O
burglary	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
OSMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witness	O
ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
)	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
and	O
another	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Osmond	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Smith	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
relate	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
hearing	O
,	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
or	O
worse	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Osmond	O
might	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
(	O
Osmond	O
called	O
in	O
again	O
)	O
.	O
Osmond	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
halfpence	O
and	O
penny	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
such	O
an	O
expression	O
as	O
this-	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
yourself	O
from	O
being	O
hanged	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
two-pence	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
:	O
Griffiths	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
halfpence	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
hid	O
under	O
a	O
stone	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
Griffiths	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
missed	O
telling	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
which	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
cellar	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Smith	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
Griffiths	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
something	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
referred	O
you	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
whether	O
his	O
father	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
his	O
reference	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
his	O
mother	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
while	O
Griffiths	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
drawers	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
coal	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
exactly	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
directed	O
me	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
you	O
directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
his	O
father	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Police-officers	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
some	O
money	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
under	O
a	O
stone	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
hid	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fit	O
exactly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
223.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Miles	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
MILES	B-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
woollen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul's-church-yard	I-place
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
livery	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
wrote	O
three	O
words	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
directly	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
cloth	O
immediately	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
into	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Queen's-head	O
,	O
in	O
Queen's-head-alley	O
,	O
Newgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
lying	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
round	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
called	O
the	O
waiter	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
for	O
those	O
men	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Waller	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
collar	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
landlady	O
had	O
set	O
him	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
her	O
over	O
almost	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
sitting	O
there	O
would	O
not	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
only	O
detained	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WALLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
St.	O
Paul's-church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
were	O
after	O
something	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
off	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
this	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
instantaneously	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
yellow	O
cloth	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
then	O
joined	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
pass	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
through	O
Cannon-alley	O
,	O
across	O
Paternoster-row	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
Cannon-alley	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
companion	O
to	O
cover	O
the	O
cloth	O
with	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
pulled	O
out	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
cover	O
the	O
remainder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Queen's-head	O
,	O
in	O
Queen's-headalley	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
some	O
cloth	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
appeared	O
confused	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
cloth	O
;	O
the	O
waiter	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
smallest	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
cloth	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
piece	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
matched	O
exactly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
224.	O
ANN	B-pers
GROCOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
thirty-six	O
penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
hundred	O
and	O
eighty-eight	O
halfpence	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
KETTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Golden	I-place
Fleece	I-place
,	I-place
Well-court	I-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
near	O
three	O
months	O
:	O
a	O
neighbour	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
some	O
copper	O
money	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
halfpence	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
of	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Forbham	O
.	O
WILLIAM-EDWARD	B-pers
FORBHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
some	O
halfpence	O
)	O
.	O
Kettle	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
halfpence	O
that	O
I	O
marked	O
.	O
Forbham	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
small	O
shop	O
for	O
greens	O
and	O
oysters	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
one	O
night	O
brought	O
me	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
and	O
penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
her	O
silver	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
counted	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
sixpenny-worths	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
good	O
and	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
from	O
that	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
mark	O
some	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
marked	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
day	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
ten-pence	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
marked	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
money	O
-	O
See	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
your	O
Lordship	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
my	O
friends	O
live	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
twenty-one	O
shillingsworth	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Forbham	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
pass	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
certainly	O
did	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
20	O
.	O
)	O
Privately	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
225.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DOYLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
three	O
glass	O
tumblers	O
,	O
value	O
9d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BACCHUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	O
Ogden	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
glass	O
manufacturer	O
s	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
tumblers	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
suspicious	O
situation	O
upon	O
our	O
premises	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
tumblers	O
,	O
marked	O
them	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
situation	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
these	O
tumblers	O
remained	O
till	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
our	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
thegoods	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
empty	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
tumblers	O
that	O
I	O
marked	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
service	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
three	O
and	O
twenty	O
years	O
with	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
as	O
warehouseman	O
,	O
stowing	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bacchus	O
made	O
him	O
deliver	O
the	O
tumblers	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
tumblers	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
50	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
226.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CONNOR	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BUSTED	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
nine	O
pounds	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sabine	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Waghorn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sabine	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ventris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Deare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
JONAS	B-pers
DEARE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
Turnpike	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
leading	O
to	O
our	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
is	O
your	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Galleyquay	B-place
;	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Connor	O
,	O
was	O
filling	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
his	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dropped	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
Connor	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
pulled	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
room	O
to	O
the	O
loop-hole	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
throw	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
loop-hole	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
we	O
both	O
sell	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
trying	O
to	O
throw	O
me	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
in	O
hold	O
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Deare	I-pers
,	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
detained	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
more	O
assistance	O
;	O
an	O
officer	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
officer	O
had	O
taken	O
charge	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
picked	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
opened	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
account	O
for	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
Connor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
matter	O
that	O
would	O
pick	O
a	O
lock	O
,	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
a	O
horse-picker	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
officer	O
unlock	O
the	O
lock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
Connor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
Busted	O
dropped	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
this	O
warehouse	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
goods	O
are	O
under	O
our	O
locks	O
:	O
Joseph	O
Sabine	O
,	O
Robert	O
Waghorn	O
,	O
John	O
Sabine	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Knight	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ventris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	O
Deare	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Baker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
yourselves	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
commonly	O
called	O
gangsmen	O
.	O
JONAS	B-pers
DEARE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Quay	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Deare	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Deare	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
Conner	O
;	O
Busted	O
had	O
just	O
passed	O
Mr.	O
Deare	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Connor	O
taking	O
sugar	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
chucking	O
it	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Capsail-room	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
Busted	O
,	O
begged	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
Connor	O
resisted	O
Mr.	O
Deare	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
chucked	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
stairs	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
sugar	O
and	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Deare	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
sugar	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
warehouse	O
;	O
we	O
weighed	O
the	O
hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
deficient	O
.	O
Connor	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
Busted	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
.	O
Busted	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Connor	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
22	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Busted	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
Jail	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
227.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
takingfrom	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
JARVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Turned	O
of	O
sixteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
James	O
Jarvis	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
your	O
father	O
's	O
family	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
at	O
Longford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
All	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Drayton	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
bringing	O
these	O
things	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
through	O
a	O
gap	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
bonnet	O
,	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
cap	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
gap	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
gap	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
chucked	O
him	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
things	O
ever	O
returned	O
to	O
you	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
JARVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
daughter	O
lives	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
her	O
behaviour	O
-	O
has	O
it	O
been	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
modest	O
,	O
decent	O
,	O
good	O
girl	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
can	O
say	O
otherwise	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EAST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
beyond	O
Drayton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Uxbridge	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
girl	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
East	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Shropshire	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
KENYON	O
.	O
228.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WISE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Christiana	B-pers
Govin	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
her	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christiana	O
.	O
CHRISTIANA	B-pers
GOVIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
26	I-place
,	I-place
Fox's-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
china-shop	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cheese	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
fastened	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
maid	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
cheese	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
cheese	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
heavy	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
any	O
further	O
.	O
Q.	O
Whereabout	O
was	O
this	O
cheese	O
before	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Lying	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
cheese	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Govin	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
cheese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
deal	O
in	O
cheeses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
Yes	O
.	O
MARY-ANN	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Going	O
on	O
fifteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
is	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Govin	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
cheese	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
or	O
bolt	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Govin	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
cheese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Brown	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
cheese	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Mrs.	O
Govin	O
deseribed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Abell	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
paviour	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Govin	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
apprehended	O
before	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
expected	O
to	O
apprehend	O
another	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Brown	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Abell	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
pay-table	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
there	O
till	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
uncle	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
25	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommend	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
229.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
seven	O
pounds	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
flour	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
RUSSEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tower-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
journeyman	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
got	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
learned	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
attend	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
men	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Lawrence	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
when	O
he	O
detected	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
four	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
seven	O
pounds	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
FORSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
spirituous	O
liquors	O
,	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
:	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
mentioning	O
his	O
suspicions	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
searched	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
flour	O
secreted	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
between	O
the	O
plaister	O
of	O
the	O
ceiling	O
and	O
the	O
shop	O
floor	O
:	O
after	O
making	O
this	O
discovery	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
wished	O
to	O
ascertain	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
his	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
bread	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
