TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1799	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
RICHARD	O
CARR	O
GLYN	O
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RAMSEY	I-pers
,	O
AND	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1799	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CARR	I-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	B-pers
GROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cabe	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Bassel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Moffatt	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dighton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fernel	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Hale	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Derard	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Tongue	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fetwell	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nunn	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Longsdale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perigale	I-pers
,	O
Follierd	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
264.	O
ANN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
metal	O
gilt	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rollins	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
ROLLINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	O
Rollins	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Robertson	O
's	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
20	I-place
,	I-place
Carlisle-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho-square	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
coachman	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
separated	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
metal	O
gilt	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
sofa	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
for	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
Wood	O
stock-street	O
,	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Draper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Draper	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
seal	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
seal	O
)	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DRAPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
1st	O
regiment	O
of	O
foot	O
guards	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
watch	O
in	O
exchange	O
from	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
May's-buildings	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
:	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
Southmolton-street	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
pulling	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
nice	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
up	O
stairs	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wished	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
changed	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
this	O
watch	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
last	O
produced	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
seal	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Draper	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
seal	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
that	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
watch-maker	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
265.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ANN	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
DANIEL	I-pers
MINES	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goodliffe	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
another	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goodliffe	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOODLIFFE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Bluecoat-fields	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
;	O
my	O
family	O
consists	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
watches	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
lifted	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
daughter	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watches	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Windsor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
's	O
,	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
at	O
the	O
Shadwell	O
Police-office	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mills	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
double	O
press-gang	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
stop	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
press-gang	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Angel	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
just	O
inside	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
seven	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
hung-over	O
the	O
fire-place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
my	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
one	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
watches	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
ship	O
at	O
Deptford	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
the	O
Flora	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
and	O
hid	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
directed	O
him	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
the	O
pressgangs	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
GOODLIFFE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mills	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
enquired	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
father	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
press-gang	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
indeed	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
corner-cupboard	O
,	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
sugar-bason	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
but	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
my	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
game-keeper	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
breaking	O
the	O
wall	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
bed's-head	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
press-gang	O
in	O
the	O
Rope-walk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
there	O
to	O
hide	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
no	O
press-gang	O
about	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
stable-door	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
breaking	O
in	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Staines	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
run	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
in	O
his	O
jacket-pockets	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watches	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
button	O
which	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
broke	O
off	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
had	O
his	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mills	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Bevan	O
who	O
was	O
examined	O
yesterday	O
at	O
Ratcliffe	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Public-office	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Goodliffe	O
and	O
his	O
daughter	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
lad	O
that	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
on	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Public-office	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Brown	O
has	O
related	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
THORNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mines	O
,	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Goodliffe	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
the	O
minute	O
hand	O
.	O
Mills	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
lad	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
month	O
's	O
advanced	O
wages	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
cast	O
away	O
going	O
upon	O
the	O
Flats	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mines	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Mills	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
12	O
.	O
)	O
Mines	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mills	O
,	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
266.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
paper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
silk	O
spencers	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
net	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
four	O
Norwich	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
four	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
a	O
half	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
twenty-six	O
coloured	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
eight	O
half	O
coloured	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
29s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Southampton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
dress	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
haberdashery	O
and	O
millinery	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
shop-door	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
breakfast-things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
ma'am	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
tea-tray	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
cired	O
likewise	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
walking	O
up	O
Maiden-lane	O
,	O
rather	O
with	O
a	O
quick	O
pace	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
-	O
that	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
-	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
was	O
alarmed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Maiden-lane	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stokes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
turn	O
down	O
a	O
narrow	O
court	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left-hand	O
,	O
in	O
Maiden-lane	O
;	O
in	O
turning	O
that	O
corner	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
Stokes	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
stand	O
close	O
at	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
folded	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
those	O
spencers	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
that	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Above	O
seven	O
pounds	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
PEARSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Wright	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
this	O
box	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
ran	O
out	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Stokes	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STOKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
,	O
an	O
accoutrement-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Maiden-lane	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bullen-court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
forced	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
a	O
second	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
box	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
equivocation	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
severe	O
reprimand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
17	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
267.	O
AARON	B-pers
BARNET	I-pers
and	O
ASHER	B-pers
BARNET	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
old	O
iron	O
screws	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
REVEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
take	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
throw	O
some	O
iron	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
aprons	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
of	O
iron	O
screws	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
marks	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PIPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Revel	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Revel	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
big	O
one	O
's	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
stopped	O
them	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
JENKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
little	O
boys	O
and	O
the	O
baker	O
going	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
iron	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
Asher	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
fatherless	O
and	O
motherless	O
:	O
my	O
mother	O
is	O
in	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
abroad	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
starving	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
in	O
stables	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
starving	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
268.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WILD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
13d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dowding	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
DOWDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
High-street	B-place
Mary-le-bonne	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
bustle	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pot-stealer	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
fetched	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pot	O
standing	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DIGNUM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Palace	O
row	O
,	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
High-street	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
up	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
alarmed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
screamed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
children	O
screamed	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
four	O
pints	O
and	O
one	O
quart	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
pots	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Dowding	O
.	O
This	O
pint	O
pot	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
269.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
BROOKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
a	O
feather	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
feather	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
copper	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
-	O
MAY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
York-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
lodging-house	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
at	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
she	O
continued	O
so	O
two	O
months	O
and	O
two	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
paid	O
me	O
any	O
rent	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
herself	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Grimshaw	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
five	O
days	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
Grimshaw	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
but	O
one	O
for	O
stripping	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
London	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GRIMSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
light-infantry	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Brookes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
takeany	O
thing	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
took	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
270.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
tallow	O
candles	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Maguire	I-pers
.	O
LAWRENCE	B-pers
MAGUIRE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler's-shop	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
room	O
adjoining	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
and	O
moving	O
some	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
reached	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
candles	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twelve	O
quarter-of-a-pound	O
candles	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
hanging	O
upon	O
hooks	O
for	O
shew	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUNCOMB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
special	O
constables	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Baldwin's-gardens	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
,	O
deformed	O
woman	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
look	O
at	O
that	O
man	O
stealing	O
the	O
candles	O
;	O
accordingly	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
passage	O
take	O
this	O
broach	O
with	O
the	O
candles	O
upon	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
hooks	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
turning	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
dropped	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
in	O
Hatton-garden	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
Longden	O
.	O
(	O
Mary	O
Hickes	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
her	O
recogniznce	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
sall	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
candles	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
24	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
271.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MADDE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slaymaker	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
wooden	O
broaches	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
and	O
eight	O
pounds	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SLAYMAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tallowchandler	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Red-cross	B-place
street	I-place
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
flap	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
window	O
shuts	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
open	O
10c	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
cellar	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
under	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
flap	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
perceived	O
something	O
move	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
stepped	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Michael	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
broaches	O
of	O
candles	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
flap	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
pounds	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
pounds	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
broaches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
day-light	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dusk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
discern	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
face	O
or	O
buttons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Michael	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
damaged	O
ones	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
or	O
threat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
VANDEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Slaymaker	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
candles	O
were	O
there	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
empty	O
broaches	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
flap	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
he	O
not	O
then	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
without	O
opening	O
the	O
flap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
flap	O
broke	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
candles	O
off	O
three	O
broaches	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
broach	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
candles	O
on	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BROOKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
candles	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
are	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
falling	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
the	O
candles	O
down	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
17	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
272.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CADMAN	I-pers
was	O
indictedfor	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
forty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
used	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
RUTTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
46	I-place
,	I-place
Newtoner's-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
two	O
privies	O
,	O
they	O
joined	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
forty	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
HUGH	B-pers
GARRET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rutter	O
's	O
:	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taking	O
the	O
lead	O
off	O
the	O
privies	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
close	O
through	O
Cross-lane	O
into	O
Parker's-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
watchman	O
's	O
box	O
stood	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
crossed	O
into	O
King-street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
man	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HUNGERFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
lead	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
lead	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
possession	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Rutter	O
.	O
This	O
lead	O
came	O
off	O
my	O
premises	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
52	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
273.	O
SARAH	B-pers
MANN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Macartney	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MACARTNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
shirts	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Jews-row	B-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
Turks-row	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Dorman	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
washing	O
for	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
shirts	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
MACARTNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
shirts	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
STORMONT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
shirt	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
shirt	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
)	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
28	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
274.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HAYLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
painted	O
floor-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Christopher-James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher-Daniel	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
)	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OSBORN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tripe-man	O
in	O
Mile-end-road	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
two	O
floor-cloths	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
room	O
enough	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
either	O
lost	O
or	O
forgot	O
the	O
directions	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
to	O
Oxford-street	O
and	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
several	O
neighbours	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
's	O
manufactory	O
,	O
at	O
Hackney	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Hackney	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
pay-table	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
called	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
recollected	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
tripe-shop	O
in	O
Mileend-road	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
floor	O
cloth	O
away	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
recollected	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
form	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
day-light	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
suspicious	O
in	O
his	O
conduct	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
floor-cloths	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
certainly	O
should	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
the	O
floor-cloths	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
exposed	O
to	O
the	O
view	O
ofevery	O
body	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
room	O
for	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
pay-table	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
sitting	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
recollected	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
floor-cloth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
behaviour	O
to	O
induce	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
least	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER-DANIEL	O
HAYES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
firm	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Christopher-James	O
Hayes	O
,	O
and	O
Christopher-Daniel	O
Hayes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
floor-cloth	O
;	O
was	O
that	O
manufactured	O
by	O
yourselves	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
stamped	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
corner	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
words	O
``	O
Spence	O
,	O
sold	O
to	O
Spence	O
,	O
of	O
Walthamstow	O
;	O
''	O
it	O
was	O
intended	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
but	O
never	O
delivered	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
his	O
property	O
when	O
delivered	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
your	O
employ	O
upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
those	O
places	O
where	O
these	O
cloths	O
were	O
deposited	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
stole	O
them	O
if	O
he	O
chose	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Eight	O
or	O
nine	O
pounds	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
grinder	O
of	O
colours	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
deranged	O
in	O
his	O
intellects	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
observe	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
frantickness	O
or	O
odd	O
conduct	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
floor-cloth	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
at	O
Hackney	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
warehouse	O
at	O
Hackney	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
DILLON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
past	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
during	O
these	O
fourteen	O
years	O
past	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
last	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
tell	O
the	O
Jury	O
what	O
state	O
of	O
mind	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
exactly	O
steady	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
back	O
as	O
formerly	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
what	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
always	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
intimate	O
with	O
him	O
lately	O
as	O
formerly	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
his	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
steady	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
fly	O
from	O
one	O
argument	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
to	O
steal	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
as	O
formerly	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
NEALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tailor	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
rightly	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
lately	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
his	O
not	O
being	O
rightly	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
-	O
did	O
he	O
follow	O
any	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
turned	O
off	O
for	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
think	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
madman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
trust	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
difference	O
between	O
honesty	O
and	O
dishouesty	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
40	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
275.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
and	O
HORATIO	B-pers
PARKINS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elias	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
five	O
dozen	O
of	O
wine-glasses	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
glass	O
decanters	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
articles	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
276.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
STINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
an	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
robbed	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Burrow-lane	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
travelling	O
in	O
a	O
single-horse	O
chaise	O
down	O
this	O
lane	O
into	O
the	O
Edgware-road	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Matthew	B-pers
Stinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
standing	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
soon	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
in	O
much	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
by	O
G-d	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half-a-guinea	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
2l	O
.	O
Banknote	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
papers	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
property	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
within	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
White-bear	O
,	O
Hendon	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
me	O
the	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
silver	O
you	O
may	O
keep	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
committed	O
this	O
act	O
,	O
he	O
stated	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
's	O
distress	O
that	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
any	O
more	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
just	O
call	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HUDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
man	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
distress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
distress	O
,	O
what	O
character	O
has	O
he	O
borne	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
true	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
employment	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
man	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
borne	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
whether	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
,	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
good	O
character	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
wished	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
that	O
recommendation	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
277.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BEVAN	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
upon	O
Henry	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
called	O
penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
KEMP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Upon	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Limehouse	B-place
to	I-place
Stepney	I-place
on	O
foot	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
for	O
safety	O
;	O
Mills	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
directly	O
afterwards	O
;	O
Mills	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
bad	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
him	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
halfpence	O
and	O
the	O
penny	O
pieces	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
nearly	O
of	O
two	O
shillingsworth	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
took	O
Martha	O
Jones	O
from	O
my	O
arm	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
upon	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Lime-house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
footpads	O
;	O
the	O
big	O
one	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
over	O
the	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
rob	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
penny	O
pieces	O
and	O
halfpence	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
safe	O
custody	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
.	O
GABRIEL	B-pers
HERRING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
headboroughs	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
hamlet	O
of	O
Ratcliff	O
;	O
my	O
duty	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
every	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
having	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
some	O
penny	O
pieces	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
finding	O
nothing	O
else	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
permitted	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
were	O
penny	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Police-office	O
to	O
come	O
forward	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Police	O
officers	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Mills	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Bevan	O
;	O
Iwas	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Haynes	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police-officer	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Brown	O
.	O
Mills	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
week	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
opposite	O
Shadwell	O
Police-office	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
officers	O
which	O
two	O
men	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
first	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
One	O
witness	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
Mills	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Bevan	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
gentlemen	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
and	O
lady	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
rely	O
upon	O
it	O
we	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
asked	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
these	O
two	O
.	O
Bevan	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
40	O
.	O
)	O
Mills	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
278.	O
JOHN	B-pers
VICKERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
ewe	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Passingham	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Raine	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DITCHUM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shepherd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Passingham	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
something	O
the	O
matter	O
among	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
sheep	O
's	O
entrails	O
and	O
feet	O
cut	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
informed	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
procured	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Helton	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
sheep	O
slaughtered	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
apartments	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
covered	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
mark	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
sheep	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
it	O
's	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
red	O
across	O
the	O
shoulders	O
,	O
about	O
as	O
wide	O
as	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
a	O
single	O
one	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Raine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
try	O
the	O
feet	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
tallied	O
with	O
the	O
legs	O
of	O
the	O
sheep	O
exactly	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
PASSINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Heston	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
apartments	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
sheep	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
try	O
the	O
feet	O
with	O
the	O
legs	O
of	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
tallied	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
coming	O
from	O
plough	O
on	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
a-bed	O
by	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
work	O
again	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
four	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
279.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
thirty-six	O
yards	O
of	O
carpeting	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
take	O
a	O
roll	O
of	O
carpeting	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
a	O
post	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
putting	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
sent	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
carpet	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
journeymen	O
;	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
NIBLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
kept	O
the	O
property	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
one	O
night	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Rose	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
an	O
R	O
on	O
it	O
with	O
ink	O
.	O
ROSE	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
carpeting	O
was	O
carried	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
further	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
up	O
under	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
same	O
carpeting	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
carpeting	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
that	O
carpet	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
carpeting	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
ticket	O
that	O
is	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
carpeting	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
forenoon	O
,	O
it	O
stood	O
on	O
a	O
board	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
carpeting	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
ticket	O
upon	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
280.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RAYNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
Philip	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
accident	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Britannia	O
East-Indiaman	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Crow	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
in	O
Guildhall	B-place
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
lottery	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Dean	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
stood	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
attend	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
'	O
room	O
in	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
inner	O
hall	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
was	O
pocket-picking	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
picked	O
Mr.	O
Crow	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
his	O
feet	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pocket-handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
six	O
old	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
old	O
pocket-books	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Johnson	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
it	O
any	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
living	O
honestly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
281.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
fifty-three	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Swann	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Swann	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Swann	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SWANN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cotton-manufacturer	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
James	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Swann	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
box-maker	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Swann	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
opposite	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
sheeting	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
into	O
King-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
dressed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
box-maker	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
sheeting	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Swann	O
's	O
,	O
running	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
property	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Swann	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
given	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Fenner	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FENNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Cheap	O
Ward	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swann	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
piece	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Swann	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
warehouseman	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
warehouse	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Swann	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
sheeting	O
up	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Trump-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
alarm	O
being	O
given	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
piece	O
lie	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Swann	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
entirely	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
service	O
all	O
the	O
war	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
my	O
leg	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
282.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fossick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
HAMMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Winkworth	O
's	O
wharf	O
for	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
cheese	O
for	O
my	O
masters	O
,	O
Messrs.	O
Benjamin	O
Wood	O
,	O
John	O
Fossick	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	O
Wood	O
,	O
cheesemonger	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
:	O
Between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
between	O
Queenhithe	B-place
and	I-place
Queen-street	I-place
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
on	O
,	O
some	O
person	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
mind	O
your	O
cheese	O
,	O
carman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
stop	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
behind	O
thecart	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
soldier	O
with	O
a	O
cheese	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
cart	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
cheese	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
person	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
cheese	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
another	O
cheese	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
soldier	O
run	O
down	O
a	O
passage	O
with	O
a	O
cheese	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
cheese	O
short	O
of	O
my	O
number	O
;	O
just	O
afterwards	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
soldier	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
cheese	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cheese	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
along	O
Shepherd's-alley	O
;	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
warehouse-door	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
directly	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
manure	O
close	O
by	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
looking	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
person	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
cheese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
manure	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
resisted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
cheese	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
plenty	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
his	O
money	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
young	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
lie-in	O
;	O
some	O
person	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
cart	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
two	O
cheeses	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
owned	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
mark	O
before	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
23	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
283.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BOYLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
twenty-six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cheesely	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
CHEESELY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
manufactory	O
for	O
agricultural	O
machines	O
,	O
in	O
Margaret-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
,	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Yowle	I-pers
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
quitted	O
my	O
service	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
perhaps	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother-in-law	O
supping	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
one	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
manufactory	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
my	O
company	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eleven	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
my	O
dog	O
took	O
to	O
the	O
centre	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
uncommon	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
watched	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
nobody	O
,	O
the	O
candle	O
would	O
not	O
keep	O
a-light	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
at	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
attempting	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
my	O
manufactory	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
round	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
dropping	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
whether	O
the	O
person	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
alarm	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
met	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Mary-le-bonne-passage	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
drop	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
justice	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
most	O
assuredly	O
would	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
coat-pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
pieces	O
that	O
were	O
dropped	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
another	O
piece	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
between	O
twenty-six	O
and	O
twenty-eight	O
pounds	O
of	O
bar	O
iron	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
iron	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
two	O
parcels	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
railing	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
convenience	O
of	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SHEHAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
in	O
Well-street	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Margaret-street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
into	O
Mary-le-bonne-passage	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cheesely	O
's	O
manufactory	O
to	O
this	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
drop	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
one	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cheesely	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Cheesely	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
iron	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
did	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BATES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Mary-le-bonne	O
watch-house	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
watch-house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
this	O
iron	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
,	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Cheesely	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAMAGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
These	O
pieces	O
of	O
iron	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
work	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
one	O
piece	O
up	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
kicked	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
iron	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
aukward	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Aged	O
32	O
.	O
)	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
284.	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
BRIAN	I-pers
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARRY	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BERRY	I-pers
,	O
PATRICK	B-pers
HOLLAND	I-pers
,	O
DANIEL	B-pers
DRISCOLL	I-pers
,	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ROMSEY	I-pers
,	O
CORNELIUS	B-pers
DONOHOUGH	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
M'CARTY	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
,	O
HANNAH	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
TIMOTHY	I-pers
BRIAN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
HERN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Miller	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
the	O
search-warrant	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
objected	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
parole	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
the	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
warrant	O
itself	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
only	O
evidence	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
warrant	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
)	O
.	O
-	O
REEVES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
to	O
that	O
warrant	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Floud	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
both	O
these	O
Magistrates	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
their	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Jones	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
with	O
Miller	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
,	O
to	O
the	B-place
King's-arms	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Maynard-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
for	O
rogues	O
and	O
vagrants	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
of	O
your	O
party	O
besides	O
Miller	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
:	O
Crocker	O
,	O
Limerick	O
,	O
Venters	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cockin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
Beresford	O
,	O
Grant	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Grant	O
a	O
Bow-street	O
patrol	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
,	O
distinctly	O
and	O
slowly	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
what	O
you	O
did	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
we	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
fiddle	O
playing	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
through	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
Miller	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Miller	O
had	O
the	O
warrant	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
men	O
and	O
women	O
,	O
thirty	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
employ	O
to	O
couple	O
the	O
men	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
coupled	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
any	O
warrant	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Miller	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
way	O
as	O
the	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
could	O
hear	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
busy	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
they	O
heard	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
began	O
coupling	O
them	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
how	O
were	O
they	O
employed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Some	O
dancing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fiddle	O
playing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
followed	O
two	O
prisoners	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
persons	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
coupled	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street-door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
opposite	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
then	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
turning	O
on	O
my	O
left-hand	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Timothy	O
Brian	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
of	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
Grant	O
,	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
remained	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
Brain	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrols	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
caught	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
came	O
upon	O
my	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
cutlass	O
;	O
Smith	O
closed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
wrung	O
the	O
stick	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
hit	O
several	O
times	O
by	O
Limerick	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
see	O
Limerick	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
our	O
backs	O
;	O
we	O
tried	O
then	O
to	O
get	O
Brian	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
losing	O
the	O
people	O
we	O
had	O
made	O
prisoners	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
New	O
Compton-street	O
,	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
Brian	O
made	O
the	O
blow	O
at	O
you	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
secured	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
patrols	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
New	O
Compton-street	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
returning	O
back	O
,	O
William	O
Smith	O
,	O
Cockin	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
ten	O
minutes	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
,	O
Birch	O
,	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
his	O
head	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
Birch	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
murder	O
being	O
committed	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
we	O
possibly	O
could	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Maynard-street	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
saw	O
Timothy	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
with	O
a	O
black-thorn	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
housewhere	O
you	O
described	O
yourself	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoners	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
doors	O
;	O
I	O
instantly	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
first	O
stick	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
wrung	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
something	O
in	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
can	O
explain	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
called	O
upon	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
flourishing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
hopping	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
bleeding	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
conducted	O
him	O
towards	O
the	O
Eight	O
Bells	O
,	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
,	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Eight	O
Bells	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Grant	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
was	O
being	O
led	O
by	O
two	O
officers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
situation	O
was	O
Grant	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
oh	O
Lord	O
,	O
oh	O
Lord	O
,	O
go	O
back	O
for	O
God	O
Almighty	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
murder	O
being	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
Smith	O
and	O
Cockin	O
to	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
Ravenhill	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
officers	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
clean	O
breach	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
like	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Beresford	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
lying	O
bleeding	O
,	O
insensible	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
for	O
Beresford	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
walked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Brian	O
first	O
attacked	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
single	O
word	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
oh	O
Lord	O
,	O
oh	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
bleeding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
bleed	O
all	O
over	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
,	O
(	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Holland	O
,	O
Driscoll	O
,	O
and	O
Romsey	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
number	O
of	O
officers	O
accompanied	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
this	O
warrant	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
patrole	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
above	O
fifty	O
in	O
number	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
.	O
Q.	O
Miller	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stay	O
any	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
apprehended	O
the	O
landlord	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
handcuffed	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
landlord	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Miller	O
produce	O
the	O
warrant	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
below	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Miller	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
your	O
hearing	O
,	O
tell	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
people	O
below	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
Miller	O
carried	O
the	O
warrant	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
accompained	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
any	O
affray	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
any	O
affray	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
while	O
you	O
were	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
those	O
persons	O
who	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
and	O
handcuffed	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
handcuffed	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
handcuffed	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
not	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
you	O
escorted	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Compton-street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
persons	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
handcuffed	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
persons	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
were	O
discharged	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
into	O
custody	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
handcuffed	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
rushed	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
tolerable	O
violence	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
quite	O
quietly	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
your	O
constables	O
staves	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
exhibited	O
them	O
directly	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
all	O
go	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
score	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
all	O
exhibited	O
your	O
constables	O
staves	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
call	O
cutlasses	O
staves	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
no	O
cutlasses	O
drawn	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
were	O
there	O
not	O
cutlasses	O
drawn	O
before	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
up	O
stairs	O
were	O
handcuffed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
of	O
course	O
no	O
riot	O
or	O
affray	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
persons	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
secured	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
tap-room	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
riot	O
then	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
all	O
quiet	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Very	O
quiet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
accident	O
had	O
not	O
happened	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
cutlasses	O
were	O
not	O
drawn	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
patrole	O
before	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
secured	O
up	O
stairs	O
by	O
handcuffs	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
tap-room	O
clear	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
women	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
tap-room	O
was	O
pretty	O
full	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
all	O
our	O
own	O
people	O
hardly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
whether	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
were	O
your	O
own	O
people	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
,	O
(	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
have	O
you	O
never	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
received	O
the	O
fatal	O
would	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
room	O
above	O
and	O
the	O
room	O
below	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
said	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Sullivan	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
was	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
landlord	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
the	O
moment	O
you	O
rushed	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
notification	O
whatever	O
being	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
landlord	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
all	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
seizing	O
the	O
people	O
below	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
people	O
seize	O
the	O
people	O
below	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
the	O
goodness	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
street	O
this	O
Maynard-street	O
is	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
,	O
dirty	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
lamps	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
only	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
Brian	O
attempted	O
to	O
strike	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
door	O
being	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
going	O
over	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
Brian	O
attempted	O
to	O
stop	O
you	O
then	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
affray	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
There	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
noise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
women	O
crying	O
for	O
their	O
husbands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
affray	O
below	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
our	O
people	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
perhaps	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
what	O
passed	O
below	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
VENTERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
patrole	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Miller	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
to	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
,	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
to	O
execute	O
a	O
warrant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
assist	O
in	O
conducting	O
these	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Jones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
AS	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
to	O
conduct	O
those	O
people	O
,	O
what	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
shovel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
that	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
had	O
these	O
people	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
conducting	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
that	O
man	O
do	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
attempted	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
shovel	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
large	O
shovel	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
prevented	O
the	O
blow	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
stepping	O
back	O
,	O
something	O
took	O
me	O
off	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
Jones	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
shovel	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
caught	O
the	O
shovel	O
with	O
the	O
hook	O
of	O
my	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
caught	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
the	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
arm	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
getting	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
shovel	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
slippery	O
,	O
frosty	O
weather	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
slippery	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
shovel	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
struck	O
at	O
you	O
and	O
Jones	O
,	O
explain	O
his	O
reason	O
,	O
or	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
these	O
prisoners	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
assault	O
upon	O
Grant	O
began	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
patrol	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Miller	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
to	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
or	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
Jones	O
and	O
Miller	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
handcuffing	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
through	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Every	O
thing	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
quiet	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
quiet	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
persons	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
opposite	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
standing	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
keep	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
men	O
or	O
women	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Men	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
their	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
your	O
desire	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
immediately	O
after	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Jones	O
,	O
leave	O
these	O
people	O
alone	O
,	O
they	O
want	O
nothing	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
accordingly	O
they	O
shut	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
round	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
this	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
Brian	O
before	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
Brian	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
slight	O
blow	O
somewhere	O
about	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
turned	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
saved	O
the	O
blow	O
from	O
Jones	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
seized	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
possibly	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
this	O
stick	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
almost	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
tried	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
stick	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
with	O
it	O
