TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Comission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1802	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIRST	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
ESQUIRE	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1802	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
ESQUIRE	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
ALVANLEY	I-pers
,	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	O
GROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOYDELL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
BROOK	O
WATSON	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STAINES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
JOHN	I-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
PETER	B-pers
PERCHARD	I-pers
;	O
Esq	O
.	O
JOHN	O
ANSLEY	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Humpleby	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lavender	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Simkin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stirland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Couchman	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Aldey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hearn	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Spurrier	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Purkis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Schultz	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Scatchard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Winbush	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Furness	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewther	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DRAPER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
LOUISA	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Elizabeth	O
West	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
aunt	O
.	O
she	O
keeps	O
the	O
King's-arms	B-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Newgate	I-place
market	I-place
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
orderd	O
sixpenny-worth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
it	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
drank	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ordered	O
another	O
sixpenny-worth	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
him	O
twice	O
attempt	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
a	O
glass	O
which	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
glass	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
JOHN	O
PAGE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
an	O
alarm	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
Miss	O
West	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
glass	O
buttoned	O
up	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
David	O
Hughes	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
glass	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
written	O
defence	O
,	O
stating	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
chairman	O
to	O
the	O
Duchess	O
of	O
Somerset	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
boys	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
bonfire	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
knock	O
the	O
glass	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
immediately	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
43	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
2.	O
HENRY	B-pers
MICHAEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William-Morley	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
WILLIAM-	O
MORLEY	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ship	O
broker	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Cannon-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
calling	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
turning	O
round	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
his	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
the	O
kirb	O
stone	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
at	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
ravelled	O
at	O
the	O
edge	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
side	O
was	O
hemmed	O
the	O
wrong	O
side	O
by	O
the	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
perceive	O
it	O
go	O
from	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sensible	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
moving	O
at	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
servant	O
here	O
who	O
hemmed	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
cripple	O
,	O
is	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
cripple	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
Mr.	O
ATKINSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
distinctly	O
draw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
claimed	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
(	O
Samuel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Marshalman	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
this	O
being	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
this	O
Counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
12	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
3.	O
WILLIAM-GEORGE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
32d	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
church	O
of	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Jewry	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
Penelope	B-pers
Bender	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Paddington	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
marry	O
and	O
take	O
to	O
wife	O
Frances-Maria	B-pers
Drought	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Penelope	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
HOLLOWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Jewry	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
marriage	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Penelope	O
Bender	O
,	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
church	O
of	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Jewry	O
;	O
I	O
witnessed	O
the	O
marriage	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Miss	O
Beuder	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Reads	O
the	O
register	O
)	O
.	O
-	O
``	O
William-	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Jewry	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
batchelor	O
,	O
and	O
Penelope	B-pers
Bender	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Stephen	O
,	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
by	O
licence	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1792	O
,	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
minister	O
.	O
''	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
if	O
that	O
Miss	O
Bender	O
is	O
now	O
living	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
this	O
licence	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Rev	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
PICKERING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
Paddington	O
;	O
I	O
recollect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
person	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
Frances-Maria	O
Drought	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
register	O
)	O
.	O
Reads	O
it	O
:	O
-	O
``	O
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
this	O
parish	O
,	O
batchelor	O
,	O
and	O
Frances-	O
Maria	B-pers
Drought	I-pers
,	O
of	O
this	O
parish	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
this	O
church	O
by	O
banns	O
,	O
this	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1802	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
the	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
banns	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
order	O
from	O
the	O
clerk	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
always	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
disappointment	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
appointed	O
a	O
previous	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
FRANCES-	O
MARIA	B-pers
DROUGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
the	O
marriage	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
news	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
had	O
an	O
effect	O
upon	O
your	O
daughter	O
's	O
mind	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
she	O
been	O
deranged	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NEWHOUSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
,	O
in	O
Jewin-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
DROUGHT	O
-	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
;	O
since	O
August	O
.	O
Q.Where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
passed	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.Perfectly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
saying	O
,	O
your	O
daughter	O
had	O
a	O
strong	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
requesting	O
me	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
learned	O
my	O
daughter	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
affection	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wished	O
her	O
to	O
wait	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
my	O
telling	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
rather	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
your	O
daughter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
a	O
tradesman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
daughter	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
fit	O
wife	O
for	O
a	O
tradesman	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
whole	O
happiness	O
depended	O
upon	O
having	O
her	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
coming	O
to	O
Islington	O
after	O
me	O
with	O
Miss	O
Welling	O
and	O
Captain	O
Brien	B-pers
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
passed	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
a	O
friend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
Cheisea	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
following	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
no	O
letter	O
had	O
passed	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
recollect	O
I	O
there	O
declined	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
your	O
daughter	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
should	O
have	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
favour	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
asked	O
my	O
opinion	O
what	O
was	O
best	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
your	O
opinion	O
;	O
you	O
were	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
first	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
town	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
The	O
infamy	O
of	O
the	O
question	O
is	O
its	O
own	O
answer	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
question	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
not	O
suffer	O
such	O
a	O
question	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
has	O
married	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
upon	O
the	O
town	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
right	O
to	O
put	O
those	O
questions	O
in	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
prove	O
any	O
facts	O
yourself	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
put	O
questions	O
in	O
an	O
irregular	O
way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
This	O
crime	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
totally	O
drawn	O
into	O
.	O
This	O
first	O
wife	O
of	O
mine	O
which	O
I	O
married	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
ten	O
years	O
happy	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
her	O
well	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
18	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
girl	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
's	O
bill	O
;	O
she	O
there	O
used	O
all	O
the	O
insinuating	O
manners	O
that	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
her	O
description	O
could	O
possibly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
resisted	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
town	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
and	O
more	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
girl	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
she	O
wrote	O
to	O
her	O
plaintiff	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
likewise	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
a	O
note	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
debt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
myself	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
letters	O
from	O
her	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
these	O
letters	O
she	O
extolled	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
good	O
of	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
bad	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wondered	O
I	O
could	O
live	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
dirty	O
drab	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
was	O
an	O
accomplished	O
girl	O
of	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
company	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
,	O
Duke	O
of	O
Clarence	O
,	O
and	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Hertford	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
account	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
always	O
resisted	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
fact	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
found	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterthat	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
day	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
people	O
after	O
me	O
with	O
messages	O
continually	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
mother	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Edgware	O
road	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
marry	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
well	O
knew	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
certificate	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
marriage	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
marry	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
the	O
Edgware-road	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mother	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Sauturday	O
evening	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
note	O
by	O
Captain	O
Brien	B-pers
's	O
servant	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
drink	O
tea	O
on	O
Sunday	O
afternoon	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
mother	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
questions	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
declined	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
question	O
her	O
mother	O
asked	O
me	O
was	O
,	O
what	O
were	O
my	O
pursuts	O
in	O
life	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
my	O
circumstances	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
income	O
could	O
not	O
exceed	O
150l	O
.	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
main	O
tain	O
a	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
represented	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
merchant	O
of	O
800l	O
.	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wished	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
marrying	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
the	O
narrowness	O
of	O
my	O
circumstances	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
consult	O
some	O
friends	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
further	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
consulted	O
a	O
male	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
Captain	O
Brien	B-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Baker-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
would	O
meet	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
letter	O
that	O
a	O
lodged	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
male	O
friend	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
a	O
cartage	O
alighed	O
at	O
she	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
footmen	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
of	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
possibility	O
of	O
my	O
income	O
being	O
increased	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
sit	O
person	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
;	O
she	O
might	O
perhaps	O
come	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
virtuous	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
that	O
answer	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Drought	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
father	O
twelve	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
fortune	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
Captain	O
Brien	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
less	O
than	O
50l	O
.	O
a	O
year	O
at	O
any	O
rate	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Drought	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Dr.	O
Drought	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
declining	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wished	O
me	O
to	O
settle	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
licence	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
hesitated	O
at	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
immediately	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
licence	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
proposed	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
banns	O
published	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
they	O
liked	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
banns	O
published	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
mother	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
was	O
nothning	O
to	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
declining	O
coming	O
near	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
coming	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
day	O
came	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
service	O
somewhere	O
;	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
and	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
tell	O
them	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
mother	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
not	O
attending	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
mother	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mother	O
knew	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
that	O
would	O
he	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
catch	O
me	O
then	O
.	O
Mr	O
Lord	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
throw	O
myself	O
upon	O
your	O
mercy	O
;	O
this	O
girl	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
illfame	O
;	O
she	O
even	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
she	O
had	O
deluded	O
a	O
better	O
man	O
than	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
from	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
not	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Drought	O
.	O
)	O
Q.Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
your	O
daughter	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Drought	O
in	O
the	O
Marthalsea	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Miss	O
Hertfont	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
by	O
a	O
dozen	O
different	O
names	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q.Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
Miss	O
Drought	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
for	O
a	O
twelvenmonth	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
happier	O
couple	O
than	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
meral	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Drought	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Daughter	O
ever	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
4.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PINCKNEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
twist	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRAIDLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
an	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
mercer	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Novemeber	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
hesiated	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
twist	O
from	O
his	O
left-hand	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
twist	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
twist	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
twist	O
is	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
man's-mercer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Braidley	O
together	O
;	O
Braidley	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
twist	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
twenty	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
high	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
married	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
frequently	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
twist	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
or	O
Braidley	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
5.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GOODGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
28lb	O
.	O
of	O
shot	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mildred	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Adds	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ADDIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shot-manufacturer	O
,	O
in	O
Tooley-street	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mildred	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
Addis	O
;	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
shot	O
from	O
our	O
cart	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
kept	O
in	O
bags	O
of	O
28lb	O
.	O
each	O
;	O
the	O
cart	O
went	O
from	O
our	O
door	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
Tooley-street	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nine	O
bags	O
of	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
opposite	O
Dice	O
Quay	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
five	O
bags	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Woodbridge	O
hoy	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
bag	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
bag	O
of	O
shot	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
whipping	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
jail	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
George	B-pers
Deverell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
shot	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
6.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
two	O
silver	O
dessert	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
ten	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
pillow	O
slip	O
;	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
eight	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
24s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
in	O
Bond-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
waiter	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
articles	O
at	O
various	O
times	O
;	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Whitcomb-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
boxes	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
some	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
in	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
winess	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
in	O
boxes	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
think	O
were	O
locked	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
break	O
them	O
open	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
ELDRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
boxes	O
in	O
his	O
apartment	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
but	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
7.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
head-piece	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
six	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Jamaica	B-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
as	O
house-maid	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
articles	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
heron	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
NEWTH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
produces	O
three	O
curtains	O
)	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
my	O
shopman	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
in	O
Long-alley	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
out	O
nursing	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
nursing	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
unlocked	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
box	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
duplicates	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
one	O
for	O
three	O
curtains	O
,	O
pawned	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
March	O
31st	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
a	O
pillowcase	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Willis	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
man	O
's	O
writing	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
curtains	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
fellow-servant	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
's	O
called	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
containing	O
these	O
duplicates	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FOLKARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
recollection	O
who	O
pledged	O
it	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
person	O
a	O
duplicate	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
other	O
duplicate	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
small	O
children	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
some	O
garden-stuff	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
washing	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
pillowcase	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
pillow-case	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
8.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MONAT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Abbey	I-pers
,	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
such	O
employment	O
,	O
take	O
into	O
possession	O
,	O
of	O
and	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Bussell	I-pers
,	O
10l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
for	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
feloniously	O
did	O
embezzle	O
,	O
secrete	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
2l	O
.	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Jurors	O
say	O
he	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BUSSELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
Henrietta-street	O
,	O
Manchester-square	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
perfectly	O
well	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
10l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Abbey	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
indebted	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbey	O
so	O
much	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbey	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
demand	O
it	O
of	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
debt	O
owing	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbey	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ABBEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
on	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
would	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
not	O
calling	O
on	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
10l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
the	O
prisoner	O
should	O
be	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
receipt	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
upon	O
my	O
desk	O
8l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
little	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
produced	O
me	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
10l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
his	O
Lordship	O
had	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
Lordship	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bussell	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
finding	O
a	O
deficiency	O
of	O
2l	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Bussell	O
)	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
made	O
any	O
enquiries	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
respecting	O
this	O
receipt	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Abbey	O
)	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
8l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
3d.	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
29l	O
.	O
or	O
something	O
on	O
account	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
sum	O
of	O
10l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
9.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
servant	O
to	O
Caleb-Welch	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
such	O
employment	O
,	O
receive	O
and	O
take	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
for	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
master	O
and	O
employer	O
,	O
of	O
and	O
from	O
Robert	O
Hill	O
,	O
18s	O
.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
feloniously	O
did	O
embezzle	O
,	O
secrete	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
6s	O
.	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Jurors	O
say	O
he	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
10.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
GOULDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
.	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Thatched-house	B-place
,	I-place
Field-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
bed	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
Mooney	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
immediately	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MOONEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shoemaker's-shop	O
,	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
keeps	O
another	O
shop	O
below	O
for	O
clothes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
detained	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
bed-gown	O
.	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
.	O
Coleman	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Publicly	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
11.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KIRVIN	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
CONNOR	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
seven-shilling-pieces	O
,	O
a	O
sixpence	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
LYON	O
BACKROW	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
pass	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
times	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
walking	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
talking	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
procession	O
had	O
passed	O
down	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
following	O
close	O
behind	O
this	O
lady	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
behind	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
crossing	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
man	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
conduct	O
you	O
safe	O
over	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
take	O
her	O
cloak	O
from	O
her	O
right-arm	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
over	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
man	O
let	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
spectables	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Kirvin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
behind	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
spectacles	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
,	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Comor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
Mr.	O
Backrow	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
here	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
knows	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
-	O
A.Seven	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
here	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A.Once	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
constable	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
an	O
extra	O
constable	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
other	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
that	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
once	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Lord	O
knows	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
tried	O
afterwards	O
by	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Jew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
Jew	O
too	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
spectacles	O
she	O
lost	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
a	O
case	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
BACKROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
procession	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
walking	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
prisoner	O
walked	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
walked	O
behind	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
go	O
by	O
for	O
very	O
near	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
passed	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
obsturcted	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
City	O
coffee-house	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
got	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
resisted	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q.Were	O
you	O
tried	O
here	O
along	O
with	O
your	O
brother	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
;	O
on	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
obstructed	O
my	O
passing	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
door-way	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
crowd	O
apparently	O
was	O
dispersing	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
a	O
possibility	O
of	O
getting	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
attempted	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
carefully	O
if	O
any	O
carriages	O
were	O
passing	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
flurried	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
slip	O
in	O
crossing	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
slipping	O
,	O
he	O
obstructed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
raised	O
my	O
leftarm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
an	O
idea	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
obstruction	O
was	O
on	O
purpose	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
a	O
carriage	O
was	O
then	O
turning	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
run	O
;	O
at	O
thattime	O
,	O
something	O
appeared	O
to	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
moment	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
ah	O
,	O
have	O
I	O
got	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
lady	O
pass	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
pocket	O
entirely	O
emptied	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
twisted	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
under	O
my	O
white	O
petticoat	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
pockets	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectable	O
,	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
purse	O
containing	O
two	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
hand	O
me	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
my	O
spectacles	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
thimble	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.There	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
crowd	O
on	O
this	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
your	O
property	O
before	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
Bow-church	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
spectacles	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RACKSTRAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
lusty	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
and	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
directly	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q.Should	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
hustled	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
crowd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
master	O
tailor	O
,	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
Southwark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
house	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.Within	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
doors	O
below	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
you	O
lived	O
four	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
A.Sixty-one	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
your	O
way	O
here	O
today	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
attending	O
here	O
all	O
the	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
brought	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A.Because	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
knew	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
forward	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Pring	O
,	O
a	O
glass-blower	O
,	O
at	O
Whitesriars	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Pring	O
to	O
bring	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
me	O
cry	O
halves	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
spectacles	O
and	O
thimble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
cry	O
halves	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
tailor	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
thimble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
why	O
Mr.	O
Pring	O
brought	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
subpoena	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
not	O
walking	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Lord-Mayor's-day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor's-day	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectarles	O
and	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
forward	O
.	O
Pring	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Connor	O
,	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Kirvin	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
forty	O
years	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
navy	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Kirvin	O
,	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Kirvin	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Connor	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
12.	O
PETER	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
rail-way	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
London	B-pers
Dock	I-pers
Company	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
in	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
iron	O
rail-way	O
was	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
freehold	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
13.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
thirty-six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
wrought	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
London	B-pers
Dock	I-pers
Company	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bosanquet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pooley	O
.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
DENNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bosanquet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
watchman	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
Dock	O
Company	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
about	O
the	O
docks	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
William	O
Oakley	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
our	O
muster-room	O
for	O
our	O
names	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
over	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
duty	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
near	O
Samson	O
's	O
gardens	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
premises	O
of	O
the	O
Dock	O
Company	O
;	O
Oakley	O
was	O
rather	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
found	O
of	O
a	O
foot	O
among	O
the	O
gravel	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
stooping	O
posture	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
hill	O
within	O
the	O
dock	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
excuses	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
suspicious	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
no	O
good	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Oakley	O
up	O
the	O
hill	O
with	O
a	O
lantern	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
Oakley	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
this	O
iron	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
among	O
the	O
gravel	O
and	O
sand	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
somebody	O
or	O
other	O
that	O
had	O
bid	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
right	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
OAKLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pooley	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Dock	O
Company	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Dennis	O
with	O
a	O
lantern	O
on	O
the	O
dock	O
;	O
I	O
say	O
a	O
man	O
upon	O
a	O
hill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
lantern	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
Dennis	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
iron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
sand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
when	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
early	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
buried	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
carried	O
the	O
iron	O
to	O
our	O
watch-office	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Besanquet	O
.	O
I	O
superintend	O
the	O
dock	O
watch	O
;	O
this	O
bolt	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
Dock	O
Company	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
but	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
dock	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
straight	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
ten	O
feet	O
long	O
;	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
chain	O
pump	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
lost	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
bolt	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
bevil-headed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
not	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
bevilheaded	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
bolt	O
till	O
that	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
14.	O
SARAH	B-pers
EATON	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
CLOUDER	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
David	O
Stevens	O
,	O
a	O
dyer	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
7	I-place
,	I-place
Eyre-street	I-place
,	I-place
Bethnal-green	I-place
;	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
some	O
silk	O
to	O
weave	O
into	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Ann	O
Cox	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
came	O
down	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
into	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
somebody	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
work	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
undone	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
one	O
damaged	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
quills	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
silk	O
,	O
one	O
purple	O
and	O
one	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gaunt	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Holywell-lane	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
work	O
was	O
tightened	O
up	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
shoot	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
bolted	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sally	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
there	O
,	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
undid	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
work	O
slack	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
threddles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
,	O
my	O
God	O
,	O
the	O
work	O
is	O
all	O
slack	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
coming	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
parted	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
that	O
conversation	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
coming	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
here	O
has	O
something	O
happened	O
to	O
your	O
work	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
work	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
twelve	O
handkerchiefs	O
done	O
all	O
but	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
counted	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
loom	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
ten	O
all	O
but	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
RICHARD	O
MATTHEWS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeymen	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gaunt	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreduch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
several	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q.Produce	O
your	O
own	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A.Here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
name	O
is	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
pawned	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
you	O
took	O
in	O
that	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
thirteen	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
attend	O
at	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
then	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
.	O
Q.Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
steadily	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
belief	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
hankerchief	O
from	O
her	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hankerchief	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
as	O
I	O
usully	O
did	O
to	O
mend	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
her	O
son	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
succoured	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
child	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
15.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARRIOIT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
40lb	O
.	O
of	O
tamarinds	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pincot	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anni	I-pers
.	O
Fourth	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas-John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ANNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
deputed	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
on	O
the	O
quays	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
the	O
goods	O
on	O
Galley-quay	B-place
;	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
quay	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
keg	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
crane-post	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
up	O
the	O
gate-way	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
seeing	O
the	O
broad-arrow	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
that	O
keg	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
keg	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Brandon	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
quitted	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
keg	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
the	O
broad-arrow	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
put	O
upon	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
our	O
charge	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q.There	O
are	O
other	O
porters	O
employed	O
upon	O
the	O
quay	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
,	O
except	O
we	O
have	O
an	O
additional	O
quantity	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
are	O
allowed	O
another	O
man	O
as	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
Q.There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
on	O
the	O
quays	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
keg	O
lying	O
by	O
itself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
among	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
persons	O
were	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
dozen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
you	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Globe-yard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Tower-street	O
.	O
THOMAS-	O
JOHN	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
enter	O
this	O
keg	O
of	O
tamarinds	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
entered	O
them	O
as	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
landed	O
and	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
quay	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
J.	O
J.	O
in	O
a	O
diamond	O
,	O
upon	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
property	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
keg	O
that	O
I	O
entered	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BRANDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
securing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
cutlass	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
cask	O
to	O
Tower-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
serjeant-major	O
and	O
a	O
corporal	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
16.	O
SARAH	B-pers
CHARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James-Cromp	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CROMP	I-pers
LOWE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
and	O
silversmith	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
stair-case	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
hand	O
take	O
a	O
pledge	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
racks	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
then	O
only	O
see	O
the	O
naked	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
into	O
her	O
bed-room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
putting	O
the	O
coverlid	O
staraight	O
;	O
upon	O
removing	O
the	O
coverlid	O
,	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
article	O
she	O
had	O
pulled	O
out	O
placed	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
striped	O
cotton	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
hand	O
draw	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
days	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
,	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
apair	O
of	O
stockings	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
pledge	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
counterpart	O
of	O
my	O
ticket	O
was	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
an	O
offence	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
17.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CRONING	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Field-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
walking	O
and	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Edwards	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
out	O
a	O
pocket-handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Croning	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
holloa	O
'd	O
to	O
Lee	O
and	O
Pope	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
pickpockets	O
;	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
towards	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partners	O
came	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
with	O
Croning	O
;	O
Pope	O
then	O
produced	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
wanted	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
prosecute	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
spare	O
time	O
to	O
attend	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
bound	O
us	O
over	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
corroborated	O
his	O
testimony	O
,	O
)	O
Edwards	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Croning	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Croning	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
18.	O
MAURICE	B-pers
DOYLE	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
HALESWORTH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
thirty	O
hods	O
of	O
lime	O
,	O
mixed	O
with	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
in	O
Cullum-street	O
,	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
yard	O
in	O
Jewin-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
years	O
in	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
employ	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
and	O
carter	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
my	O
carter	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
lime	O
to	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
coarse	O
stuff	O
,	O
lime	O
and	O
hair	O
mixed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
rubbish	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
load	O
thirty	O
hods	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
received	O
some	O
information	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Doyle	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
shed	O
,	O
in	O
Gitter	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
your	O
father	O
any	O
share	O
in	O
this	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
that	O
day	O
with	O
the	O
stuff	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
New-road	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
likewise	O
brought	O
another	O
load	O
to	O
Cullum-street	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
three	O
loads	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
New-road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
loads	O
had	O
he	O
in	O
fact	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
New-road	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
to	O
Cullum-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
loads	O
from	O
your	O
yard	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
two	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
not	O
answer	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
struck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Little	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Halesworth	O
has	O
some	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stable	O
,	O
or	O
shed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
lime	O
and	O
hair	O
there	O
.	O
Q.When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
like	O
such	O
as	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
mixed	O
some	O
rubbish	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
rather	O
changes	O
its	O
colour	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Halesworth	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
his	O
attorney	O
appeared	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
answered	O
for	O
his	O
appearance	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
your	O
father	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
in	O
Cullum-street	O
;	O
he	O
carries	O
on	O
business	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Two	O
loads	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
loads	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Jewin-street	O
leads	O
into	O
Aldersgate-street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
Redcross-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
at	O
either	O
end	O
of	O
Jewin-street	O
?	O
-	O
A.He	O
might	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
way	O
round	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
lime	O
and	O
hair	O
was	O
mixed	O
with	O
rubbish	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
other	O
plaisterers	O
mix	O
rubbish	O
with	O
lime	O
and	O
hair	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
that	O
which	O
remained	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
shade	O
of	O
difference	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
place	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
was	O
Halesworth	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
from	O
Doyle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
,	O
Halesworth	O
's	O
solicitor	O
,	O
answer	O
for	O
his	O
appearance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
attend	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q.What	O
is	O
the	O
rubbish	O
composed	O
of	O
?	O
-A.Sand	O
and	O
old	O
stuff	O
that	O
we	O
knock	O
out	O
of	O
ceilings	O
,	O
and	O
earth	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
earth	O
as	O
rubbish	O
;	O
sometimes	O
we	O
use	O
druft	O
sand	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
coarse	O
stuff	O
.	O
Q.That	O
is	O
the	O
term	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
sometimes	O
called	O
coarse	O
stuff	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
lime	O
and	O
hair	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
understood	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
as	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q.Suppose	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
lime	O
and	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
you	O
lime	O
and	O
hair	O
,	O
with	O
rubbish	O
mixed	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
should	O
you	O
think	O
yourself	O
defrauded	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
perfectly	O
satisfied	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GREGURY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
Greenwhich	O
,	O
Alaersgate-street	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
place	O
for	O
carts	O
and	O
carriages	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Halesworth	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
be	O
had	O
some	O
houses	O
there	O
upon	O
a	O
reparing	O
lease	O
.	O
Q.In	O
the	O
begining	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
's	O
cart	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Doyle	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
lime	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shoot	O
it	O
opposite	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
shot	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
rubbish	O
enough	O
before	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Halesworth	O
stepped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
draw	O
it	O
up	O
here	O
,	O
either	O
I	O
or	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
shot	O
close	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Halesworth	O
's	O
premises	O
.	O
Q.Where	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Halesworth	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
is	O
was	O
shot	O
upon	O
his	O
premises	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
car	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
information	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
seeing	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
care	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
I	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
Def	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
was	O
a	O
sickly	O
horse	O
and	O
subject	O
to	O
garping	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Jowln-street	O
the	O
horse	O
wanted	O
to	O
bye	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
shoot	O
the	O
load	O
in	O
Little	O
Greenwich	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Halesworth	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
not	O
shoot	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
I	O
was	O
terrified	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
made	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
nuisance	O
for	O
putting	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
seventeen	O
years	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
too	O
good	O
a	O
master	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
Aldersgate-street	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
short	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Castle-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Gregery	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
the	O
horse	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
shooting	O
his	O
load	O
there	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
that	O
as	O
a	O
reason	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Nor	O
did	O
he	O
mention	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Halesworth	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Doyle	O
called	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
Halesworth	O
nine	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Doyle	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
50	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Halesworth	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
53	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
19.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PERKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CROFT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
articled	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
Norwich	O
shawls	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
some	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
;	O
after	O
looking	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
then	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
ro	O
three	O
ladies	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
young	O
men	O
belonging	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
lowest	O
price	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
shawls	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
2l	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
shawls	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
;	O
our	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
hearing	O
me	O
say	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
,	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
hollea	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
having	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shawls	O
in	O
the	O
crown	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
shawls	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cost	O
19s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
18s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
shawls	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
.	O
FRANIS	O
COLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
a	O
shawls	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
shawl	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
seeking	O
for	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
his	O
hat	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
before	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
slipped	O
his	O
hat	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
shawl	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
snatched	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
shawls	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
crammed	O
in	O
very	O
tight	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
intended	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
shawls	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
witnesses	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
written	O
defence	O
,	O
stating	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
offence	O
having	O
been	O
committed	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
some	O
shipmates	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
to	O
intoxication	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
of	O
committing	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
navy	O
nineteen	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
20.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LAMB	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniouslystealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tuck	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TUCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair-dresser	O
in	O
Brook-street	B-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
watch	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
hair-dresser	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Catherine	O
Wheel-alley	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
watch	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
in	O
prossession	O
of	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
STARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
recollection	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
pledged	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
TROTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Lambeth-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Catherine	O
Wheel-alley	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
passed	O
a	O
window	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
duplicate	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
pledged	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
street	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn-hill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Fetter-lane	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
pledged	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
attended	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
settle	O
it	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
37	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
21.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
MAHONEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	O
WOLFE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tailor	O
and	O
salesman	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
17	B-place
,	I-place
Panton-street	I-place
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
coat	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
that	O
a	O
coat	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
52	O
.	O
Six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
22.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HIGGS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
goose	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Krimmelmeyer	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	O
KRIMMELMEYER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Plough-street	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
stand	O
in	O
High-street	B-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
:	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
goose	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
goose	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
goose	O
with	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
a	O
start	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
patrol	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WHITFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
of	O
Whitehapel	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
stand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goose	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
feet	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
immediately	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
goose	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
66	O
.	O
Publicly	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
23.	O
ANN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keppel	I-pers
.	O
ANN	O
KEPPEL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keppel	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
hired	O
her	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
but	O
one	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
WILLIAMS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
sheet	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
William	I-pers
;	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
duplicate	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
sheet	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sheet	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Keppel	O
from	O
the	O
geneeral	O
appearance	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
took	O
the	O
sheet	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
24.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
COLLIER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
valeu	O
20s	O
.	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
twoneck-handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
handckerhief	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Harriot	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
HARRISON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
home	O
form	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
eveing	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
one-horse	O
,	O
chaise	O
,	O
with	O
Miss	O
Harriot	O
Richardson	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
passing	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
fall	O
back	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
a	O
man	O
hanging	O
by	O
his	O
arm	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
whipped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
by	O
the	O
chaise	O
before	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
this	O
bundle	O
hand	O
been	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
still	O
in	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
I	O
pursuing	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
that	O
street	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
assembled	O
on	O
he	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Rose-street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
remarked	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
and	O
trowsers	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
going	O
through	O
Crown-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
threatened	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
threw	O
a	O
bundle	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
from	O
me	O
into	O
Rose-street	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NOWLAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
;	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
something	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Denmark-street	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
up	O
Rose-street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
gateway	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
The	O
bundle	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Miss	O
Richardson	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
sick	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
senses	O
almost	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
recollection	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
deep	O
consumption	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Confined	O
seven	O
days	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
25.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOTCHINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
97	I-place
,	I-place
East	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Septemeber	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
:	O
nobody	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
lodger	O
walked	O
through	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
change	O
from	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
minute	O
he	O
walked	O
away	O
without	O
his	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
WILLIAM-THOMAS	O
LINLEY	O
sworn	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bunn	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
watch	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
50	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
26.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
PASS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
