TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
THE	O
15th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1802	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1802	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDING	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
LE	I-pers
BLANC	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALLAN	O
CHAMBRE	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
WATKIN	B-pers
LEWES	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SKINNER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CARR	I-pers
GLYN	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
PETER	B-pers
PERCHARD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ANSTEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
TIPPING	O
RIGBY	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Savigny	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dadley	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nutting	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Heap	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gustard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Cornman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Strahan	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Machinlay	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowie	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smallpiece	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
John-Hutchinson	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Emmett	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
De	I-pers
Force	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Doncaster	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
586.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
seven-shilling-pieces	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
ISAAC	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Clapton	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
About	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
all	O
the	O
gold	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
book-case	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
usually	O
kept	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
leaving	O
my	O
money	O
all	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
searched	O
a	O
press	O
in	O
which	O
his	O
clothes	O
were	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
a	O
picklock	O
dropped	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
then	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
press	O
again	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
seven-shilling-pieces	O
,	O
partly	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
light-coloured	O
brick-dust	O
,	O
among	O
them	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
guineas	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
from	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
Captain	O
Pole	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
received	O
a	O
very	O
excellent	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
character	O
I	O
received	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
idle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
talk	O
of	O
a	O
picklock	O
-	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
was	O
it	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
mop	O
nail	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
mop	O
nail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
green-house	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
there	O
not	O
such	O
nails	O
in	O
the	O
green-house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
lock	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
picked	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
press	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
which	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
access	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
VINCENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
cloaths	O
into	O
the	O
press	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
used	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
man-servant	O
's	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
observed	O
something	O
glisten	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
fellowservant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
acquainted	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
FRAUNCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
(	O
John	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
Captain	O
Pole	B-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
.	O
587.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WHITTINGHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Waghorn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Senham	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sabine	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ventris	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Deare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
gangsman	O
proved	O
the	O
firm	O
as	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
story	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
warehouse	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
below	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
knap-sack	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
pointed	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
deficiency	O
in	O
one	O
hogshead	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
scattered	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	O
Hunter	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
SIMON	B-pers
MAZE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
Galley-quay	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
building	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
striving	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
where	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Hinton	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
sugar	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
responsible	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
sugar	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
three	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
Jury	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
588.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SNOWDEN	I-pers
and	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
30l	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
15l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Fillingham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
CREW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fillingham	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
a	O
farm	O
on	O
the	O
Harrow-road	B-place
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
and	O
a	O
grey	O
poney	O
safe	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
field	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
black	O
gelding	O
was	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fillingham	O
's	O
groom	O
,	O
Thacker	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FILLINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
horses	O
were	O
missed	O
,	O
hand-bills	O
were	O
published	O
describing	O
them	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Old	O
Brompton	O
,	O
near	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
perfectly	O
well	O
since	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
Snowden	O
occupied	O
a	O
house	O
adjoining	O
mine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
was	O
frequently	O
there	O
;	O
Snowden	O
occupied	O
a	O
stable	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
Wednesday	O
of	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
hay-lost	O
over	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
horses	O
seeding	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
,	O
apparently	O
a	O
carthorse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
grey	O
horse	O
feeding	O
from	O
the	O
rack	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
another	O
black	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
Snowden	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Wood	O
distinctly	O
say	O
to	O
somebody	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
,	O
''	O
I	O
wish	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
''	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
meant	O
the	O
horses	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
clipping	O
with	O
scissars	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
horses	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
gone	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fillingham	O
's	O
servant	O
afterwards	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
cart-horse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
horses	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
odd	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
remain	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
hay-lost	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
;	O
Snowden	O
had	O
promised	O
me	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
it	O
wanted	O
some	O
repairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
condition	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
being	O
above	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
mare	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
WESTMORE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
tap-boy	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
Wood	O
rode	O
upon	O
a	O
black	O
poney	O
,	O
and	O
Snowden	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
black	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
black	O
poney	O
was	O
a	O
carthorse	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
.	O
JAMES	O
CAREY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peace-officer	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
Bath	O
;	O
Bryant	O
asked	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
horses	O
in	O
Bath	O
,	O
Snowden	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
horses	O
at	O
the	O
old	O
Bridge	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
to	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
found	O
an	O
advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
cart-horse	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
that	O
to	O
Thacker	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Peaceofficer	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Carey	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
that	O
cart-horse	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Snowden	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fillingham	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
answered	O
every	O
description	O
.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
THACKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
horse	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
horse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
at	O
Rumsey-fair	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
this	O
year	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wood	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
shoe-stall	O
in	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
ale	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
an	O
elderly	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
halter	O
;	O
Wood	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agreed	O
for	O
twenty-eight	O
guineas	O
;	O
Wood	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Snowden	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
bargaining	O
for	O
another	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
Wood	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
bargain	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
should	O
I	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
harm	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
two	O
10l	O
.	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
guinea	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
first	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
tail	O
,	O
a	O
gelding	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
cordwainner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Living	O
at	O
Rumsey	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Southampton	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
done	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Rumsey	O
from	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Southampton	O
from	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
A.I	O
can	O
not	O
rightly	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
between	O
fifty	O
and	O
sixty	O
miles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
less	O
than	O
seventy-eight	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
name	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
stall	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
receipt	O
given	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
witness	O
the	O
transaction	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
you	O
your	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
buying	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
custom	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
you	O
lived	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
Southampton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
your	O
stall	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
minded	O
your	O
stall	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
,	O
William	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Southampton	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gelding	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
mare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
marks	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
leg	O
behind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
know	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
wanted	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
over	O
at	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
letter	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
subpoena	O
with	O
that	O
letter	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
contain	O
any	O
money	O
to	O
bear	O
your	O
expences	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
expences	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
application	O
made	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
an	O
attorney	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
told	O
your	O
story	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
since	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
given	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
had	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
Solicitor	O
for	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
arrive	O
in	O
town	O
till	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
examined	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Thacker	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
white	O
heel	O
behind	O
,	O
a	O
star	O
in	O
the	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
long	O
tail	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
.	O
589.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NORRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
therein	O
being	O
,	O
burglariously	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
in	O
evidence	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
day-light	O
when	O
the	O
offence	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
590.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MURPHY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
9	I-place
,	I-place
White's-alley	I-place
,	I-place
Chancery-lane	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
while	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
mean	O
appearance	O
was	O
trying	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
hanging	O
up	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
name	O
at	O
length	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
hung	O
up	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
off	O
the	O
nail	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
round	O
the	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
immediately	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
ISSAC	O
CHAPMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Howard	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
trying	O
on	O
some	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
boy	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Rolls	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
13	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
591.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TUCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
six	O
gallons	O
of	O
anniseed	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
distiller	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	O
Chamberlain	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
liquor	O
before	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
six	O
gallons	O
,	O
a	O
quart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
anniseed	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
numbered	O
8483	O
,	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
waggon	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
servants	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Lambert-street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
spirits	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
value	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman's-yard	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cask	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
say	O
,	O
''	O
Go	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
''	O
meaning	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Levi	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
step	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
carrying	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
cask	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
cask	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Hodges	O
.	O
)	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
last	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
;	O
the	O
cask	O
is	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
is	O
returned	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
my	O
servants	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Levi	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
when	O
that	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
592.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDY	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
JOHN-HUGHES	I-pers
EDY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRANNAM	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
value	O
40l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Murdock	B-pers
M'Kenzie	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Const	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
M'KENZIE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
father	O
lives	O
in	O
Green-street	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
coachmaker	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Edy	O
,	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
hired	O
chaises	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
before	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
chaise	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Brighton	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
five	O
shillings	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
call	O
on	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
return	O
the	O
chaise	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
Brannam	O
;	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
chaise	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
Brighton	O
,	O
but	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
must	O
pay	O
five	O
shillings	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
putting	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
price	O
was	O
forty	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
if	O
he	O
paid	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
forty	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
try	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
a	O
draft	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
draft	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
draft	O
at	O
a	O
short	O
date	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
take	O
no	O
such	O
draft	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
it	O
on	O
hire	O
at	O
five	O
shillings	O
a	O
day	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Brighton	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
drove	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
livery	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
Mrs.	O
Duss	O
,	O
called	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
addressed	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
at	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
signed	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
for	O
forty	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
draft	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
write	O
at	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Edy	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
Bolton-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
note	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
;	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Edy	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
turn	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
chaise	O
he	O
had	O
hired	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
word	O
and	O
honour	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
lent	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
telling	O
him	O
we	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
George-inn	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
hear	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
gentleman	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
had	O
talked	O
of	O
putting	O
it	O
up	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hiscox	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
went	O
on	O
before	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
;	O
Edy	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
hired	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Brannam	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
if	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
Brannam	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
Edy	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
Hiscox	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chaise	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
refused	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
got	O
the	O
chaise	O
on	O
the	O
Hammersmith-road	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
Newman	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
said	O
you	O
sold	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
payment	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
last	O
year	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q.Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
money	O
transactions	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
days	O
hire	O
for	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
at	O
five	O
shillings	O
a	O
day	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Brighton	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
recollection	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
conversation	O
between	O
your	O
father	O
and	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
father	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
France	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
proposition	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
chaise	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
chaise	O
at	O
forty	O
pounds	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
paid	O
you	O
at	O
a	O
short	O
period	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
paid	O
when	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
doceur	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
forty	O
pounds	O
a	O
fair	O
ready	O
money	O
price	O
for	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
Newman	O
's	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
although	O
you	O
have	O
sold	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
sold	O
the	O
harness	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
returned	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
harness	O
returned	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
chaise	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
before	O
the	O
note	O
became	O
due	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Georgeinn	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
sawthem	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
Brannam	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
one	O
hore	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
West-Indians	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Brighton	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
Edy	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
told	O
Brannam	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
Edy	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
out	O
;	O
Brannam	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Edy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
,	O
said	O
;	O
next	O
afternoon	O
,	O
at	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Brannam	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
twenty-one	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
without	O
taking	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
coach-maker	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
twenty-five	O
guineas	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
twenty-one	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
harness	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
up	O
when	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Brannam	O
and	O
Edy	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
Brannam	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
Edy	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
receipt	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Brannam	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
selling	O
horses	O
and	O
chaise	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
Edy	O
signed	O
the	O
receipt	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hughes	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
receipt	O
,	O
(	O
receipt	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
August	O
5th	O
,	O
1802	O
.	O
``	O
Received	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
Twenty-two	O
pounds	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
chaise	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
Bolton-street	O
,	O
Piccaddly	O
,	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Brannam	O
.	O
``	O
(	O
Indorsed	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
Deliver	O
the	O
harness	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
Hughes	O
.	O
''	O
Signed	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
by	O
Edy	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hughes	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
chaise	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
out	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
chaise	O
from	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
information	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
a	O
writ	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
,	O
with	O
horizontal	O
springs	O
,	O
painted	O
yellow	O
and	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
lined	O
with	O
blue	O
cloth	O
,	O
with	O
yellow	O
nails	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
rumble	O
tumble	O
behind	O
of	O
a	O
peculiar	O
make	O
.	O
Newman	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
make	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
I	O
brought	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
;	O
Mackenzie	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
conversation	O
;	O
Edy	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
that	O
chaise	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Mackenzie	O
came	O
to	O
claim	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
the	O
fair	O
value	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Mackenzie	O
acknowledge	O
selling	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
taking	O
the	O
draft	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
a	O
consideration	O
for	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
consideration	O
for	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
insisted	O
on	O
leaving	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
draft	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Duff	O
's	O
coachman	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
insist	O
on	O
leaving	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
desk	O
.	O
Edy	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Brannam	O
was	O
not	O
called	O
on	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Edy	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Brannam	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
593.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
spirituous	O
liquors	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holme	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SEWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
William	B-pers
Holme	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	O
Wilson	O
,	O
rectisiers	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
Upper	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
their	O
service	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
years	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
wages	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
stick	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
tin	O
canister	O
with	O
the	O
spirit	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
would	O
excuse	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
miss	O
the	O
quantity	O
put	O
of	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
stock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
it	O
is	O
theirs	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
spirit	O
,	O
gin	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
sugar	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.Upwards	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
sugar	O
and	O
spirit	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
this	O
tin-case	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
this	O
spirit	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
store	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
kept	O
him	O
,	O
unless	O
you	O
had	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
gin	O
or	O
sugar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
knowing	O
,	O
bytaking	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
stock	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
gin	O
or	O
sugar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
impossible	O
to	O
miss	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
thirteen	O
years	O
in	O
their	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wronged	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
594.	O
DAVID	B-pers
KINGSTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LITTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
Robinhood-court	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
shirts	O
to	O
my	O
sister-in-law	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
liberty	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
's	O
wife	O
to	O
hang	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
:	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
finished	O
at	O
the	O
arms	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Bennett	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WADE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
left	O
off	O
work	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
just	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
18	O
,	O
Robinhood-court	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
workhouse	O
passage	O
,	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
shirts	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
back	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
belonged	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Little	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
lenity	O
,	O
and	O
admitted	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
.	O
ALICE	B-pers
HOTHRAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sister-in-law	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
15	I-place
,	I-place
Robinhood-court	I-place
;	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
in	O
Charles	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
washing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
Gearing	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
shirts	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
shirts	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
Gearing	O
's	O
wife	O
rented	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
Gearing	O
ever	O
lived	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HILSTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
helping	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Gearing	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
on	O
board	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
these	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RATCLIFF	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
shirts	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirts	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
intoxication	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
plate	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
37	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
595.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Philip	B-pers
Matravers	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
such	O
employment	O
,	O
take	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
of	O
and	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
clerk	O
and	O
servant	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Bennet	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
6s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
for	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
masters	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
did	O
feloniously	O
and	O
fraudulently	O
embezzle	O
and	O
secrete	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Jurors	O
say	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Philip	B-pers
Matravers	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	O
Wilson	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wharfinger	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Philip	B-pers
Matravers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
carting	O
line	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
our	O
servant	O
as	O
carman	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
double	O
load	O
of	O
currants	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
6s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
and	O
accounted	O
only	O
for	O
one	O
load	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
partner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Matravers	O
,	O
liable	O
to	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
losses	O
you	O
may	O
sustain	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
loaded	O
at	O
Fresh-wharf	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bennett	O
and	O
Co	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOWLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Matravers	O
and	O
Co.	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
their	O
carman	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
turn	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
loaded	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
butt	O
of	O
currants	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Bennett	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
more	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
received	O
a	O
summons	O
next	O
day	O
from	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
for	O
carrying	O
a	O
double	O
load	O
of	O
currants	O
in	O
one	O
cart	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
law	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
booked	O
a	O
single	O
load	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
;	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bennett	O
and	O
Co.	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
goods	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
measures	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WASHINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Bennett	O
and	O
Co	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten-pence	O
for	O
the	O
cartage	O
of	O
two	O
loads	O
of	O
currants	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
carman	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
a	O
man	O
brings	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
;	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
.	O
Bowler	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
carman	O
settle	O
accounts	O
every	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Always	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
regular	O
rule	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
entered	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
one	O
load	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
set	O
it	O
right	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten-pences	O
for	O
two	O
butts	O
of	O
currants	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sluck	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
but	O
one	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
case	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
44	O
.	O
Fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
596.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
sixty	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
an	O
error	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
597.	O
MARY	B-pers
MULLINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Grady	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Cornelius	O
Foley	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
GRADY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milkwoman	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
Bluewall-court	B-place
,	I-place
Tottenham	I-place
Court-road	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Foley	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
milk	O
the	O
cows	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
;	O
she	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
pocket-book	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
ticket	O
of	O
my	O
silk	O
cloak	O
that	O
cost	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
pawned	O
for	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
ninepence	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
ticket	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
JOHN	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stone	O
sawyer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
distress	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
girl	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
apron	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
cloak	O
or	O
she	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
for	O
every	O
one	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
herself	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
does	O
with	O
her	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
robbed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
598.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
son	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Clarke	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
watch-case	O
maker	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	B-place
;	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
service	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
some	O
silver	O
wire	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
Davis	O
and	O
Dublin	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
silver	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
crying	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
not	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
partner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GASS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
our	O
lock-up	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
top	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
silver	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
such	O
stamps	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hatham	I-pers
.	O
599.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HAWES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
mother	O
lives	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
,	I-place
Bunhill-row	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
service	O
two	O
months	O
on	O
liking	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
privy	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
was	O
halfpence	O
,	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
bits	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
watched	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
was	O
silver	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
bag	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
halfpence	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ledge	O
that	O
supported	O
the	O
roof	O
,	O
very	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
fight	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
common	O
necessary	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
PHILLIPS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
privy	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
on	O
the	O
ledge	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
put	O
there	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
also	O
employed	O
by	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
silver	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
plates	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
drawn	O
through	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
14	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12d	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
600.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENT	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SAVILLE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
pencil-case	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
bodkin	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holbrooke	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HOLBROOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
Pratt-street	B-place
,	I-place
Camden-town	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BARNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
on	O
horseback	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Saville	O
alone	O
,	O
running	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
from	O
Camden-town	O
to	O
Kentish-town	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
thieving	O
of	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
water	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
jumped	O
into	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
floating	O
on	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
poking	O
my	O
whip	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
up	O
came	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
memorandum-book	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BASS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
very	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Holbroke	O
's	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
half-past	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
opposite	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Holbrooke	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Saville	O
make	O
several	O
attempts	O
to	O
get	O
upon	O
a	O
wall	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
watching	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
signal	O
,	O
by	O
whistling	O
,	O
he	O
withdrew	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
sprung	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
to	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Saville	O
was	O
pulling	O
from	O
his	O
dress	O
different	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
steal	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Saville	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
bad	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
''	O
me	O
,	O
ma'am	O
,	O
''	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
his	O
shoes	O
off	O
,	O
left	O
them	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Kent	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
about	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
twenty	O
yards	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
away	O
for	O
Kentish-town	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WESTBROKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Holbroke	O
.	O
)	O
Kent	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
bathing	O
in	O
a	O
pond	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Saville	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
on	O
our	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
Saville	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Kent	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
Saville	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
15	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
601.	O
JAMES	B-pers
M'GUIRE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
thousand	O
sixpenny	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BARON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
porter	O
to	O
me	O
near	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
watched	O
;	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
words	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Broadnacks	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shopman	O
was	O
taking	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
papers	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner'spocket	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
his	O
employment	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROADNACKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sweeping	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
two	O
papers	O
of	O
nails	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
from	O
a	O
shelf	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
a	O
recess	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
coat-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
paper	O
of	O
nails	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
himself	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
officer	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
parcels	O
are	O
marked	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
nails	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
loose	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
papered	O
exactly	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Chambre	I-pers
.	O
602.	O
MARY	B-pers
M'DONALD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
Banknote	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BEAUMONT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
Bank-note	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
18th	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
directly	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
her	O
giving	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
women	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
lefthand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
stays	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
it	O
among	O
themselves	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Hotham	O
.	O
603.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHEEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
unmade	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
an	O
error	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
604.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
SOLOMON	I-pers
ROBUS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John-Edward	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
five	O
watch	O
chains	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
seven	O
watch	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
five	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
four	O
watch	O
hooks	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN-	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
clock-maker	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
58	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
Within	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
of	O
June	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evenning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
watch	O
papers	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
for	O
watch-strings	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
every	O
thing	O
secure	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shop-window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
tray	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
sold	O
no	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tray	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
are	O
remarkable	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
damaged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
anybody	O
else	O
serve	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Sun-street	O
,	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
together	O
talking	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
ran	O
away	O
towards	O
Shoreditch-church	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
went	O
down	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
towards	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Gravelend	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
Bishopslgate	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
hardware	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Lawson	O
claimed	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Henry	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
corroborated	O
the	O
audience	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lawson	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asking	O
for	O
watch	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
strings	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	O
SELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop-window	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
the	O
middle	O
shutter	O
had	O
been	O
raised	O
by	O
a	O
Dutch	O
clinker	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
I	O
travel	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
hardware	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
605.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROOKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Sneaven	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SNEAVEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sugar-baker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
,	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
singing	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
past	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
watch-chain	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
;	O
the	O
chain	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nowlan	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
value	O
it	O
at	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Of	O
petty	O
larceny	O
only	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
606.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
three	O
tooth-picks	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pencil	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
left-hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
with	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
away	O
up	O
Cock-court	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
book	O
over	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
constables	O
;	O
the	O
book	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
removed	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
book	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
memorandums	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
police	O
officer	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
spar	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BIGGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Blue	O
Last	O
,	O
Blackstiars	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
rushed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
innocent	O
man	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
607.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
YARMOUTH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
glass	O
bottle	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
castor	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
jalap	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
saffron	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
glass	O
vial	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
bark	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
salt	O
of	O
lemons	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
other	O
bark	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
sponge	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Fawkes	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
HORNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Fawkes	I-pers
,	O
druggist	O
,	O
in	O
Bucklersbury	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
more	O
than	O
twelve	O
months	O
'	O
,	O
we	O
paid	O
him	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
department	O
was	O
to	O
sweep	O
the	O
warehouse	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
rub	O
the	O
desk	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
both	O
his	O
coat	O
pockets	O
,	O
the	O
staps	O
were	O
inside	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
remained	O
there	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
warehouse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
staid	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
very	O
deliberately	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
sheet	O
of	O
brown	O
paper	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
that	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
was	O
buttoned	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
flaps	O
were	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sink	O
to	O
wash	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
he	O
straddled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
breakfast	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
twelve	O
yards	O
,	O
when	O
Fenner	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Fenner	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
jalap	O
root	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
untied	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
bulk	O
in	O
then	O
front	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
castor	O
oil	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
we	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
saffron	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
parcels	O
of	O
salt	O
of	O
lemons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
bark	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
our	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bark	O
as	O
a	O
curiosity	O
;	O
the	O
leather	O
bag	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
your	O
ownknowledge	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
ascertain	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
threatened	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
long	O
before	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FENNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
constables	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
castor-oil	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
in	O
his	O
bowels	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Horner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
the	O
jalap	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
sleep	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
had	O
rheumatism	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
junr	O
.	O
corroborated	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
his	O
uncle	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
leather	O
bag	O
and	O
bottle	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
608.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
of	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
a	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Courthorpe	O
.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
GOODSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Goodson	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
schoolmaster	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Crescent	O
,	O
Kingsland-road	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
party-wall	O
that	O
divides	O
my	O
premises	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
little	O
girl	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mammy	O
will	O
beat	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
two	O
young	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
my	O
parlour	O
boarders	O
,	O
got	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
the	O
cottage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
passion	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
breast	O
pockets	O
with	O
great	O
violence	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
school-yard	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
sit	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
stool	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
great-coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
job	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
G.	O
S.	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
his	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
crown	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
Peter	O
Mason	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Goodson	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
dropped	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chamber	O
.	O
609.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BESSET	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
BISEX	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Leake	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LEAKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jobbing	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Walworth	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
used	O
with	O
my	O
cart	O
,	O
worth	O
about	O
four	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
into	O
Lock's-fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
leaning	O
upon	O
a	O
post	O
by	O
a	O
horse-boiler	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
tied	O
to	O
a	O
post	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
Leake	O
afterwards	O
claimed	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
horse	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
three	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
weeks	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
his	O
throat	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
arm	O
into	O
his	O
belly	O
;	O
his	O
breath	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
bleeding	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
throat	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
from	O
Walworth	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
throat	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
reason	O
for	O
wishing	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
the	O
boiler	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
ordered	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Flyinghorse	O
,	O
in	O
Lambeth-street	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
false	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
whose	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
confession	O
-	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
sign	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Hotham	O
.	O
610.	O
MARY	B-pers
CALLAHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
loaf	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Catharine	O
.	O
CATHARINE	O
ISAACS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Catherine-street	B-place
,	I-place
Rosemary-lane	I-place
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
half-past	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
doors	O
all	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
half-past	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
wood-work	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
bolt	O
goes	O
in	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
property	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
with	O
my	O
apron	O
round	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
apron	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
for	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BASSETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
apron	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
bacon	O
,	O
some	O
rump-streaks	O
,	O
some	O
potatoes	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
cabbages	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
sixpence	O
for	O
that	O
and	O
a	O
quartern-loaf	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
apron	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
sickness	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
apron	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
round	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
611.	O
WILFRY	B-pers
EYRES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
42s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
oil	O
shop	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
7	I-place
,	I-place
Vere-Street	I-place
,	I-place
Clare-market	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
various	O
articles	O
,	O
but	O
purchased	O
nothing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
the	O
moment	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
advertisement	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
BROWN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rattle	O
spring	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
through	O
Bowl-yard	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
botom	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
BUCKLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
boys	O
gathering	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
sprang	O
my	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
13	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Hotham	O
.	O
612.	O
SARAH	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
28s	O
.	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LITTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
,	O
in	O
Mortimer-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
GARDENER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Little	O
left	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
during	O
his	O
absence	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
from	O
her	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
garret	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
wash	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
pair	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
between	O
the	O
sacking	O
and	O
the	O
seather-bed	O
some	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
shirts	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
cotton	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
for	O
shirts	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mother	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
seven	O
yards	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
bedgown	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
seven	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
had	O
sent	O
seven	O
yards	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
for	O
her	O
sister	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
the	O
foreman	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
cutting-room	O
,	O
up	O
there	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
measuring	O
some	O
cotton	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Little	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Marthe	O
Mosely	O
up	O
to	O
question	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
MOSELY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Little	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
desire	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
cuttingout	O
room	O
,	O
rolling	O
up	O
the	O
calico	O
very	O
carefully	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
calico	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
MADAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
cotton	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
measure	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Joseph	O
Avery	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
in	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Little	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
15	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
613.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wreaks	I-pers
.	O
-	O
BROWN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
assistant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wreaks	I-pers
,	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopgate-street	B-place
Without	I-place
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
from	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
twisted	O
it	O
round	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
print	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sapwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
cotton	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Brown	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
roll	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cotton	O
sell	O
upon	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
immediately	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
One	O
year	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
614.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Const	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
In	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
hired	O
some	O
waggons	O
to	O
remove	O
my	O
goods	O
from	O
North	B-place
Badgley	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Hampshire	I-place
,	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
arrived	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Jewels	O
and	O
trinkets	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
inclosed	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
petticoat	O
was	O
placed	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
ROSETTA	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
packing	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
jewels	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
into	O
another	O
box	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
petticoat	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
waggon	O
arrived	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cord	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
loose	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
jewels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
petticoat	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Smith	O
and	O
Nowlan	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
upon	O
looking	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
breadth	O
of	O
a	O
muslin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
hanging	O
as	O
a	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
Smith	O
found	O
some	O
duplicates	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
which	O
matched	O
it	O
exactly	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
's	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
work	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Griffiths	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
upon	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
knowing	O
him	O
)	O
,	O
Bill	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
full	O
of	O
Bank-notes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
nothing	O
there	O
but	O
my	O
duplicates	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
shew	O
you	O
my	O
distressed	O
situation	O
,	O
and	O
convince	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
nothing	O
lately	O
among	O
the	O
duplicates	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
petticoat	O
and	O
gold	O
seal	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
claimed	O
the	O
petticoat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
a	O
certificate	O
of	O
their	O
marriage	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
produced	O
is	O
a	O
curtain	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
petticoat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milford	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
