TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1802	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALITY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1802	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
ELLENBOROUGH	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
NEWNHAM	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CURTIS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
HARVEY	B-pers
CHRISTIAN	I-pers
COMBE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HIBBERT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
FLOWER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fraser	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Robson	I-pers
Robley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
,	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
Waster	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mari	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Peppercorn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Moffatt	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pobjoy	I-pers
,	O
Eldershaw	B-pers
Tunstall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burrock	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Marsden	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bissett	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jeffervs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Line	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
.	O
747.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
nineteen	O
yards	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
value	O
27s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BEAUMONT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Aytebary-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Williams	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Woodbridge	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
flannel	O
has	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Williams	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ESTERBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
my	O
barrow	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
within	O
three	O
doors	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Beaumont	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Beaumont	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Williams	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
;	O
he	O
peeped	O
twice	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
from	O
my	O
barrow	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
run	O
down	O
Wood-bridge-street	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
persons	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WHITEHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
make	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
down	O
Woodbridge-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
forward	O
into	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
must	O
come	O
out	O
into	O
St.John's-street	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
into	O
Northampton-street	O
;	O
one	O
took	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
Clarke	O
turned	O
down	O
to	O
some	O
ruins	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
secured	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
back	O
together	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
Mrs.	O
Beaumont	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
running	O
down	O
Woodbridge-street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
flannel	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
ruins	O
,	O
Isaw	O
Charke	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
necessary	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
loosed	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
-	O
Taverner	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
stannel	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
)	O
Williams	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
.	O
Williams	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Clarke	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
748.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
BAXTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John-Christian-Frederick	B-pers
Wassman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
two	O
Banknotes	O
.	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
and	O
six	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN-CHRISTIAN-FREDERICK	B-pers
WASSMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Drury-lane	B-place
Theatre	I-place
;	O
when	O
the	O
piece	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
lobby	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Schutz	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lobby	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
moment	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
pushing	O
against	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
pocketbook	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
me	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
my	O
face	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
wanted	O
to	O
crowd	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Schutz	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Schutz	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
stooped	O
cowr	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
held	O
the	O
book	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
book	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
six	O
Bank-notes	O
of	O
1l	O
.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
2l	O
.	O
each	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
crowd	O
pushed	O
me	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Schutz	O
kept	O
held	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Pickering	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
crowd	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
you	O
felt	O
something	O
which	O
induced	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
your	O
hand	O
to	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
missed	O
your	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
LUDOLPH	B-pers
SCHUTZ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wassman	O
in	O
the	O
lobby	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
countryman	O
and	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
almost	O
immediately	O
took	O
his	O
arm	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
is	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
pointing	O
at	O
Baxter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
fellow	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
suspicious	O
look	O
,	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
blow	O
from	O
some	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
from	O
whom	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
pushed	O
about	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
another	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lobby	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
grenadiers	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
some	O
persons	O
who	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
those	O
persons	O
were	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
pocket-book	O
upon	O
the	O
very	O
spot	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
stoop	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wassman	O
claimed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pocket-book	O
and	O
notes	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wassman	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wassman	O
.	O
)	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopped	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
PICKERING	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrol	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
gentleman	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
putting	O
his	O
book	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
749.	O
ELIJAH	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
eighty-four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
loaf	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	O
IBELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
wholesale	O
grocer	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
St	B-place
Swithin's-lane	I-place
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
cart	O
loaded	O
with	O
bags	O
of	O
loaf	O
sugar	O
;	O
the	O
carman	O
was	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
at	O
Iron-gate-wharf	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
produced	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KENNIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
carman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Travers	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
several	O
packages	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Ibell	O
)	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
packages	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
with	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Kennie	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
packages	O
to	O
leave	O
at	O
different	O
wharfs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
three	O
at	O
Iron-gate-wharf	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Iron-gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
tail	O
ladder	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
in	O
crossing	O
Little	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
one-horse	O
cart	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Charles	O
Turner	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
Turner	O
and	O
another	O
pursued	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
warehouseman	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
carman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Harris	O
and	O
Co.	O
tea	O
dealers	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Lower	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Kennie	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
minutes	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
afterwards	O
.	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
with	O
Kennie	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
an	O
officer	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
head	O
borough	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
Upper	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
I	O
head	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Ibell	O
and	O
Kennie	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rosemary-lane	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
bundle	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
750.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
CATON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CRAGG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
surveyor	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
porter	O
s	O
to	O
unload	O
the	O
craft	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Two	O
Henrys	O
lighter	O
lying	O
at	O
Ralph's-quay	B-place
,	O
close	O
to	O
a	O
ship	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
the	O
lighter	O
had	O
sugar	O
on	O
board	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
scale	O
board	O
of	O
sugar	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
landed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
shuffling	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
seeing	O
his	O
hand	O
come	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
his	O
hand	O
covered	O
with	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cuff	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
raised	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
after	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
been	O
taking	O
a	O
little	O
sugar	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
no	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
India	O
Company	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
place	O
was	O
worth	O
of	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
gateway	O
where	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
weighed	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
three	O
pounds	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
sugar	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
sugar	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
quality	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STEVENSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
offered	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
sugar	O
as	O
it	O
scattered	O
from	O
a	O
cart	O
where	O
the	O
packages	O
had	O
broke	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
751.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DALEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
called	O
Louis	O
d'ors	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
value	O
250l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
,	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CAMERON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
German	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
rings	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
pointed	O
to	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
which	O
she	O
liked	O
;	O
my	O
hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
pointed	O
at	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
meant	O
that	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
found	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
turned	O
to	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
faacs	O
assisted	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
recover	O
your	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
two	O
Louis	O
d'ors	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
for	O
250l	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
say	O
lie	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
20	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
people	O
running	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
20	O
yards	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GUYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
poulterer	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
some	O
poultry	O
to	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
ragged	O
boy	O
close	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
America-square	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
went	O
close	O
up	O
behind	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
bosom	O
;	O
directly	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
America-square	O
,	O
into	O
John-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
court	O
that	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
again	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
calling	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three-streets	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
stopped	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
high	O
change	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
this	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
running	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
ran	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
pocketbook	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
with	O
250l	O
.	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Lambeth-street	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
pocket-book	O
found	O
;	O
we	O
observed	O
a	O
lump	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
plaister	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sore	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
found	O
three	O
single	O
pound	O
notes	O
between	O
his	O
stocking	O
and	O
his	O
skin	O
;	O
hewas	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
all	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
LEVI	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
at	O
Messrs	O
Todd	O
and	O
Co.	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
four	O
witnessess	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
752.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
LEMON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bowley	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOWLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oilman	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
2dof	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
passing	O
along	O
Lower	B-place
Thames-street	I-place
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pocket	O
picked	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
sailor	O
's	O
cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
two	O
men	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
sprang	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
from	O
whose	O
hands	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
spoke	O
of	O
a	O
cart	O
wheel	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
29	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
753.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EARLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Bird	O
Savage	O
,	O
and	O
Bird	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pocket	O
picked	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
the	O
arm	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Allen	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
witness	O
Read	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Welch	O
,	O
Read	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
feel	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
go	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
the	O
least	O
sensation	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Newgate-street	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
them	O
to	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
Allen	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
them	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
was	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
all	O
through	O
Cheapside	O
till	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
Crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
;	O
a	O
cart	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
rubbish	O
;	O
a	O
plank	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
which	O
stopped	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
Allen	O
and	O
Welch	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Allen	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Welch	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
that	O
gentleman	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Allen	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
this	O
boy	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Welch	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
12	O
.	O
Allen	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
13	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
754.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MYERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FALKNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
boot	O
and	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
Little	B-place
New-street	I-place
,	I-place
Shoe-lane	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
finish	O
teaching	O
him	O
the	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
apprenetice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
beater	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
instantiy	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
costable	O
take	O
the	O
shoes	O
fromhis	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
besides	O
my	O
own	O
workmanship	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
give	O
5s	O
.	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
shoes	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
year	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
755.	O
ANN	B-pers
BARBARY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mulligan	I-pers
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
MULLIGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mulligan	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
West-street	B-place
,	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
paralytic	O
stroke	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
workhouse	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shirt	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
morning	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
daughter	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Ing	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
which	O
be	O
received	O
in	O
pledge	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirt	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Her	O
daughter	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
for	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
often	O
pledge	O
things	O
for	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
756.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
KELSO	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
two	O
mussing	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
17s	O
.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
night	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
PRITCHARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brushmaker	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
54	O
,	O
Newgate-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
O'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
bed-room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Malin	I-pers
and	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
behind	O
St.	O
Geroge's-market	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
admittance	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
found	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
secured	O
;	O
Miss	O
Malin	O
keeps	O
a	O
school	O
,	O
and	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
MALIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
school	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
our	O
young	O
ladies	O
were	O
nearly	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
met	O
a	O
person	O
very	O
much	O
resembling	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
dress	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Peppercorn	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
who	O
wished	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
quarter	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
address	O
I	O
would	O
wait	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
described	O
very	O
particularly	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
neither	O
bonnet	O
nor	O
cloak	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Peppercorn	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
produced	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
William	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Mary	O
Britchard	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
identified	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
that	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
gown	O
about	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
3d	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
lady	O
has	O
sworn	O
false	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
757.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
portmauleau	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Day	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
DAY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
Philip	O
Day	O
,	O
trunk-maker	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Grocer's-hall-passage	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
not	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Fenner	I-pers
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
trunk	O
and	O
three	O
knives	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
trunk	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Day	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stupid	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Fenner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
56	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
758.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
KERSHAW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
31b	O
.	O
1	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Spanish	O
juice	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garcias	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	O
Garcias	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Lewis	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Galley-quay	B-place
,	O
attending	O
to	O
the	O
landing	O
of	O
some	O
Spanish	O
juice	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
surveyor	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
some	O
persons	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
sample	O
of	O
juice	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Stennett	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
seven	O
sticks	O
of	O
Spanish	O
juice	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stennett	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
must	O
mind	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
juice	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
juice	O
upon	O
the	O
Quay	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
seven	O
stcks	O
weighed	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stennett	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
STENNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
assistant	O
at	O
Galley-quay	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
call	O
out	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
robbing	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
juice	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
collared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
seven	O
sticks	O
of	O
juice	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
case	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
nine	O
more	O
sticks	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
some	O
chests	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
struck	O
against	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
759.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
ROBERTSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
twelve	O
quarts	O
of	O
peas	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
four	O
quarts	O
of	O
beans	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
eight	O
ounces	O
of	O
feed	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Field	I-pers
(	O
John	O
Field	O
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
proved	O
the	O
firm	O
as	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Fields	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
Lower	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
I	O
packed	O
the	O
articles	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
K.W.H	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
carman	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
79	O
,	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
boxes	O
;	O
the	O
carman	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
carman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Fields	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
evening	O
last	O
I	O
received	O
four	O
boxes	O
and	O
two	O
bags	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
79	O
,	O
Basinghall-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
behind	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
drew	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
me	O
coming	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
Old	O
Jewry	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
ASHWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Jewry	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
stop	O
thief	O
cried	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
's	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
round	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Jewry	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
were	O
given	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Martin	O
and	O
Allen	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
BROWN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
horses	O
head	O
,	O
making	O
for	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Ashwin	O
collared	O
him	O
nearly	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
760.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WARNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
foot	O
of	O
leather	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
state	O
whether	O
the	O
pipe	O
was	O
fixed	O
or	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
761.	O
JANE	B-pers
JAMES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pintpewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stayton	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	O
STAYTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Sugar-loaf	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
my	O
boy	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
STAYTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	O
STAYTON	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
boy	O
called	O
out	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
pot	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
from	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
corroborated	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Slayton	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
tap-room	O
table	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
pot	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
fatherless	O
children	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
42	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
762	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FICKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
twenty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
nails	O
.	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
John	O
Jackson	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
occasionally	O
worked	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
suspicion	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
straw	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
nalls	O
immediately	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
bag	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
usually	O
packed	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
S.	O
I.	O
and	O
G.	O
underneath	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
bag	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Wainewright	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Morgan	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
basket	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
straw	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Maynes	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
owing	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
basket	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
there	O
was	O
anything	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
straw	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
763.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Church	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	O
CHURCH	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
lost	O
a	O
cask	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
transaction	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cask	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
in	O
Distaff-lane	B-place
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CUNNINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Shaw	O
and	O
Church	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
rolling	O
the	O
hogshead	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
putting	O
the	O
pin	O
in	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
rolled	O
it	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
comrade	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
masters	O
'	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
masters	O
'	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
hogshead	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
hogshead	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Church	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Distaff-lane	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
hogsheads	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
waggon	O
unloading	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
my	O
coat	O
might	O
have	O
touched	O
the	O
hogshead	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
hand	O
was	O
never	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Publicly	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
764.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
Teathers	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	O
SEDDON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partner	O
ship	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Seddon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
feather-room	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
of	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
;	O
a	O
small	O
bag	O
of	O
feathers	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
wood	O
in	O
his	O
inside	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
know	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
bag	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bag	O
or	O
the	O
feathers	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
remarkable	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
toMess	O
.	O
Seddon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
feathers	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Alexander	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
corroborated	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Martin	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Francis	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Seddon	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
next	O
to	O
impossible	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
feathers	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
feathers	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
feather-room	O
;	O
the	O
bag	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
765.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
seven	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
seven	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
possession	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
766.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EARLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
sixty-nine	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Pussord	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
PUSSORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
204	O
,	O
Upper	B-place
Thames-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
Mary-Ann	B-pers
Pussord	I-pers
,	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
BATES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
patterns	O
to	O
shew	O
his	O
aunt	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
aunt	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
what	O
ribbon	O
he	O
liked	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
shewed	O
him	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
another	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
ribbon	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
step	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
turn	O
out	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
dared	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
rolls	O
of	O
ribbon	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
ours	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
for	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pussord	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
honestly	O
bought	O
these	O
ribbons	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
767.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
ABIJAH	B-pers
PENNY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Excise	O
watchman	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
Chester-quay	B-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
scuttle	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cutting	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
letting	O
the	O
coffee	O
run	O
into	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
Smith	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
bags	O
belonging	O
to	O
different	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
this	O
bag	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
quays	O
and	O
the	O
Thames	O
Police	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
coffee	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
coffee	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
coffee	O
to	O
Hunter	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
coffee	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
coffee	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
picking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
45	O
.	O
Fourteen	O
days	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
768.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RAWEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Glenning	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macbean	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Gawthrop	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
at	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
West-dock	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
lumper	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	B-place
Alexander	I-place
;	O
she	O
was	O
lying	O
right	O
abreast	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
search	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
labourers	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
searching	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
run	O
forward	O
on	O
the	O
forecastle	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
to	O
contain	O
sugar	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
heel	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
's	O
bowsprit	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
raw	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
at	O
the	O
Shadwell	O
Police-office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
sugar	O
of	O
that	O
quality	O
in	O
the	O
ship	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
captain	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Peter	O
Wright	O
Gawthrop	O
.	O
(	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holebrook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
Wilson	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
GAWTHROP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
Alexander	O
,	O
the	O
owner	O
s	O
are	O
Alexander	O
Donaldson	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Glenning	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macbean	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
threw	O
down	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
canvas	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
wiping	O
my	O
hands	O
with	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
60	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Wet	O
Docks	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Dogs	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
769.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PIPER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
glass	O
quart	O
bottle	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
gin	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tunbridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bottle	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
770.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
pannikin	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flinn	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
except	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
extorted	O
by	O
a	O
promise	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
771.	O
JOSEPH-ALFORD	B-pers
SAVILLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
mustin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Renaud	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
RENAUD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
51	O
,	O
Lower	B-place
Brook-street	I-place
,	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
an	O
elderly	O
man	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
enquired	O
for	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
floor	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
elderly	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
shall	O
we	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
these	O
apartments	O
are	O
lett	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
floor	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
shape	O
as	O
the	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
,	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
situation	O
was	O
very	O
airy	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
enquired	O
concerning	O
a	O
servant	O
's	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
kitchen	O
for	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
awkward	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
again	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
like	O
those	O
apartments	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
they	O
wouldsoon	O
be	O
to	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
those	O
rooms	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
army	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
navy	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
would	O
bear	O
a-hand	O
,	O
another	O
sailor	O
would	O
soon	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
answered	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
proper	O
sea	O
phrase	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bed-room	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
liked	O
that	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
larger	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
them	O
equally	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
correct	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
ascertain	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
stepping	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
follow	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
recollected	O
I	O
should	O
leave	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
apartments	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
told	O
man	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
returning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
elderly	O
man	O
went	O
down	O
towards	O
,	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
cotton	O
band	O
hanging	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
With	O
his	O
hat	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pardon	O
me	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
whether	O
in	O
my	O
hurry	O
I	O
knocked	O
his	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
came	O
off	O
by	O
touching	O
the	O
band	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
hat	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
caught	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
the	O
crown	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
gown	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
which	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
open	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
honour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
suppose	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
my	O
appearance	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
merely	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hit	O
of	O
fun	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
landing	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
Jack	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
hearing	O
me	O
scream	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
screamed	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Simpson	O
,	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
stole	O
my	O
gown	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
Simpson	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
elderly	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
your	O
gown	O
lying	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
drawer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
wardrobein	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Japan	O
Muslin	O
gown	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Renaud	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
an	O
elderly	O
man	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lady	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lady	O
directly	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
elderly	O
man	O
was	O
then	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
Jack	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
lady	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
between	O
a	O
run	O
and	O
a	O
walk	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
her	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Dalby	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
directly	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
clapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Brook-street	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
you	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stealher	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
very	O
timid	O
and	O
frightened	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
need	O
be	O
under	O
no	O
apprehension	O
of	O
my	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
intention	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
alarmed	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
perfectly	O
reconciled	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
supposing	O
she	O
was	O
perfectly	O
reconciled	O
,	O
having	O
her	O
gown	O
left	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
brick	O
layer	O
's	O
boy	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
immediately	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Dalby	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dalby	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
at	O
seeing	O
such	O
a	O
mob	O
round	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
seeing	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
boy	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
return	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
very	O
quietly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
not	O
finding	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
they	O
proposed	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
772.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STOKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lefevre	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
LEFEVRE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Robert	O
Lefevre	O
,	O
a	O
seaman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
abroad	O
in	O
the	O
East-India	O
service	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
several	O
men	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
Red-lion-street	B-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Stokes	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
walked	O
and	O
talked	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
.	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
insist	O
upon	O
walking	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
his	O
company	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
dragged	O
his	O
hand	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
pushed	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
with	O
half-a-guinea	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
last	O
seen	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
changed	O
one	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
highway	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sober	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
drank	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
glasses	O
of	O
spirits	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
some	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
liquor	O
had	O
you	O
had	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
drank	O
one	O
glass	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
one	O
with	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
glass	O
coming	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
Ship	O
and	O
Horseshoe	O
;	O
my	O
friend	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
nutmeggrater	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
half-a-guinea	O
remaining	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
9d	O
.	O
in	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
you	O
were	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
terrible	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
across	O
from	O
Red-lion-street	O
to	O
Essex-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
nutmeg	O
grater	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
close	O
up	O
togetherwith	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
woman	O
with	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
young	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
called	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
walked	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
George-street	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
ship	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
with	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
2l	O
.	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
ship	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
these	O
young	O
men	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
alone	O
;	O
she	O
clapped	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
walked	O
right	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
story	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
told	O
,	O
true	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
773.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WEBBER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GILES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
himself	O
over	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
soap	O
,	O
was	O
lying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
blue	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
blue	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
packing	O
up	O
some	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
other	O
apprentice	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
served	O
him	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
blue	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
three	O
halfpence	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ekelso	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
missed	O
any	O
soap	O
;	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
soap	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
STORER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
blue	O
;	O
he	O
lolled	O
over	O
the	O
soap	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
blue	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
miss	O
the	O
soap	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Ekeiso	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
mottled	O
soap	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
small	O
corner	O
off	O
just	O
before	O
as	O
a	O
sample	O
;	O
the	O
small	O
bit	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EKELSO	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
stable-yard	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
paper	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Magpye-alley	O
;	O
I	O
tapped	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
soap	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Worship-street-office	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
the	O
soap	O
.	O
)	O
Storer	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
cake	O
of	O
soap	O
that	O
I	O
cut	O
the	O
corner	O
from	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
largest	O
piece	O
there	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
timberyard	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
box-maker	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
soap	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nineteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
774.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
YEOMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kingsbury	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KINGSBURY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Hampshire-hog	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Peartree-street	I-place
,	I-place
Goswell-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
poker	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
grate	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
after	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
borrowed	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
bought	O
another	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Salmon	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
we	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Salmon	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
your	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
SALMON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
Kingsbury	O
's	O
hat	O
upon	O
the	O
poker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
tap-room	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
Kingsbury	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hat	O
under	O
the	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
form	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Kingsbury	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
behind	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
served	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
corn	O
and	O
coals	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
porter	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Kingsbury	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
there	O
as	O
a	O
trick	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
55	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1s	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
775.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
goose	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
.	O
EMANUEL	B-pers
CASTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
public-house	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Saunder	I-place
's	I-place
gardens	I-place
,	I-place
Kingsland-road	I-place
:	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
geese	O
of	O
the	O
Leeds	O
waggoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
picked	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
thirteen	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
them	O
up	O
backwards	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
safe	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
hook	O
,	O
separately	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
them	O
up	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
lit	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
his	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
goose	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
different	O
public-houses	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
,	O
in	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goose	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
goose	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
goose	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
has	O
more	O
right	O
to	O
this	O
goose	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
let	O
them	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
by	O
Kingstand-turnpike	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
waggoner	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
clapped	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mason	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
goose	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
this	O
on	O
the	O
hook	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
BROWNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
goose	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Castle	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
goose	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
;	O
Browne	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
for	O
sixteen	O
years	O
.	O
Browne	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
66	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
776.	O
MARY-JANE	B-pers
HASTED	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WHITE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
a	O
plate	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
three	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
other	O
articles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mathew	B-pers
Murdock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
777.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
seven	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
carryway	O
seeds	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soap-maker	O
and	O
perfumer	O
,	O
in	O
Holywell-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
carraway	O
seed	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2d	O
.	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
some	O
yellow	O
,	O
some	O
mottled	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
white	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
Short-street	O
,	O
Cumberland-street	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
first	O
?	O
-	O
Q.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
soap	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Three	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
for	O
soap-stealing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
soap	O
at	O
this	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
himself	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
carraway	O
seeds	O
for	O
his	O
children	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
778.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
bars	O
of	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Alley	O
.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
warehouseman	O
and	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
I	O
attended	O
at	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
nails	O
were	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
usually	O
sold	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wished	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
any	O
promise	O
,	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
inducement	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
collected	O
them	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
fell	O
them	O
by	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
are	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
nail	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
steel	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
five	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
Nails	O
in	O
their	O
passage	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
frequently	O
drop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
drop	O
also	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
nails	O
are	O
of	O
different	O
sizes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MORTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrols	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
in	O
Old-street-road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
very	O
much	O
agitated	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
nails	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
,	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
where	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Houghton	O
,	O
under	O
Charterhouse-wall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
,	O
the	O
wheeler	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Houghton	O
and	O
Mr.	O
James	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
-	O
HOUGHTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
nails	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
going	O
with	O
some	O
nails	O
to	O
the	O
Curtain-road	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
taken	O
any	O
.	O
-	O
James	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
nails	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
nails	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Martin	O
;	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
nails	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
-	O
LANGER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
steel	O
bars	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
779.	O
JAMES	B-pers
THANE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Cortissos	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cortissos	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	B-pers
of	I-pers
Excise	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Fourth	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
,	O
or	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
MAJOR	B-pers
PRATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Brandon	O
and	O
Co.	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
coffee	O
in	O
their	O
warehouses	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Excise	O
Lock	O
,	O
(	O
proves	O
the	O
firm	O
as	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Excise-Locker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
lock	O
up	O
the	O
doors	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
labourers	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Thomas	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
information	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
locked	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
intimated	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
were	O
carrying	O
on	O
wrong	O
practices	O
;	O
I	O
now	O
had	O
an	O
intention	O
of	O
searching	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
touched	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
contained	O
coffee	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
in	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
labourers	O
into	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thane	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
deliver	O
up	O
this	O
coffee	O
,	O
or	O
