TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1802	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SIXTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1802	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
GILES	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
SOULDEN	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
PAUL	B-pers
LE	I-pers
MESURIER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MACKENZIE	I-pers
MACAULEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CADELL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Eadys	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Looker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Springall	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coke	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Greaves	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Besom	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hacking	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Elborough	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Widt	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wegevina	I-pers
,	O
Stephen-James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
George-Wren	B-pers
le	I-pers
Grand	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Huxley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
James-Edward	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wightman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barling	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Files	I-pers
.	O
494.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
EMBLIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
being	O
employed	O
as	O
clerk	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Benbow	I-pers
,	O
gentleman	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
such	O
employment	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
receive	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
master	O
,	O
a	O
banker	O
's	O
draft	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
2091	O
.	O
11s	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
afterwards	O
embezzle	O
,	O
secrete	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
draft	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jurors	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
thereby	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
draft	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Benbow	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Banknotes	O
,	O
value	O
200l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Benbow	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	O
BENBOW	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
You	O
are	O
an	O
attorney	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
chambers	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
service	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
draft	O
was	O
presented	O
at	O
my	O
chambers	O
for	O
209l	O
.	O
11s	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chambers	O
very	O
soon	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half-past	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
Messrs.	O
Gosling	O
,	O
for	O
209l	O
.	O
11s	O
.	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
draft	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
draft	O
upon	O
the	O
desk	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Gosling	O
and	O
Sharpe	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Esdailes	O
'	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
draft	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
presented	O
at	O
my	O
chambers	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
chambers	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
returned	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
draft	O
you	O
drew	O
upon	O
Goslings	O
and	O
Sharpe	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Had	O
you	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
drafts	O
to	O
your	O
banker	O
's	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
small	O
amount	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
his	O
dress	O
was	O
then	O
totally	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hair	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
material	O
difference	O
in	O
his	O
appearance	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
intrusted	O
me	O
with	O
drafts	O
for	O
small	O
sums	O
-	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
bill	O
for	O
250l.	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
question	O
put	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
sending	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
bankers	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
did	O
send	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
draft	O
of	O
250l	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
with	O
160	O
or	O
170l	O
.	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
EWINGS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
cashier	O
to	O
Goslings	O
and	O
Sharpe	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
pay	O
a	O
check	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
's	O
of	O
209l	O
.	O
11s.	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
50l	O
.	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
51	O
,	O
9410	O
,	O
6304	O
,	O
and	O
1644.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Do	O
you	O
know	O
at	O
what	O
hour	O
you	O
paid	O
that	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
ten	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
disguised	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
whatever	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
so	O
altered	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
some	O
difficulty	O
in	O
knowing	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
check	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	O
DAVIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
change	O
four	O
50l	O
.	O
notes	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
10	O
tens	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
fives	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
4	O
fifties	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
No	O
.	O
9410	O
,	O
6304	O
,	O
1644	O
,	O
and	O
51	O
;	O
the	O
notes	O
that	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
posted	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sutton	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Sutton	O
took	O
the	O
four	O
50l	O
.	O
notes	O
to	O
another	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
indorsed	O
them	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
J.	O
Emblin	O
,	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hand-writing	O
indorsed	O
upon	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Benbow	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Benbow	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
gave	O
him	O
this	O
order	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
any	O
notes	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
three	O
notes	O
,	O
each	O
for	O
10l	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
8632	O
,	O
8633	O
,	O
and	O
8634	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ATKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bath	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
two	O
Banknotes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
10l	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
8634	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
5l	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
8717.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Davis	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
numbers	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Atkins	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
where	O
his	O
lodgings	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
twenty	O
half-guineas	O
and	O
sixteen	O
seven-shilling	O
pieces	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
guineas	O
,	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
seven-shilling	O
pieces	O
in	O
change	O
for	O
the	O
notes	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
bankers	O
,	O
or	O
Bank	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
which	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
afraid	O
of	O
carrying	O
them	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
of	O
an	O
evening	O
when	O
he	O
employed	O
girls	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
changed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
from	O
him	O
any	O
directions	O
respecting	O
any	O
box	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Southampton	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
two	O
10l	O
.	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
8632	O
,	O
and	O
8633	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
two	O
5l	O
.	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
8720	O
,	O
and	O
8725	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
detained	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
has	O
the	O
watch	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
that	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
refused	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Ford	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
received	O
a	O
reward	O
for	O
apprehending	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Do	O
you	O
expect	O
a	O
reward	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
reward	O
offered	O
certainly	O
.	O
JOHN-CROSSLEY	O
COGAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Efdailes	O
'	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
draft	O
for	O
payment	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
,	O
for	O
209l	O
.	O
11s	O
.	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Benbow	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
bill	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Cogan	O
took	O
up	O
for	O
you	O
at	O
Efdailes	O
'	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
make	O
my	O
defence	O
,	O
I	O
submit	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
my	O
case	O
comes	O
within	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
breach	O
of	O
trust	O
;	O
the	O
act	O
expresses	O
merchants	O
,	O
bankers	O
and	O
tradesmen	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Benbow	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
considered	O
either	O
as	O
a	O
tradesman	O
,	O
a	O
banker	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
merchant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
The	O
act	O
says	O
,	O
bankers	O
,	O
merchants	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
42	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
495.	O
JAMES	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
an	O
elephant	O
's	O
tooth	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitehorn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HINTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
gangsman	O
,	O
at	O
Galley-quay	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
repeating	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
)	O
on	O
Friday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
landing	O
some	O
elephant	O
's	O
teeth	O
from	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Union	O
;	O
after	O
having	O
landed	O
a	O
quantity	O
,	O
we	O
placed	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
weigher	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
gate-way	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
tooth	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
gangsman	O
,	O
responsible	O
for	O
these	O
elephants	O
'	O
teeth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
weigher	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
tooth	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
DAVIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
weighter	O
at	O
Galley-quay	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
tooth	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
away	O
up	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
towards	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
partners	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
tooth	O
;	O
)	O
Green	O
is	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
this	O
tooth	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
gangsman	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
tooth	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
the	O
ship	O
mark	O
and	O
tvhe	O
number	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Customhouse	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
being	O
paid	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
counting	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
tooth	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Publicly	O
whipped	O
100	O
yards	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
near	O
Galley-quay	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
496.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TYLER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
eight	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
PETER	O
PEARSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
nephew	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ann	O
Pearson	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
:	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
coffee	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
by	O
our	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
accidentally	O
through	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
collecting	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
some	O
coffee	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
carman	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
cart	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
drove	O
the	O
cart	O
for	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
take	O
some	O
coffee	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
Tyler	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
held	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
gateway	O
,	O
into	O
an	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Tyler	O
put	O
the	O
coffee	O
into	O
Lucas	O
's	O
shirt	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
street-keeper	O
just	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Lucas	O
opposite	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Tyler	O
taking	O
another	O
hat-full	O
of	O
coffee	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
both	O
well	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
guinea	O
from	O
another	O
man	O
you	O
caught	O
stealing	O
coffee	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
a	O
man	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
offered	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
What	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
carwoman	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
answerable	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LUDLAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
:	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Lucas	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
coffee	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Tyler	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
WOOD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
coffee	O
safe	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
at	O
Brewer's-quay	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
coffee	O
gone	O
.	O
ROBERT	O
WRIGHT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gangsmen	O
on	O
Brewer's-quay	O
;	O
I	O
landed	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
cargo	O
;	O
this	O
bag	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
weighed	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
after	O
wards	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
weighed	O
only	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
deficiency	O
of	O
eight	O
pounds	O
.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
what	O
coffee	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Tyler	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Pearson	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Tyler	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
both	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
drive	O
a	O
cart	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
Lucas	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
29	O
.	O
Tyler	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
29	O
.	O
Whipped	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
497.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
EARL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
printed	O
bound	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
printed	O
bound	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LAYCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
1	I-place
,	I-place
Long-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
shelf	O
at	O
each	O
of	O
my	O
windows	O
fastened	O
into	O
the	O
wood	O
work	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
having	O
repeatedly	O
lost	O
books	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
right	O
behind	O
the	O
partition	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
a	O
window	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
a	O
push	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
his	O
bosom	O
two	O
books	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
printed	O
bound	O
books	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
an	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
marked	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
with	O
a	O
pencil	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
string	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
without	O
the	O
string	O
being	O
removed	O
.	O
(	O
Francis	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
books	O
lying	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
them	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
;	O
my	O
poor	O
mother	O
has	O
been	O
blind	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
498.	O
ANN	B-pers
PRATT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	O
CHADWICK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
BOWMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street-door	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
cloak	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
and	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chadwick	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
pots	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pots	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
499.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
THROPP	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
three	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Titus	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
TITUS	B-pers
FARMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Bethnal-green	B-place
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
ducks	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
ROBERT	O
PULLER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Farmer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
among	O
the	O
ducks	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
ducks	O
cry	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
catch	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
stirred	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
fence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
sideof	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
assistance	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
three	O
live	O
ducks	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
counted	O
the	O
ducks	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
short	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
found	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
ducks	O
we	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
ducks	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Twenty-one	O
dozen	O
and	O
five	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
You	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
ducks	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
remarkable	O
in	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
those	O
ducks	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
count	O
them	O
over	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
counted	O
them	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
fought	O
stoutly	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pretty	O
handsome	O
cut	O
;	O
that	O
mark	O
upon	O
his	O
cheek	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
carry	O
to	O
his	O
grave	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
cut	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
a	O
cutlass	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
HOWES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
inspector	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
Bethnal-green	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
watch-house	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
bag	O
and	O
these	O
ducks	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	O
PRYKE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
securing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Farmer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
ducks	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
500.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
ROBERT	I-pers
NEWTON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
were	O
you	O
in	O
Baker-street	O
when	O
the	O
balloon	O
went	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
North	B-place
Baker-street	I-place
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
balloon	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
crowd	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
that	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
when	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
squeezed	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
While	O
you	O
were	O
so	O
pressed	O
,	O
somebody	O
took	O
your	O
watch	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
,	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Close	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
him	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
pressed	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
one	O
but	O
him	O
;	O
several	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
hands	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
gang	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Was	O
he	O
one	O
that	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
hands	O
to	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
The	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
induced	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Because	O
he	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
squeezed	O
round	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
me	O
fast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
him	O
pressing	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Was	O
the	O
pressure	O
while	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
going	O
or	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
distinctly	O
perceive	O
Charles	O
Williams	O
press	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
only	O
conclude	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
from	O
seeing	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
pressed	O
upon	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
distinctly	O
you	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
press	O
upon	O
you	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
stick	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
distinctly	O
press	O
upon	O
you	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
attempting	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
,	O
immediately	O
the	O
crowd	O
pressed	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
press	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
absolutely	O
saw	O
him	O
press	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
saw	O
him	O
press	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
At	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
balloon	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
spectators	O
pressing	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bull	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
pressure	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
more	O
pressure	O
upon	O
you	O
than	O
there	O
was	O
upon	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
pressing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
great	O
pressing	O
upon	O
every	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
did	O
not	O
lift	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
wasnot	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
From	O
whence	O
do	O
you	O
conclude	O
that	O
they	O
meant	O
to	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
by	O
lifting	O
up	O
their	O
hands	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
They	O
held	O
their	O
hands	O
to	O
me	O
almost	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
crowd	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
your	O
watch	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Baker-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
James	O
Munyard	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
MAYHEW	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
conductors	O
of	O
the	O
patrol	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Were	O
you	O
in	O
North	O
Baker-street	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
ballon	O
went	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
other	O
men	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
About	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
balloon	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
rather	O
more	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
narrow	O
passage	O
between	O
the	O
carts	O
where	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
to	O
pass	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
that	O
passage	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
pushing	O
and	O
huslling	O
people	O
about	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
front	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
doing	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
particluar	O
thing	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
this	O
party	O
who	O
were	O
pushing	O
the	O
people	O
about	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
immediately	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
patrols	O
behind	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
a	O
scuffle	O
enfued	O
;	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrols	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
up	O
Baker-street	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
stoop	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
his	O
shoe	O
up	O
at	O
heel	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
watch	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
James	O
Munyard	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MUNYARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrols	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
North	O
Baker-street	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
balloon	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
Mayhew	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Mayhew	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
bad	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
from	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
sung	O
out	O
,	O
serve	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
r	O
,	O
serve	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
you	O
were	O
struck	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Afterwards	O
;	O
the	O
patrol	O
came	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
dispersed	O
the	O
mob	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
this	O
watch	O
down	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
four	O
yards	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
stooped	O
down	O
upon	O
my	O
hands	O
and	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Ward	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
some	O
carts	O
standing	O
there	O
-	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
bridge	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Baker-street	O
,	O
North	O
,	O
which	O
leads	O
to	O
a	O
field	O
.	O
Mayhew	O
.	O
This	O
bridge	O
is	O
close	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
carts	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
drawn	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
for	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
balloon	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Ward	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
number	O
and	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
Downham	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
4958	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
curiousity	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
balloon	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
bridge	O
,	O
somebody	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mad	O
bullock	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
press	O
and	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
thieves	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
scuffle	O
ensued	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
watch	O
produced	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
watch	O
from	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ford	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
his	O
oath	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
his	O
oath	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
violently	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
501.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
RODGERS	I-pers
,	O
MARY	B-pers
RODGERS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HORN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
,	O
made	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
the	O
current	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
did	O
coin	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
their	O
allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
RODGERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
of	O
the	O
Police	O
,	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
some	O
information	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
what	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Suffolk-street	O
,	O
Pentonville	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
Charlotte-place	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
Rodgers	O
,	O
himself	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
rented	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Describe	O
what	O
you	O
observed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Suffolk-street	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
two	O
rooms	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
noticed	O
that	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
story	O
had	O
cloths	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
exceedingly	O
dirty	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
view	O
whatever	O
of	O
any	O
thingthat	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
person	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
from	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
till	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
went	O
in	O
or	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Rodgers	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
wipe	O
her	O
hands	O
and	O
arms	O
with	O
a	O
cloth	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
returned	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
contained	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
;	O
she	O
instantly	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
person	O
went	O
in	O
or	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Horn	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
how	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
instantly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
no	O
person	O
went	O
in	O
or	O
came	O
out	O
till	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
then	O
Mary	B-pers
Rodgers	I-pers
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
returned	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
with	O
a	O
loaf	O
and	O
some	O
butter	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
then	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
key	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
no	O
person	O
went	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
till	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Springall	O
,	O
a	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Solicitor	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
Horn	O
should	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
Horn	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
Springall	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
;	O
Horn	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
wine-vault	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Suffolk-street	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Daniel	O
Holland	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
more	O
assistance	O
and	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
;	O
when	O
Horn	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
person	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
till	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
;	O
Horn	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
Holland	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
Horn	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
looked	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
Holland	O
return	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
concluded	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Holland	O
to	O
rap	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
maid	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Rodgers	I-pers
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
again	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
started	O
in	O
;	O
Horn	O
and	O
Mary	O
Rodgers	O
were	O
below	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Holland	O
to	O
take	O
Horn	O
and	O
Mary	O
Rodgers	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
Rodgers	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Holland	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
teaster	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
rather	O
inclining	O
towards	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
struck	O
my	O
attention	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
furnace	O
made	O
of	O
brick	O
in	O
the	O
chimney-place	O
;	O
that	O
furnace	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
it	O
of	O
coke	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
coke	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
fire-place	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
crucibles	O
,	O
some	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
furnace	O
,	O
some	O
upon	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
some	O
had	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
metal	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
new	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
used	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
I	O
observed	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bench	O
fixed	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
could	O
sit	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
sciffars	O
,	O
files	O
,	O
and	O
plyers	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
this	O
child	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
containing	O
these	O
blanks	O
,	O
which	O
adhere	O
together	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
different	O
coin	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
metal	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
or	O
lifting	O
the	O
melting	O
pots	O
off	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
that	O
struck	O
my	O
attention	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
flask	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
used	O
in	O
coining	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
trough	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
sounder	O
's	O
earth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
common	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
hurry	O
in	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
flask	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
founder	O
's	O
earth	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
flask	O
;	O
the	O
earth	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
these	O
frames	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
with	O
a	O
mallet	O
till	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
hard	O
substance	O
;	O
the	O
oil	O
and	O
lamp	O
black	O
are	O
put	O
over	O
it	O
to	O
harden	O
the	O
earth	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
fresh	O
metal	O
more	O
easy	O
;	O
the	O
impression	O
is	O
generally	O
taken	O
from	O
good	O
coin	O
;	O
the	O
metal	O
is	O
poured	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
the	O
impression	O
without	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
dye	O
or	O
press	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
can	O
take	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
the	O
coin	O
of	O
different	O
kingdoms	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
founder	O
's	O
earth	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
flask	O
;	O
close	O
by	O
that	O
trough	O
was	O
hanging	O
these	O
two	O
sieves	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
which	O
are	O
used	O
for	O
sitting	O
the	O
earth	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
state	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
exceedingly	O
black	O
,	O
so	O
black	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
the	O
sieves	O
where	O
they	O
hung	O
up	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
composition	O
for	O
hardening	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
made	O
of	O
black	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
lamp	O
black	O
and	O
oil	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
burnt	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
coke	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
sand-paper	O
,	O
some	O
used	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
What	O
is	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
sandpaper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
rough	O
edges	O
after	O
the	O
sciffars	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
cut	O
them	O
apart	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
pair	O
of	O
players	O
,	O
and	O
filed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
sand-paper	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
rough	O
edges	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pipkin	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
,	O
)	O
with	O
some	O
oil	O
and	O
some	O
cotton	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
burn	O
this	O
compositioin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
flask	O
to	O
harden	O
the	O
earth	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
fit	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
impression	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
this	O
dirty	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
contained	O
this	O
money	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cork	O
;	O
the	O
cork	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
smoothing	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
unfinished	O
coin	O
;	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
piece	O
adhering	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
J.	O
S.	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
finished	O
state	O
,	O
with	O
J.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
could	O
sit	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
place	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
sit	O
for	O
circulation	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
were	O
these	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
discoloured	O
since	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
copper	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
common	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
very	O
soon	O
discoloured	O
;	O
the	O
utteres	O
generally	O
keep	O
them	O
in	O
papers	O
separately	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
You	O
mixed	O
that	O
shilling	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Would	O
that	O
mixing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
tenders	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
colouring	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
this	O
paper	O
,	O
containing	O
white	O
vitriol	O
,	O
(	O
produce	O
it	O
,	O
)	O
which	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
dimness	O
to	O
the	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
containing	O
white	O
arsenic	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
for	O
mixing	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
white	O
arsenic	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
crucible	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
comes	O
out	O
quite	O
white	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
this	O
apron	O
by	O
the	O
bed-side	O
,	O
which	O
smelt	O
very	O
strong	O
of	O
aquafortis	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
copper	O
cut	O
into	O
pieces	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
surnace	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Were	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
found	O
those	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
when	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
make	O
farther	O
search	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Springall	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
shed	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
brush	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
,	O
)	O
which	O
smelt	O
very	O
strong	O
of	O
aqua	O
fortis	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
shed	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
shed	O
without	O
passing	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
also	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
black	O
ing	O
and	O
black	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
mixed	O
up	O
for	O
burning	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Are	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
produced	O
to-day	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
coining	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
coming	O
,	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
condition	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
their	O
persons	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Rodgers	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
old	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
arms	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
yellow	O
,	O
green	O
,	O
and	O
black	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Horn	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Rodgers	I-pers
were	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
very	O
duty	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
sort	O
of	O
dirt	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
about	O
the	O
palm	O
of	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
fingers	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Holland	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
Horn	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Would	O
aqua-fortis	O
give	O
that	O
appearance	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
;	O
Horn	O
afterwards	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
from	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
his	O
hands	O
dirty	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
distance	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
an	O
apron	O
of	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
this	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
below	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bason	O
with	O
some	O
water	O
,	O
which	O
some	O
person	O
had	O
washed	O
their	O
hands	O
in	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
aqua-fortis	O
was	O
a	O
necessary	O
ingredient	O
in	O
the	O
colouring	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
material	O
ingredient	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bevil	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
cases	O
where	O
silver	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
composition	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
silver	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
aqua-fortis	O
must	O
be	O
used	O
;	O
but	O
here	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
composition	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Aqua-fortis	O
is	O
necessary	O
in	O
every	O
process	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
shilling	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
indictment	O
is	O
framed	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
persons	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Mint	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
got	O
that	O
shilling	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
you	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
At	O
the	O
examination	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
as	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
discoloured	O
;	O
they	O
appeared	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
passable	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Thursday	O
much	O
discoloured	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
last	O
process	O
through	O
which	O
they	O
pass	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
dulled	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
passed	O
through	O
that	O
process	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
It	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
state	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
good	O
judge	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
common	O
tradesman	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Many	O
common	O
tradesmen	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
this	O
shilling	O
to	O
be	O
altered	O
between	O
the	O
Saturday	O
and	O
the	O
Thursday	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
It	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
dulled	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Am	O
I	O
to	O
understand	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Thursday	O
it	O
was	O
passable	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
In	O
my	O
opinion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
know	O
Horn	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
Horn	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Horn	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
just	O
before	O
-	O
how	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
you	O
were	O
concealed	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
;	O
the	O
windows	O
up	O
stairs	O
were	O
half	O
blinded	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
blanket	O
hung	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
These	O
people	O
were	O
apprehended	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
And	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
examined	O
till	O
Thursday	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
the	O
King	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Parliament-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
was	O
attending	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
stood	O
over	O
to	O
Thursday	O
.	O
JOHN	O
SPRINGALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vernon	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
with	O
Rodgers	O
,	O
were	O
looking	O
from	O
some	O
window	O
which	O
commanded	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
You	O
were	O
particularly	O
directed	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Horn	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
observations	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Horn	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
first	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
suspicious	O
manner	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
wine-vaults	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
having	O
some	O
gin	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
bottle	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
singular	O
that	O
he	O
passed	O
one	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
farthest	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
from	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
first	O
come	O
;	O
Rodgers	O
then	O
followed	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
watching	O
;	O
after	O
waiting	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Horn	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
timet	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
each	O
way	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
houset	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
Rodgers	O
and	O
Holland	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Rodgers	O
,	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
fash	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
two	O
bags	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
fell	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
too	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
retire	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
,	O
get	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
bags	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
containing	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
good	O
pattern	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
pattern	O
six-pences	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
which	O
exactly	O
corresponds	O
with	O
the	O
impression	O
on	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
pattern	O
shillings	O
,	O
you	O
mean	O
shillings	O
to	O
cast	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bevil	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
shillings	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
particularly	O
attend	O
to	O
the	O
shilling	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sufficiently	O
conversant	O
with	O
the	O
good	O
coin	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
coin	O
to	O
know	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
.	O
DANIEL	O
HOLLAND	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
Police	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
extra	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
with	O
Rodgers	O
when	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
collected	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
CALEB-	O
EDWARD	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Solicitor	O
for	O
the	O
Mint	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Can	O
you	O
explain	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
these	O
implements	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
further	O
explanation	O
than	O
Rodgers	O
has	O
given	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
a	O
very	O
correct	O
explanation	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
apparatus	O
is	O
such	O
as	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
process	O
that	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
adopted	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
aqua-fortis	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
necessary	O
to	O
the	O
colouring	O
;	O
these	O
blanks	O
contain	O
no	O
particle	O
of	O
silver	O
whatever	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
them	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
mode	O
of	O
colouring	O
them	O
would	O
be	O
by	O
doing	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
solution	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
aqua-fortis	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
blanks	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
coloured	O
myself	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
that	O
by	O
which	O
this	O
process	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
compleated	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
solution	O
of	O
silver	O
found	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
But	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
a	O
brush	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
smelt	O
of	O
aqua-fortis	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
brush	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
used	O
for	O
stirring	O
the	O
pickle	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
materials	O
found	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
colour	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
solution	O
nor	O
any	O
vessel	O
with	O
the	O
remains	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
one	O
instance	O
in	O
twenty	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
do	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
only	O
prepare	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
pickle	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
the	O
solution	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
immediately	O
want	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Being	O
in	O
small	O
quantities	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
easily	O
thrown	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Were	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
shilling	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
subject	O
matter	O
of	O
this	O
inquiry	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
state	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
confident	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
coloured	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
incautious	O
person	O
certainly	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
coloured	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
lost	O
part	O
of	O
its	O
colour	O
,	O
but	O
even	O
then	O
an	O
incautious	O
person	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
an	O
incautious	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
passed	O
to	O
a	O
tradesman	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
skilled	O
in	O
silver	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
certainly	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bevil	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
pattern	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
is	O
from	O
the	O
dye	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
1758	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
consider	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
pattern	O
of	O
this	O
shilling	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
graining	O
at	O
the	O
edges	O
is	O
very	O
full	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
dye	O
so	O
wornas	O
to	O
lose	O
the	O
grain	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
letters	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
it	O
more	O
remarkable	O
,	O
J.S	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
a	O
resemblance	O
to	O
the	O
pattern	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
explain	O
to	O
you	O
why	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
one	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
round	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
REUBEN	B-pers
FLETCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Does	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
the	O
current	O
coin	O
of	O
the	O
realm	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
counterpart	O
of	O
this	O
pattern	O
shilling	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Rodgers	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Mary	O
Rodgers	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Edward	O
Horn	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
502.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CLAYTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
floor-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
,	O
floor-cloth	O
manufacturer	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
57	I-place
,	I-place
Broad-street	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
;	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
after	O
my	O
dinner	O
,	O
about	O
half-past	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
nearly	O
opposite	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
reaching	O
over	O
some	O
Chinese	O
railing	O
that	O
was	O
fixed	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
try	O
the	O
hatch	O
door	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
scraper	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
from	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
floor-cloth	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
oil-cloth	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
65	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
503.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
ROBINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
two	O
doe	O
slops	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
unsewed	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lingham	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
employ	O
;	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
duplicates	O
which	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
-	O
PRITCHARD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Short's-gardens	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Robins	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
wife	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
pledged	O
these	O
articles	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Lingham	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sign	O
this	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
voluntary	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
read	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
purchased	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
now	O
produced	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
Lucy	O
Robins	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
CROWAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
made	O
these	O
leather-breeches	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
unsewed	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
these	O
gloves	O
made	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lingham	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lingham	O
.	O
The	O
leather	O
breeches	O
are	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
doe	O
slops	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
they	O
are	O
known	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
we	O
stamped	O
every	O
skin	O
we	O
had	O
with	O
a	O
stamp	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
gloves	O
are	O
stamped	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
nankeens	O
by	O
the	O
particular	O
way	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
them	O
made	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
an	O
exclusive	O
right	O
of	O
making	O
them	O
so	O
by	O
patent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
sold	O
any	O
leather	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
GRACE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Robins	O
since	O
her	O
husband	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
trouble	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
drinking	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Robins	O
,	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
Easter	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
leather	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
damaged	O
leather	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
504.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SPIKES	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
SOLLIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
21s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joyce	B-pers
Duce	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Duce	O
,	O
at	O
Pancras	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Sollis	O
go	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Duce	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
basket	O
hung	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Duce	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
way	O
towards	O
Tottencourt-road	O
,	O
Sollis	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
JOYCE	O
DUCE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
alarm	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
under	O
a	O
wall	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
walking	O
till	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
run	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
basket	O
down	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Sollis	O
throw	O
down	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Marsh	O
.	O
-	O
STONE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Spikes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
solider	O
afterwards	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
Sollis	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Sollis	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Spikes	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
14	O
.	O
Confined	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
505.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PACKEVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
cotton	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
MARY	O
PHILLIPS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
36	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
road	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Cloth-fair	B-place
into	I-place
Long-lane	I-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
snatched	O
my	O
bundle	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
velvet	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
all	O
through	O
Cloth-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
snatched	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
posts	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
snatched	O
your	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
velvet	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
STEELE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
King-street	O
,	O
Cloth-fair	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Phillips	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
dropped	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
parcel	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
greengrocer	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
New-street	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
parcel	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
right-arm	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
James	O
Steele	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
New-street	O
,	O
into	O
Little	O
Bartholomew-close	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
into	O
a	O
yard	O
that	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
running	O
.	O
(	O
Richard	O
Dean	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
velvet	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
506.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WACY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newhouse	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NEWHOUSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
worsted	O
-	O
weaver	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
a	O
print-shop	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Cree-church	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stopped	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
rush	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
turned	O
on	O
the	O
right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
hurled	O
it	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
pocket-book	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
black	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
)	O
JOHN	O
SMITH	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Newhouse	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
sing	O
out	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
an	O
innocent	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
malicious	O
piece	O
of	O
business	O
;	O
my	O
uncle	O
and	O
aunt	O
are	O
now	O
lying	O
bad	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
;	O
I	O
very	O
lately	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Newhouse	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
sworn	O
his	O
life	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
507.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
KING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
dress	O
,	O
value	O
13s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	O
HAYWARD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tailor	O
and	O
salesman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
made	O
waistcoats	O
for	O
me	O
these	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
articles	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Red-lion-market	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
duplicates	O
;	O
among	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
this	O
child	O
's	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Little-Britain	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
produced	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
dress	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
)	O
Hayward	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
dress	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
or	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
frequently	O
left	O
there	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
)	O
``	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
very	O
much	O
lament	O
my	O
inability	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
extreme	O
poverty	O
to	O
procure	O
legal	O
assistance	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
the	O
humanity	O
of	O
your	O
Lordship	O
to	O
supply	O
that	O
defect	O
;	O
I	O
humbly	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
informing	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
upwards	O
of	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
impeachment	O
of	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
most	O
solemnly	O
assure	O
your	O
Lordship	O
the	O
property	O
pledged	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bought	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
remnants	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
sale	O
at	O
my	O
leisure	O
intervals	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
producing	O
witnesses	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
known	O
for	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
say	O
what	O
character	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
borne	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
my	O
character	O
really	O
is	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
Jail	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
508.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BRADY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Louis	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Sage	I-pers
.	O
LOUIS	O
LE	O
SAGE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
2	I-place
,	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
only	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
two	O
pair	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
standing	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
before	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
his	O
messmate	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
rescued	O
himself	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Le	O
Sage	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
509.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
DALEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
of	O
Bedford-square	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
watch	O
over	O
the	O
chimney-piece	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
hungry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
water	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
12	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
510.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
brass	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
hundred	O
and	O
seven	O
miles	O
from	O
Hyde-park-corner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
to	O
Butcher-row	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
family	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
Anderson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
Anderson	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
cheer	O
,	O
shipmate	O
?	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
what	O
cheer	O
?	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
,	O
which	O
cut	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
ear	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
watch-chain	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
tripped	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
then	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sung	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
robbery	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
but	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
my	O
watchchain	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
watch	O
-	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
chain	O
by	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
chain	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
two	O
other	O
watchmen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
guard	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
guard	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
hold	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
This	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
-	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
There	O
was	O
no	O
moon	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
You	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
afternoon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
gin	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
drink	O
any	O
spirituous	O
liquors	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
your	O
journey	O
towards	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
number	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
They	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
at	O
your	O
watch	O
-	O
had	O
not	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
or	O
felt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
women	O
during	O
that	O
afternoon	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
rightly	O
tell	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
say	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
these	O
women	O
by	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
talking	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
women	O
nor	O
men	O
but	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
forty	O
pounds	O
if	O
this	O
man	O
is	O
convicted	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Justice	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
hanged	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
hanged	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
the	O
blood	O
of	O
any	O
man	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	O
WRIGHT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
watchman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
watch-chain	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
INCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
watchman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
thieves	O
,	O
murder	O
,	O
watchman	O
,	O
cried	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
watch-chain	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch-chain	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
never	O
let	O
go	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
There	O
were	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
about	O
-	O
were	O
there	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
always	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
at	O
that	O
particular	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
It	O
was	O
all	O
done	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
in	O
liquor	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
he	O
drink	O
gin	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
my	O
glass	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drink	O
any	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Townsend	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
-	O
chain	O
-	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
chain	O
by	O
this	O
three-penny-piece	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
cut	O
a	O
notch	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
hole	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
the	O
chain	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
LAW	O
RUSSELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Sun-yard	O
,	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
When	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
On	O
that	O
night	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
fore	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
challenged	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
rushing	O
past	O
against	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
called	O
it	O
a	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
lantern	O
from	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
or	O
two	O
cried	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
chain	O
downthere	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
snatch	O
,	O
or	O
attempt	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
property	O
at	O
all	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
chain	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
sure	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
several	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pass	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
men	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
but	O
women	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
must	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Then	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
headborough	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
led	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
By	O
being	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
guilty	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Then	O
the	O
watchman	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Then	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
because	O
you	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
guilty	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
protect	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
But	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
turn	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
again	O
why	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
to	O
keep	O
guard	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
but	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
give	O
such	O
evidence	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
prove	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proving	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
questions	O
asked	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
asked	O
a	O
question	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Then	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Inch	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
desired	O
any	O
assistance	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
kept	O
his	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Russell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Who	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
What	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
chain	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Inch	O
.	O
)	O
Who	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
chain	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
some	O
person	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
chain	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Russell	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
that	O
other	O
man	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
knows	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
than	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
About	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Anderson	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
tradesman	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Just	O
as	O
the	O
chain	O
was	O
dropped	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
You	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
