TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
JUNE	O
,	O
1802	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1802	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
KNIGHT	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	B-pers
GROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STAINES	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOYDELL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
BROOK	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nunn	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Grierson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Freers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Feltwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perrigal	I-pers
,	O
Folliard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ivatts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keaton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Larn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rosser	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Brennand	I-pers
.	O
419.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
AXFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WESTWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
property	O
from	O
my	O
barge	O
,	O
at	O
Scotland-yard	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
a	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
of	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
supper	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
barge	O
lying	O
along	O
side	O
our	O
barge	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
sleep	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
consented	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cabin	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
last	O
Sunday	O
week	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
BOONE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tailor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
buy	O
old	O
clothes	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28the	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
such	O
good	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
tailor	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
had	O
made	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
thirty-two	O
shillings	O
;	O
on	O
a	O
cross-examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
thirty-six	O
shillings	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
never	O
bought	O
for	O
any	O
such	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
on	O
the	O
jacket	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
jacket	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
shirt	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
his	O
shirt	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
interrogated	O
the	O
man	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coward	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-court	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Coward	O
knew	O
the	O
boy	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
inquired	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
she	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
clothes	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
mother	O
was	O
extremely	O
fond	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
wild	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
let	O
the	O
boy	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
near	O
a	O
month	O
afterwards	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Westwood	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cabin	O
of	O
my	O
barge	O
.	O
Norris	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
things	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DONALDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
420.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PIPER	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Laurie	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
Berwick	O
wharf	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAURIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
from	O
the	O
wharf	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
Leith	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Berwick	O
smack	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Shipping	O
Company	O
of	O
Berwick	O
,	O
the	O
firm	O
of	O
the	O
partnership	O
is	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
boots	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
pair	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pair	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
jacket-pocket	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Piper	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
come	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
vessel	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
clerk	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
gentleman	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
clerks	O
,	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cheap	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Thomas-Coxhead	O
Stevens	O
,	O
Alexander	O
Bowmaker	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sitted	O
themselves	O
;	O
I	O
noticed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boots	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
rent	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
cask	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
dozen	O
pair	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pair	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
rent	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
boots	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
tacked	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
those	O
taken	O
from	O
Piper	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
when	O
we	O
counted	O
the	O
number	O
in	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
there	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
four	O
dozen	O
in	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
four	O
pair	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
where	O
the	O
boots	O
were	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
BOWMAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Laurie	O
's	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
boots	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
called	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
upon	O
business	O
,	O
who	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
rentto	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
cask	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
Berwick	O
wharf	O
in	O
the	O
employ	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Laurie	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
move	O
leather	O
from	O
one	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
losts	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
landed	O
from	O
the	O
vessel	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
out	O
the	O
boots	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
dozen	O
and	O
four	O
pair	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
in	O
Griffiths	O
's	O
jacket-pocket	O
;	O
his	O
jacket	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
a	O
case	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
his	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
boots	O
in	O
his	O
jacket	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Laurie	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
jacket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Laurie	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Griffiths	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
boots	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
jumping	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
loop-hole	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
officer	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
searched	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
Piper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
After	O
Griffiths	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
jacket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Piper	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
jacket	O
on	O
the	O
stool	O
in	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
in	O
each	O
pocket	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
boots	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
(	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Piper	O
.	O
)	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Griffiths	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
Piper	O
submitted	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
very	O
readily	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
GRIFFITHS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Police-office	O
,	O
Lambeth	O
street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Laurie	O
's	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
jacket	O
on	O
the	O
stool	O
in	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Piper	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
jacket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
out	O
of	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
jacket	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
;	O
the	O
lining	O
was	O
tore	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pair	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Laurie	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
He	O
had	O
no	O
hesitation	O
in	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Jones	O
.	O
)	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
soldiers	O
employed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
other	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
always	O
worked	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Laurie	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
boot	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
rent	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
of	O
boots	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
boots	O
were	O
consigned	O
from	O
Scotland	O
in	O
a	O
cask	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
They	O
do	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
about	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
No	O
;	O
Piper	O
certainly	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
the	O
least	O
symptom	O
of	O
criminality	O
or	O
fear	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
wished	O
the	O
Justice	O
not	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
five	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Piper	O
,	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
written	O
defence	O
,	O
stating	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Piper	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
421.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
six	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William-John	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
parish	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Andrew	I-pers
,	I-pers
Holborn	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
workhouse	I-place
,	O
Shoe-lane	B-place
;	O
this	O
property	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
trust	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
responsible	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
lose	O
my	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
,	O
Holborn	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
care	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
nurse	O
to	O
the	O
boys	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
sheets	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
beds	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
boys	O
ward	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
sheets	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
them	O
presently	O
;	O
the	O
overseets	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
till	O
she	O
said	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
laid	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
duplicates	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
were	O
subpoenaed	O
;	O
they	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
sheets	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
William-John	O
Reeves	O
is	O
a	O
church-warden	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	O
Whittingham	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Wilson	O
are	O
overseers	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
They	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
for	O
the	O
parish	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
Shoe-lane	O
workhouse	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
overseers	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
;	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
further	O
than	O
taking	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
stock	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
Thomas	O
Bennett	O
has	O
described	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
six	O
sheets	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TYRRELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
at	O
separate	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
three	O
duplicates	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
pledged	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
so	O
dirty	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
mark	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
had	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LEPARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Bennett	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
had	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
''	O
Shoe-lane	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
''	O
stamped	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
stamp	O
upon	O
them	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
has	O
no	O
mark	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
59	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
422.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SCHOFIELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles-Robert	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
423.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
34lb	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
16s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Levi	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
LEVI	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
at	O
Battle-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
flats	O
of	O
butter	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Strickland	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-market	B-place
;	O
we	O
always	O
return	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
the	O
cloths	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
responsible	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
having	O
the	O
butter	O
booked	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
through	O
Mr.	O
Strickland	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
(	O
Edward	O
Harris	O
corroborated	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
424.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
RASPBERRY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heapy	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEAPY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
in	O
Fore-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
Mr.	O
Heapy	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lad	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
can	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
shop-door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
were	O
lying	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
shop-door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Ironmonger-lane	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
shoes	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
corroborated	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Johnson	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
James	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
Marshalman	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
425.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
INWARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JAMES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
private	O
gentleman	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pocket	O
picked	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
containing	O
a	O
one-pound	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
blackfriar's-bridge	O
towards	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
nearly	B-place
opposite	I-place
Fetter-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
that	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
catch	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
up	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
constables	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
half-way	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
from	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
a	O
one-pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
memorandums	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
much	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
generally	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
carriages	O
passing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
respecting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
book	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
name	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
George	O
Donaldson	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cut	O
across	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
up	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
James	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DONALDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
426.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHAMBRAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
427.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SKINNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Garnett	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GARNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
:	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
yesterday	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
pot	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COLES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
pot	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Producing	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
GARNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Trinity-lane	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
pot	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
settle	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
man	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
of	O
wronging	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
54	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
428.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DEGRANGES	I-pers
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
two	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
table	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TOMPKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinetmaker	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
,	I-place
London-wall	I-place
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
table	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mills	O
,	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
THORBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
calico-glazer	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Goodman's-fields	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Degranges	O
standing	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Tompkin	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
London-wall	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
table	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Tompkins	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Robinson	O
was	O
following	O
him	O
close	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
them	O
talk	O
together	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
the	O
table	O
was	O
split	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mahogany	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
going	O
towards	O
White-cross-street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
DANIEL	O
CARTWRIGHT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
;	O
Rogers	O
and	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Robinson	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
and	O
Degranges	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mills	O
,	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
for	O
9s	O
.	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
backroom	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
Mills	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
harm	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
ROGERS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Cartwright	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
table	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Tompkins	O
)	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thetable	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
;	O
but	O
Mills	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Degranges	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
15	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Mills	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Degranges	O
was	O
afterwards	O
tried	O
upon	O
a	O
capital	O
charge	O
,	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
death	O
.	O
)	O
429.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
seven	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
21s	O
.	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
.	O
NICHOLAS	O
FELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
James-street	B-place
,	I-place
Manchester-square	I-place
,	O
and	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
across	O
the	O
yard	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
washhouse	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
copper	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
shoved	O
me	O
backwards	O
,	O
dropped	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Gray-street	O
,	O
Manchester-square	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JOSEPH	O
RADFORD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Gray-street	O
,	O
Manchester-square	O
;	O
Mr	O
Fell	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
that	O
is	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
with	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
month	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
430.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
APPLETON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
thirty-seven	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
and	O
forty-seven	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milkman	O
:	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
after	O
doing	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
penny-pieces	O
and	O
halfpence	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
in	O
Crown-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
a	O
woman	O
fell	O
down	O
some	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
wheel	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
undressed	O
,	O
about	O
half-past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
bag	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
corn-chandler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
had	O
any	O
connection	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
(	O
William	O
Newman	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
9	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
431.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SIBLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Norden	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
NORDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
several	O
pair	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
would	O
suit	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
staying	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
redcloth	O
waistcoat	O
from	O
a	O
shelf	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
stolen	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Carson	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
for	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
them	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fearnley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
DENJAMIN	O
FEARNLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Norden	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
waistcoats	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Carson	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Norden	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
CARSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
432.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BORCOMBE	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STOKES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
takingfrom	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
seven	O
shilling-piece	O
,	O
and	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
identify	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
BOTH	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
433.	O
EDMUND	B-pers
BRAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
434.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1801	O
,	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
20s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1801	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
bread	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
weekly	O
accounts	O
;	O
he	O
requested	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
one-pound	O
note	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Gray	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
discharge	O
a	O
bill	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
returned	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
basket	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
monies	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
last	O
Friday	O
fortnight	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
awoke	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
mercy	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
mercy	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
acted	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
435.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TAPSTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
whip	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
cart-load	O
of	O
hay	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
load	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
dung	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
victuals	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
load	O
my	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Paddington	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
water	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
victuals	O
,	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
satisfied	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
horses	O
on	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
furlong	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
shovel	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
A	O
gentleman	O
,	O
riding	O
up	O
,	O
desired	O
his	O
footman	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
at	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
CARWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
West-End	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
at	O
Kilburn	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
being	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Buffalo	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
ostler	O
knew	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Bent	O
's	O
coat	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Bent	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drive	O
his	O
team	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
sell	O
off	O
the	O
cart	O
into	O
the	O
high	O
road	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
13d	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
436.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HENTON	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MERRITT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Alexander	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
Id	O
.	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half-crown	O
,	O
and	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
from	O
the	O
Royal	O
Circus	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
George's-fields	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
King's-road	B-place
we	O
met	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
dressed	O
as	O
soldiers	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
a	O
snatch	O
at	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Which	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
John	O
Heaton	O
,	O
the	O
tallest	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
Heaton	O
knocked	O
my	O
brother	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
hedge	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
Merritt	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches-pocket	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
hand	O
over	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
;	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
murder	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
robbing	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
Merritt	O
was	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
Henton	O
said	O
,	O
d-n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
b-r	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
that	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
beautiful	O
moonlight	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
this	O
transaction	O
take	O
in	O
all	O
?	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Several	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
;	O
my	O
father-in-law	O
gave	O
information	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
information	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
transaction	O
long	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
observe	O
their	O
faces	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Merritt	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
found	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Circus	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
soldiers	O
before	O
us	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
suddenly	O
surprized	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
us	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
JOSEPH	O
CRIDLAND	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrole	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
:	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
private	O
road	O
;	O
William	O
Williams	O
and	O
John	O
Austin	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Kenton	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
comrados	O
.	O
and	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
this	O
bludgeon	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
hat	O
from	O
Merritt	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
patrole	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Cridland	O
has	O
related	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
AUSTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Cridland	O
and	O
Williams	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
conductor	O
of	O
that	O
party	O
of	O
patrole	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
road	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Henton	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Merritt	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Henton	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Merritt	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
437.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRAINE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
24s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
TODD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
aunt	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Rackstraw	O
;	O
they	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
a	O
half-shawl	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
requested	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
her	O
shuffling	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
cover	O
something	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
some	O
muslin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
agitated	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
servant-maid	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
neighbour	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Trim	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Trim	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
her	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
yards	O
down	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
towards	O
Mr	O
.	O
Trim	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
muslin	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Have	O
you	O
no	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
frequently	O
bought	O
things	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
Does	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Isaac	O
Thomas	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
AARON	B-pers
TRIM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Todd	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Todd	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
something	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
pulled	O
the	O
muslin	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
some	O
trepidation	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Todd	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
aunt	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
shawl	O
;	O
Mr	O
Todd	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
her	O
mistress	O
(	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
her	O
wages	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
purchasing	O
some	O
articles	O
of	O
wearing-apparel	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
438.	O
PETER	B-pers
CARRONS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
one-half	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Oldroyd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Masheter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	O
GROSS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Oldroyd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Masheter	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
cast	O
his	O
eyes	O
round	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
tohim	O
,	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
against	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
which	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
secured	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
calico	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Two	O
boys	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
dropped	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
calico	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
12	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
439.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Barham	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BARHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
footman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wlhtaker	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half-past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
had	O
been	O
having	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
suspicion	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
court	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
from	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
coat	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
an	O
occasional	O
waterman	O
to	O
coaches	O
.	O
-	O
FLETCHER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stooping	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
coat	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
water	O
thrown	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
coat	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
440.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SCHOLER	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEFEVRE	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
three	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
thousand	O
six	O
hundred	O
and	O
eighty	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Currie	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Court	O
.	O
Charging	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Raine	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
carman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Currie	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
halfpence	O
from	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Bethnal-green	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
scavenger	O
's	O
cart	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
almost	O
immediately	O
and	O
saw	O
thde	O
rail	O
board	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
let	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
again	O
in	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
comes	O
up	O
into	O
Wentworth-street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
contained	O
five	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
copper	O
in	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
old	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
new	O
halfpence	O
.	O
ANN	O
JENK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
George-street	O
,	O
Spiralfields	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Scholer	O
lift	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
let	O
the	O
tail	O
board	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
towards	O
George-yard	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
George-yard	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lesevre	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
heard	O
somebody	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
Lesevre	O
upon	O
the	O
landingplace	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
and	O
welcome	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
men	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SPARROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
21	O
,	O
George-yard	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
upon	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
19.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Wright	O
.	O
)	O
Who	O
removed	O
the	O
box	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
(	O
Richard	B-pers
Osman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
produced	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Clarke	O
.	O
)	O
Scholer	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jenks	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
falseswearing	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
tried	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
disorderly	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
away	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Lesevre	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
yet	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
till	O
Sunday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Scholer	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Lefevre	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
441.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
MULBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
beech	O
chair	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
in	O
Crispin-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
beech	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
West-street	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
fromher	O
,	O
several	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
woman	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
chair	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
Union-street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
my	O
brother	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
corroborated	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
his	O
brother	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
senior	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
in	O
Crispin-street	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
sons	O
,	O
the	O
chair	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
(	O
The	O
chair	O
was	O
pro	O
duced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
potatos	O
to	O
Spitalfields-market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
nearly	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
chair	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
50	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1s	O
.	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
442.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
BOOTHMAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
RHODE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KNIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
stowed	O
my	O
boat	O
at	O
our	O
junk	O
chain	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
fasten	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
cast	O
on	O
shore	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
boat	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Thames	O
Police-office	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
disfigured	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hired	O
the	O
boat	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
from	O
February	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
up	O
to	O
Christmas	O
next	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
three	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
let	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
a	O
wherry-boat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
boat	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Policeoffice	O
;	O
I	O
built	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
marked	O
her	O
with	O
this	O
marking-iron	O
,	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
marks	O
were	O
punched	O
in	O
her	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
her	O
keel	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
boat	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MASSINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
repairing	O
the	O
boat	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
officers	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MAPHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
boat	O
upon	O
some	O
timbers	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
New	O
Crane-stairs	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hodge	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
branded	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
keel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
boat	O
of	O
a	O
quartermaster	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
with	O
me	O
last	O
war	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
59	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
443.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DONNELLAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
lst	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
186lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rankin	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Rankin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
be	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
444.	O
BRIDGET	B-pers
CHALKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Tape	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
with	O
the	O
lodging	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
TAPE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Mile-end	I-place
New-town	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
just	O
after	O
Bow-fair	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
lodgings	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
duplicates	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
BRIDGMAN	O
MATTHEWS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
frequently	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
sheet	O
;	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Burton	O
took	O
this	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
bolster	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
three	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chalker	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
445.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WEATHERHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
assistant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
193	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Chancery-lane	I-place
:	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
dusk	O
,	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
candles	O
were	O
lit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
discover	O
the	O
features	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
shop-door	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
any	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
given	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
lace	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
lace	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
andpointed	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
the	O
boy	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
lace	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
give	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
this	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
conceived	O
,	O
mending	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
glazier	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
passed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
occurred	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
mending	O
a	O
window	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
drawing	O
something	O
throught	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
turned	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
lace	O
;	O
he	O
drew	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
both	O
hands	O
pretty	O
rapid	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
young	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
beyond	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
lace	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
was	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
up	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
card	O
still	O
remained	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Weatherhead	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
this	O
lace	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
yard	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
the	O
square	O
of	O
glass	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
perfectly	O
secure	O
with	O
putty	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
cracked	O
part	O
was	O
shoved	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
(	O
Alexander	B-pers
Auld	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
my	O
mother	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
to	O
Tooley-street	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
through	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
boys	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
gentleman	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
11	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
446.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OVEREE	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COX	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
window-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Archibald-Kennedy	B-pers
Malcolm	I-pers
.	O
ARCHIBALD-KENNEDY	O
MALCOLM	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
broker	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
window-curtains	O
from	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HARLOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
side	O
door	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
,	O
an	O
oilman	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Malcolm	O
's	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
curtains	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
Overee	O
come	O
past	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
curtains	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
across	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
Curtain-road	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
curtains	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
Cok	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
.	O
(	O
Peter	O
Mason	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
curtains	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Overee	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
three-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Curtain-road	O
.	O
Cox	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Harlow	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
conversation	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Cox	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Overee	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Overee	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
11	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
Cox	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
14	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
447.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BURBURY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
nankeen	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
calico	O
wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
High-Holborn	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
our	O
porter	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
offering	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
circumstances	O
under	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
one	O
d-d	O
rogue	O
,	O
that	O
never	O
would	O
have	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Being	O
taxed	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
warehouse	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
mark	O
was	O
D.	O
Y.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
nankeen	O
,	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
white	O
calico	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
calico	O
wrapper	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
excellent	O
character	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
character	O
with	O
any	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
if	O
his	O
friends	O
are	O
respectable	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
(	O
Edward	O
Crocker	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
448.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHEAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
15	I-place
,	I-place
Lower	I-place
East	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
rail	O
outside	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
449.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
OLANDER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
18	O
penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Wright	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
by	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
half	O
foreigners	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Nunn	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Freere	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Saffle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bone	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sahun	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Welmer	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Grierson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hesker	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Techimond	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
tide-waiter	O
in	O
the	O
Customs	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
St.	O
Catherine's-lane	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
entire	O
stranger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
in	O
pretty	O
good	O
English	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tolerably	O
well	O
for	O
a	O
foreigner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
street	O
they	O
call	O
Cats-hole	B-place
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
feet	O
from	O
me	O
behind	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
watch	O
and	O
murder	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
his	O
nails	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
was	O
employed	O
at	O
both	O
my	O
right	O
and	O
left	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pockets	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
forward	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
a	O
word	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
gound	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
almost	O
choaked	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
woman	O
withdrew	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
turned	O
out	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
scarcely	O
sensible	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
empty	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
halfpence	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
about	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
laid	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
bleeding	O
at	O
my	O
mouth	O
;	O
my	O
arms	O
were	O
both	O
cut	O
with	O
the	O
fall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
supping	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Queen's-head	O
,	O
Tower-street	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
another	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
supper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
morsel	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
for	O
dinner	O
and	O
supper	O
;	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
afford	O
suppers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
upon	O
duty	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
clear	O
you	O
were	O
sober	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Perfectly	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
true	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
some	O
gin	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
person	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
SPITTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
cried	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
murder	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
same	O
words	O
repeated	O
with	O
a	O
shrill	O
voice	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
old	O
gentleman	O
down	O
flat	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
across	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
collar	O
and	O
hauled	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
charge	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
watchman	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
comrade	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
in	O
pretty	O
good	O
English	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
then	O
another	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
list	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
himself	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
fourteen	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
goand	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
near	O
the	O
spot	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
single	O
halfpence	O
,	O
one	O
lying	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
past	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
steady	O
;	O
indeed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Wright	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
says	O
you	O
were	O
his	O
comrade	O
;	O
had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
declare	O
to	O
God	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
duty	O
is	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
any	O
ship	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
Never	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Spittle	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
man	O
says	O
is	O
false	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
vomited	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
helping	O
him	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
450.	O
ANN	B-pers
BOWEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HOWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
coat	O
in	O
Gardiner's-lane	B-place
,	I-place
York-street	I-place
,	O
two	O
serjeants	O
were	O
having	O
a	O
dispute	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
dispute	O
was	O
ended	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
near	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
soldier	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
(	O
John	O
Hobbs	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
fighting	O
;	O
a	O
drummer	O
threw	O
the	O
coat	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
50	O
.	O
One	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
451.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
6lb	O
.	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	O
ROGERS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cock-hill	B-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
and	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
off	O
a	O
stool	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
bacon	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
it	O
laid	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
452.	O
JAMES	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
intoxication	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
charged	O
two	O
women	O
with	O
the	O
offence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
453.	O
ELIZA	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Moore	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
William	O
Rumbold	O
,	O
the	O
apprentice	O
,	O
served	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
produced	O
sixpence	O
more	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
apprentice	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
shoes	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
lad	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
shoes	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
outside	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
leaning	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
keep	O
an	O
eye	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
then	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Saunders	O
,	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
petticoats	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
our	O
coat	O
;	O
she	O
clapped	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
our	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
absconded	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
up	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
had	O
been	O
hanging	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
before	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
fire	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	O
Hubbard	O
,	O
a	O
headoorough	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
454.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
PRITCHARD	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
ten	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Taylor	O
,	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
at	O
Whitehall	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
linen	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
linen	O
that	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Girder	O
's	O
and	O
Slaughter	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
bacon	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bacon	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
muslin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
produce	O
;	O
the	O
shopman	O
delivered	O
the	O
muslin	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
for	O
tambour	O
work	O
,	O
from	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
it	O
from	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WALDRON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Girder	O
and	O
Slaughter	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
reply	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
bacon	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
feeling	O
for	O
the	O
bacon	O
,	O
I	O
discovered	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
detained	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
muslin	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Wilson	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
muslin	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
49	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
455.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PATTEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
three	O
garden-pots	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
three	O
plants	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
of	O
identity	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
456.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TEGGATT	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
DEGRANGES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
six	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Harry	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
HARRY	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
12	I-place
,	I-place
Pall-Mall	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
who	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
grooms	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
particular	O
pattern	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
handkerchief	O
they	O
described	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
Teggatt	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
expressed	O
himself	O
with	O
more	O
politeness	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
expected	O
from	O
such	O
a	O
lad	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
apologies	O
for	O
giving	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
moment	O
after	O
both	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
instant	O
before	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
Cockfour-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bow-street	O
officers	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
enquire	O
I	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
boys	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
During	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
the	O
boys	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
whatever	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
There	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CROCKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Strand	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gibbs	O
,	O
about	O
half-past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
following	O
three	O
other	O
boys	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
behind	O
a	O
hackney-coach	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Charing	O
cross	O
towards	O
Temple-bar	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
Degranges	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
boys	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
following	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
Charging-cross	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
down	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
head	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
Teggatt	O
stopped	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
boys	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
from	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
unbottoned	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
he	O
coat	O
dropped	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gibbs	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
Degranges	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
both	O
before	O
frequently	O
.	O
-	O
GIBBS	O
