TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
NOVEMBER	O
,	O
1803	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIRST	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
AND	O
BLANCHARD	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1803	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PEPPER	I-pers
LORD	O
ALVANLEY	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	B-pers
GROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOYDELL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
BROOK	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STAINES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
-	O
FLOWER	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
JOSHUA-JONATHAN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
NEWMAN	B-pers
KNOWLYS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
M'Namara	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horncastle	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Christie	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Roshter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Seguino	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Frederick	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sutch	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dunnage	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coxhead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Diak	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Cressall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GIBBONS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Trustees	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Islington	I-pers
Poor	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
METCALF	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
Poor-house	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
bricks	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
nurses	O
of	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
something	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shift	O
under	O
the	O
tail-board	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
nurses	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
to	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
tucking	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
frock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
informed	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
shift	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
bricks	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
horses	O
startled	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
line	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
tail-board	O
and	O
great	O
coat	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
to	O
my	O
horses	O
'	O
heads	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
shift	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
here	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
2.	O
JAMES	B-pers
COLLETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
feloniously	O
intermarried	O
with	O
Joanna	B-pers
Shaddock	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
being	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
;	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
is	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
go	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
Southwark	O
,	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Collett	I-pers
,	O
by	O
banns	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
They	O
lived	O
together	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
called	O
in	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
sold	O
off	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
leave	O
her	O
or	O
she	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
JOANNA	B-pers
SHADDOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
married	O
me	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1802	O
,	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Lambeth	I-place
,	O
by	O
banns	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
wife	O
-	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
I	O
might	O
hear	O
something	O
disagreeable	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
sixteen	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
ill-usage	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
(	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLLETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
Joanna	B-pers
Shaddock	I-pers
before	O
my	O
son	O
married	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
harm	O
in	O
her	O
having	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
better	O
stop	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
certainly	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
it	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
banns	O
in	O
my	O
absence	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
married	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
of	O
the	O
banns	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
forbid	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
week	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6	O
d.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
3.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BROADBRIDGE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
twelve	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Houlditch	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOULDITCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
fourteen	O
pigeons	O
;	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
to	O
bird-shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pigeons	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
boy	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
-	O
KEMP	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
pigeons	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
bag	O
containing	O
thirteen	O
pigeons	O
,	O
twelve	O
alive	O
and	O
one	O
smothered	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
their	O
father	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
wring	O
their	O
necks	O
off	O
.	O
From	O
their	O
appearance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
price	O
they	O
asked	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
boys	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Roberts	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Roberts	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
conversation	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Houlditch	O
;	O
Broadbridge	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
walk	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
theother	O
boy	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
pigeons	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
but	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
pigeons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
holes	O
.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
10	O
.	O
Broadbridge	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
10	O
.	O
Confined	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
4.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BURBAGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
thirteen	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Battye	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATTYE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ealing	B-place
,	O
and	O
lost	O
thirteen	O
geese	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
last	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
following	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
Cridland	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
thirteen	O
years	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
ASHBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Battye	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
geese	O
on	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Cridland	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
CRIDLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
apprehending	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
my	O
duty	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
towards	O
Kensington	O
Gravel-pits	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
and	O
thirteen	O
geese	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
Henley-upon-Thames	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
poulterer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tyburn-turnpike	O
.	O
Instead	O
of	O
turning	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
Cumberland-street	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
through	O
different	O
streets	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
geese	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Battye	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
owned	O
the	O
geese	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
written	O
defence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
``	O
My	O
Lords	O
,	O
with	O
humble	O
submission	O
,	O
I	O
most	O
humbly	O
implore	O
your	O
humanity	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
unfortunate	O
situation	O
.	O
Returning	O
from	O
Windsor	O
with	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
geese	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
fifteen	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ever	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
5.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DURANT	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
ENNIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
eight	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
FISH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Long-Acre	I-place
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
shop-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Durant	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
was	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
reached	O
the	O
curbstone	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
horrid	O
imprecations	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
cutting	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
;	O
after	O
a	O
violent	O
resistance	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
secured	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
looking	O
into	O
my	O
shop-window	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
apron	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
;	O
Durant	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
first	O
into	O
one	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
Ennis	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
seized	O
Durant	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
bacon	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
struggled	O
much	O
;	O
Ennis	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
liver	O
;	O
I	O
flinched	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
touched	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
cut	O
me	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
flinching	O
;	O
he	O
again	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
hearing	O
a	O
bustle	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Ennis	O
say	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
bacon	O
,	O
loose	O
him	O
;	O
Hughes	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
;	O
Hughes	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
accomplices	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
seize	O
hold	O
of	O
Durant	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
Hughes	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
repeated	O
the	O
blow	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
let	O
go	O
Durant	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
James-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
Ennis	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Little	O
White-Lion-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
some	O
person	O
halloaed	O
out	O
,	O
beware	O
of	O
his	O
knife	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
somebody	O
pulled	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
struggling	O
and	O
fighting	O
;	O
having	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
was	O
frightened	O
;	O
he	O
recovered	O
himself	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
before	O
me	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
A	O
number	O
of	O
young	O
men	O
about	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
to	O
give	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Durant	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
but	O
four	O
days	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Ennis	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
beating	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
shame	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
instantly	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Durant	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Ennis	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
32	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
6.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LONG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raw	O
coffee	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FERGUSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
Scott's-yard	O
,	O
Bush-lane	O
,	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
merchants'-broker	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
by	O
commission	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
coffee	O
in	O
our	O
warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
coffee	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
was	O
from	O
a	O
vessel	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
coffee	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
by	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
small	O
bags	O
,	O
each	O
containing	O
about	O
fifty-six	O
pounds	O
,	O
marked	O
Q.	O
S.	O
77	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
97	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	B-place
called	I-place
The	I-place
Four	I-place
Sisters	I-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
coffee	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
landed	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
two	O
numbers	O
were	O
wanting	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
also	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Thames	O
Police-officer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
near	O
St.	O
Catharine's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
before	O
as	O
a	O
waterman	O
)	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
each	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
bag	O
on	O
their	O
shoulders	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
walking	O
very	O
fast	O
;	O
the	O
moon	O
was	O
very	O
clear	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
heels	O
and	O
ran	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
dropped	O
his	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
slipped	O
the	O
bolt	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
pursued	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
also	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
his	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
two	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
land	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bags	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
assist	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
smuggled	O
coffee	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
purchased	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
7.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
pelice	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
DALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
as	O
house-keeper	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
,	I-place
Charlotte-street	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
:	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
pelice	O
,	O
and	O
cloak	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CUMMINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Charlotte-street	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stooping	O
and	O
peeping	O
through	O
the	O
palisadoes	O
of	O
No	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
round	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
past	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
arch-way	O
of	O
the	O
area-door	O
,	O
peeping	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
slip	O
back	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
something	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Plumsted-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
Lee	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
suspicious	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
pelice	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Lee	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
seeing	O
me	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
you	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
you	O
were	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
observed	O
your	O
bulk	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
I	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
on	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
Frankfort	O
,	O
in	O
High	O
Germany	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
above	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
for	O
a	O
pass	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
Imperial	O
Ambassador	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Cummins	O
with	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
watch	O
screw	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
finisher	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
them	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
till	O
Lee	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Cummins	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
catched	O
a	O
nice	O
green	O
horn	O
;	O
I	O
questioned	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
my	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
in	O
confinement	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
three	O
or	O
fourchildren	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
turned	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Cummins	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
true	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
tenant	O
in	O
confinement	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
8.	O
JAMES	B-pers
INGRAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
hen	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
David	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
a	O
corn-chandler	O
,	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
a	O
fowl	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
roost	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
given	O
that	O
somebody	O
had	O
stolen	O
my	O
fowls	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Cherry-tree	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
body	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
LILLYWHITE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Lawrence	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Cherry-tree	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
hustling	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
something	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
ostler	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
say	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
fowl	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
fowl	O
on	O
the	O
tiles	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
ankles	O
in	O
fresh	O
mud	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Cherry-tree	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
fowl	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
off	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
9.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
wheelbarrow	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
bushels	O
of	O
potatoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Church	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHURCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
intimation	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
lurking	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
of	O
my	O
potatoe-warehouse	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
potato	O
heap	O
greatly	O
disturbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
applied	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
near	O
three	O
bushels	O
of	O
potatoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
sacks	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
JOHN-PARSONS	B-pers
MAYNARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
potatoes	O
and	O
sacks	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sacks	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
always	O
bought	O
potatoes	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
peck	O
or	O
half	O
a	O
bushel	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
cart	O
selling	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Church	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
sack	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
bushels	O
of	O
peas	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
10.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
Seven-stars	O
public-house	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
quartered	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
our	O
servant	O
was	O
cleaning	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
a	O
table	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicates	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
table-cloths	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
basket	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
mangler	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
duplicates	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOURKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOURIL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
knap-sack	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
odd	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
fellows	O
of	O
those	O
pawned	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gell	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
and	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
produce	O
;	O
the	O
table-cloth	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sheet	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
11	O
SARAH	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
anapron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Burdon	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BURDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
13	I-place
,	I-place
Little	I-place
Charles-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-le-bonne	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
chair	O
woman	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
somebody	O
else	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
duplicates	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Burdon	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
thing	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ENSOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
pledge	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
from	O
whom	O
;	O
the	O
duplicates	O
correspond	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Burdon	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
41	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
12.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BOOTE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Jollisaint	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
JOLLISAINT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine-merchant	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Suffolk-street	O
,	O
Charing-cross	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
women	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
up	O
James-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
lifted	O
up	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
feel	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
hands	O
upon	O
my	O
breeches	O
pockets	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
one	O
arm	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
buttoned	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
put	O
her	O
hands	O
into	O
each	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pockets	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
six	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
her	O
hand	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
sister	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
Going	O
through	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
patten	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
sister	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
giving	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
one	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
some	O
silver	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
she	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
call	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
two	O
girls	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
girl	O
from	O
his	O
left-hand	O
,	O
and	O
sprung	O
the	O
rattle	O
;	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Going	O
through	O
Orange-court	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
got	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
called	O
for	O
her	O
sister	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
her	O
pattens	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
in	O
holding	O
out	O
her	O
left-hand	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
pattens	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
gold	O
;	O
three	O
guineas	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
(	O
-	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Bailey	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
a	O
girl	O
having	O
some	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
very	O
quietly	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
13.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRADFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
tippet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
two	O
bed-gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Checquer-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Whitecross-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
quitted	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
reason	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
slept	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
articles	O
till	O
Sunday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
confined	O
to	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
clothes-chest	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
fetched	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
mangler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
they	O
were	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Suspicion	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
false	O
direction	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
applied	O
to	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
charity-school	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mother	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
new	O
bonnets	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
fifteen	O
duplicates	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
examined	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
called	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
them	O
.	O
CHARLES-EDWARD	B-pers
SALMON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
rememberFord	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
,	O
and	O
produce	O
several	O
articles	O
pledged	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TRIGG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Ford	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
tickets	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
burnt	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
pledged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
no	O
promises	O
whatever	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
reason	O
for	O
not	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
14.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
CLIFFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HEWITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
38	I-place
,	I-place
Henry-street	I-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
weaver	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
lace	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
all	O
day	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
ashamed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
foolish	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GEARY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
:	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
apron	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Black-Boy-alley	O
,	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
duplicates	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
landlady	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
articles	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
WOOD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shopman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Alvanley	O
.	O
15.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROADSTOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
eight	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
twenty	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
counterpanes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
vallances	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
of	O
carpet	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
George-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
tenanted	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
the	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
more	O
open	O
than	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
boy	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
a	O
scuffle	O
ensued	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
hard	O
blows	O
passed	O
;	O
my	O
hand	O
slipped	O
from	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
a	O
soldier	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
prison	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
passage	O
full	O
of	O
articles	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
lantern	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
;	O
the	O
bed-furniture	O
was	O
removed	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HAYES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
16.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOLDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
dog	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
bolt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
the	O
London-Dock	B-pers
Company	I-pers
.	O
Other	O
Counts	O
,	O
varying	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
charging	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAPLIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
London-Dock	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
labourer	O
s	O
:	O
About	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coffer-dam	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
as	O
near	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
they	O
took	O
nothing	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
abreast	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
Burton	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
bolt	O
and	O
dog	O
weretaken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
bolt	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
dog	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
building	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
moveable	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
driven	O
into	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
crooked	O
at	O
each	O
end	O
,	O
to	O
brace	O
two	O
logs	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
piles	O
even	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
driven	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
moveable	O
from	O
one	O
pile	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
iron	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SIBLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
store-keeper	O
of	O
the	O
London-Dock	O
Company	O
;	O
these	O
irons	O
have	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
mark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
17.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PATMORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
and	O
wittingly	O
,	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
and	O
custody	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Banknote	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
1	O
l.	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Alvanley	O
.	O
18.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PATMORE	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
1	O
l.	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
him	O
with	O
feloniously	O
disposing	O
of	O
and	O
putting	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intent	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Counts	O
,	O
varying	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
charging	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
Four	O
other	O
Counts	O
,	O
charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Edward	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
being	O
offered	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Alvanley	O
.	O
19.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sentenced	O
was	O
expired	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
lawful	O
excuse	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GLANNON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police-officer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
pleaded	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
convicted	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
.	O
(	O
Copy	O
of	O
record	O
of	O
conviction	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police-officer	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Star	I-place
,	I-place
Wentworth-street	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
20.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOODROOFE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Holdsworth	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HOLDSWORTH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Windmill-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bethnal-green	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
seafaring	O
lad	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
and	O
identifies	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
beadle	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
week	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
21.	O
JOANNA	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barrister	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
watch	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
window-seat	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
conveying	O
away	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
)	O
Were	O
you	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
some	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
22.	O
JAMES	B-pers
POTTER	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
was	O
indictedfor	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
white	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Prescott	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PRESCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
and	O
glazier	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
22	I-place
,	I-place
Queen	I-place
Ann-street	I-place
East	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
articled	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
PRESCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BRINK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Prescott	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
white	O
lead	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
convert	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
fetch	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
till	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
words	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prescott	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
job	O
out	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
stationed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
shop	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
23.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
BRYAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Maycock	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MAYCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
64	I-place
,	I-place
Broad-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
edging	O
;	O
Bryan	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
edgings	O
.	O
Having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
their	O
motions	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Welch	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
conceal	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
far	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
?	O
and	O
immediately	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HUSSELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Maycock	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Bryan	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
voice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
while	O
Bryan	O
was	O
employing	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
questions	O
,	O
Welch	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
concealed	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Maycock	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
lace	O
.	O
Welch	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Bryan	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Welch	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
45	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Bryan	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
24.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DRISCOLL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Vincent	B-pers
Kennett	I-pers
,	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Vincent	B-pers
Kennett	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
2	I-place
,	I-place
New	I-place
Cavendish-street	I-place
,	I-place
Portland-place	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Kennett	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
lady	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
name	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
sent	O
word	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
wait	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
be	O
within	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
mistress	O
it	O
was	O
particular	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
detain	O
her	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
doe-skin	O
breeches	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
there	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
street-door	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
with	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
breeches	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
ALICE	B-pers
ARUNDEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kennett	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Good	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
acquaint	O
my	O
mistress	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
wanted	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
(	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Nunn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
maker	O
,	O
by	O
Good	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kennett	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
small	O
phials	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
as	O
samples	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
like	O
some	O
brandy	O
for	O
the	O
winter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
brandy	O
for	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
59	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
25.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DORAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
TIDMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
Aldersgate	O
ward	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
betweenbrought	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
and	O
patrol	O
of	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
FRANCIS	O
-	O
sworn	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
instant	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
man	O
on	O
my	O
beat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asleep	O
on	O
some	O
steps	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
raise	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
rose	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
solder	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
the	O
patrol	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
man	O
asleep	O
upon	O
the	O
steps	O
;	O
we	O
rose	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
solder	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
plumber	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
this	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
solder	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FOWLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
:	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
raising	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
solder	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
plumber	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
a	O
job	O
at	O
Layton	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
allowed	O
him	O
these	O
perquisites	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
piece	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Tidman	O
.	O
I	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
trowsers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
solder	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
allowed	O
it	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
perquisite	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
his	O
master	O
lived	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wildman	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wildman	O
and	O
the	O
patrol	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
solder	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Wildman	O
sent	O
to	O
Layton	O
for	O
the	O
ladles	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
melted	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILDMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
at	O
Layton	O
,	O
the	O
ladles	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
this	O
solder	O
was	O
certainly	O
melted	O
in	O
these	O
ladles	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
particularly	O
marked	O
by	O
a	O
dent	O
in	O
the	O
ladle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
suffer	O
men	O
to	O
take	O
solder	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Clarke	O
say	O
before	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
absconded	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
positively	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Clarke	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
job	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
openly	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
told	O
who	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EASTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Clarke	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
cakes	O
of	O
solder	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel-road	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
GEORGE	O
WHITSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Clarke	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
cakes	O
of	O
solder	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
26.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TROTT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dowding	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
-	O
GARDINER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dowding	O
,	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
Redcross-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
that	O
some	O
people	O
of	O
a	O
suspicious	O
character	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
strict	O
eye	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door-post	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
parcel	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
rushed	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
with	O
assistance	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
with	O
that	O
parcel	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
parcel	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
pardon	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HARDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
full	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
Beach-street	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
twenty	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GIBBONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
step	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
and	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CONSTABLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
across	O
Smithfield	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
bringing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
beat	O
and	O
cut	O
dreadfully	O
with	O
sticks	O
and	O
their	O
fists	O
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
BRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
towards	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
very	O
quietly	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
amob	O
of	O
I	O
suppose	O
two	O
hundred	O
people	O
;	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
immediately	O
began	O
upon	O
us	O
with	O
sticks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
began	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
beat	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
head	O
open	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
arm	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dowding	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
27.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
two-penny	O
receipt	O
stamps	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ruff	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RUFF	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
warehouseman	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Ironmonger-lane	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Bridge-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
show	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
opposite	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Bailey	I-place
,	O
where	O
it	O
stopped	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
taking	O
the	O
horses	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
more	O
,	O
stopped	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
buttoned	O
in	O
my	O
right-hand	O
coat-pocket	O
outside	O
;	O
directly	O
after	O
I	O
stopped	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pocket	O
unbottoned	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
book	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
collared	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Levy	O
at	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
foot-path	O
into	O
the	O
horse-road	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
foot-path	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Levy	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Levy	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Giltspur-street	O
Compter	O
;	O
Levy	O
has	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
NATHAN	B-pers
LEVY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
make	O
several	O
attempts	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
Ludgate-hill	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
follow	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
first	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
book	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
watching	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Giltspur-street	O
Compter	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Alderman	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
book	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
)	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
begin	O
the	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
said	O
by	O
you	O
about	O
being	O
turned	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
since	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
less	O
than	O
twenty	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
a	O
constable	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Any	O
man	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
innocent	O
affair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
turn	O
King	O
's	O
evidence	O
against	O
a	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
-	O
Were	O
you	O
never	O
committed	O
by	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
evidence	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
no	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
two	O
hundred	O
pound	O
Bank-note	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
were	O
my	O
Counsel	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
discharged	O
me	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wrong	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
time	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
two	O
guineas	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
SOUTHERN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
Levy	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
publican	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
Levy	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
like	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
the	O
trick	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
money	O
pass	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
part	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
pork-butcher	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Pelham-street	O
,	O
Mile-end	O
New	O
Town	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
Stationers	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John-street	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
eight	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
28.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
VINE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
theprisoner	O
take	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
cart	O
in	O
Oxford-street	B-place
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
helping	O
a	O
drayman	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
into	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
had	O
been	O
mine	O
;	O
my	O
own	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
55	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
29.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
70	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lyons	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Kiernan	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LYONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Charles-street	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
lead	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
above	O
the	O
garret	O
window	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
Lyons	O
's	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
that	O
some	O
men	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
garret	O
window	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
stripped	O
in	O
their	O
jacket	O
sleeves	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
till	O
some	O
more	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
leads	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
lead	O
missing	O
on	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
hanging	O
by	O
the	O
bed-side	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
quilt	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
till	O
two	O
officers	O
came	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Green	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
garret	O
windows	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Shut	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Green	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
partner	O
was	O
shutting	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
Green	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
WEDBY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
breaking	O
into	O
my	O
garret-window	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
learnt	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
gone	O
past	O
the	O
garret-window	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Kennedy	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
brother	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
standing	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
Kennedy	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
;	O
Kennedy	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
detain	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Kennedy	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
bed	O
rather	O
rumpled	O
she	O
turned	O
down	O
the	O
bed-clothes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
discovered	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
for	O
two	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Green	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
lodge	O
there	O
as	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
might	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
declared	O
his	O
innocence	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
entered	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
,	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Green	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
not	O
indicted	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
in	O
Wharton's-court	O
,	O
Holborn	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
falsehood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
not	O
your	O
sister	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
,	O
keep	O
a	O
disorderly	O
house	O
for	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
she	O
lets	O
her	O
house	O
out	O
to	O
lodgers	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrol	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
received	O
the	O
wound	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Green	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
Griffiths	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
)	O
Lyons	O
.	O
I	O
compared	O
the	O
lead	O
with	O
Wedby	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
window	O
where	O
it	O
came	O
off	O
.	O
Wedby	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
compared	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Lyons	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
receive	O
the	O
rent	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
lease	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Leverton	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
houses	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
Green	O
oppose	O
your	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
up	O
stairs	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
Griffiths	O
before	O
.	O
Green	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
London	O
Militia	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
upon	O
guard	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
got	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
's	O
defence	O
,	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
there	O
that	O
rented	O
this	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
cook	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
coat	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
Green	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
incommode	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
cook's-shop	O
and	O
get	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
when	O
those	O
people	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
full	O
of	O
disorderly	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
is	O
always	O
open	O
to	O
all	O
comers	O
and	O
goers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Green	O
,	O
called	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
pouch	O
and	O
bayonet	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
guard	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Townsend	O
will	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Townsend	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
pouch	O
and	O
bayonet	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
48	O
.	O
Green	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
30.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HOLMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
FENNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Williams	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
'	O
boxes	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
his	O
box	O
would	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
keys	O
tied	O
together	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
waistcoat-pocket	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
calico	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
claimed	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
that	O
part	O
.	O
Mr.	O
HOBLER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
reduced	O
into	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Fenner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
servant	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Proves	O
the	O
the	O
firm	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
our	O
porter	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Fenner	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
property	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
31.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HAYDON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
seven	O
hundred	O
crab	O
quicksets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
IRONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Market-street	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
Enfield	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
ditching	O
and	O
planting	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
line	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
quicksets	O
,	O
some	O
white	O
thorn	O
and	O
some	O
crab	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Plumb	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
the	B-place
Nag	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Enfield	I-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Plumb	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Plumb	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
we	O
should	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
go	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
back	O
way	O
leads	O
up	O
a	O
passage	O
by	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
quicksets	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
they	O
might	O
take	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
command	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
while	O
I	O
stood	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
across	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
quicksets	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
turned	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
so	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Plumb	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Plumb	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
close	O
together	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
quicksets	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
stable-door	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-nine	O
bundles	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
only	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
carried	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
bundles	O
;	O
each	O
bundle	O
generally	O
contains	O
one	O
thousand	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
one	O
shilling	O
a	O
hundred	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
bundles	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
line	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
through	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
both	O
doors	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Alvanley	O
.	O
32.	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
GODDARD	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
nineteen	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
PROSSER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
8	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Agnes	I-place
Terrace	I-place
,	I-place
Tabernacle-walk	I-place
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
a	O
linendraper	O
's	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Price	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
standing	O
with	O
Goddard	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
Price	O
and	O
the	O
mancame	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
prints	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
they	O
chose	O
a	O
dark	O
print	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
two	O
yards	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Price	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
the	O
print	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Before	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Goddard	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
eleven	O
pence	O
for	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
and	O
Price	O
went	O
up	O
North-street	O
,	O
and	O
Goddard	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
print	O
;	O
she	O
returned	O
with	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
son	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
City-road	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
gutter	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
she	O
kept	O
her	O
hand	O
close	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
pocket-hole	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
drew	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
print	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
through	O
her	O
pocket-hole	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
she	O
dropped	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
the	O
print	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
assistance	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
having	O
lately	O
been	O
brought	O
to-bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Goddard	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
her	O
speak	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
nothing	O
further	O
between	O
them	O
than	O
Price	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
after	O
them	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police-officer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
print	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Price	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
poverty	O
that	O
drove	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
knows	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Price	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
55	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Goddard	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
33.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
ALDUS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
34.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
KEMP	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
CHATTERTON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
poker	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	O
.	O
JUDITH	B-pers
ANTHONY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3	I-place
,	I-place
Sun-yard	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GREENMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Anthony	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
INCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
CALLIHORN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Anthony	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
candlestick	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
