TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1803	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SIXTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
ESQUIRE	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W	B-pers
.	I-pers
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1803	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	O
PRICE	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ARCHIBALD	O
MACDONALD	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
GILES	O
ROOKE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
SOULDEN	O
LAWRENCE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
HARLEY	O
,	O
PAUL	O
LE	O
MESURIER	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ANDERSON	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAM	O
ROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
CHARLES	O
FLOWER	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
MATTHEW	O
BLOXAM	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
-	O
LEE	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
JOHN	O
SILVESTER	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pardy	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Romanis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Vandome	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cuffs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neighbour	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Britten	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Semple	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ringer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Benstead	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Patmore	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Kingdon	I-pers
.	O
519.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jennett	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
JENNETT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
53	I-place
,	I-place
Compton-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
drab	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
inside	O
the	O
parlour-door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jennett	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
blue	O
ointment	O
spread	O
upon	O
some	O
lint	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jennett	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
medical	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
reached	O
the	O
pot	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
spread	O
the	O
plaister	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
dress	O
an	O
ulcer	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
over	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
among	O
the	O
bottles	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
pills	O
of	O
tincture	O
of	O
bark	O
and	O
calomel	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
again	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Jennett	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
knock	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
pills	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
something	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
pocket	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
for	O
some	O
pills	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
small	O
blister	O
spread	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
spread	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
thumb	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
into	O
Church-street	O
,	O
and	O
heat	O
the	O
patler	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
coat	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
more	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
(	O
John	O
Alcock	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
,	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Confined	O
12	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
520.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
TYE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
twelve	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
36s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Townrow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JOHN	O
TOWNROW	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
43	I-place
,	I-place
Crispin-street	I-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
servant	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Windsor	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
TOWNROW	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
articles	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
service	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
missed	O
twelve	O
shifts	O
from	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
petticoat	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Townrow	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
a	O
ticket	O
of	O
a	O
petticoat	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Townrow	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Townrow	O
brought	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
work-house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Joseph	O
Saunders	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Townrow	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Aged	O
18	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3s	O
.	O
Confined	O
12	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
521.	O
MARY	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLACKMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Green-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
Friday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
room-door	O
was	O
not	O
fastened	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	O
Knight	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
does	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
door	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
landing-place	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
drop	O
from	O
behindher	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
dressed	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
breakfast	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
wrong	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
till	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
522.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOLDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
SAMUEL	O
LEWIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
31	I-place
,	I-place
Grub-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
possession	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
twelve	O
days	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
a	O
drug	O
mill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
never	O
worked	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
duplicates	O
.	O
SARAH	O
LEWIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
gave	O
him	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
slept	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
duplicate	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
produced	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
)	O
ALEXANDER	O
STEVENS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
Cripplegate	O
ward	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
duplicate	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
duplicate	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sheet	O
from	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
his	O
man	O
come.	O
(	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Lewis	O
identified	O
the	O
other	O
sheet	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
look	O
it	O
over	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
39	O
.	O
Confined	O
two	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
523.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DUTTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
four	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
.	O
CHARLES	O
WHALEY	O
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
-On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
sheep	O
barn	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
used	O
formerly	O
to	O
keep	O
sheep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Potter's-Bar	B-place
.	O
The	O
witness	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
to	O
watch	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
again	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
came	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
four	O
trusses	O
away	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
another	O
barn	O
adjoining	O
that	O
where	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
the	O
draught	O
barn	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
ladder	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
lost	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
to	O
watch	O
both	O
barns	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
lost	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
wheat	O
barn	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
sat	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
ladder	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
binding	O
hay	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
colour	O
and	O
quality	O
was	O
exactly	O
like	O
our	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.Are	O
you	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
partner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A.Four	O
years	O
next	O
Michaelmas	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carman	O
and	O
hay-binder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
to	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
carrying	O
this	O
hay	O
?	O
-	O
A.Not	O
more	O
than	O
thirty	O
yards	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
it	O
moon-light	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
cloudy	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
LORD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
wheat	O
barn	O
with	O
young	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
four	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
stubble	O
in	O
the	O
sheep	O
barn	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.This	O
was	O
a	O
cloudy	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
never	O
very	O
dark	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
at	O
thirty	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
said	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
distinctly	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
prisoner	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
resolute	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
handcuff	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
is	O
a	O
respectable	O
farmer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Why	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
particular	O
reason	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
.	O
Q.Perhaps	O
what	O
you	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
was	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
sure	O
you	O
tell	O
us	O
the	O
truth	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
SARAH	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wharley	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
dubble	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
unusual	O
thing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
sheep	O
house	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
rick-yard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
WARWICK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
borne	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Confined	O
12	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
524.	O
JANE	B-pers
HOLMES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Henson	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	O
HENSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Henson	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
sheet	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
.	O
-	O
BURTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
sheet	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
sheet	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
G	O
B	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
number	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
a	O
decent	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
525.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RUSSELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	O
MARTIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
1	I-place
,	I-place
Court-street	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
hung	O
the	O
sheet	O
upon	O
a	O
line	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
shirts	O
from	O
the	O
line	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lambeth-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
Monday	O
at	O
the	O
Police	O
Office	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
shirt	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
still	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
finished	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
buttons	O
wanting	O
,	O
I	O
often	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
complete	O
shirt	O
till	O
the	O
buttons	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
526.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
JEFFERYS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
containing	O
ten	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John-Augustus	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
527.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
NORTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pin-a-fore	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
HANNAH	O
DAVIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Spencer	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Bethnal-green	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leading	O
the	O
child	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
its	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
child	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
insisted	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
stripped	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
528.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CASWELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
an	O
axe	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	O
HUNT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
,	O
in	O
Union-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
an	O
axe	O
,	O
a	O
plane	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
saws	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Blackwall	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
my	O
tools	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
shop	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
hinges	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
afterwards	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
BEALES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
two	O
saws	O
and	O
a	O
chissel	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
themfor	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
sold	O
his	O
tools	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
afterwards	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
an	O
axe	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
axe	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
London	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mother	O
living	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
axe	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
18d	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
duplicate	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
axe	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
axe	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
plane	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
Bristol	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
duplicate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
plane	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Caswell	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
saw	O
.	O
)	O
EDWARD	O
COOMBER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Produces	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
a	O
plane	O
,	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
axe	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Beales	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
tools	O
outside	O
the	O
shop-door	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
63	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
days	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
529.	O
ROSETTA	B-pers
PRESTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	O
GREEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
8	I-place
,	I-place
Gray's-buildings	I-place
,	I-place
Duke-street	I-place
,	I-place
Manchester-square	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
slept	O
in	O
one	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
things	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
the	O
gown	O
across	O
the	O
wash-tub	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Betts	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
-	O
DARE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
situation	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
leave	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Sunday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
for	O
her	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
being	O
sunday	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
Betts	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
is	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
bundle	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
HENRY	O
BETTS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Marybone	O
watch-house	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
bundle	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Preston	O
had	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
gown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
gown	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Green	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
sell	O
her	O
this	O
gown	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
offer	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
five-pound	O
note	O
,	O
a	O
ten-pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
;	O
another	O
person	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
examined	O
at	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
lost	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Betts	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
delivered	O
back	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
there	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
530.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TUTET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Luppino	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	O
LUPPIND	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
auction-rooms	O
,	O
walked	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
and	O
Compton-street	O
;	O
Blackman	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
rooms	O
before	O
;	O
Blackman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
These	O
stockings	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
your	O
rooms	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
had	O
ticketed	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
BLACKMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
and	O
Compton-street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
hundred	O
and	O
one	O
duplicates	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	O
DUNNAGE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Luppino	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
his	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
lot	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
writing	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.When	O
had	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
sale	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
day	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
sold	O
these	O
stockings	O
that	O
day	O
week	O
with	O
the	O
ticket	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Galabin	O
,	O
Bridge-master	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
32	O
.	O
Confined	O
12	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
531.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
.	O
PATRICK	O
RYAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Stewart's-rents	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
fell	O
across	O
my	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
lifting	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
dragged	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
dropped	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
Q.Who	O
dragged	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A.The	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
hustling	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
hustled	O
me	O
three	O
doors	O
below	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
of	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
MARY	O
RYAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
husband	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
watch	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
chain	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
-	O
PIPPIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Ryan	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
Jeremiab	O
Obrien	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Ryan	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
shoved	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
532.	O
JANE	B-pers
ANDREWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jerome	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	O
BARNES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
Wheeler-street	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
keeps	O
an	O
iron-shop	O
:	O
On	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sit	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
chair	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
tired	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
rest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
chair	O
been	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Windsor	O
chair	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
rags	O
.	O
JEROME	O
BARNES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
a	O
portering	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
chair	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
sight	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
days	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
533.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
three	O
printed	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mudie	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MUDIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
81	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Swallow-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
:	O
About	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
missed	O
Guthrie	O
's	O
Geographical	O
Grammar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Test	O
of	O
Honour	O
,	O
two	O
volumes	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
bookseller	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Kindon	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	O
KINDON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
two	O
volumes	O
of	O
the	O
Test	O
of	O
Honour	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
Guthrie	O
's	O
Grammar	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
either	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
or	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
fifteen-pence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mudie	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
books	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
534.	O
WINIFRED	B-pers
M'LOCHLAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
15d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	O
LUCAS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
,	O
High-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Oak	I-place
eating-house	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Lawrence-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
number	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
the	O
pot	O
upon	O
her	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
assistant	O
cook	O
at	O
this	O
eating-house	O
.	O
GILES	O
HEMENS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
two	O
pots	O
for	O
sale	O
at	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
promiscuously	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
pewter	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pot	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
boy	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
535.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SEARLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stockley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
536.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
four	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rachael	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
RACHAEL	O
PRICE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
tea	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
parlour	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
looked	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
wash	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
to	O
put	O
water	O
into	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
frock	O
.	O
MARGARET	O
PRICE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
clothes	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
King-street	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
loose	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	O
BUCKLAND	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brushmaker	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Charles-street	O
and	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
opposite	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
girl	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
caught	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Charles-street	O
;	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Queen-square	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
MORGAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
SARAH	O
SPARR	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
Morgan	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
stopped	O
the	O
thief	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
537.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YEOMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
twelve	O
boards	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poynder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poynder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
POYNDER	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
scaffolding-boards	O
and	O
six	O
other	O
boards	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
Hill-street	B-place
,	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
employed	O
by	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Reeve	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hill-street	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
twelve	O
boards	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
marked	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
being	O
mine	O
.	O
GEORGE	O
WHITE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mason	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
Finsbury-square	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Poynder	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
in	O
Hill-street	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
boards	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
scassolding-boards	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Paul-street	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Reeve	O
's	O
is	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Paul-street	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
setched	O
one	O
more	O
board	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
saw	O
a	O
direction	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
labourer	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
public-house	O
.	O
-	O
REEVE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Paul-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
old	O
boards	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nine	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
then	O
two	O
more	O
at	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
three	O
more	O
at	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Poynder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
claimed	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
boards	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Poynder	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
68	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
538.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BLACKALL	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
wheel	O
,	O
barrow	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Amelia	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
AMELIA	O
WYNN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
barrow	O
from	O
the	O
court	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
,	O
Fletcher's-court	B-place
,	I-place
Church-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
after	O
breakfast	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
barrow	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
over	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
a	O
barrow-maker	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
barrows	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
MACARTY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
barrow	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wynn	O
chaimed	O
the	O
barrow	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
barrow	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
CORNELIUS	O
CURTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
Macarty	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
detained	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
barrow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
wheel	O
the	O
barrow	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Short's-gardens	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
539.	O
MARY	B-pers
LEAF	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
shawl	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	O
PORTER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cranbourn-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
suspected	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
pulled	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
shawl	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
cut	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
540.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
servant	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chabot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
and	O
take	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
1l	O
.	O
9s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
for	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
so	O
received	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
fraudulently	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
embezzle	O
and	O
secrete	O
it	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
a	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
varying	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
charging	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Alley	O
.	O
)	O
CHARLES	O
HICKSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
carman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chabot	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Forbes	O
3cwt	O
.	O
of	O
potatoes	O
at	O
4s	O
.	O
per	O
hundred	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
4cwt	O
.	O
at	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
3cwt	O
.	O
at	O
4s	O
.	O
making	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
40s	O
.	O
worth	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Chabot	O
?	O
-	O
A.Very	O
near	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
.	O
CHARLOTTE	O
FORBES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
greengrocer	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
potatoes	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Chabot	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
;	O
Hickson	O
delivered	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gathered	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
sometimes	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
receipts	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
.	O
JOSEPH	O
CHABOT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
potatomerchant	O
,	O
in	O
Christopher-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
account	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Forbes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
owed	O
the	O
remainder	O
,	O
1l	O
.	O
9s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
never	O
accounted	O
for	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
carried	O
on	O
business	O
on	O
your	O
own	O
account	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
succeeded	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
I	O
married	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
reserved	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
to	O
himself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
assists	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A.He	O
is	O
taking	O
the	O
business	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
have	O
managed	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
what	O
proportion	O
has	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
profits	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
leave	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
capital	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
A.None	O
whatever	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
is	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
taken	O
the	O
business	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A.About	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
another	O
servant	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Molloy	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
received	O
money	O
frequently	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
allowed	O
to	O
take	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
was	O
allowed	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
did	O
account	O
to	O
Molloy	O
for	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
account	O
to	O
Molloy	O
,	O
Molley	O
never	O
accounted	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
Molloy	O
has	O
absconded	O
,	O
has	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
not	O
absconded	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
Q.Has	O
he	O
not	O
absconded	O
?	O
-	O
A.I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
absconding	O
.	O
Q.Upon	O
the	O
oath	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
meant	O
by	O
absconding	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
mean	O
running	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
I	O
do	O
-	O
has	O
he	O
not	O
absconded	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
charge	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
leave	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
hasty	O
manner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
notice	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
words	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
certain	O
penalties	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
from	O
the	O
Stamp-Office	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
not	O
the	O
business	O
assigned	O
over	O
to	O
you	O
merely	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
an	O
assignment	O
prior	O
to	O
my	O
marriage	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
of	O
attorney	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
450l	O
.	O
and	O
finding	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
bad	O
,	O
I	O
entered	O
up	O
judgment	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
lately	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
sometimes	O
paid	O
money	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
sometimes	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
sometimes	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
somethines	O
to	O
Molloy	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
ROGER	O
BRANNING	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Chabot	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
myself	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
paying	O
money	O
to	O
Molloy	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
received	O
for	O
potatoes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Chabot	O
's	O
clerk	O
;	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q.How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Chabot	O
's	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
turn	O
you	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
May	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
conducted	O
yourself	O
too	O
honestly	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
541.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
BANKS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
33d	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
,	O
Kingswood	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
,	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Weddon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
41st	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Strand	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
wife	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
her	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
(	O
Elizabeth	O
Banks	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	O
WEDDON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
wedding	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
sister	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
by	O
banns	O
,	O
at	O
Kingswood	O
,	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Gloucestershire	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Christmasday	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
what	O
year	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
sister	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
.	O
DAVID-WYBUT	O
PALMER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary-le-Strand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1800	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
banns	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Alice	O
Higgins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Higgins	O
?	O
-	O
A.From	O
the	O
intructions	O
given	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
banns	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
introduced	O
into	O
the	O
church	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
.	O
Q.There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
persons	O
married	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary-le-Strand	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
exceeded	O
fifty	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
hundred	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
counted	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
population	O
act	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
first	O
wife	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
her	O
;	O
Mary	O
Weddon	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
army	O
several	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
living	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
letters	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
marry	O
my	O
second	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
fairly	O
told	O
her	O
friends	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wrote	O
to	O
this	O
very	O
woman	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Weddon	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
your	O
sister	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
live	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
A.About	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
34	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
542.	O
JANE	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pardon	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
PARDON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
,	O
at	O
Kentish-town	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Brown-bear	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
one	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
awoke	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
servant	O
girl	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coatpocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
fourth	O
day	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q.Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ASHLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dry	O
,	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
offered	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
one	O
pound	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Pardon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JAMES	O
FITZPATRICK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
ticket	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Ashley	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
our	O
duplicate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
ticket	O
of	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
ticket	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
543.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GYTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
time-piece	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goulding	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GOULDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
ANN	O
DUDLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
Eagle	O
street	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
has	O
lived	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Orange-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Goulding	O
's	O
boy	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
shutters	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
shutter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
whip	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
time-piece	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Goulding	O
's	O
boy	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Joseph	O
Beale	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BEALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Prosser	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Red-lion-street	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
time-piece	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goulding	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
inside	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
time-piece	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
544.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HORTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
GODDARD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barrett	O
lives	O
in	O
Chapel-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Barrett	O
's	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
's	O
shops	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
linen-drapers	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unpin	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
's	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
shopman	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
WATSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
my	O
grandfather	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taking	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
our	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
nothing	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
print	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
turning	O
into	O
Cooper-street	O
arch	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
before	O
him	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
crying	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
Orchard-street	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
witness	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Crofts	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
watching	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
.	O
ROBERT-THOMAS	O
CROFTS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Orchard-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
print	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
halloaing	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Pye-street	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
JOHN	O
CRIDLAND	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Barrett	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
row	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
545.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BOWMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Lord	O
Harcourt	O
,	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
red	O
box	O
coat	O
off	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Mews	I-place
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
HOLLIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
31	O
,	O
Monmouth-street	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
with	O
this	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
better	O
by	O
half	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
thirty-six	O
shillings	O
for	O
this	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
know	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
quiet	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
held	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
a	O
spring	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	O
PICKERING	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officerbelonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Mews	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
546.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
carpet	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
RYAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
slop-seller	O
,	O
at	O
Wapping-wall	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
carpet	O
from	O
my	O
back	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
high-street	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Pennington-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
carpet	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
carpet	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
distress	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
a	O
press-gang	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
carpet	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
43	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
547.	O
DAVID	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DENNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Hole	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
my	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
JONES	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Between	O
the	O
15th	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
at	O
midnight	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hearing	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dismissed	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
the	O
clothes	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
found	O
since	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
548.	O
ANN	B-pers
M'CARTHY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Condon	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CONDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
Bull's-head	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Charles-street	I-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
DANIEL	O
MEAD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
pot-boy	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Condon	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
kettle	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
boiling	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
her	O
porter	O
I	O
missed	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
detected	O
her	O
,	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
549.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SWEEDON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
two	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
CONNOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
my	O
place	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
cradle	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
FITZGERALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
this	O
shawl	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Connor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
shawl	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
just	O
born	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
52	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
550.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
twenty-nine	O
lambs	O
,	O
value	O
29l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel-Robert	B-pers
Coffer	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CRACE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q.You	O
are	O
bailiff	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coffer	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q.Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
North	O
Mims	O
,	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
Thomas	O
Tew	O
with	O
any	O
lambs	O
and	O
sheep	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
twenty-nine	O
lambs	O
and	O
a	O
ewe	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Baslington	O
,	O
a	O
salesman	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sheep	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
and	O
yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
remarkable	O
about	O
the	O
ewe	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
only	O
one	O
horn	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TEW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lambs	O
and	O
sheep	O
towards	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
pens	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
past	O
two	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Angel	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tallest	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Harris	O
,	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
pen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
salesman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Basleton	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
ne'er	O
a	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
you	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
salesman	O
sends	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
my	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Crisp	O
and	O
Smith	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-nine	O
lambs	O
and	O
one	O
horned	O
ewe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
desire	O
Harris	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	O
DAVIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
drover	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
door	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
b-r	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
somebody	O
is	O
coming	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
out	O
the	O
lambs	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
turned	O
them	O
towards	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
Road	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
big	O
one	O
drove	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
City	O
Road	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
fieldkeeper	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
lambs	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Smith	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Smith	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
bring	O
them	O
both	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
lambs	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
lambs	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
light	O
and	O
dark	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brown	O
lambs	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
CRISP	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q.You	O
are	O
a	O
watchman	O
at	O
the	O
pens	O
at	O
Islington	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
Pentonville	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
my	O
beat	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
door	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
pens	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
for	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
Williams	O
said	O
to	O
Harris	O
,	O
(	O
upon	O
seeing	O
a	O
drover	O
getting	O
some	O
sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pens	O
)	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
that	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
mix	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
drover	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
quick	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
and	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
lambs	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
Goswell-street	O
Road	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
you	O
observe	O
them	O
particularly	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
direct	O
road	O
;	O
the	O
direct	O
road	O
would	O
be	O
down	O
St.	O
John-street	O
;	O
Smith	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
just	O
by	O
Goswell-street	O
turnpike	O
;	O
Williams	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
driving	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
any	O
answer	O
;	O
Smith	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
twenty-nine	O
lambs	O
and	O
one	O
ewe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
since	O
shewn	O
them	O
to	O
Crace	O
and	O
to	O
Tew	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOSEPH	O
SMITH	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
fieldkeeper	O
we	O
understand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
Davis	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
follow	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
with	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
Q.Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
what	O
Williams	O
said	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
EDMUNDS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q.Were	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
examination	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Smith	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
Williams	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baslington	O
,	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
countryman	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Tew	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
these	O
boys	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
my	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Crisp	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
say	O
about	O
turning	O
them	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
make	O
haste	O
in	O
turning	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
fort	O
.	O
Harris	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
door	O
;	O
one	O
John	O
Smith	O
was	O
taking	O
some	O
sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pens	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
somebody	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
helped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
bring	O
them	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
Goswell-street	O
Road	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
mix	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Williams	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
countryman	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
helped	O
him	O
.	O
Harris	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
Williams	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
551.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q.Where	O
doyou	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
No	O
.	O
73	O
,	O
Whitecross-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henley	O
's	O
for	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
behaving	O
rather	O
rudely	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
interrupt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
pass	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
whole	O
pavement	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
nook	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
pass	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
cheek	O
and	O
hair	O
;	O
she	O
fetched	O
blood	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
bonnet	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
snatched	O
at	O
my	O
parcel	O
,	O
containing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q.What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
my	O
head	O
down	O
between	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
snatched	O
the	O
parcel	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
the	O
men	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Paulin	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Paulin	O
picked	O
up	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q.How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
carrying	O
stockings	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A.My	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henley	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
three	O
pair	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
choice	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Q.Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
PAULIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
78	O
,	O
Whitecross-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
interruption	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
girl	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
extricate	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
situation	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
servant	O
within	O
a	O
dozen	O
doors	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hair	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
pinned	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
two	O
hands	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Paulin	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
strike	O
at	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
ran	O
away	O
upon	O
my	O
coming	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
matter	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
hands	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
hair	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
possession	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
the	O
girl	O
picked	O
up	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
pair	O
was	O
looked	O
after	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
that	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
fellow-servant	O
of	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	O
HENLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
)	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
that	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
Q.Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
at	O
Worship-street	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Moore	O
.	O
)	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
you	O
took	O
up	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
them	O
(	O
pointing	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pairs	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Henley	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
it	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Paulin	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
burst	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
but	O
one	O
pair	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
held	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
552.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ASLETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
servant	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
as	O
such	O
officer	O
and	O
servant	O
was	O
entrusted	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
bill	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
an	O
Exchequer	O
bill	O
,	O
numbered	O
14l	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
Exchequer	O
bill	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1000l	O
.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
with	O
another	O
bill	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
an	O
Exchequer	O
bill	O
,	O
numbered	O
2694	O
,	O
which	O
last-mentioned	O
bill	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1000l	O
.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
with	O
another	O
bill	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
an	O
Exchequer	O
bill	O
,	O
numbered	O
1060	O
,	O
which	O
last-mentioned	O
bill	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1000l	O
.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
such	O
servant	O
and	O
so	O
entrusted	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
secrete	O
,	O
embezzle	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
bills	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
peace	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
the	O
bills	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
effects	O
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
securities	O
.	O
And	O
several	O
other	O
Counts	O
,	O
varying	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
laying	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
The	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
called	O
over	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Joseph	O
Harvey	O
challenged	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Pardy	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Romanis	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Vandome	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Cuffs	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neighbour	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Clinch	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gorton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
sworn	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hosier	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Sansum	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
challenged	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
May	O
it	O
please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
attend	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
instructions	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
to	O
state	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
case	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
this	O
cause	O
had	O
been	O
appointed	O
for	O
trial	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Session	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
postponed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
become	O
my	O
duty	O
presently	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
reason	O
which	O
induced	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
discharge	O
of	O
their	O
duty	O
,	O
to	O
postpone	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
the	O
cause	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
interrupt	O
more	O
important	O
narrative	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
stated	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
the	O
conduct	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
requested	O
that	O
postponement	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
only	O
be	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
approbation	O
of	O
their	O
Lordships	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
the	O
case	O
before	O
you	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
importance	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
importance	O
inasmuch	O
as	O
it	O
affects	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
offence	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
charged	O
has	O
for	O
the	O
security	O
of	O
this	O
most	O
important	O
Corporation	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
interests	O
of	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
been	O
made	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
statute	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
reign	O
,	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
for	O
any	O
officer	O
or	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
embezzle	O
or	O
secrete	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
securities	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
intrusted	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
are	O
,	O
in	O
many	O
instances	O
,	O
trustees	O
for	O
the	O
public	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
become	O
my	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
occupy	O
any	O
great	O
portion	O
of	O
your	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
state	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
is	O
carried	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
respects	O
this	O
particular	O
department	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Aslett	I-pers
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
employment	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
about	O
twenty-five	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
twenty-three	O
years	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Newlan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Chief	O
Cashier	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
unfit	O
I	O
should	O
say	O
thus	O
early	O
,	O
that	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
period	O
which	O
brings	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
bar	O
as	O
a	O
criminal	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
conducted	O
himself	O
very	O
faithfully	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
very	O
meritorious	O
services	O
.	O
Some	O
unfortunate	O
speculations	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
Funds	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
probably	O
sustained	O
some	O
losses	O
,	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
drawn	O
him	O
aside	O
from	O
that	O
fidelity	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
unhappy	O
moment	O
to	O
subtract	O
from	O
those	O
securities	O
under	O
his	O
immediate	O
care	O
immense	O
portions	O
of	O
that	O
property	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
today	O
to	O
answer	O
before	O
you	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
year	O
1799	O
,	O
having	O
thus	O
passed	O
through	O
the	O
gradations	O
of	O
office	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Aslett	O
was	O
appointed	O
a	O
Cashier	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
You	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
part	O
,	O
to	O
purchase	O
Government	O
securities	O
of	O
various	O
sorts	O
,	O
particular	O
Exchequer-bills	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
issued	O
in	O
vast	O
amounts	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
that	O
Company	O
purchase	O
to	O
supply	O
the	O
exigencies	O
of	O
the	O
State	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
these	O
purchases	O
are	O
made	O
is	O
this	O
:	O
When	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Exchequer-bills	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
money-market	O
,	O
the	O
purchase	O
is	O
left	O
entirely	O
to	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
the	O
Cashier	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
past	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
age	O
and	O
growing	O
infirmities	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Newland	O
,	O
the	O
principal	O
Cashier	O
,	O
this	O
business	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
entire	O
controul	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
purchases	O
made	O
immediately	O
from	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
are	O
made	O
through	O
the	O
respectable	O
house	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Goldsmid	O
;	O
those	O
purchased	O
in	O
the	O
money-market	O
are	O
made	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Templeman	O
,	O
the	O
broker	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
is	O
made	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
suppose	O
Messrs.	O
Goldsmid	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
an	O
enumeration	O
of	O
the	O
various	O
Exchequer-bills	O
,	O
describing	O
them	O
by	O
their	O
numbers	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
every	O
person	O
sees	O
immediately	O
what	O
the	O
one	O
has	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
has	O
sold	O
.	O
This	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
has	O
been	O
delivered	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
instances	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
to	O
call	O
your	O
attention	O
to-day	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Aslett	O
;	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
instances	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
duty	O
to	O
compare	O
the	O
bundle	O
of	O
Exchequer-bills	O
with	O
the	O
enumeration	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
order	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
,	O
to	O
direct	O
the	O
payment	O
from	O
the	O
Cashiers	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
for	O
the	O
bills	O
so	O
purchased	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
then	O
entered	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
bought-book	O
;	O
a	O
corresponding	O
entry	O
to	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
is	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
bought-book	O
.	O
The	O
Exchequer-bills	O
themselves	O
are	O
deposited	O
in	O
a	O
strong	O
chest	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
Cashier	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
increase	O
to	O
a	O
bulk	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
placed	O
under	O
the	O
more	O
immediate	O
eye	O
of	O
the	O
Directors	O
themselves	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
selected	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Directors	O
transact	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
this	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
proceed	O
to	O
describe	O
:	O
You	O
will	O
suppose	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Exchequer-bills	O
,	O
containing	O
one	O
thousand	O
each	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
100	O
,	O
or	O
200,000l	O
.	O
in	O
value	O
,	O
or	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
better	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
amounting	O
to	O
227,000l	O
.	O
The	O
course	O
that	O
is	O
taken	O
is	O
to	O
count	O
off	O
a	O
certain	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
clerk	O
counts	O
off	O
the	O
remainder	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
ascertain	O
the	O
number	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
accompained	O
by	O
the	O
book	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
duty	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
parcels	O
he	O
carried	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
state	O
the	O
entry	O
presently	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
parlour	O
they	O
are	O
received	O
by	O
the	O
Directors	O
in	O
waiting	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
by	O
them	O
counted	O
and	O
examined	O
,	O
each	O
by	O
itself	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
corresponds	O
with	O
the	O
entry	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
,	O
for	O
