TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1803	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
ESQUIRE	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1803	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
ELLENROROUGH	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CURTIS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
HARVEY-CHRISTIAN	B-pers
COMBE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
-	O
ROWCROFT	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
JOSHUA-JONATHAN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
NEWMAN	B-pers
KNOWLYS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skirving	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Steinmetz	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mashiter	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Higginbotham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Groat	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scowling	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Nairne	I-pers
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
John-Goodrich	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tapp	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Varley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Petchin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Magin	I-pers
.	O
705.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
MASON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twenty-six	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clementson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Borrodaile	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clementson	I-pers
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Blackwell-Hall	O
factor	O
,	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	B-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clementson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Borrodaile	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clementson	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
partner	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
red	O
cloth	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
across	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
warehouse-door	O
was	O
open	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
a	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BROGDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
his	O
way	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pursue	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
King	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Brogden	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
46	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
706.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FAULKNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
six	O
tea-cups	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
six	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
tumblers	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
goblet	O
,	O
value	O
9d	O
.	O
a	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
9d	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
butter-boats	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
ABBOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
china	O
,	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
earthen-ware	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
82	O
,	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
carman	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
servant	O
discovered	O
some	O
things	O
secreted	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
among	O
some	O
straw	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
remain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
addition	O
of	O
six	O
saucers	O
,	O
nankeen	O
china	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
packed	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
WAGSTAFF	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbott	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
things	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
they	O
remained	O
there	O
till	O
Friday	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
we	O
watched	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
concealed	O
under	O
some	O
straw	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sold	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BADDELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
packer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbott	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
concealed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
informed	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Wagstaff	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
merciful	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Abbott	O
nearly	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
,	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
707.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GREENFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
porter	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
in	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
my	O
warehouse	O
is	O
in	O
Clement's-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
near	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
DOROTHY	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenfield	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
down	O
Clement's-lane	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HICKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
in	O
Red	O
Lion-court	O
,	O
Clement's-lane	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
parcel	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
basket	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Greenfield	O
's	O
shopman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
basket	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
came	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
hewas	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
now	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
about	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.About	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
then	O
any	O
doubt	O
about	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.About	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
trusted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
thousands	O
of	O
pounds	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
708.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
saw	O
from	O
a	O
building	O
in	O
Watling-street	B-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
saw	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
off	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HIGGINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
saw	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
pledge	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
three	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
saw	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
possessed	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Confined	O
fourteen	O
days	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
709.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
23lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HAWES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
,	O
a	O
stone	O
mason	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
him	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
:	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
suspicion	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
watched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
labourers	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
facing	O
Founders-hall-court	O
,	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
up	O
Basinghall-street	O
,	O
across	O
Fore-street	O
,	O
into	O
Moor-lane	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
back-door	O
to	O
an	O
old-ironshop	O
,	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
lead	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
23lb	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
back-door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
23lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
quite	O
warm	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tried	O
to	O
prevail	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
settle	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
better	O
manner	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
ladle	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
the	O
ladle	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Bank-buildings	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
43	O
.	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
710.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PRESCOTT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
3lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
9d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HAWES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Poynder	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
suspicion	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
left	O
work	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
basket	O
with	O
some	O
shavings	O
;	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
3lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
coatpocket	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
resistance	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
warm	O
,	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ladle	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
bottoms	O
of	O
the	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
foreman	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
aged	O
52	O
.	O
Confined	O
fourteen	O
days	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
711.	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
CARY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Ocotber	O
,	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Botheroyd	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BOTHEROYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Beach-street	B-place
and	O
Golden-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
15th	O
instant	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
ofsomething	O
falling	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
towards	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stooping	O
to	O
pick	O
something	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
apron	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
cask	O
of	O
brandy	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
cask	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
opposite	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
the	O
beer	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
cask	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
brand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
customer	O
's	O
name	O
marked	O
with	O
chalk	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
years	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Another	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
712.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WITNEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
turkies	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tottenham	B-place
;	O
I	O
kept	O
turkies	O
in	O
my	O
orchard	O
enclosed	O
with	O
a	O
high	O
paling	O
,	O
and	O
spikes	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
footsteps	O
of	O
some	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
outside	O
the	O
fence	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
feathers	O
of	O
turkies	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
orchard	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
turkies	O
under	O
a	O
bush	O
;	O
I	O
traced	O
the	O
feathers	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
two	O
persons	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DOBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
to	O
watch	O
these	O
turkies	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
behind	O
a	O
hedge	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
persons	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
they	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
packed	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
escaped	O
had	O
two	O
turkies	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
713.	O
MARY	B-pers
CLAGHORN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
;	O
she	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
clean	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
,	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
after	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
all	O
right	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
afterwards	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
no	O
promise	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
a	O
bonnet	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JACQUES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
a	O
bonnet	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
shilling	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
my	O
daughter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
teaspoon	O
.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JACQUES	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
spoon	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
714.	O
SARAH	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
RAYMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
Richmond-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
hung	O
a	O
counterpane	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
leads	O
,	O
up	O
three-pair-of-stairs	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
counterpane	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
MACKENZIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
fall	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
door	O
is	O
generally	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
counterpane	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
to	O
some	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
a	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
counterpane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
reply	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
watch-housekeeper	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
counterpane	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Raymond	O
came	O
homein	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
counterpane	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
counterpane	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Raymond	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
46	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
715.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DUNNING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hans	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MOSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
to	O
Great	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-inn-fields	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Howard-street	O
with	O
some	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
parcels	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
servant	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Howard	O
lived	O
in	O
Howard-street	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
knew	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Charing-cross	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Vine-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Vine-street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mortimer	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
parcels	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
delivered	O
my	O
parcel	O
to	O
Miss	O
Grellet	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
brown	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Churton	O
,	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
upon	O
credit	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
GRELLETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
parcel	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
immediately	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
Lakin	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
parcel	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
supposing	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lakin	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
LAKIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
Miss	O
Grellett	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
parcel	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Miss	O
Grellett	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lakin	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
leave	O
the	O
parcel	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
unless	O
Mr.	O
Mortimer	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
pay	O
I	O
would	O
settle	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
exactly	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
parcel	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
nighest	O
way	O
to	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
716.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
GROVES	I-pers
and	O
CORNELIUS	B-pers
CONNELL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
May's-buildings	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
shoes	O
outside	O
my	O
shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
LAZARUS	O
LEVI	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
;	O
I	O
generally	O
put	O
the	O
shoes	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
an	O
evening	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
put	O
out	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shoes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
five	O
pair	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
Connell	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
alone	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
obstinate	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
till	O
a	O
good	O
bit	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
other	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Connell	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
the	O
half	O
hatch	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
Connell	O
still	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
offered	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
shewed	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
then	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
immediately	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
me	O
made	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Q.What	O
has	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.I	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
at	O
me	O
for	O
selling	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
stamps	O
.	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Connell	O
near	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
you	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
this	O
window	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
about	O
Covent-garden	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
dare	O
say	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
Dirty	O
Dick	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Dirty	O
Dick	O
's	O
I	O
saw	O
Groves	O
;	O
Connell	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
shoes	O
from	O
his	O
bosom	O
;	O
he	O
tossed	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
crying	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Groves	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
followed	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
shoes	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
shelf	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
separate	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
717.	O
LYON	B-pers
LAZARUS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
seventy-two	O
yards	O
of	O
bed-lace	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ranshall	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
RANSHALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ranshall	I-pers
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
bed-lace	O
;	O
I	O
bad	O
seen	O
it	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hours	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
seventy-two	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
bed-lace	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
piece	O
out	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
matched	O
since	O
.	O
JOSHEPH	O
BUNTER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
:	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
fortnight	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
bed-lace	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
yards	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
extraordinary	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
length	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
swapped	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
:	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honesty	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
it	O
advertised	O
;	O
she	O
stopped	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ranshall	O
's	O
which	O
was	O
just	O
accoss	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ranshull	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
pattern	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
tallied	O
with	O
the	O
piece	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
:	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
lying	O
loose	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
it	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Bunter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
lace	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
shutting	O
the	O
shop	O
up	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
lace	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Waltham-Abbey	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
said	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
ISRAEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
mind	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
by	O
accident	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
very	O
good	O
friends	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
give	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
guineas	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
to	O
buy	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lie	O
in	O
bed	O
till	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
spent	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
before	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
throw	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
water	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sober	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Ray	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
be	O
insane	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Bunter	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
perfectly	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
dealing	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
thrown	O
half	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
water	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
55	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
718.	O
JAMES	B-pers
OLIVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
peck	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
split	O
peas	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bowstreed	I-pers
.	O
EMANUAL	O
CASTLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
kitchen	O
washing	O
some	O
oysters	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
window	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
bolted	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
peas	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
's	O
man	O
should	O
stand	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
a	O
bag	O
through	O
the	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
an	O
armed	O
chair	O
;	O
his	O
miscress	O
lived	O
opposite	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bowstreed	O
,	O
a	O
corn-chandler	O
.	O
Q.Who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
's	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
,	O
the	O
brewer	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Armstrong	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bowstreed	O
;	O
nobody	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
it	O
remained	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
;	O
Lydia	B-pers
Bowstreet	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Armstrong	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
binn	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
LYDIA	B-pers
BOWSTREED	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bowstreed	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
16	O
,	O
Kingsland-road	B-place
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
corn-chandler	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
message	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
containing	O
about	O
a	O
peck	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
split	O
peas	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
S.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Armstrong	O
had	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
applied	O
to	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
adjoining	O
Castle	O
's	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
the	O
bag	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Oliver	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Castle	O
says	O
you	O
have	O
left	O
,	O
these	O
peas	O
here	O
;	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
words	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
this	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
bag	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Castle	O
's	O
possession	O
.	O
Castle	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Bishop	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
-	O
BISHOP	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
bag	O
from	O
Castle	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Lydia	B-pers
Bowstreed	I-pers
.	O
The	O
S	O
is	O
marked	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
by	O
my	O
youngest	O
sister	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Ware	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
miss	O
this	O
quantity	O
of	O
peas	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Castle	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
719.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PURNELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twelve	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
32s	O
.	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
earthen	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
WINIFRED	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
dozen	O
tea-spoons	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cupboard	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
have	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
losing	O
my	O
spoons	O
from	O
such	O
a	O
cupboard	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
child	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
farthing's-worth	O
of	O
pins	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
spoons	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
child	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
mind	O
the	O
place	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
could	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
by	O
a	O
cap	O
on	O
a	O
bureau	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
two	O
plates	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
plates	O
and	O
the	O
cap	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
passes	O
as	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Trott	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Trott	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
child	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
carving	O
knife	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
run	O
me	O
through	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
never	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
plates	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
plates	O
concealed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
dish	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
cap	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
behind	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
BARLOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
send	O
the	O
child	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
farthing's-worth	O
of	O
milk	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
child	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HARMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
never	O
sent	O
the	O
child	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
that	O
served	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
milk	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
keys	O
;	O
this	O
one	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
opened	O
the	O
cupboard	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
spoons	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
found	O
the	O
cap	O
and	O
plates	O
herself	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
cap	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
plates	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnessess	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
720.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PURDIE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
24s	O
.	O
two	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
pap-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wickings	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
identify	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
721.	O
HENRY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GOODMAN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ALICE	B-pers
SHERRARD	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
feet	O
of	O
lead	O
pipe	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LANGLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
an	O
alteration	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
No.1	O
,	O
Great	B-place
Cumberland-place	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
occupation	O
of	O
Lord	O
Jersey	O
;	O
a	O
roll	O
of	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
premises	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
making	O
a	O
water-closet	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
Lady	O
Jersey	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
;	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
lead	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
from	O
the	O
Public-office	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
thisalteration	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
Lord	O
Jersey	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Langley	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
lead	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
drawing-room	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
removed	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
.	O
Q.Are	O
you	O
a	O
plumber	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
furnished	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
furnish	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
in	O
which	O
that	O
is	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
coiled	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
roll	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
its	O
being	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
in	O
trying	O
it	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
particular	O
hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
points	O
it	O
out	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
hole	O
blown	O
in	O
the	O
metal	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
find	O
in	O
one	O
roll	O
in	O
fifty	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
:	O
On	O
Michaelmas	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Smith	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
in	O
Short's-gardens	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
coiled	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Goodman	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
then	O
Goodman	O
and	O
Smith	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Sherrard	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bowl-yard	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Treadway	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
directly	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
you	O
who	O
can	O
confirm	O
your	O
account	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
-	O
have	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
here	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
last	O
Session	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
in	O
Bedford-square	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
never	O
tried	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
tried	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q.Any	O
where	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
ever	O
tried	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
ever	O
committed	O
as	O
a	O
vagrant	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
ever	O
committed	O
to	O
Clerkenwellprison	O
from	O
Hicks's-hall	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sherrard	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Smith	O
and	O
Mumford	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sherrard	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
her	O
bed-gown	O
and	O
night-cap	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sherrard	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
lead	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
lead	O
pipe	O
,	O
brought	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
there	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pipe	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
Smith	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Gross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
was	O
consumed	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Sherrard	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
appeared	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
her	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Treadway	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
collared	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Treadway	O
collared	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
Smith	O
had	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
farthings	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
Treadway	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
Treadway	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Sherrard	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
was	O
exposed	O
to	O
view	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
concealed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MUMFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
brother	O
officers	O
have	O
stated	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Sherrard	O
called	O
eight	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Goodman	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
39	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Shertard	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
50	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
722.	O
ANN	B-pers
WALLACE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
21s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Court	O
.	O
Charging	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cubitt	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
AUSTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
Upper	B-place
John-street	I-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stocking-dresser	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
then	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lonsdale	O
,	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
of	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
packed	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lonsdale	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
O'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
discovered	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
advertisement	O
from	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
;	O
one	O
pair	O
was	O
marked	O
W.	B-pers
Cubitt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
marked	O
C	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Cubitt	O
's	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CUBITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Londsdale	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
dressed	O
;	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
marked	O
W.	B-pers
Cubitt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
marked	O
C.	O
withcommon	O
ink	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
HARRIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
High-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
dinner	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
her	O
condition	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
sent	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
six	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
pair	O
is	O
new	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
appeared	O
very	O
like	O
the	O
pair	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
had	O
brought	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
obtained	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
some	O
laundress	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
hardly	O
reply	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
led	O
to	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stocking	O
were	O
produced	O
(	O
five	O
pair	O
)	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Austin	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Austin	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
pair	O
is	O
marked	O
S	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
stands	O
for	O
Sanderson	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
water-cresses	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
stockings	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
723.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
EZEKIEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pantaloons	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Levi	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
identify	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
724.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
FITZGERALD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday-morning	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Dyot-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
decoyed	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
slipped	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
seven-shilling-piece	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
the	O
pocket	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
pocket	O
a	O
purse	O
containing	O
twelve	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
into	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
through	O
another	O
passage	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
you	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
intoxicated	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
morning	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
glasses	O
of	O
brandy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
your	O
consent	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
passage	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
two	O
officers	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Dyot-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
identified	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
Dutch	O
coin	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
the	O
foreign	O
coins	O
were	O
all	O
different	O
;	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
money	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
Dyot-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
pointed	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Rat	O
's	O
Castle	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
close	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MUMFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Treadway	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
prisoner	O
while	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
all	O
laughing	O
at	O
his	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
he	O
pulled	O
some	O
papers	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
notes	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
silver	O
and	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
girls	O
that	O
were	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
nomore	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
foreign	O
coin	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
flurried	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
truth	O
in	O
what	O
she	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
725.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COX	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
COCK	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
104lb	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	O
ALLEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
Flower	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
carman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stapp	O
,	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Flower	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
for	O
twenty	O
firkins	O
of	O
butter	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Stapp	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
myself	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
Waterford	O
butter	O
from	O
the	O
wharf	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
casks	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cart	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
certain	O
quantity	O
of	O
butter	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
remainder	O
without	O
knowing	O
the	O
number	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
these	O
firkins	O
nearly	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
one	O
parcel	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
lowered	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
crane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
.	O
CORNELIUS	O
CORNELLON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
cooper	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Flower	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
;	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
butter	O
was	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
twenty	O
firkins	O
of	O
Cork	O
butter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hay-basket	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
bottom	O
upwards	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
Waterford	O
butter	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
butter	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
cask	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
without	O
asking	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
the	O
cask	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Flower	O
;	O
we	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
726.	O
MARY	B-pers
ROBE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
four	O
women	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
three	O
children	O
's	O
bonnets	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
's	O
beaver	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pedder	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
DANIEL	O
PEDDER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
in	O
Beach-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lined	O
and	O
bound	O
hats	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
her	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
them	O
till	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
little	O
bonnets	O
and	O
caps	O
that	O
we	O
never	O
put	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
never	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
purpose	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
PHILIP	O
GREEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Pedder	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Pedder	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	O
PEDDER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
bonnets	O
and	O
some	O
caps	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
laying	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
in	O
a	O
ban-box	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
our	O
shop	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
sell	O
hats	O
in	O
this	O
state	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
's	O
hats	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
put	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
six	O
children	O
's	O
hats	O
that	O
never	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
Q.What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.About	O
2l	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
above	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
deposit	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
written	O
defence	O
,	O
stating	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
hats	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shopman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
shopkeepers	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
line	O
and	O
bind	O
,	O
as	O
would	O
appear	O
from	O
the	O
book	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
shopman	O
entered	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Pedder	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
shopman	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
he	O
enlisted	O
into	O
thefirst	O
regiment	O
of	O
Surrey	O
militia	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
camp	O
near	O
Ashford	O
,	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
hats	O
old	O
shopkeepers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
a	O
book	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
an	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
white	O
had	O
lined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Pedder	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
had	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
white	O
hat	O
to	O
line	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
so	O
from	O
this	O
entry	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
book	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
keeps	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
they	O
are	O
entered	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
these	O
hats	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
entry	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
their	O
way	O
back	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
727.	O
MARY	B-pers
ROBE	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Harnett	I-pers
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
HARNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	O
Harnett	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Baker's-arms	B-place
,	I-place
Whitecross-street	I-place
:	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sheet	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
house	O
better	O
than	O
five	O
months	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
couple	O
left	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
back	O
room	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
sheet	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
person	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
fortnight	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
sheet	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
EDWARD	O
GREEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
some	O
hats	O
and	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
hat-box	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
vast	O
number	O
of	O
duplicates	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
this	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Harnett	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
sheet	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
marks	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
its	O
being	O
her	O
sheet	O
.	O
-	O
SHEPHERD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
sheet	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	O
Betts	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
customer	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Harnett	O
.	O
The	O
mark	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
E	O
M	O
H	O
,	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
my	O
other	O
sheet	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sheet	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
never	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Harnett	O
's	O
sheet	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
728.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lott	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Alley	O
.	O
)	O
DANIEL	O
LOTT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
at	O
Twickenham	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
goose	O
hid	O
in	O
some	O
straw	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
a	O
barn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
afterwards	O
placed	O
myself	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
from	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
till	O
near	O
twelve	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rustling	O
in	O
the	O
straw	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gun	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
goose	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
you	O
,	O
Hall	O
,	O
stop	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
his	O
leg	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
shot	O
mark	O
;	O
the	O
goose	O
had	O
been	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
LOTT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
desire	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shots	O
in	O
his	O
leg	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
somebody	O
to	O
pick	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
KEEZEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lott	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
four	O
children	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
I	O
got	O
too	O
much	O
liquor	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
lock	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
straw	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
altered	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
I	O
was	O
fired	O
at	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
729.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HAYES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
108	O
,	O
Shadwell	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
new	O
copper	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
being	O
put	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
returned	O
fromdinner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	O
BENNER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
copper	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
copper	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bruise	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
noticed	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
join	O
near	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
copper	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
;	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
opposite	O
the	O
Office	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
remarkably	O
deep	O
copper	O
for	O
the	O
circumserence	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
JARVIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
in	O
Love-lane	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
new	O
copper	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Fast-day	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
sight	O
before	O
.	O
ELEANOR	O
OSBORN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Love-lane	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
my	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Fast-day	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
turnpike	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
returning	O
back	O
into	O
Brook-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
copper	O
.	O
ROBERT	O
BROWN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Police	O
Office	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
all	O
that	O
morning	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
copper	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
730.	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITHERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	O
SHERWIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
tablespoon	O
and	O
one	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
,	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
story	O
she	O
told	O
about	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
GEORGE	O
JUPP	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
pledge	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
from	O
whom	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
Sherwin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
table-spoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
ANN	O
SHERWIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Butterfield	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
and	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
tablespoon	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
sometimes	O
absent	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
seldom	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
of	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
no	O
promise	O
of	O
favor	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
GABELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Cadman	O
was	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
she	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
Cadman	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
Edmonton-fair	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
duplicate	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Butterfield	O
.	O
SARAH	O
BUTTERFIELD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
interrogated	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
duplicate	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
forgiveness	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
duplicate	O
from	O
her	O
upon	O
that	O
promise	O
.	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
being	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
sheet	O
and	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
)	O
.	O
Gabell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
Susan	O
Cadman	O
's	O
sister	O
.	O
SUSAN	O
CADMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
pledge	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sherwin	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
sheet	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
some	O
tears	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
731.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
WEBB	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
slippers	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Yelf	I-pers
.	O
FRANCES	O
YELF	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
146	O
,	O
Oxford-street	B-place
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
property	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
,	O
if	O
her	O
master	O
was	O
home	O
in	O
time	O
;	O
a	O
customer	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
errand	O
boys	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
customer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
pockets	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
stuck	O
out	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
each	O
pocket	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
jean	O
slippers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
any	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
-	O
a	O
nine	O
months	O
character	O
.	O
(	O
William	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
slippers	O
,	O
which	O
wre	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
neither	O
father	O
nor	O
mother	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
creature	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
732.	O
FANNY	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
ANN	O
HARWOOD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
mending	O
a	O
black	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-horse	B-place
in	I-place
Rupert-street	I-place
,	O
kept	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Tibby	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
called	O
me	O
away	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
her	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
chair	O
where	O
my	O
gown	O
hung	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
SLADE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
gown	O
in	O
an	O
unlocked	O
cupboard	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Harwood	O
)	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
sitting	O
against	O
the	O
chair	O
and	O
your	O
charging	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A.Not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
cupboard	O
is	O
never	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
733.	O
SARAH	B-pers
DANCER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
sixteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
welting	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hyatt	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
CHARLES	O
HYATT	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
leather-cutter	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
183	O
,	O
Shoreditch	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
purchase	O
some	O
leather	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
another	O
customer	O
myself	O
;	O
she	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
closer	O
or	O
binder-woman	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
wait	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
out	O
some	O
leather	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
bundle	O
containing	O
sixteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
welting	O
leather	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
instantly	O
enquired	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
leather	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
just	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
instantly	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
customer	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
maniac	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
who	O
is	O
deranged	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
officer	O
produced	O
the	O
leather	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
leather	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
exposed	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
cellar	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
consider	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
keep	O
in	O
it	O
articles	O
for	O
sale	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
articles	O
not	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
this	O
leather	O
is	O
not	O
manufactured	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
saleable	O
condition	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
45	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
week	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
6d	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
734.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HADLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
of	O
sheet	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Felix	B-pers
Bulkeley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JOHN	O
HARRISON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surveyor	O
and	O
builder	O
,	O
in	O
Berkeley-square	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ellis	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
information	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
ELLIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Essex-street	O
,	O
Strand	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
arch-way	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Plowden	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
sheet	O
of	O
white	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
in	O
Shire-lane	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
General	O
Bulkeley	B-pers
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
key	O
that	O
opened	O
Mr.	O
Plowden	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
General	O
Bulkeley	B-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
does	O
not	O
match	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
repairing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
the	O
proper	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plowden	O
's	O
house	O
belongs	O
to	O
General	O
Bulkeley	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Felix	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
lead	O
belongs	O
to	O
General	O
Bulkeley	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
ASKEW	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
premises	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
lead	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
735.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
KEEFE	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
WELCH	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
1l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
MARTIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Barley-court	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
army	O
work	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
clean	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Sunday	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
for	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
Sarah	O
Tanner	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
one	O
pound-note	O
to	O
take	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
out	O
for	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Keefe	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Tanner	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
scrupled	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
twelve	O
penny	O
pieces	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pound-note	O
and	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
pound	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
a	O
sevenshilling	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Keefe	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
solid	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
gown	O
,	O
new	O
slippers	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
new	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
discharged	O
;	O
the	O
frock	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
TANNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
landlady	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
towards	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
refused	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
twelve	O
penny-pieces	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
lock	O
the	O
box	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
pound	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
towards	O
her	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
stopped	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
lumbering	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
nobody	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
nobody	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
