TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1803	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
ESQUIRE	O
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
&	O
BLANCHARD	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1803	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
LE	I-pers
BLANC	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty's-Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALAN	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
WATKIN	B-pers
LEWES	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SKINNER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CARR	I-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shingler	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Samson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lackington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Southey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willement	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mylne	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gupter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Senior	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas-William	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lightly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Duffield	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Williams	O
.	O
592.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
IRELAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
fifty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rawdon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Rawdon	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Sage	O
,	O
Rawdon	O
,	O
and	O
Jennings	O
;	O
Irish	O
factor	O
s	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
cutting	O
open	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
one	O
piece	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
placed	O
in	O
our	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
down	O
Foster-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
goods	O
within	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
in	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
good	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
witness	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
passage	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
,	O
one	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
private	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
a	O
glass	O
door	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
at	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
attempted	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
thrown	O
down	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
SIMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
a	O
knife	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
stab	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
stab	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
cut	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
throwing	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CRISP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
it	O
into	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
upon	O
my	O
heel	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
GILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
goods	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
sam	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
knife	O
from	O
James	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
other	O
knives	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
Producing	O
them.	O
)	O
(	O
Mr	O
.	O
Jennings	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Gilson	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
are	O
your	O
partners	O
names	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	O
Rawdon	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
593.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ALLAMBY	I-pers
and	O
JANE	B-pers
PROSSER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tongue	O
scraper	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
paste	O
pin	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
tooth-pick	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Doratt	I-pers
;	O
a	O
shift	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
four	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Doratt	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DORATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Bruton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Berkeley-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
my	O
man	O
servant	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
my	O
cook	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
at	O
various	O
times	O
,	O
numberless	O
articles	O
,	O
which	O
created	O
in	O
me	O
suspicion	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
man	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
defiring	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
during	O
my	O
absence	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
near	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Allamby	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Doratt	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Prosser	O
's	O
box	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
upper	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
box	O
at	O
my	O
request	O
,	O
and	O
unlocked	O
it	O
herself	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
boxes	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
keys	O
and	O
unlocked	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
property	O
in	O
his	O
boxes	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
acknowledged	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
boxes	O
a	O
silver	O
tongue	O
scraper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Doratt	O
claimed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
pin	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
and	O
gave	O
methis	O
pin	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Ally	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
pin	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
using	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
down	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
duplicate	O
,	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
pawned	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DEARE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mulcaster	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Chandler's-street	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
har	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
pledged	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
mother	O
or	O
sister	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
shortish	O
young	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
only	O
reason	O
for	O
believing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
her	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
duplicate	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
upon	O
the	O
pledging	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Doratt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Doratt	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
since	O
Christmas	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
from	O
respect	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
charity	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
service	O
upon	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Allamby	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
pin	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
by	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
the	O
duplicate	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
,	O
my	O
box	O
has	O
been	O
left	O
open	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Prosser	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Doratt	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
removing	O
from	O
one	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
litter	O
worth	O
my	O
acceptance	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Allamby	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Allamby	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Prosser	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
594.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
twelve	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
twenty-one	O
yards	O
of	O
sarcenet	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
sarcenet	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
twelve	O
other	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
and	O
six	O
other	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-court	B-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
manufacturer	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
our	O
accompting-house	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
PURSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
London	O
Wall	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
me	O
twelve	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
improperly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary-axe	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
send	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
learnt	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gabell	I-pers
proved	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
and	O
Richard	O
Smith	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
-	O
Leadbeater	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
were	O
also	O
identified	O
by	O
Gabell	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
36	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
595.	O
ELIZA	B-pers
BARRY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
sarcenet	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Shem	B-pers
Batho	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
a	O
loss	O
but	O
from	O
his	O
books	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
596.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
THEW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maudsley	I-pers
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
MAUDSLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maudsley	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Panyer-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Newgate-street	I-place
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
silk-dyer	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
my	O
gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WOODMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11thof	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
thirty-four	O
or	O
thirty-five	O
duplicates	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
relates	O
to	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Maudsley	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
darned	O
in	O
the	O
tail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
gown	O
shewn	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
production	O
of	O
that	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
the	O
gown	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
presented	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
ticket	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
597.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
THEW	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glazier	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
24	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-without	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
herself	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
wait	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
her	O
in	O
in	O
a	O
sew	O
minutes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
leading	O
to	O
the	O
parlour	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
not	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
rather	O
wait	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
sit	O
with	O
the	O
servant	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
a	O
person	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
short	O
conversation	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
for	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
then	O
missed	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offering	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
and	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
suit	O
me	O
,	O
very	O
few	O
words	O
passed	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
case	O
I	O
altered	O
my	O
mind	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Maudsley	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Maudsley	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Woodman	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
upon	O
our	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
search	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
table-spoons	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
answer	O
no	O
question	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
at	O
London-wall	O
;	O
Woodman	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master's-house	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
out	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
talking	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop-passage	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
in	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
in	O
the	O
parlour-window	O
just	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WOODMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
duplicates	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
one	O
of	O
this	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
pledged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Purse	O
's	O
,	O
London-wall	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
left	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Purse	I-pers
,	O
London-wall	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
teaspoon	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
pledge	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoons	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
598.	O
RAPHAEL	B-pers
MARTINI	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
apair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
GRIFFIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
117	O
,	O
Oxford-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
some	O
artificial	O
flowers	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
having	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
pleasure	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
box	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
beyond	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
trash	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
repeatedly	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
him	O
between	O
the	O
counters	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pass	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
direction	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspecion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
confirmed	O
me	O
,	O
being	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
immediately	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
down	O
Prince's-street	O
;	O
being	O
satisfied	O
I	O
could	O
soon	O
overtake	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
missed	O
the	O
stockings	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
5s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
maid-servant	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
;	O
by	O
dint	O
of	O
persuasion	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
Princes-street	O
is	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
stockings	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
stop	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
call	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
take	O
him	O
quietly	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
's	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
-	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Griffin	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
manufacturer	O
's	O
marks	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Griffin	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
to	O
know	O
perfectly	O
well	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
officer	O
when	O
he	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
52	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
599.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RICKERBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
shag	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Foulds	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Imeson	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
FOULDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
,	O
in	O
Holywell-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Imeson	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
our	O
servant	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
shag	O
tobacco	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
identify	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
such	O
tobacco	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
explanation	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MESSENGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Foulds	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
him	O
for	O
tobacco	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
cap	O
and	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
persisted	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
exactly	O
one	O
pound	O
three	O
quarters	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
tears	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
dearest	O
of	O
masters	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
kept	O
myself	O
honest	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
this	O
trouble	O
;	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
only	O
words	O
exchanged	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foulds	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
tobacco	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
little	O
tobacco	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foulds	O
.	O
Till	B-pers
this	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
highest	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
custom	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
giving	O
them	O
tobacco	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
an	O
equivalent	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
tobacco	O
at	O
the	O
wholesale	O
price	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
36	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Hotham	O
.	O
600.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
RUSSELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East	I-pers
Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BACKHOUSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
assistant-elder	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
superintend	O
the	O
top	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
teas	O
;	O
the	O
floor	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
tea	O
laid	O
out	O
to	O
shew	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
William	O
Brandon	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
BRANDON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
adjoining	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
shoes	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
tied	O
his	O
shoes	O
I	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
by	O
an	O
Excise	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
tea	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
Matthew	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Excise	O
officer	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
In	O
walking	O
among	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
43	O
.	O
Publickly	O
whipped	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
opposite	O
the	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
601.	O
JAMES	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brignall	I-pers
.	O
BENJAMIN	O
BRIGNALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
backwards	O
at	O
breakfast	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
weighed	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
HANSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Brignall	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
past	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Brignall	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
servants	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
into	O
Bell-court	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
then	O
by	O
the	O
knuckle	O
;	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
intoxication	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
quite	O
stupid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
frolic	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
a	O
felony	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
31	O
.	O
Fined	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
602.	O
SARAH-ANN	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
BOND	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
card	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
CARVER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
mercer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
Oxford-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
Charles	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bond	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WEBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Carver	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
discharged	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
lace	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
Mr	O
.	O
Carver	O
and	O
myself	O
were	O
engaged	O
with	O
customers	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
leisure	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
black	O
lace	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
they	O
meant	O
white	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
white	O
French	O
lace	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
doors	O
higher	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
is	O
discharged	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bell	O
,	O
draw	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
with	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bond	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
when	O
the	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bell	O
;	O
I	O
continued	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
lace	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
none	O
would	O
suit	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
lace	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
card	O
that	O
was	O
dropped	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bond	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bond	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Newman-street	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bond	O
,	O
walking	O
slowly	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
on	O
together	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
looked	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
card	O
lying	O
without	O
the	O
lace	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
behind	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
card	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
betrays	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
drew	O
the	O
lace	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
right-hand	O
pocket-hole	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
card	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bell	O
,	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
then	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bell	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
lace	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
lace	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
card	O
C.	O
C.	O
A.	O
C.	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
pattern	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
shewn	O
them	O
that	O
card	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
3l	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
master	O
has	O
a	O
partner	O
,	O
has	O
not	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
discharged	O
was	O
the	O
spokeswoman	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
children	O
were	O
playing	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
lace	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
draw	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bond	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lace	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoners	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Bell	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
603.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
GARDENER	I-pers
and	O
THO-MAS	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
unnatural	O
crime	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
But	O
detained	O
to	O
take	O
their	O
trials	O
for	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
604.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
BARTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
of	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
two	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
two	O
salt-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
four	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
glass	O
decanter	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
three	O
glass	O
salt-cellers	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
twenty-four	O
silver-handled	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
24s	O
.	O
twenty-three	O
silver-handled	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
23s	O
.	O
two	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
glass	O
rummers	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
tea-caddee	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
two	O
four	O
cruets	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
cruet	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
two	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
four	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
longs	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
an	O
iron	O
poker	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GORDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Orchard-house	B-place
,	I-place
Blackwall	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
secured	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
were	O
you	O
awaked	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
name	O
called	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
directly	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
windows	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
that	O
window	O
any	O
shutters	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
knife	O
case	O
empty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
window	O
did	O
the	O
person	O
get	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
kitchen	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
that	O
window	O
fastened	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
shutter	O
was	O
bolted	O
with	O
a	O
bolt	O
at	O
bottom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
shutter	O
forced	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
forced	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
vacancy	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
sun	O
having	O
drawn	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
an	O
instrument	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
opened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
sure	O
that	O
shutter	O
had	O
been	O
bolted	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
dressed	O
myself	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
garden	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
bundles	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
that	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
alley	O
where	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
bundles	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
low	O
sence	O
over	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
round	O
table	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
three	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
decanter	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
salt-cellers	O
,	O
three	O
glass	O
salt-cellers	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
salt-spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
bring	O
the	O
bundle	O
away	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
shewn	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
led	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
bundles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
promise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
threat	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
accomplices	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
about	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
go	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
earn	O
an	O
honest	O
living	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
livedin	O
my	O
service	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
poker	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
old	O
poker	O
found	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
officer	O
fit	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
instrument	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
shutter	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
opened	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
MARK	B-pers
MILGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
headborough	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
things	O
put	O
into	O
your	O
charge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
poker	O
near	O
the	O
back	O
kit	O
chen-window	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
found	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Gordon	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
silver	O
salt-cellers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
table-spoon	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
salt-spoons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Thirty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
day-light	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Perfectly	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
family	O
all	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
youth	O
and	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
.	O
605.	O
JAMES	B-pers
AYRES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
An	O
ironmonger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Messrs.	O
Downer	O
and	O
Sandys	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Saturday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
towards	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
collected	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Birkett	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
chymist	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
fits	O
;	O
I	O
remained	O
there	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
only	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
an	O
alarm	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
''	O
your	O
pocket	O
is	O
picked	O
,	O
''	O
or	O
,	O
``	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
''	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
immediately	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
Mr.	O
March	O
collared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
press	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARCH	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fishing-tackle	O
maker	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
take	O
a	O
yellow	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARCH	I-pers
,	O
fen	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
Owen	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
March	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
,	O
who	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
606.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
and	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pring	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in-the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
tin	O
canister	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
four	O
loaves	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
eight	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
five	O
1b	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
11d	O
.	O
four	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
two	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
20d	O
.	O
two	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
value	O
20d	O
.	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
5d	O
.	O
and	O
ninety-six	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pring	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PRING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kenton	B-place
Green	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Harrow	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
windows	O
shut	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
returned	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
unlocked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
pushed	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
then	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
write	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
four	O
loaves	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
eight	O
pounds	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
five	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
shuff	O
,	O
2	O
ounces	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
tea	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
tin	O
canister	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
kept	O
a	O
little	O
shop	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
suppose	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
bread	O
was	O
ninepence	O
halfpenny	O
a	O
loaf	O
,	O
the	O
bacon	O
one	O
shilling	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
the	O
tea	O
and	O
the	O
tin	O
canister	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
servant	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
evening	O
belonging	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
Kenton	O
Green	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
a	O
scaffold	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Pring	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Pring	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
they	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Daniel	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
did	O
more	O
than	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
stop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
the	O
tea-canister	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
canister	O
upon	O
the	O
stones	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
public-house	O
near	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
sitting	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
drinking	O
beer	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
contradicted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
searched	O
in	O
your	O
presence	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
something	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
tea-canister	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
canister	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Lost	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
near	O
the	O
spot	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
man	O
some	O
promise	O
of	O
forgiveness	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
heard	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LOFT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Kenton	O
Green	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
after	O
the	O
stone-mason	O
's	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
put	O
the	O
tea-canister	O
among	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
nettles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
canister	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
canister	O
in	O
the	O
bunch	O
of	O
nettles	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public-house	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
were	O
you	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
bunch	O
of	O
nettles	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
canister	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
nothing	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pring	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
by	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
after	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
canister	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Pring	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
that	O
canister	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
your	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Lost	O
bring	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
canister	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
canister	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
bruised	O
it	O
by	O
salling	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
tea	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
canister	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
you	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
-	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
latch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
lock	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
locked	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
latched	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
pushed	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
drinking	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
canister	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
607.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PUNCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
a	O
hone	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
prayer-book	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Hinchley	I-pers
.	O
MICHAEL	O
HINCHLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
lodged	O
and	O
slept	O
together	O
:	O
Last	O
Monday	O
week	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
articles	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
Ruffell-street	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
I	O
owe	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
stick	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HATCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Stoke	O
Newington	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
with	O
the	O
cloaths	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
stick	O
over	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Stoke	O
Newington	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
bundle	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rather	O
denied	O
it	O
when	O
his	O
master	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
on	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
drunk	O
;	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
608.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOLTON	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHARPE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
two	O
bushels	O
of	O
wheat-flour	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
.	O
FREDERICK-CHARLES	B-pers
DAVENPORT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Charles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
miller	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Staines	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
building	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
mill	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
joined	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
all	O
under	O
one	O
roof	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
fence	O
surrounding	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
your	O
brother	O
and	O
yourself	O
live	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bolton	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Just	O
after	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
one	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
day-break	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
mill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
mill	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
walk	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
stop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
mill	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
a	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
mill	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
mill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
opposite	O
house	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
opposite	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
Bolton	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
distance	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
ten	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Star-light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
heard	O
him	O
stop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
twice	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
latch	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
it	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
attempt	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
the	O
latch	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
but	O
pull	O
the	O
latch	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
that	O
be	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
passed	O
the	O
door	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
wait	O
where	O
you	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
which	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
latch	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
you	O
had	O
fastened	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
perceived	O
a	O
light	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
mill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
light	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
light	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
Bolton	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
flour	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
entered	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Bolton	O
with	O
any	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Somebody	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Immediately	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bottom	O
door	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
called	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
brother	O
to	O
mind	O
the	O
sack	O
and	O
flour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Sharpe	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
with	O
.	O
Bolton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
Sharpe	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Grinding	O
wheat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
judge	O
,	O
from	O
what	O
you	O
observed	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
whether	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
flour	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
upwards	O
of	O
seventy	O
sacks	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
mill	O
is	O
opposite	O
the	O
house	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
straight	O
line	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
connected	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
internal	O
communication	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
either	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
yard	O
that	O
is	O
behind	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAVENPORT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
with	O
your	O
brother	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bolton	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
heard	O
it	O
strike	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
while	O
Bolton	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
mill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
Bolton	O
come	O
and	O
pull	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
mill	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
mill	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
open	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
pulled	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
again	O
directly	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
opened	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
wait	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
watching	O
the	O
door	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
light	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
whether	O
the	O
light	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Bolton	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mill	O
with	O
the	O
flour	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
he	O
the	O
flour	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Sharpe	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
some	O
one	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
bag	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
those	O
who	O
apprehended	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
staid	O
behind	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
Bolton	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
remained	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
contained	O
wheat	O
flour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Sharpe	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
up	O
with	O
Bolton	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
mill	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
that	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Sharpe	O
was	O
employed	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
Bolton	O
entered	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
within	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
mill	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
but	O
Sharpe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
the	O
mill	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
nobody	O
there	O
but	O
Sharpe	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
how	O
many	O
does	O
your	O
father	O
's	O
family	O
consist	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
sons	O
,	O
three	O
daughters	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
maid-servants	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
mill	O
was	O
fastened	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
communicating	O
with	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
yard	O
communicates	O
with	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
flour	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
bushell	O
and	O
three	O
pecks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Frederick-	O
Charles	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
fasten	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
locked	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
mill	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
Sharpe	O
worked	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
our	O
service	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Bolton	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Sharpe	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Bolton	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
42	O
.	O
Sharpe	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
52	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Chambre	O
.	O
609.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
11.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
seven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
an	O
half-guinea	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
;	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
great-coat	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
11.	O
and	O
three	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
value	O
11.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
SEWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
St.	B-place
Andrew's-hill	I-place
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
does	O
not	O
reside	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
other	O
persons	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
between	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
half-past	O
six	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
double	O
looked	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
my	O
boxes	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
locked	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
split	O
across	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
is	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
his	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
by	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
recovered	O
the	O
notes	O
or	O
money	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
M'KAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Mrs.	O
Sewell	O
hired	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
home	O
some	O
greens	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lifting	O
the	O
things	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stepped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITEHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
contending	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
great	O
trouble	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
turned	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
down	O
Addle-hill	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
without	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Labourin-vain-hill	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
himself	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
over	O
some	O
rails	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
ask	O
a	O
boy	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
AARON	B-pers
HALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
church	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
some	O
buildings	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
bag	O
over	O
some	O
fencing	O
adjoining	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sewell	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
claimed	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BEBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
messenger	O
to	O
the	O
Phoenix	O
Company	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
these	O
keys	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
some	O
picklock	O
keys	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
these	O
picklock	O
keys	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
three	O
picklock	O
keys	O
were	O
also	O
found	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Sewell	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
ply	O
at	O
the	O
markets	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
610.	O
ANN	B-pers
LEACH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Sweden	O
's	O
passage	O
,	O
Moor-lane	O
,	O
and	O
drive	O
a	O
hackney-coach	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Moorgate	B-place
on	O
the	O
ranks	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
drink	O
,	O
onthe	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
after	O
drinking	O
the	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
horses	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
LACEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
over	O
her	O
arm	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
coachman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
mend	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Roberts	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Moor-lane	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
husband	O
looking	O
for	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
EDDINBORO	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
Crown-street	O
,	O
Finsbury-square	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
this	O
great	O
coat	O
was	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
brought	O
the	O
ticket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
pledged	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
as	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
trifle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
coat	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
duplicate	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
611.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
FINES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DARBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Lloyd	O
lodges	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
chairing	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
NEEDHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GEARY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
a	O
duplicate	O
to	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lloyd	O
owed	O
me	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
something	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
46	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
612.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LEADER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
5s	O
.	O
3	O
1/4d	O
.	O
for	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
embezzle	O
,	O
secrete	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
at	O
Bow	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
barrow	O
of	O
bread	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
he	O
never	O
returned	O
,	O
or	O
brought	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
barrow	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
loaves	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
a	O
stranger	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Old	B-place
Ford	I-place
,	O
and	O
deal	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
half	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
threepence	O
farthing	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
owed	O
for	O
bread	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
bread	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1s	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
613.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PAUL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
held	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
42d	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
George	O
III	O
.	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
common	O
utterer	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sentenced	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
one	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
sureties	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
shilling	O
,	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
utter	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Soane	I-pers
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
CALEB-EDWARD	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
conviction	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	O
Paul	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Office	O
of	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
for	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
compare	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
original	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
correct	O
copy	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
Copy	O
of	O
record	O
of	O
conviction	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
deputy-keeper	O
of	O
the	O
New-prison	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
-	O
was	O
he	O
ever	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
February	O
sessions	O
,	O
1802	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
him	O
into	O
your	O
custody	O
after	O
the	O
trial	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
remain	O
in	O
prison	O
after	O
the	O
trial	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
possibly	O
be	O
mistaken	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
SOANE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
public-house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Portugal-street	I-place
,	I-place
Lincoln's-Inn-fields	I-place
?	O
--	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
come	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
upon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
him	O
the	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Seven	O
farthings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
turn	O
your	O
attention	O
to	O
the	O
shilling	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shilling	O
from	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
towards	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
shilling	O
in	O
a	O
peace	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
separate	O
from	O
all	O
others	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Next	O
day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
furnished	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
payment	O
for	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
offered	O
me	O
another	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
stop	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
smasher	O
,	O
or	O
passer	O
of	O
bad	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
next	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
throw	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
;	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
quickly	O
to	O
his	O
mouth	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
gullet	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
swallowed	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
pass	O
between	O
my	O
fingers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
;	O
no	O
silver	O
whatever	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
halfpence	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
gin	O
,	O
without	O
offering	O
the	O
shilling	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
five-pence	O
or	O
sixpence	O
to	O
spare	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
shilling	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
SOANE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Soane	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Soane	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
mind	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
set	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
shilling	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MENCELIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Moniers	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mint	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
shilling	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
indeed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
silver	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
colouring	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
change	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
supposed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
55	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Hotham	O
.	O
614.	O
ANN	B-pers
GREENHILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gillman	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
GILLMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linendraper	O
,	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GREENWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gillman	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
shopmen	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
for	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
busy	O
;	O
the	O
article	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
lay	O
just	O
by	O
on	O
the	O
shelf	O
where	O
she	O
stood	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
confused	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
fitting	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
stoop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
she	O
fixed	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
print	O
that	O
was	O
shewn	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shopmen	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
stepped	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
led	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
private	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
about	O
twenty-four	O
or	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
cotton	O
for	O
a	O
frock	O
;	O
I	O
chose	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
four	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
detain	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
stolen	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
prints	O
but	O
some	O
bedfurniture	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
,	O
jail	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
615.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DREW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
two	O
jackets	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
another	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
two	O
Guernsey	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
two	O
nankeen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
valveteen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
