TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1804	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
AND	O
BLANCHARD	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1804	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	O
GROSE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOYDELL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
BROOK	O
WATSON	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STAINES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
CHARLES	I-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
CHARLES	B-pers
FLOWER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
JOSHUA-	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
NEWMAN	O
KNOWLYS	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tippett	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Tasker	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Osmond	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fredder	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dole	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hanston	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas-Andrew	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Percy	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sabine	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Syre	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dolgleish	I-pers
,	O
Duncan	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
311.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
CLAYTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Incledon	I-pers
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
INCLEDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Brompton	B-place
Crescent	I-place
,	I-place
Knightsbridge	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
:	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
laid	O
the	O
cloth	O
for	O
dinner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
were	O
placed	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
silver	O
spoons	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Cooke	O
,	O
the	O
actor	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
giving	O
some	O
orders	O
to	O
some	O
painters	O
that	O
were	O
painting	O
the	O
railing	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
speaking	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
who	O
were	O
employed	O
in	O
painting	O
my	O
garden	O
railing	O
went	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
their	O
names	O
are	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Winter	O
;	O
after	O
pursuing	O
them	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
searched	O
prior	O
to	O
their	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Incledon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
these	O
spoons	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
painting	O
the	O
rails	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
brought	O
back	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
garden	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Incledon	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Incledon	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
painters	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
yard	O
?	O
we	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
stole	O
our	O
spoons	O
;	O
we	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
Winter	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
currant	O
jelly	O
and	O
two	O
table-spoons	O
;	O
walking	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
further	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
two	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Incledon	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
hackney-coach	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
this	O
man	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Incledon	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
accomplices	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
.	O
LAWRENCE	B-pers
WINTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
currant	O
jelly	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
other	O
spoons	O
to	O
Taylor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoons	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
312.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
IVORY	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LILLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
respecting	O
this	O
mare	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
mare	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
possession	O
upon	O
Hampstead-heath	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
your	O
mare	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
brown	O
mare	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
of	O
Hatton-garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
officers	O
'	O
names	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Wood	O
and	O
Trott	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Hatton-garden	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
offered	O
two	O
horses	O
for	O
sale	O
in	O
John	O
's	O
Mews	O
,	O
Bedford-row	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
by	O
the	O
bridle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Ivory	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
brown	O
mare	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Turner	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
horse	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
locked	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
mistake	O
that	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
only	O
foundone	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
locked	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Turner	O
till	O
his	O
father	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
.	O
Q.Where	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Mews	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
the	O
mare	O
;	O
Ivory	O
had	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
stable-door	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
officers	O
;	O
Ivory	O
said	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
persuaded	O
by	O
Turner	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hendon	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
the	O
mare	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
the	O
horse	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
mare	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Common	O
near	O
Hendon	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
bridle	O
on	O
her	O
in	O
Golder's-green	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
,	O
was	O
Turner	O
near	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TROTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
White	O
and	O
Wood	O
,	O
from	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
we	O
received	O
that	O
two	O
boys	O
were	O
selling	O
two	O
horses	O
in	O
John	O
's	O
Mews	O
,	O
Bedford-row	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Ivory	O
,	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
enquired	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
horse	O
or	O
the	O
mare	O
that	O
Ivory	O
stood	O
near	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
Ivory	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
positive	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
standing	O
about	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Turner	O
's	O
father	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
some	O
officers	O
came	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
Ivory	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
led	O
the	O
horses	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
;	O
then	O
Turner	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
another	O
boy	O
riding	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
riding	O
him	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
horse-dealers	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
thinking	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Ivory	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Hendon	O
together	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
lambs	O
,	O
fowls	O
,	O
ducks	O
,	O
geese	O
,	O
or	O
horses	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
a	O
barn	O
open	O
at	O
Hendon	O
,	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
horse	O
from	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
back	O
to	O
town	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
mare	O
in	O
question	O
off	O
the	O
green	O
from	O
among	O
some	O
others	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
charged	O
one	O
another	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
one	O
laid	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
laid	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
ever	O
offer	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
information	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
they	O
had	O
offered	O
the	O
mare	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Lilly	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
mare	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
mare	O
.	O
Q.Was	O
that	O
the	O
mare	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
stole	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
mare	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
gave	O
four	O
pounds	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
We	O
understand	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
favour	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
further	O
than	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
crime	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
must	O
lead	O
him	O
into	O
it	O
first	O
.	O
Q.	O
Turner	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
and	O
locked	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
poney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
the	O
poney	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
dun	O
.	O
Lilly	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
lately	O
lost	O
her	O
coat	O
,	O
that	O
makes	O
her	O
appear	O
so	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
's	O
master	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
boy	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
minded	O
his	O
business	O
exceeding	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
on	O
this	O
poney	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Horn's-alley	O
,	O
Liquorpond-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
bridle	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
bridle	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
poney	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
horse	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
dismount	O
the	O
poney	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
bridle	O
;	O
I	O
drove	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
before	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Mews	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
will	O
run	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
immediately	O
a	O
person	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officers	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Ivory	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
12	O
.	O
Turner	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
14	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
mercy	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
youth	O
.	O
313.	O
HARRIET	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
fourteen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
eight	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
six	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Burns	I-pers
and	O
Clarissa	B-pers
Wigmore	I-pers
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
BURNS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
12	I-place
,	I-place
Great	I-place
Shire-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Temple-bar	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Rolls	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
lay	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
awakened	O
by	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
creeping	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
andran	O
after	O
her	O
down	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
hold	O
so	O
hard	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
all	O
your	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
how	O
you	O
are	O
distressing	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
two-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Wilkinson	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
fourteen	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q.What	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
guineas	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
delivered	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
iron	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Burns	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLUNDLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Rolls	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Burns	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
the	O
street-door	O
being	O
left	O
upon	O
the	O
jar	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
ironing	O
late	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
frequently	O
leaves	O
the	O
key	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
fastens	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
or	O
outside	O
,	O
with	O
putting	O
too	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
being	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
fast	O
asleep	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
that	O
were	O
folded	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
ready	O
for	O
ironing	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BURNS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
things	O
to	O
iron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
shirts	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
different	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
intrusted	O
with	O
to	O
iron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
girl	O
brought	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
husband	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
things	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
pert	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
no	O
account	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
shirts	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
bought	O
under	O
a	O
guinea	O
a-piece	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
MERRITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
recollect	O
the	O
voice	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burns	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
of	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burns	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
has	O
all	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
husband	O
and	O
children	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Witness	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
you	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
CLARISSA	B-pers
WIGMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
:	O
six	O
of	O
these	O
shirts	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
property	O
that	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
entrusted	O
Mrs.	O
Burns	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
iron	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
worth	O
a	O
guinea	O
a-piece	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
guineas	O
the	O
half	O
dozen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
person	O
that	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
back	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
this	O
gentleman	O
caught	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
314.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
JANE	B-pers
NUN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
burglariously	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
ELDRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bear	I-place
and	I-place
Ragged-staff	I-place
,	I-place
Whitecross-street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
,	O
my	O
husband	O
keeps	O
that	O
public-house	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
past	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
;	O
my	O
family	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
undressed	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
pair	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
the	O
drawers	O
stood	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pushed	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
rush-light	O
by	O
this	O
cotton	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
the	O
rushlight	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Williams	O
shove	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
shoulders	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
window	O
put	O
to	O
,	O
or	O
only	O
hasped	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
hasp	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
sash	O
,	O
it	O
draws	O
with	O
a	O
slide	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
husband	O
put	O
the	O
sash	O
to	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
closed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
arms	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
very	O
stedfast	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
fright	O
seized	O
me	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
nothing	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
screaming	O
out	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
roll	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
tiles	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
shed	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
tiling	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
roll	O
off	O
the	O
tiles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Good	O
woman	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
candle	O
within	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
you	O
lit	O
the	O
rushlight	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lighted	O
the	O
rush-light	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
light	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
must	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A.He	O
certainly	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ELDRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged-staff	O
public-house	O
,	O
Whitecross-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
Eldridge	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
jumped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
person	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
body	O
but	O
not	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
suspicion	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
up	O
on	O
purpose	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
persons	O
of	O
suspicious	O
character	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
family	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
ways	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
candle	O
burning	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
shutting	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
walked	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
we	O
only	O
want	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
after	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
unlocked	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
a	O
misfortune	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
candle	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
governor	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
you	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Williams	O
got	O
me	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
served	O
them	O
each	O
with	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Having	O
seen	O
these	O
prisoners	O
so	O
satisfactorily	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
that	O
rolled	O
off	O
the	O
tiles	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
rolled	O
from	O
the	O
tiles	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
stand	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
tiles	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
;	O
the	O
tiles	O
broke	O
where	O
he	O
rolled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rafters	O
gave	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
;	O
I	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
shed	O
on	O
the	O
right-hand	O
side	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
any	O
person	O
getting	O
on	O
the	O
tiles	O
of	O
that	O
shed	O
may	O
easily	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
foot	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
foot	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
tiles	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sliding	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
hasp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
follow	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
tallish	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shortish	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
neighbour	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
then	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gateway	O
over	O
to	O
Gloucester-court	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
resisted	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
very	O
bad	O
language	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
y	O
thief	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
want	O
,	O
getting	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
near	O
twenty	O
yards	O
to	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
an	O
alley	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
stuck	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
her	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
women	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Prince	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
this	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
gilt	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
halfpence	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
drawers	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
club-box	O
containing	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
drawers	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
counted	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
far	O
enough	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
easily	O
get	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
middling	O
sized	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
negligent	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
either	O
;	O
I	O
positively	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
was	O
reprimanded	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
of	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
JOSEPH	O
PRINCE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
my	O
benefit-club	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Eldridge	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
only	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
shirt	O
on	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
man	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
followed	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PENRIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Police-officer	O
:	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
hard	O
to	O
work	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
mended	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
till	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tooley-street	O
before	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
an	O
alley	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
drink	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
you	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
another	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
tore	O
my	O
jacket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
constable	O
do	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
bad	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
two	O
watchmen	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
their	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prince	O
.	O
He	O
tried	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
before	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tare	O
his	O
jacket	O
,	O
he	O
tore	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Nun	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eldridge	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
piece	O
of	O
nonsense	O
this	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
toWilliams	O
;	O
tell	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
wife	O
neither	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
to	O
Playhouse-yard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Saturday	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
suit	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
after	O
the	O
club-box	O
,	O
or	O
privately	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
her	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
positive	O
to	O
Williams	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Prince	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
tore	O
your	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
315.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
PATRICK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pantaloons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward-Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH-	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
book-keeper	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
with	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
Mrs.	O
Hoole	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
double	O
locked	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
single	O
locked	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
heard	O
so	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
dog	O
that	O
we	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
;	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
dog	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
begged	O
his	O
lantern	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
bed-room	O
had	O
been	O
entered	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
kerseymere	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pantaloons	O
,	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
toilenet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
from	O
a	O
large	O
trunk	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
trunk	O
locked	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
kerseymere	O
breeches	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
a	O
salesman	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Parr	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
deposit	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
traced	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
this	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
violence	O
used	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
bed-room	O
door	O
was	O
never	O
fastened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
violence	O
used	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
opened	O
by	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
more	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
than	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
so	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
articles	O
till	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Abrahams	O
,	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
it	O
was	O
through	O
the	O
intelligence	O
of	O
this	O
Jew	O
you	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
first	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Parr	O
first	O
,	O
then	O
Abrahams	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
White	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
small	O
clothes	O
that	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
purchased	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
purchased	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Abrahams	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
VICKERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
found	O
charged	O
to	O
Parr	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Abrahams	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Jew	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
LAZARUS	O
ABRAHAMS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
breeches	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
breeches	O
handed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
)	O
did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
receive	O
these	O
breeches	O
from	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Patrick	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
bought	O
those	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
nine	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
-	O
you	O
shall	O
tell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
swear	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
fancy	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
second	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linings	O
are	O
dirty	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
wore	O
once	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
no	O
more	O
thanhalf	O
a	O
guinea	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
fancy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
stuff	O
cost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
,	O
on	O
recollection	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
remember	O
that	O
this	O
woman	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
enquire	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
got	O
these	O
breeches	O
in	O
your	O
possession	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ask	O
whose	O
breeches	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
enquired	O
that	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
would	O
be	O
much	O
more	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
these	O
breeches	O
till	O
you	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
-	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
any	O
Police-officer	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
information	O
-	O
you	O
gave	O
no	O
information	O
till	O
you	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Vickery	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
something	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
scalded	O
leg	O
.	O
-	O
LEVI	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Lazarus	O
Abrahams	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Patrick	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
hear	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
buys	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
for	O
nine	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
scruple	O
about	O
believing	O
him	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
316.	O
MARIA	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander-Colville	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TOMKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
13	I-place
,	I-place
Norton	I-place
Falgate	I-place
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
print	O
;	O
she	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
print	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
doors	O
off	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
necessity	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
printed	O
cotton	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cotton	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
was	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
say	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
the	O
shop-door	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
the	O
New-prison	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipped	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
317.	O
MARY	B-pers
BLAKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Magill	I-pers
.	O
-	O
MAGILL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q.	O
Mrs.	O
Magill	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
not	O
quite	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
tailor	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Parr	O
;	O
my	O
initials	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
are	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
PARR	O
sworn	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
High-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
spoons	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
she	O
required	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
her	O
mother	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
was	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
hesitated	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
make	O
a	O
mistake	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
but	O
wished	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
spoons	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
detain	O
the	O
spoons	O
till	O
her	O
mother	O
came	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
two	O
spoons	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoons	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
HARVEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
gowns	O
pledged	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Peters	O
.	O
ISABELLA	O
PETERS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
rapped	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
place	O
through	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
wash	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
refuse	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
hungry	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
gave	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
sixpence	O
or	O
sixpence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
I	O
pawned	O
those	O
two	O
gowns	O
by	O
her	O
order	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
got	O
these	O
gowns	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
Captain	O
Holmes	B-pers
gave	O
them	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
present	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
received	O
those	O
gowns	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
advanced	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
on	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
The	O
gowns	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Peters	O
's	O
apartments	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicates	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
opening	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
enquiring	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
stop	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
sweep	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
my	O
mistress	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
enough	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
my	O
clothes	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
apartment	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
breakfast	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
to	O
pledge	O
these	O
gowns	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
sister	O
had	O
died	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Harvey	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
twenty-seventh	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
15	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
318.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
COOLING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Drewett	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
6	I-place
,	I-place
Artillery-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
James	B-pers
Drewett	I-pers
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
my	O
landlord	O
;	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop-door	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
entrance	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
observed	O
him	O
going	O
out	O
first	O
(	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
passage	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
)	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
good	O
God	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
somebody	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
I	O
touched	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
arm	O
;	O
friend	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Drewett	O
's	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
)	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
round	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
again	O
;	O
a	O
thought	O
struck	O
me	O
from	O
his	O
having	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
,	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
road	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Dunning's-alley	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Christopher's-alley	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
dropped	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
and	O
picked	O
that	O
one	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
steps	O
and	O
dropped	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
things	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
picked	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
careless	O
about	O
picking	O
the	O
rest	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
some	O
little	O
boys	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
play	O
about	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
assisted	O
him	O
in	O
picking	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robbing	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
your	O
's	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
them	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
a	O
scuffle	O
ensued	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
,	O
but	O
till	O
I	O
knew	O
whose	O
things	O
they	O
were	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
right	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Mason	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
MASON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
towels	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Kennedy	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Drewett	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
Deptford	O
from	O
the	O
regiment	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
mother	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
workhouse	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
small	O
relief	O
;	O
in	O
coming	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Finsbury-square	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
three	O
boys	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
's	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Drewett	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
towels	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
saw	O
him	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
two	O
towels	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
boys	O
pick	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
several	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
dropped	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
first	O
one	O
,	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
followed	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Drewett	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
confident	O
as	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
319.	O
WALTER	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixey	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DIXEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
customer	O
's	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
serve	O
.	O
-	O
GREGORY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
quart	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right-hand	O
coat-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
pint	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
left-hand	O
waistcoat-pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
near	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JOSHUA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pass	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
into	O
No	O
.	O
40	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Keys	O
;	O
I	O
passed	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
repassed	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
remain	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
quart-pot	O
in	O
the	O
stair-case	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
I	O
passed	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pots	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
was	O
through	O
extreme	O
distress	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
61	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
whipped	O
in	O
jail	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
320.	O
DAVID	B-pers
FITZGERALD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pantaloons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sowerby	I-pers
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sowerby	I-pers
:	O
Last	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
pledged	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
apprentice	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sudden	O
pull	O
or	O
crush	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
trowsers	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
trowsers	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
trowsers	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
fall	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
tied	O
with	O
a	O
string	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
collared	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
me	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
fall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
when	O
you	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
still	O
at	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
them	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
sudden	O
jerk	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
string	O
he	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
any	O
questions	O
about	O
the	O
trowsers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
pledge	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Eight-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
trowsers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Five	O
shillings	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
78	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
321.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FLOOD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
five	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
half-quartern	O
loaves	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
383	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
took	O
my	O
basket	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
pitched	O
it	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
loaves	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
shop	O
is	O
rather	O
small	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
room	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
customers	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
serve	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
cellar	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Mary	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
it	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
going	O
up	O
Southampton-street	O
with	O
the	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
loaves	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
when	O
you	O
caught	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
basket	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Southampton-street	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
basket	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
found	O
two-pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
322.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
thirty-six	O
boards	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brick-mould	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HEBERTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
seeing	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
upon	O
Hackney	O
Downs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
;	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hobson	O
's	O
brick-fields	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
in	O
Love-lane	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Clapton	O
towards	O
Stamford-hill	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
working	O
tools	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Old	O
Lee	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
had	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
father	O
and	O
the	O
son	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
stolen	O
;	O
Payne	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hobson	O
's	O
brick-field	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
belonged	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
drawn	O
from	O
the	O
sand-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
by	O
a	O
chissel	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
in	O
their	O
bag	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
chissel	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
sand-house	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Heberton	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
working	O
tools	O
;	O
we	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
mistrusted	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Hobson	O
's	O
sand-house	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
drawn	O
;	O
we	O
tried	O
the	O
chissel	O
,	O
it	O
fitted	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hobson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
sand-house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SYMONDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hobson	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
sand-house	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
thirty-six	O
pallet-boards	O
and	O
a	O
brick-mould	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
sand-house	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
before	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
the	O
boards	O
and	O
the	O
brick-mould	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
bag	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
with	O
a	O
chisel	O
,	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
chisel	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hackney	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
shirts	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
works	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Shoreditch	O
with	O
my	O
little	O
bag	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
sons	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
over	O
Hackney-downs	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
not	O
my	O
son	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Downs	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Dock	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
sister	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
bacon	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
followed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
's	O
fields	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Dalston-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
bag	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
misfortune	O
was	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
across	O
my	O
shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
walking	O
across	O
Hackney-downs	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
John	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Dock	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
just	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
crossing	O
the	O
stiles	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
stopped	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
see	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Heberton	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
walking	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
answered	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
64.	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
323.	O
ANN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Tipko	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
TIPKO	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
families	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Marshall-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
gown	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
this	O
woman	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
employed	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
lately	O
before	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
with	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
my	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
of	O
her	O
knowing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
duplicate	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wanted	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
with	O
that	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Lovitt	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
duplicate	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
has	O
the	O
gown	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
apprentice	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stafford	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
Cambridge-street	O
,	O
Manchester-square	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
the	O
counter	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
LOVITT	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
duplicate	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Tattersell	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
39	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
324.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
stating	O
the	O
property	O
as	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Officers	B-pers
of	I-pers
his	I-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	I-pers
Customs	I-pers
.	O
And	O
a	O
Third	O
Count	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
GRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gatesmen	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
tobacco-warehouse	I-place
,	I-place
upon	I-place
Tower-hill	I-place
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
gate-keeper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
parish	O
is	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labouring	O
cooper	O
in	O
this	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
when	O
the	O
labourers	O
came	O
from	O
work	O
did	O
you	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
rubbed	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
seam	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
hard	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
detained	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
my	O
partners	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
no	O
farther	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
detained	O
him	O
at	O
our	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
this	O
tobacco-warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
tobacco-warehouse	O
keeper	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PEARSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
tobacco-warehouse	O
,	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
warehouse	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
tobacco	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
tobacco	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
course	O
you	O
are	O
answerable	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
this	O
tobacco	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
18	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
60	O
.	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
100	O
yards	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
325.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
KING	I-pers
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MUSSARD	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
MUSLIN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
eighty	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
one	O
hundred	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
four	O
gold	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
four	O
gold	O
broaches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
hundred	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
ninety	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
twenty-four	O
silk	O
purses	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
two	O
hundred	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
forty-eight	O
watch-chains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
sixty	O
watch-keys	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
;	O
four	O
Bank-notes	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
four	O
Banknotes	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
sixteen	O
Bank-notes	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
six	O
promissory	O
notes	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
ten	O
guineas	O
each	O
,	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
ten	O
promissory	O
notes	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
ten	O
guineas	O
each	O
,	O
value	O
110	O
l.	O
six	O
promissory	O
notes	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
five	O
promissory	O
notes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
said	O
Bank-notes	O
and	O
bills	O
of	O
exchange	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
ALDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Alder	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Yarmouth	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
and	O
cutler	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pack	O
up	O
the	O
property	O
that	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
Waltham-cross	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
one-horse	O
chaise	O
;	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
two	O
broad	O
straps	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
inches	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
on	O
iron	O
pins	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
travelled	O
for	O
twelve	O
years	O
before	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Long-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
yards	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
safe	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
whipped	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
forty	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
inn	O
,	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Immediately	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
you	O
looked	O
and	O
you	O
observed	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
left	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
chaise	O
in	O
care	O
at	O
the	O
inn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
trunk	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
Oliver	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Woodland	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
information	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
at	O
Yarmouth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Carrying	O
on	O
trade	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
partner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
happened	O
momentarily	O
-	O
it	O
happenedalmost	O
instantaneously	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
quick	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
observing	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
in	O
course	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
very	O
few	O
people	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Being	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
whether	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
struck	O
your	O
attention	O
at	O
Long-lane	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
London	O
at	O
dusk	O
,	O
it	O
strikes	O
your	O
attention	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
you	O
careful	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dusk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
perfectly	O
safe	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OLIVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
Jacob's-court	O
,	O
Turnmill-street	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
King	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Mussard	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
chaise	O
coming	O
along	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
same	O
gentleman	O
come	O
along	O
Smithfield	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
King	O
take	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
strap	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
strap	O
or	O
a	O
rope	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
arms	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
observed	O
King	O
cut	O
the	O
straps	O
,	O
whereabouts	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
?	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
standing	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
Ryland	O
was	O
standing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
standing	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
Ryland	O
and	O
Mussard	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Just	O
against	O
the	O
cross-way	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
Ryland	O
was	O
not	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
Muslin	O
was	O
standing	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
close	O
to	O
King	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
King	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
King	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
towards	O
Long-lane	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
pass	O
after	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Long-lane	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
King	O
;	O
King	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
Muslin	O
and	O
Ryland	O
were	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
saw	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
toy-shop	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
then	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
Ryland	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
Ryland	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
one-pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
King	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
one-pound	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Higgins	O
;	O
King	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
take	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
offer	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
see	O
you	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
standing	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
am	O
talking	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
-	O
did	O
they	O
see	O
you	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
yards	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
standing	O
,	O
could	O
they	O
see	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
other	O
thing	O
pass	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Ryland	O
and	O
Muslin	O
standing	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
door	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
asked	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Ryland	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
this	O
business	O
,	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
right	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
said	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
hear	O
,	O
whoever	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
that	O
said	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
King	O
doing	O
the	O
act	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
,	O
Muslin	O
and	O
Ryland	O
were	O
as	O
far	O
off	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
three	O
yards	O
.	O
Q.	O
Muslin	O
and	O
Ryland	O
were	O
close	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Muslin	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
Ryland	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
cross	O
way	O
just	O
where	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
trunk	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
you	O
met	O
Ryland	O
and	O
Muslin	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
distant	O
was	O
Muslin	O
from	O
Ryland	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
time	O
we	O
met	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
talking	O
to	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
man	O
must	O
hear	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
if	O
he	O
liked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
,	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
must	O
hear	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
door	O
that	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
both	O
their	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
was	O
nearest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
both	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
King	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Near	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alder	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
least	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
ill	O
used	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
your	O
courage	O
enabled	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
three	O
men	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
his	O
trunk	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
courage	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
-	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
an	O
odd	O
way	O
of	O
swearing	O
-	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
understand	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Alder	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Ann	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Sarcut	O
,	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
trunk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Alder	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
the	O
information	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
he	O
taken	O
by	O
an	O
officer	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
-	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
their	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
large	O
reward	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
hundred	O
guineas	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
published	O
the	O
handbills	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
names	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
knew	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
murdered	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
reward	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
recovery	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
property	O
was	O
never	O
recovered	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOODLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brick	O
maker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
before	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
observed	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
King	O
.	O
)	O
Your	O
name	O
is	O
King	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Woodland	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
;	O
King	O
bore	O
away	O
towards	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged	O
Staff	O
,	O
it	O
takes	O
you	O
round	O
by	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
down	O
to	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Muslin	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
King	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
some	O
where	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ostler	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
young	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brick	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
account	O
for	O
working	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hale	O
,	O
of	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Sommers	O
'	O
Town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
in	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
drove	O
a	O
hay	O
cart	O
all	O
the	O
winter	O
for	O
William	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged	O
Staff	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
name	O
,	O
Woodland	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Barber	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Goodland	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
those	O
names	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
called	O
the	O
Barber	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Oliver	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
further	O
than	O
seeing	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alder	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
King	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Oliver	O
tell	O
you	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
name	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
belie	O
my	O
conscience	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
any	O
pains	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
man	O
afterwards	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
these	O
doings	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
was	O
market-day	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
talking	O
with	O
two	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Oliver	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
officers	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
neverwent	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
officers	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
nigh	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
Pray	O
how	O
soon	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
reward	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
,	O
nor	O
yet	O
write	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
have	O
ears	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
understand	O
English	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
plainer	O
in	O
English	O
than	O
reward	O
?	O
-	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LIMERICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
some	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
King	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
at	O
the	O
Merry	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
,	O
Blackman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
King	O
,	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Mussard	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Stilton	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
sixty	O
miles	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
journey	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
King	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Mussard	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
45	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
326.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
CHAMBERLAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
weaver	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Great	B-place
Pelham-street	I-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
she	O
fetched	O
it	O
herself	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
again	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
quart	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
asked	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
cup	O
of	O
tea	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Swan-yard	O
watch-house	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
cloak	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
drunk	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Were	O
you	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
work	O
for	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
drank	O
about	O
a	O
cupfull	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
NEEZER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
cloak	O
on	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
without	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
POPE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pawned	O
this	O
cloak	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cloak	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
39	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
327.	O
ANN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
;	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CROOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
servant	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
she	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
sheets	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
immediately	O
and	O
found	O
nobody	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
sent	O
off	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
we	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pledged	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAYWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
pledged	O
the	O
sheets	O
on	O
