TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1804	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
AND	O
BLANCHARD	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1804	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
ELLENBOROUGH	I-pers
,	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
NEWNHAM	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
CURTIS	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
HARVEY-CHRISTIAN	B-pers
COMBE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
ANSLEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
-	O
ROWCROFT	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
NEWMAN	B-pers
KNOWLYS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hoppey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nottingham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sockett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hoppey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Firmley	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
William-Augustus	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Plume	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Patman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Radden	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
224.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HUTCHINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
wheat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OSBORNE	I-pers
(	O
the	O
younger	O
)	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
your	O
partners	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
wharfinger	O
s	O
on	O
the	B-place
Grand	I-place
Junction	I-place
Canal	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Uxbridge	I-place
;	O
we	O
had	O
fifty	O
quarters	O
of	O
wheat	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
delivered	O
excepting	O
twelve	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-four	O
sacks	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
landed	O
from	O
the	O
barge	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
suspicion	O
fell	O
upon	O
two	O
boats	O
which	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
my	O
wharf	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Canal	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
a	O
barge	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pickford	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RADLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Fourteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
wheat	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
off	O
Mr.	O
Osborne	O
's	O
wharf	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
the	O
waggon	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
waggon	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
waggon	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
wheat	O
upon	O
the	O
wharf	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
barley	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
sack	O
out	O
at	O
Ganford-green	O
,	O
near	O
Harrow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
sack	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
wharf	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
could	O
you	O
tell	O
whose	O
sack	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
ever	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
at	O
Ganford-green	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
told	O
your	O
master	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
your	O
master	O
had	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
prison	O
since	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
accused	O
with	O
taking	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Paddington	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
told	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
you	O
were	O
taken	O
a	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
you	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
other	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
were	O
there	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
the	O
boat	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
going	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
horses	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
standing	O
still	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
man	O
must	O
have	O
known	O
that	O
the	O
barge	O
was	O
stopped	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
helm	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
NEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
boat-man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
master	O
boat-man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
employed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pickford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
boat-man	O
employed	O
under	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
canal	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
recollect	O
his	O
being	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
barge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
accompany	O
the	O
barge	O
the	O
whole	O
way	O
to	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bring	O
any	O
sack	O
on	O
board	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
out	O
at	O
Ganford-green	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
must	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
have	O
observed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
Pickford	O
's	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
employ	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
waggon	O
loaded	O
with	O
wheat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
shore	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
horses	O
out	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
quite	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
board	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
disposed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sleep	O
on	O
board	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
what	O
were	O
you	O
doing	O
on	O
board	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
-	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
boat	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
board	O
at	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
boat	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
there	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
till	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
till	O
you	O
left	O
Uxbridge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
horses	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
after	O
I	O
fetched	O
the	O
horses	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
boat	O
stop	O
at	O
Ganford-green	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
without	O
my	O
seeing	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
wheat	O
without	O
your	O
knowing	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARLBOROUGH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
boat	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
boat	O
left	O
Uxbridge	O
till	O
she	O
got	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
shore	O
with	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
wheat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
without	O
my	O
knowing	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
steered	O
the	O
boat	O
to	O
Bull	O
's	O
green	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
miles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
left	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
wheat	O
in	O
the	O
barge	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
left	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
lock	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
gates	O
back	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
shore	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
loaf	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
return	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
boat	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do'nt	O
know	O
justly	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half-past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
till	O
ten	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
slept	O
pretty	O
sound	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
awake	O
at	O
Ganford-green	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
steered	O
to	O
Ganford-green	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
returned	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
a	O
sack	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
brought	O
some	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CATLIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
boat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
Uxbridge	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
his	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
before	O
the	O
boat	O
left	O
Uxbridge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
some	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
bring	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
wheat	O
on	O
board	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
sack	O
at	O
all	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
barges	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
boat	O
stopping	O
at	O
Ganford-green	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
on	O
shore	O
and	O
carry	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
shore	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
horses	O
from	O
Ganford-green	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
on	O
shore	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
waggon	O
load	O
of	O
wheat	O
upon	O
the	O
wharf	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
waggon	O
of	O
wheat	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
waggon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
a	O
pretty	O
considerable	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Osborne	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
waggon	O
from	O
the	O
barge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
;	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Heath	O
.	O
225.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MANCHESTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
bushels	O
of	O
pollard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
BRIGGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Acton	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
carter	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
mill	O
,	O
at	O
Moulsey	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
six	O
quarters	O
of	O
pollard	O
;	O
twelve	O
sacks	O
my	O
man	O
helped	O
to	O
unload	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sacks	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HOGSFLESH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
pollard	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
quarters	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
twelve	O
sacks	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
bin	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
sacks	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
bin	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
nine	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
granary	O
,	O
just	O
across	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
unloaded	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
the	O
pollard	O
over	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
one	O
sack	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
measure	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bin	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
strike	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
strikes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
granary	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
's	O
,	O
just	O
opposite	O
,	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
pollard	O
standing	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
sack	O
was	O
marked	O
G.	O
and	O
M.	O
Martin	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
brothers	O
partners	O
;	O
the	O
sacks	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
marked	O
like	O
them	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
supply	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
farmers	O
in	O
your	O
neighbourhood	O
with	O
pollard	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Several	O
farmers	O
deal	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pollard	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
employ	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
any	O
pollard	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
for	O
pollard	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
bring	O
me	O
one	O
sack	O
of	O
a	O
bettermost	O
sort	O
of	O
pollard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
tap-room	O
table	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
pay	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
bring	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
pollard	O
was	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
me	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
sixpence	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
his	O
trouble	O
in	O
bringing	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
employing	O
his	O
carter	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
neighbours	O
round	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
pollard	O
for	O
besides	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
bring	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
pollard	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
and	O
Hogsflesh	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
unusual	O
for	O
the	O
servant	O
of	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
team	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
some	O
pollard	O
for	O
the	O
neighbours	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
general	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
many	O
times	O
for	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
mill	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
secret	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
pollard	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
pollard	O
and	O
the	O
sack	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
and	O
Hogsflesh	O
saw	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
gave	O
him	O
eight	O
shillings	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
one	O
shilling	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
always	O
paid	O
ready	O
money	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
day-light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
live	O
directly	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Briggs	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
Martin	O
's	O
sacks	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
generally	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
marks	O
with	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sack	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Howard	O
's	O
was	O
marked	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
226.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fulton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Fulton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Fulton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pollock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Fulton	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
FULTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Watling-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
warehouseman	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fulton	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
generally	O
up	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
banisters	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bale	O
which	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
it	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bale	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Robert	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
's	O
back	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
two	O
houses	O
from	O
our	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
being	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
his	O
assistance	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
bale	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
neighbour	O
pursued	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
street	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
threw	O
himself	O
against	O
a	O
new	O
building	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
neighbour	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
bale	O
laid	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
with	O
the	O
bale	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
bale	O
wasbrought	O
back	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
assistants	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
two	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
paper	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
called	O
calendar	O
paper	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
you	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
constable	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ELLIOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Duncan	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
Manchester	O
warehousemen	O
,	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Fulton	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Fulton	O
's	O
servant	O
running	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
run	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
throw	O
the	O
bale	O
from	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
Morris	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
bale	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
bale	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
Going	O
along	O
Watling-street	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
bale	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
marked	O
the	O
bale	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bale	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Morris	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
bale	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fulton	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Fulton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Fulton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pollock	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
other	O
partner	O
who	O
has	O
any	O
interest	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
all	O
your	O
partners	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
partners	O
pay	O
the	O
rent	O
and	O
taxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
227.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
pound	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willan	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
DOWKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
porter	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Willan	I-pers
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
Mr.	O
Willan	O
any	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
,	O
in	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
carman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
duty	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
waggon	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
drive	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
look	O
to	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
his	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
attended	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
waggon	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Excise-Office	O
towards	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
waggon	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
church	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
a	O
great-coat	O
over	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
supposed	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
button	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
get	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Helmet	O
public-house	O
opposite	O
where	O
the	O
waggon	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
load	O
some	O
other	O
bales	O
of	O
goods	O
for	O
shipping	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
waggon-office	O
,	O
and	O
communicated	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jefferies	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Jefferies	O
opened	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
silk	O
buttoned	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
weighed	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
with	O
Jefferies	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
raw	O
silk	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
duty	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
bales	O
of	O
silk	O
were	O
loose	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
his	O
duty	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
bale	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
but	O
that	O
.	O
Q.	O
Supposing	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
loose	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
his	O
duty	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
employ	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Willan	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
employment	O
is	O
as	O
carman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
his	O
duty	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
saying	O
why	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
property	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
mention	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
attempt	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
shew	O
an	O
inclination	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Basinghall-street	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pickford	O
's	O
waggoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
carman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
carman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JEFFERIES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
book-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Dowker	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
top	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
silk	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
pound	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
silk	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
containing	O
silk	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
this	O
bag	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
opened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
bag	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
Inn	O
;	O
the	O
bag	O
had	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
having	O
been	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
drawn	O
as	O
under	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
silk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
Inn	O
with	O
a	O
four-wheeled	O
cart	O
,	O
or	O
waggon	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
silk	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
situated	O
near	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
charge	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
silk	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
pack	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
larger	O
deficiency	O
than	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
writing	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jefferies	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
the	O
remainder	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
privy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
hank	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
one	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
bale	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
228.	O
MARY	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
SANDERS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pail	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
frying	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Berwick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BERWICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hackney	O
road	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Angel-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
;	O
Mary	O
Price	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
rent	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
distressed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
again	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
enquired	O
her	O
character	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
husband	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
other	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cotton	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
quilt	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GIBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Tyler	O
and	O
Laycock	O
,	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
sheet	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
pledged	O
it	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LILLYWHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
(	O
produces	O
two	O
duplicates	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
a	O
sheet	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Berwick	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
our	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
quilt	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
PERKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Angel-alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Berwick	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
the	O
lodging	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
box-maker	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
furniture	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Berwick	O
sent	O
the	O
things	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
them	O
.	O
Berwick	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
sheet	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
is	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
quilt	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
lodging	O
houses	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
have	O
all	O
sheets	O
and	O
all	O
quilts	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
myself	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
;	O
the	O
duplicate	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
officer	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
gentleman	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
room	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
articles	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
229.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DANIELS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
tenwine-glasses	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew-John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
and	O
George-Augustus	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
)	O
ANDREW-JOHN	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partner	O
ship	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
George-	O
Augustus	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
packer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
that	O
goods	O
were	O
secreted	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
directed	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
clerks	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
mark	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
directed	O
a	O
warehouseman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jordan	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
went	O
way	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
glasses	O
so	O
marked	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
Jordan	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
shortly	O
after	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
put	O
any	O
question	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
neither	O
promise	O
nor	O
threat	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
produce	O
what	O
property	O
of	O
mine	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
hesitation	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
three	O
wine-glasses	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
a	O
sleeping	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glassman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
employ	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
.	O
In	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
direction	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
wine-glasses	O
concealed	O
among	O
some	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
thirteen	O
glasses	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
tumblers	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
marked	O
them	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
JORDAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
employ	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Nash	O
:	O
In	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
thirteen	O
wineglasses	O
and	O
two	O
tumblers	O
concealed	O
under	O
some	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
mark	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
men	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
six	O
wine-glasses	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
four	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
-	O
TRENCHARD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
wine-glasses	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Brown	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
glasses	O
that	O
I	O
marked	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
cellar	O
.	O
Jordan	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
glasses	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
mark	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
230.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BEVINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
hops	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gould-square	B-place
,	I-place
Crutched-friars	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
druggist	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
occurrence	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
:	O
Having	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
articles	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartments	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
found	O
a	O
paper	O
parcel	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
hops	O
which	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
bought	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
but	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sample	O
of	O
hops	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
warrant	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
his	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
compare	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
samples	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Bristol	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
marks	O
corresponded	O
with	O
those	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
keep	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
servants	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
confined	O
to	O
his	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
ribs	O
broke	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ARTHUR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
druggist	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davey	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Davey	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
sample	O
of	O
hops	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Davey	O
asked	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
examine	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
heart	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SKINNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
hops	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Davey	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
sample	O
of	O
hops	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
number	O
,	O
which	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
original	O
invoice	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
samples	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
marked	O
from	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
to	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
hops	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
these	O
are	O
two	O
ounces	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
two-pence	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Or	O
perhaps	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
hops	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
this	O
parcel	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
opened	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
you	O
swear	O
it	O
contains	O
hops	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
conceive	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hops	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
opened	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
sample	O
of	O
hops	O
of	O
any	O
value	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
samples	O
ever	O
charged	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
231.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARNOLD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Swan	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Bury-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
quart	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
King's-place	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
took	O
the	O
two	O
pots	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MOSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Bow-street	O
patrol	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Richmond	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
poacher	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
meant	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
directly	O
:	O
Mr.	O
White	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
stolen	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
pots	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
different	O
directions	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pots	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
each	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
White	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
pots	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
written	O
defence	O
,	O
stating	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
five	O
small	O
children	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
fell	O
from	O
a	O
scaffold	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
60	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
232.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
RADLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
sixty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
William-Booth	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
break	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
RICKARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
living	O
in	O
Lower	B-place
Brook-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William-Booth	O
Grey	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
alarmed	O
by	O
bricks	O
falling	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
Hannah	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Franks	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
hotel	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
hanging	O
over	O
the	O
front	O
area-rails	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
pipe	O
that	O
conveyed	O
the	O
water	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
at	O
the	O
joint	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
by	O
an	O
hold-fast	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
separated	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wished	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
quite	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
separated	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
confined	O
by	O
an	O
iron	O
hold-fast	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
confined	O
by	O
bricks	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
does	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
bricks	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
inches	O
.	O
-	O
FRANKS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
almost	O
opposite	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Grey	O
lives	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Grey	O
's	O
servants	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
candle	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
a	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
pipe	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
joints	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
hold-fasts	O
pulled	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
from	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
feet	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
bricks	O
torn	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
twisted	O
off	O
within	O
an	O
inch	O
.	O
In	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looking	O
past	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
come	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
over	O
very	O
quick	O
indeed	O
to	O
the	O
pipe	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
twisted	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
times	O
;	O
some	O
bricks	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
dark	O
as	O
pitch	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
two	O
very	O
large	O
lamps	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
it	O
as	O
light	O
as	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
quick	O
for	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
some	O
bricklayers	O
labourers	O
came	O
up	O
before	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
threatening	O
to	O
strike	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
233.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
six	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
glass	O
tumblers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
salt-cellar	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
nine	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
three	O
looking-glasses	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
tin	O
canister	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
variety	O
of	O
other	O
articles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BUCKLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
Thursday	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
articles	O
mentionedin	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
repeats	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Buckridge-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Portpool-lane	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
CONNOR	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Buckle	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
SCALES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
seeing	O
the	O
property	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
She	O
lent	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
these	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
234.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
RADLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
sixty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
William-Booth	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
in	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
lead	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
removed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
235.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John-Vickriss	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
two	O
pocketbooks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
another	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
seven	O
other	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
sixteen	O
other	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
value	O
80	O
l.	O
three	O
other	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
six	O
other	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
value	O
106	O
l.	O
a	O
Cambridge	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
106	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
another	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
37	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
112	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
sixteen	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
respectable	O
tradesman	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Heath	O
.	O
236.	O
EPHRAIM	B-pers
FERMITEGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
bottle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
varnish	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
six	O
maps	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
sheets	O
of	O
globe	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
sheets	O
of	O
other	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CARY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
181	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
engraver	O
of	O
maps	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
globe	O
making	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
depredations	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
various	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
varnish	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
precaution	O
to	O
mark	O
some	O
bottles	O
of	O
varnish	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
premises	O
where	O
I	O
carry	O
on	O
my	O
globe	O
making	O
business	O
in	O
Angel-court	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
manufactory	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
some	O
bottles	O
of	O
varnish	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
marked	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
varnish	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Swinsin	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bottles	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
premises	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
quart	O
bottle	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bottles	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
premises	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Fore-street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
purchased	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
peace-officer	O
,	O
Limerick	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
manufactory	O
,	O
to	O
observe	O
if	O
the	O
bottles	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
were	O
still	O
remaining	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
removed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
such	O
bottles	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
preceding	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
bottles	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
marked	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
now	O
brought	O
as	O
having	O
purchased	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Swinsin	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
pressed	O
to	O
discover	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
bottles	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
very	O
much	O
pressed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
;	O
upon	O
questioning	O
a	O
lad	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
information	O
,	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
dust-hole	O
;	O
that	O
lad	O
has	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
concealed	O
in	O
some	O
soot	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
confession	O
of	O
the	O
theft	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
concealed	O
these	O
bottles	O
;	O
we	O
afterwards	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
there	O
found	O
paper	O
of	O
various	O
descriptions	O
,	O
brown	O
paper	O
and	O
globe	O
paper	O
;	O
the	O
papers	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
are	O
these	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
they	O
are	O
papers	O
for	O
mounting	O
small	O
pocket	O
globes	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
varnish	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
corroborated	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
finding	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
LIMERICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
bought	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
varnish	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
quart	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
bottles	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
bottles	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
237.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
HEWITT	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
Indian	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Common-council	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
reside	O
at	O
Hackney	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
own	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Hackney	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
over	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
the	B-place
Hide	I-place
,	I-place
behind	I-place
Clapton	I-place
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
upon	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
Hide	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
twice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
therefore	O
you	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
observing	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
Love-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
Love-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
very	O
gently	O
along	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
narrow	O
walk	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
elbow	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
neither	O
see	O
the	O
top	O
nor	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
that	O
elbow	O
he	O
popped	O
out	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
collared	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
fast	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
long	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
carving	O
knife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
at	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
leather	O
purse	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Indian	O
piece	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
:	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
looking	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
go	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
and	O
looked	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
a	O
person	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
person	O
turned	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
Philip	B-pers
Read	I-pers
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
passed	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
minute	O
almost	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
myself	O
tell	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
at	O
the	O
turnpike	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
shall	O
you	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
seal	O
with	O
S.	O
B.	O
and	O
another	O
seal	O
with	O
three	O
heads	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Cold-bath	O
lane	O
,	O
Church-street	O
,	O
Hackney	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
either	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
pointing	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
pointing	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
instantly	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
point	O
his	O
stick	O
in	O
a	O
direction	O
which	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
who	O
got	O
into	O
your	O
sight	O
again	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
again	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Clapton	O
I	O
got	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
Pound-lane	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
field	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
wheeled	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
Clapton	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
tack	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
Hackney	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
jumped	O
over	O
some	O
low	O
paling	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
jumped	O
over	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
field	O
to	O
some	O
high	O
paling	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stoop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
stooped	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
laying	O
something	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
stoop	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
running	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
describing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
rose	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
high	O
paling	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
paling	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thurling	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
me	O
call	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
to	O
Hackney-cage	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
afterwards	O
present	O
when	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
high	O
paling	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stoop	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
lying	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
leather	O
bag	O
underneath	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
laid	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
in	O
Hackney-grove	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
identified	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Brown	O
)	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
watch	O
and	O
the	O
leather	O
bag	O
which	O
the	O
witness	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
had	O
shown	O
it	O
to	O
Brown	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
)	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
bag	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
seals	O
are	O
my	O
seals	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THURLING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
paling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stoop	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
if	O
dropping	O
something	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
paling	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
expect	O
a	O
few	O
friends	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
of	O
his	O
not	O
having	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
238.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRANHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FRAZER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Whitcomb-street	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happened	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Whitcomb-court	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
my	O
kitchen	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
that	O
lets	O
light	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
wooden	O
bars	O
outside	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
glass	O
inside	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
doing	O
something	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
saucepan	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
saucepan	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
second	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
yourself	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
after	O
being	O
cleaned	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
there	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pretty	O
light	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
growing	O
dusk	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
very	O
distinctly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
does	O
it	O
shove	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
slider	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
made	O
to	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
bolt	O
inside	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
to	O
push	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
;	O
the	O
wooden	O
bars	O
were	O
broke	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
first	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
GARDINER	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
window	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
casement	O
window	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
squares	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
to	O
push	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
saucepans	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
saucepans	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
both	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
saucepans	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Whitcomb-court	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
work	O
about	O
some	O
kettles	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
curious	O
enough	O
to	O
stop	O
and	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
46	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
239.	O
JAMES	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BURROWES	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Crozier	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
therein	O
being	O
burglariously	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
neither	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
or	O
any	O
servant	O
of	O
his	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Heath	O
.	O
240.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITWORTH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
two	O
umbrellas	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BURNELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
level	O
with	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
similar	O
to	O
a	O
window	O
being	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
window	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
umbrellas	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
immediately	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Spearing	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nearly	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
distinctly	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
umbrellas	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
-	O
SPEARING	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
May's-buildings	B-place
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Burnell	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
looking	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
ways	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
cellar-window	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
window	O
crack	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
one	O
umbrella	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burnell	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
directed	O
a	O
person	O
whereabout	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
was	O
bleeding	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
touched	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
umbrellas	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
15	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
241.	O
CAROLINE	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
forty	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kay	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
KAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kay	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
his	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
28	I-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff-highway	I-place
,	O
a	O
milliner	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
attend	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
ribbons	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Matthews	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
Fisher	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
ribbons	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
over	O
the	O
ribbons	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
there	O
that	O
would	O
please	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
choice	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
scarlet	O
,	O
with	O
chocolate	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
was	O
difficult	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
choice	O
of	O
any	O
;	O
Fisher	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
choice	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
each	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
for	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
called	O
Nance	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
six	O
good	O
shillings	O
in	O
change	O
;	O
she	O
hesitated	O
about	O
the	O
change	O
being	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
change	O
them	O
;	O
a	O
Mrs.	O
Kemp	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
pins	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Fisher	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
silver	O
to	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
her	O
reason	O
for	O
saying	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
shop-lifters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
present	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
immediately	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
ribbon	O
come	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
shilling	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
called	O
Nance	O
sat	O
upon	O
a	O
low	O
seat	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
cough	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
all	O
her	O
face	O
entirely	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
either	O
her	O
gown	O
or	O
her	O
cloak	O
over	O
her	O
face	O
at	O
times	O
;	O
Fisher	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
drop	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
certainly	O
had	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
dropping	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
lap	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
go	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
plain	O
white	O
ribbon	O
from	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
when	O
you	O
produced	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
figured	O
ribbon	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
drawer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
five	O
pieces	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
my	O
shop	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Matthews	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
Fisher	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Fisher	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
altogether	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
with	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
apprehension	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
persons	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
and	O
Miss	O
Bromet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Miss	O
Bromet	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
yourself	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mrs.	O
Kemp	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FENWICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
's	O
employ	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
175	O
,	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Kay	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Matthews	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
standing	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
near	O
a	O
public-house	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
whom	O
Ido	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
Fisher	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Kay	O
's	O
,	O
Matthews	O
went	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
John's-hill	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
Mrs.	O
Kemp	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
after	O
no	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Kemp	O
's	O
door	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Kay	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
business	O
at	O
Ratcliff-cross	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
the	O
parcels	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
carry	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Kay	B-pers
I	O
would	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
Matthews	O
standing	O
by	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
together	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
proceeded	O
towards	O
Ratcliff-cross	O
;	O
Fisher	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
Matthews	O
first	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
shewing	O
Matthews	O
to	O
Brown	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
company	O
together	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Matthews	O
staid	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Brown	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
where	O
Fisher	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
gone	O
in	O
;	O
Brown	O
then	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Matthews	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
road	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
gone	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
back	O
to	O
Shadwell-office	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
ran	O
away	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
ribbon	O
found	O
upon	O
Fisher	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
office	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
:	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
near	O
Cock-hill	O
,	O
Ratcliff	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
found	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Nance	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Matthews	O
standing	O
opposite	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Kays	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Fisher	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
ribbon	O
about	O
her	O
(	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
out	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
Matthews	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
her	O
in	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
eleven	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
lock-up	O
room	O
in	O
our	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fenwick	O
took	O
one	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
secured	O
Matthews	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fenwick	O
brought	O
Fisher	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
of	O
ribbon	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
Matthews	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
Fisher	O
;	O
Fisher	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
she	O
heard	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ribbons	O
were	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Kay	O
.	O
These	O
pieces	O
have	O
my	O
shop-mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
some	O
small	O
quantity	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pattern	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
brought	O
it	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
I	O
cut	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
blanket	O
pin	O
into	O
it	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
uncommon	O
thing	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
blanket	O
pin	O
in	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
ribbon	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
ribbon	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
Matthews	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
that	O
bundle	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
coming	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Brown	O
.	O
)	O
Were	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
loose	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
defence	O
to	O
her	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Fisher	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
242.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
NETTLEFORD	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
BRADFORD	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
four	O
window-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
GARRETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Fifteen	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Elias	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
kitchen-stairs	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
privy	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
strings	O
of	O
the	O
curtains	O
hanging	O
down	O
her	O
petticoat	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
FLETCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
curtains	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
curtains	O
were	O
right	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
dropped	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
curtains	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
curtains	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
curtains	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Heath	O
.	O
243.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
and	O
MARY-ANN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
ten	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
leather-dresser	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
first	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Holderness	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
dwelling-room	O
;	O
Treadway	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Holderness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
made	O
the	O
search	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
;	O
was	O
she	O
told	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOLDERNESS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
47	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
apartment	O
of	O
me	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
took	O
about	O
twenty	O
one-pound	O
notes	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
indorsed	O
the	O
persons	O
names	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
back	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
sleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
deposited	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
drawer	O
had	O
you	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
miss	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
drawer	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
ten	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
Banknotes	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
in	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
among	O
some	O
leaves	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
occupied	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
in	O
those	O
two	O
places	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
you	O
had	O
received	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
herself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
property	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
notes	O
were	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
's	O
mother	O
,	O
in	O
Henrietta-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
that	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
lost	O
this	O
table-cloth	O
and	O
the	O
sheets	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
first	O
missed	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
missed	O
till	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
marked	O
the	O
same	O
names	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Bank-notes	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
these	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Court	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
these	O
notes	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HOLDERNESS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
husband	O
write	O
upon	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
notes	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
near	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
under	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
say	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
bed	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
