TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1804	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
AND	O
BLANCHARD	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1804	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
ELLENBOROUGH	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
NEWNHAM	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
CURTIS	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
HARVEY-	O
CHRISTIAN	B-pers
COMBE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
ANSLEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROWCROFT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
NEWMAN	O
KNOWLYS	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buzzard	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ravenscroft	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Till	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Davidge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hilyard	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Austerbury	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Joining	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Mowbray	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Roby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
Raynham	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gillings	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Homan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clover	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
.	O
516.	O
MARY	B-pers
LYE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
six	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
six	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Prisley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
PRISLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Butcherhall-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
saleswoman	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
preceding	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
worn	O
,	O
and	O
dirtied	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
dirty	O
shirts	O
of	O
my	O
apprentice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
night-cap	O
in	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
bandbox	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
duplicates	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
them	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
her	O
till	O
Monday	O
noon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
stockings	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
examined	O
the	O
duplicates	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
separated	O
the	O
duplicates	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twelve	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
's	O
,	O
within	O
about	O
six	O
doors	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
at	O
Reeves	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Redcross-street	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
coloured	O
aprons	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
five	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
coloured	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
teaspoon	O
;	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
table-cloths	O
was	O
pawned	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
pawned	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
the	O
duplicates	O
which	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
are	O
counterparts	O
of	O
our	O
duplicates	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
(	O
Robert-Samuel	O
Hudson	O
,	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
his	O
recognizance	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	O
WOODMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
seat	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Prisley	O
gave	O
me	O
change	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
duplicates	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Prisley	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prisley	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
48	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
517.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
BRADY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
14	O
ounces	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
,	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East	I-pers
Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
,	O
charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HUGGINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
,	O
in	O
Crutched	B-place
Friars	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
employ	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
taking	O
in	O
goods	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
Ganges	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
each	O
different	O
bed	O
of	O
tea	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
chest	O
was	O
perceived	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Crutched-Friars	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
cutting	O
off	O
the	O
canes	O
that	O
go	O
round	O
the	O
chests	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
chests	O
,	O
take	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
about	O
twenty	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sayer	O
the	O
elders	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
elders	O
at	O
the	O
India-Company	O
's	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Crutched-friars	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Accompting-house	O
and	O
found	O
14	O
ounces	O
of	O
tea	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pockets	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
knees	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
tea	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
sold	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
family	O
of	O
children	O
.	O
(	O
Pinner	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produces	O
the	O
tea	O
.	O
)	O
Sayer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
more	O
tea	O
than	O
that	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
67	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
518.	O
JAMES	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	B-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
drawn	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
draw	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
dropped	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
drawn	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
feet	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
intoxicated	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
giving	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
519.	O
JANE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
HARTMAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
four	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
half-shawl	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas-Perry	B-pers
Tuther	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS-	O
PERRY	B-pers
TUTHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
on	O
Holborn-hill	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
rung	O
down	O
by	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
detained	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
stolen	O
some	O
shawls	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
agitated	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
deliberate	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
circumstances	O
,	O
as	O
coolly	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
related	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
shawls	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
particular	O
and	O
whimsical	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
fix	O
upon	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
purchase	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
appeared	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
walked	O
towards	O
them	O
and	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
produced	O
one	O
quantity	O
of	O
two	O
shawls	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
Jones	O
appeared	O
very	O
much	O
agitated	O
;	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
to	O
bring	O
some	O
water	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
bason	O
of	O
water	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Jones	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
distress	O
of	O
the	O
poor	O
creature	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
girl	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
became	O
very	O
much	O
agitated	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
some	O
shawls	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
what	O
has	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
has	O
been	O
thrown	O
over	O
,	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
and	O
go	O
round	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
more	O
shawls	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
shawl	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
property	O
,	O
take	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
mark	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
a	O
city	O
officer	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tuther	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
shawls	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
,	O
apparently	O
shuffling	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
shawl	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
apparently	O
very	O
much	O
confused	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
put	O
two	O
shawls	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
related	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tuther	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
some	O
water	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
something	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
throw	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
two	O
shawls	O
and	O
a	O
half-shawl	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
mark	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Marshals	O
'	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoners	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
shawls	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
Wells	O
.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
from	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Hartman	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Jones	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Confined	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
520.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
16	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
William	I-pers
Eastman	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
;	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pencil-case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry-	O
William	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
;	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jay	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry-	O
William	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry-	O
William	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
only	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
HENRY-	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EASTMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
,	O
we	O
are	O
packers	O
,	O
in	O
Sise-lane	B-place
;	O
the	O
warehouses	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
communication	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Millard	O
lives	O
in	O
another	O
house	O
lower	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
warehouse	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
or	O
warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
porter	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
missed	O
half	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
superfine	O
cloth	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
to	O
pack	O
for	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
bedroom	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pencil-case	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat-piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
bedroom	O
door	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
with	O
the	O
kitchen	O
poker	O
;	O
the	O
poker	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Jay	O
is	O
my	O
mother-in-law	O
;	O
her	O
property	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
chest	O
ofdrawers	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
other	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
directly	O
;	O
we	O
make	O
an	O
allowance	O
to	O
the	O
widow	O
Ward	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
article	O
charged	O
to	O
be	O
partnership	O
property	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Golden	O
Anchor	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Park-street	O
,	O
Borough	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
brother	O
;	O
that	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Carter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
dishabille	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
his	O
Sunday	O
's	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
remained	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
officers	O
came	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
empty	O
boxes	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
Carter	O
lodged	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
have	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
different	O
lodgers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
placed	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
double-bedded	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
lodgers	O
slept	O
there	O
every	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
city	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
Carter	O
slept	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
JAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Eastman	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
four	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
curtains	O
;	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Eastman	O
identified	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
pencil-case	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
32	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
521.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Wales	O
with	O
a	O
drove	O
of	O
sheep	O
,	O
to	O
the	B-place
Yorkshire-grey	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
:	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
notes	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Yorkshire-grey	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
two	O
pound	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
ragged	O
purse	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
notes	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
called	O
the	O
Cannon	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
notes	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
recovered	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
DESNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
different	O
places	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
great	O
favour	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
dollars	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
remainder	O
in	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
refused	O
the	O
penny-pieces	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
note	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
DEVEREUX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
niece	O
to	O
George	O
Wall	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Cannon	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
new	O
two	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
two	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
loose	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
dollar	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
out	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NOWLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Yorkshire-grey	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
's	O
notes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
numbers	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
find	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
the	O
numbers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
numbers	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
two	O
dollars	O
at	O
the	O
Kettle-drums	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
dollar	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Cannon	O
,	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
hehad	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
chucked	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Hall	O
.	O
)	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
notes	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
No	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
522.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WEEDON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
in	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
Temple-bar	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
523.	O
MARY	B-pers
SHARPE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Russian	O
duck	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
having	O
been	O
stolen	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
possession	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
524.	O
ANN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
fruit-knife	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
night-cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
William	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
525.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
flat-irons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
526.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ROBEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
eight	O
pecks	O
of	O
split	O
horse-beans	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Viner	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Viner	O
's	O
stable-yard	O
,	O
at	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
corn-chandler	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
in	O
his	O
employ	O
as	O
foreman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Viner	O
's	O
horse-keeper	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
bag	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
loft	O
,	O
among	O
some	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
near	O
one	O
corner	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
again	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
situation	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
filled	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sack	O
that	O
would	O
hold	O
a	O
bushel	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
full	O
of	O
split	O
beans	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
access	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
constantly	O
,	O
the	O
beans	O
were	O
kept	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
at	O
near	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
with	O
a	O
tarpauling	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
tarpauling	O
by	O
the	O
bulk	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Viner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
again	O
by	O
a	O
patch	O
near	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
common	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
bags	O
with	O
beans	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
bushel	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Viner	O
has	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
bags	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
put	O
the	O
bags	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Other	O
persons	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
VINER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
corn-dealer	O
and	O
miller	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
hay-loft	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
beans	O
for	O
our	O
horses	O
;	O
we	O
send	O
a	O
weekly	O
allowance	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
had	O
to	O
feed	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
into	O
his	O
custody	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
's	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
load	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
load	O
to	O
deliver	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
cart	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
tarpauling	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
bulky	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
doubled	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
load	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
tarpauling	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
opening	O
it	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
discovered	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
beans	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
beans	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
beans	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
damaged	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
split	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
remarkablefor	O
age	O
,	O
smell	O
,	O
and	O
blackness	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
beans	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
give	O
directions	O
to	O
the	O
carman	O
to	O
take	O
beans	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
horses	O
a	O
taste	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
would	O
have	O
suffered	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
tarpauling	O
was	O
often	O
used	O
for	O
covering	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
wet	O
weather	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
remarkably	O
fine	O
day	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Viner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
delivered	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
beans	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Plaistow	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
property	O
)	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
sample	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
loft	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
bag	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
loft	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
50	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
527.	O
MARY	B-pers
LYON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twenty-three	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
and	O
Basil	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Basil	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
a	O
lady	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Gear	I-pers
with	O
a	O
print	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GEAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
Ormond-yard	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
go	O
into	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
different	O
shops	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
on	O
a	O
stool	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
both	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
print	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
got	O
the	O
print	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
BICKNELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
take	O
the	O
print	O
;	O
Gear	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Holborn	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Gear	I-pers
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
's	O
door	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
print	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Francis	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
print	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
placed	O
it	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Another	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
pawn	O
it	O
and	O
spend	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
528.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Pritchett	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PRITCHETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Short's-gardens	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Pritchett	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
trowsers	O
in	O
concealed	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
trowsers	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
string	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
following	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
trowsers	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
jerk	O
;	O
finding	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
them	O
higher	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
both	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
force	O
got	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
hook	O
;	O
he	O
rolled	O
them	O
up	O
very	O
carefully	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Pritchett	O
that	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
them	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
answered	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
65	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
529.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOLTON	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
BOLTON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WAKELIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
boot	O
and	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
corner	O
of	O
Lamb	O
's	O
Conduit-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
carry	O
into	O
the	O
Boroughto	O
another	O
shop	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
Borough	O
to	O
Lamb	O
's	O
Conduit-street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
resistance	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
suspected	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
there	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
see	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
one	O
shoe	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
out	O
the	O
fellow	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Union-hall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
Hatton-garden	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
he	O
was	O
fully	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mother	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GLASS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
lad	O
from	O
Union-hall	O
to	O
Hatton-garden	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
,	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
found	O
another	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Wakelin	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
pledged	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
Lamb	O
's	O
Conduit-street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SHORTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
used	O
our	O
shop	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Portpool-lane	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
Shorter	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
one	O
shilling	O
on	O
one	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen-pence	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
one	O
pair	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
Wakelin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
both	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
assistant	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Turnmill-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Wakelin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
shoes	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
me	O
something	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
good	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
530.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
extorted	O
by	O
a	O
promise	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Both	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
531.	O
JANE	B-pers
LIPSOM	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
CALLAGHAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
62	O
,	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
's	O
shop	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
prints	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
shopman	O
,	O
shewed	O
them	O
several	O
patterns	O
;	O
Lipsom	O
had	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
concealing	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
this	O
quantity	O
,	O
containing	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
her	O
towards	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Allen	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Lipsom	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
532.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARDING	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
rode	O
him	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
10th	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
live	O
,	O
at	O
Berwick	B-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Wiltshire	I-place
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
who	O
did	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
else	O
was	O
he	O
kept	O
besides	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
generally	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
field	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
the	O
field	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
generally	O
put	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
about	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
clog	O
put	O
round	O
his	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
clog	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
his	O
leg	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
residing	O
at	O
a	O
village	O
adjoining	O
for	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
that	O
village	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Fonthill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
your	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Q.What	O
name	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
reside	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
inquiry	O
about	O
the	O
horse	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Giles-hill	O
.	O
Q.Where	O
did	O
you	O
next	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
farmer	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HANKIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ashford	O
,	O
near	O
Belfont	O
.	O
Q.What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
higler	O
.	O
Q.When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A.About	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
at	O
Belfont	O
.	O
Q.Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
a	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
bay	O
gelding	O
.	O
Q.Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
that	O
bay	O
gelding	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
Q.What	O
price	O
did	O
he	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Eighteen	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
the	O
horse	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
any	O
distance	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
very	O
much	O
fatigued	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
seem	O
hot	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
cold	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sweaty	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
had	O
cried	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
eighteen	O
guineas	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
fourteen	O
.	O
Q.Had	O
you	O
bid	O
him	O
a	O
less	O
price	O
than	O
eighteen	O
guineas	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
useful	O
serviceable	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
kept	O
two	O
breeding	O
mares	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bred	O
this	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
you	O
then	O
buy	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
his	O
father	O
lived	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
Hindon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
mention	O
the	O
place	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
jumped	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
making	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
nor	O
him	O
either	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
horse	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
spot	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
up	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
when	O
young	O
Harding	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
person	O
here	O
who	O
received	O
the	O
horse	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
last	O
Sunday	O
at	O
Belfont	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
rode	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Harding	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
Hankin	O
saw	O
you	O
with	O
on	O
Sunday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
your	O
father	O
's	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Hankin	O
.	O
)	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
horse	O
you	O
saw	O
on	O
Sunday	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
you	O
for	O
sale	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Harding	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
the	O
horse	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
a	O
stable	O
near	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
Berwick	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
to	O
Belfont	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Eighty-four	O
miles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Hankin	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
he	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
fourteen	O
guineas	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
liked	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
,	O
knowing	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
thought	O
him	O
worth	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
at	O
Romsey	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Star	O
and	O
Garter	O
,	O
at	O
Andover	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
there	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
bear	O
my	O
expences	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
good	O
bargain	O
;	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
market	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
533.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BARRETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
and	O
watchman	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
living	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
nail	O
by	O
the	O
bed	O
side	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
minutes	O
past	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
gardens	O
,	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
waiting	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
secure	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Behave	O
decently	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
appeared	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
.	O
)	O
Q.Who	O
searched	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
dropped	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
charged	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
fall	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
taking	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
entering	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
certainly	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
particular	O
mark	O
that	O
you	O
discover	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
keys	O
and	O
the	O
seal	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
different	O
keys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
itself	O
;	O
how	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
paper	O
inside	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
paper	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
paper	O
very	O
much	O
worn	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
so	O
fill	O
the	O
case	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
printed	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
plain	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
examined	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
torn	O
at	O
one	O
corner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
or	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
he	O
cohabits	O
with	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
addicted	O
to	O
drinking	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
an	O
improper	O
connexion	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
concern	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
very	O
often	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
got	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Clement	O
's	O
lane	O
he	O
was	O
beating	O
and	O
turning	O
the	O
woman	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Betsey	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
murdered	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
a	O
charing	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Large	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
and	O
some	O
victuals	O
for	O
my	O
day	O
's	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
half-crown	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
more	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
ought	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
to	O
my	O
shame	O
be	O
it	O
spoken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
begged	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
take	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
connexion	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
uncle	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
property	O
at	O
South	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
property	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
by	O
all	O
account	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
care	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
for	O
money	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
534.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RIPPINGHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
falsely	O
making	O
and	O
forging	O
a	O
certain	O
order	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
Messrs.	O
Drummond	O
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
13	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
it	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Andrew-Berkley	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
ROSS	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hairdresser	O
and	O
perfumer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
119	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
Within	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
some	O
day	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
exactly	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
wig	O
he	O
had	O
ordered	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
usual	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
wig	O
tried	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
draft	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
for	O
payment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Thirteen	O
pounds	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
change	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
difference	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
draft	O
,	O
or	O
somebody	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
wait	O
till	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
Drummonds	O
'	O
and	O
Co.	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
gone	O
long	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
for	O
the	O
difference	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
Drummond	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
that	O
draft	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
refused	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
exactly	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
wig	O
?	O
-	O
A.Five	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
draft	O
again	O
if	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
wig	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
offered	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
wig	O
;	O
you	O
telling	O
him	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Drummonds	O
'	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
two	O
miles	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
Messrs.	O
Drummonds	O
'	O
is	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
check	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Drummonds	O
'	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
refused	O
;	O
how	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
did	O
you	O
part	O
with	O
that	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
Messrs.	O
Drummonds	O
'	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
O	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
draft	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
READ	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
cashier	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Drummonds	O
'	O
bank	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
Q.What	O
are	O
the	O
partners	O
'	O
names	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Berkley	I-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Drummond	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
check	O
presented	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
presented	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
kept	O
cash	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
change	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
VICKERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
door	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
with	O
a	O
city	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Rippingham	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
father	O
lived	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
highway	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
information	O
lodged	O
against	O
him	O
at	O
Worship	O
street	O
office	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
committed	O
a	O
forgery	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
to	O
compromise	O
that	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
had	O
promised	O
his	O
friend	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
proceed	O
any	O
farther	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
;	O
this	O
check	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
the	O
elder	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
apprehended	O
him	O
his	O
observation	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
compromise	O
the	O
business	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
;	O
was	O
not	O
that	O
the	O
expression	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
settled	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	O
ROSS	O
,	O
sen.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
in	O
life	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sorry	O
for	O
any	O
person	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
compromise	O
this	O
business	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
A	O
thousand	O
things	O
may	O
be	O
said	O
behind	O
your	O
back	O
,	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
attach	O
upon	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whom	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
this	O
check	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mrs.	O
Ross	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
check	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
difference	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
check	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
fraud	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
myself	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
tell	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
check	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
idea	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
forgery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
check	O
which	O
the	O
officer	O
Vickery	O
has	O
produced	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
you	O
yourself	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
personally	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Very	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
that	O
draft	O
before	O
?	O
(	O
The	O
draft	O
handed	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
clerks	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Ross	O
's	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hands	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
hands	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mrs.	O
Ross	O
and	O
several	O
people	O
reading	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
look	O
at	O
that	O
draft	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
draft	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
535.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
VITON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
ideot	O
,	O
or	O
lunatic	O
,	O
and	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
536.	O
ANN	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
bolsters	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-board	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
,	O
admitted	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
permission	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
537.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
FOLLETT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
mahogany	O
shelves	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
New	I-place
Hummums	I-place
in	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
:	O
On	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
my	O
coffee-room	O
was	O
under	O
repair	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
mahogany	O
shelves	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
repair	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
worked	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
NEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
I	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
Hummums	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Follett	O
in	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Collins	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
Follett	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
Collins	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
coat	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Follett	O
put	O
something	O
under	O
the	O
coat	O
that	O
Collins	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
Follett	O
buttoned	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
waiter	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
before	O
;	O
mind	O
my	O
question	O
-	O
was	O
Welch	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Welch	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
drinking	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Duke's-head	O
,	O
and	O
Welch	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
this	O
same	O
mahogany	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
sober	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
instructed	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
questions	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
drunk	O
I	O
certainly	O
shall	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
persons	O
can	O
not	O
keep	O
themselves	O
sober	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witness	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
down	O
being	O
intoxicated	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Nest	O
to	O
the	O
Duke's-head	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
Nest	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
mahogany	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
mahogany	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
shelves	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Follett	O
,	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
drinking	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Northumberland	O
arms	O
,	O
Russell	O
street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
:	O
Welch	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
last	O
Monday	O
morning	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
drinking	O
there	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
Hummums	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
Follett	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
Welch	O
did	O
not	O
work	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
partner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
Hummums	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Nest	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
foreman	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Collins	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
place	O
to	O
be	O
foreman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Collins	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
afterwards	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
Welch	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
mahogony	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
shelf	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
First	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
Welch	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Hummums	O
;	O
Follett	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Hummums	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
by	O
themselves	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
join	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
those	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
drinking	O
altogether	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
Q.	O
Collins	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
mahogany	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
drank	O
together	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
EASTWICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
our	O
Office-door	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Nest	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Headson	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Nest	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Follett	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
property	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
this	O
Follett	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
information	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Headson	O
,	O
the	O
head	O
carpenter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Hummums	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
flung	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
generally	O
meet	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
trifle	O
of	O
a	O
skirmish	O
;	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
call	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
flung	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
hang	O
upon	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
flung	O
out	O
;	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
circumstance	O
of	O
an	O
axe	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
entered	O
the	O
room	O
along	O
with	O
Nest	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
axe	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hit	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
deal	O
better	O
behaviour	O
;	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
can	O
make	O
of	O
that	O
fellow	O
Nest	O
's	O
behaviour	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
behaved	O
very	O
improper	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
told	O
thetruth	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
represented	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
From	O
that	O
situation	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
removed	O
.	O
Welch	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Follett	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
538.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
WEAVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
WHITEHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
and	O
fish	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LAMBLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
gown	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
through	O
Manor-row	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
running	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
leading	O
to	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
it	O
immediately	O
struck	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
apron	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
gown	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
employer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bourne	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
gown	O
in	O
pledge	O
myself	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
mercy	O
entirely	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drove	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
distress	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
539.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TROY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tablespoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
ASHLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
Great	O
William-street	O
,	O
Marylebone-lane	O
.	O
Q.What	O
house	O
does	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
keep	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	B-place
Harp	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Edgeware-road	I-place
:	I-place
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
pot	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
far	O
he	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Harp	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Harp	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
him	O
home	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
holiday	O
on	O
purpose	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
recollect	O
your	O
face	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
recollect	O
your	O
face	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
married	O
away	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Westminster	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
cooked	O
the	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
dinner	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
could	O
make	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
stopping	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
very	O
small	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
where	O
he	O
laid	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
must	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
dinner	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
a	O
good	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
him	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
gin	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
warm	O
water	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sugar-tongs	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
ask	O
when	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
finding	O
him	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
paying	O
for	O
the	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
nobody	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
ourselves	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
spoons	O
ever	O
found	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
nobody	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
any	O
body	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
lived	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Westminster	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
recollect	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
your	O
niece	O
had	O
your	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
conversing	O
together	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
was	O
treating	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
wide	O
open	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
conversing	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
deficient	O
by	O
twopence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
why	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
So	O
far	O
from	O
depriving	O
this	O
man	O
of	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
CHARLOTTE	B-pers
PLOWMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Ashley	O
was	O
frying	O
some	O
bacon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
dinner	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
biscuit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
twopence	O
halfpenny	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
down	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
at	O
that	O
present	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Ashley	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ashley	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
bar	O
by	O
dusk	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
nobody	O
else	O
came	O
in	O
till	O
my	O
mistress	O
and	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
nobody	O
else	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
else	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
found	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
perfectly	O
well	O
that	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
from	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
asked	O
for	O
twopence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
that	O
deficient	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
the	O
sister	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
girl	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
done	O
treating	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
when	O
the	O
sister	O
returned	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Witness	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Ashley	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
property	O
ever	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
(	O
Read	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
case	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Troy	I-pers
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Troy	I-pers
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Harp	O
,	O
was	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
his	O
old	O
friend	O
kept	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Mitre	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
sister	O
pressed	O
him	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
niece	O
and	O
sister	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
pig	O
was	O
being	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
remaining	O
conversing	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
sister	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
was	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
returning	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
should	O
make	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
meet	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
sister	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
been	O
treating	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
change	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
departed	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
meeting	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
any	O
thing	O
should	O
be	O
said	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
sister	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
several	O
peculiar	O
transactions	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
mistake	O
before	O
;	O
still	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
odds	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
soon	O
have	O
gone	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
seeing	O
my	O
employer	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
accosted	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
Troy	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
begs	O
leave	O
to	O
observe	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
open	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
sister	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
inclined	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
he	O
deposited	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
humbly	O
implores	O
that	O
this	O
honourable	O
Court	O
will	O
grant	O
him	O
that	O
mercy	O
and	O
humanity	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
them	O
so	O
conspicuous	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
sister	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
you	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
town	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
leave	O
town	O
till	O
I	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
meet	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
540.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WESTLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
time-piece	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Vine-street	B-place
,	I-place
Hatton-garden	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
the	O
shop	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
shutter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
jump	O
off	O
the	O
step	O
with	O
the	O
time-piece	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
with	O
the	O
time-piece	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
trying	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
time-piece	O
up	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
boy	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
his	O
mother	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
boy	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Hatton-garden	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
time-piece	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
supposed	O
his	O
mother	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
string	O
broke	O
where	O
this	O
time-piece	O
hung	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
time-piece	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
15	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
541.	O
MARY	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
JAMES	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Butts	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
brick-field	O
,	O
at	O
Clapton	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
travelling	O
about	O
after	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
,	O
at	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
drink	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
some	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
about	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
till	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
this	O
woman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
up	O
Kingsland-road	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
tired	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awoke	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
there	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
tired	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
slept	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
wandered	O
away	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
then	O
about	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
landlady	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
in	O
two	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
appeared	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
kept	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
liberty	O
