TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1804	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SECOND	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
AND	O
BLANCHARD	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
,	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1804	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
MACDONALD	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
SOULDEN	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
GILES	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
PAUL	B-pers
LE	I-pers
MESURIER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EAMER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LEA	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
NEWMAN	B-pers
KNOWLYS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
John-Goodridge	B-pers
Gossling	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gascoigne	I-pers
,	O
Henry-Gundy	B-pers
Renshaw	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fraser	I-pers
,	O
Henry-Robson	B-pers
Robley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
M'Corn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gledhill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Forrest	I-pers
.	O
61.	O
CORNELIUS	B-pers
DELTENON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
thirty	O
lemons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
copper	O
pocket-piece	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
farthing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
copper	O
money	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
farthing	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TILLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
green-grocer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
lemons	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
containing	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lemons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
inside	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
imitation	O
of	O
a	O
farthing	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
dropped	O
into	O
the	O
basket	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pocket-piece	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
boys	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
up	O
Church-street	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
crawl	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Tilley	O
's	O
shop	O
upon	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
knees	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Church-street	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
taken	O
a	O
few	O
apples	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
lemons	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
lemons	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
11	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
the	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
.	O
62.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
KNIGHT	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
and	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
dressing-glass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
washing-tub	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
pitcher	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MITCHELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
28	I-place
,	I-place
Tower-street	I-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
lodging-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
back-room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
floor	O
;	O
she	O
hired	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
furnished	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
,	O
whom	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
her	O
daughter	O
;	O
she	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
daughter	O
worked	O
at	O
child-bed	O
linen	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
borrowed	O
a	O
cloak	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
aunt	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
ill	O
;	O
the	O
daughter	O
remained	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
days	O
afterwards	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
;	O
the	O
daughter	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
aunt	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
daughter	O
disappeared	O
;	O
after	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
door	O
broken	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
true	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
there	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
served	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
trick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
thankful	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
which	O
never	O
was	O
returned	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MITCHELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Repeats	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
trace	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
)	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
opportunity	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
mother	O
going	O
away	O
and	O
the	O
daughter	O
,	O
of	O
seeing	O
whether	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
rag	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
the	O
lodging	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
fortnight	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
felon	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
missing	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
premises	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
persuade	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
of	O
this	O
bulk	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
carried	O
out	O
without	O
his	O
knowing	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
hear	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
child	O
say	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
allows	O
his	O
lodgers	O
tohave	O
a	O
latch-key	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
very	O
portable	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
feathers	O
a	O
few	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
one	O
night	O
without	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
63.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LATHAM	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PRUDEN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JACOB	B-pers
VANDOME	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
HUGH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Fountain	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Virginia-row	I-place
,	I-place
Bethnal-green	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
porter	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
whether	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
get	O
some	O
steaks	O
dressed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
might	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
with	O
some	O
beef-steaks	O
;	O
they	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
by	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
cooked	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
cooking	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
another	O
place	O
to	O
eat	O
it	O
in	O
than	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
others	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
put	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
supped	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
supper	O
,	O
Pruden	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
bar-door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
after	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
glasses	O
of	O
liquor	O
among	O
his	O
acquaintances	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
supper	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
Pruden	O
served	O
those	O
people	O
with	O
the	O
liquor	O
over	O
the	O
bar-door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
facing	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Pruden	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
proper	O
person	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
settle	O
among	O
one	O
another	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Vandome	O
sitting	O
behind	O
the	O
tap-room	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
look	O
what	O
the	O
time	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
fire-place	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
Pruden	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Turk-street	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
very	O
quiet	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
watch	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Symonds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
bar	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLESSIT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
lads	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Latham	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
watchmen	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
no	O
case	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
is	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
several	O
questions	O
;	O
Vandome	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
seemed	O
to	O
accuse	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HASSENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Blessit	O
had	O
got	O
Latham	O
out	O
,	O
examining	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
Pruden	O
and	O
Vandome	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
thrown	O
through	O
the	O
bars	O
of	O
the	O
cage	O
upon	O
the	O
pathway	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
outside	O
case	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
lights	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Pruden	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Pruden	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Pruden	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Latham	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Vandome	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
64.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DEVISE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adshead	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ADSHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tin-plate	O
worker	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
74	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
High-street	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
lighted	O
my	O
candles	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
scarcely	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
person	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
immediately	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lit	O
up	O
another	O
candle	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
thedoor	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
scarce	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
I	O
saw	O
Devise	O
collared	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
six	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lurking	O
about	O
different	O
shops	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
in	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
watching	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
suppose	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
short	O
man	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
try	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
times	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
by	O
getting	O
hold	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
peeping	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
watching	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Devise	O
running	O
towards	O
Aldgate	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
bellows	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
struggle	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
fell	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
mob	O
had	O
collected	O
;	O
taking	O
him	O
along	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
enquiry	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
resistance	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
mob	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
confederate	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
bellows	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Baker	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
collected	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
Devise	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Adshead	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
Devise	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
bellows	O
.	O
Baker	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Devise	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Confined	O
twelve	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
.	O
65.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NORMAN	I-pers
and	O
WALTER	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
51	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Liptrap	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Liptrap	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
John	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Liptrap	I-pers
,	O
distiller	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel-road	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
servant	O
s	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Oakes	O
and	O
Brown	O
,	O
coppersmiths	O
,	O
Houndsdith	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
fixing	O
a	O
new	O
copper	O
in	O
the	O
spirit	O
warehouse	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
we	O
received	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
regularly	O
entered	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
the	O
entry	O
myself	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Fisk	I-pers
;	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptraps	O
were	O
then	O
accountable	O
for	O
the	O
solder	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
solder	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
fixing	O
a	O
new	O
pump	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
pump	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
Oakes	O
and	O
Brown	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
pump	O
fixed	O
in	O
a	O
workman	O
like	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
solder	O
that	O
was	O
necessary	O
was	O
used	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
for	O
the	O
solder	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
used	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptraps	O
were	O
accountable	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
MIST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
cooper	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptraps	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Norman	O
if	O
the	O
work	O
was	O
finished	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
solder	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
quantity	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
solder	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
OAKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
to	O
do	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sent	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
solder	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptraps	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
is	O
the	O
solder	O
when	O
it	O
arrives	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptraps	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
did	O
a	O
job	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
solder	O
you	O
sent	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
credit	O
for	O
what	O
was	O
returned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
these	O
men	O
worked	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
As	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
business	O
,	O
near	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
very	O
industrious	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FISK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptraps	O
:	O
We	O
have	O
frequently	O
had	O
solder	O
from	O
Mess	O
.	O
Oakes	O
and	O
Brown	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
solder	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
one	O
pound	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
job	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
to	O
come	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
solder	O
that	O
remains	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
was	O
used	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
who	O
does	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
consider	O
yourselves	O
as	O
answerable	O
for	O
what	O
remains	O
after	O
the	O
job	O
is	O
done	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
ours	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
solder	O
came	O
in	O
pigs	O
I	O
apprehend	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
use	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
was	O
necessary	O
for	O
fixing	O
this	O
pump	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
have	O
used	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
necessary	O
,	O
the	O
remainder	O
is	O
usually	O
weighed	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
in	O
your	O
book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
solder	O
was	O
taken	O
back	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Oakes	O
and	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
omission	O
was	O
their	O
not	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
your	O
course	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
called	O
us	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
weighed	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
PoliceOffice	O
,	O
Worship-street	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Baker's-row	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
passed	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
as	O
from	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptraps	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
to	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
knocking	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
brazier	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Newberry	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
name	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
something	O
heavy	O
wrapped	O
up	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
public-house	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
,	O
Davis	O
,	O
rescued	O
himself	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
throwing	O
down	O
this	O
solder	O
,	O
which	O
weighs	O
26	O
lb	O
.	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
solder	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
working	O
jacket	O
;	O
this	O
weighs	O
25	O
lb	O
.	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
largest	O
piece	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
was	O
warm	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Liptrap	O
;	O
Norman	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Liptrap	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
ladles	O
that	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
solder	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
told	O
you	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
told	O
you	O
who	O
their	O
masters	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Oakes	O
.	O
)	O
If	O
these	O
men	O
had	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
solder	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accounted	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Liptrap	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Liptrap	O
's	O
for	O
six	O
years	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
custom	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
from	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Norman	O
called	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
66.	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Brinckworth	I-pers
.	O
LUKE	B-pers
BRINCKWORTH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
1	I-place
,	I-place
Church-row	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
japan	O
chair	O
from	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MARR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chair-maker	O
:	O
Yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
chair	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
new	O
chair	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
chair-makers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Brinckworth	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Brinckworth	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
chair	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
chair	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
nor	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
husband	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Confined	O
12	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
.	O
67.	O
MARY	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gallie	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GALLIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
myself	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Horse	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Clare-market	I-place
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
for	O
some	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
speaking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
locked	O
out	O
from	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
counted	O
it	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
by	O
a	O
lamp	O
near	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
journeyman	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
came	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
to	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
twisted	O
the	O
chain	O
round	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
charge	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
a	O
watchman	O
immediately	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICKMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
beadle	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
housewife	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
quell	O
the	O
riot	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
again	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Rickman	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
two-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Rickman	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
was	O
Gallie	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Half	O
drunk	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
68.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLIGH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
ten	O
sacks	O
of	O
foot	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FOXLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Sixteen	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Marybone-passage	B-place
,	I-place
Wells-street	I-place
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sweep	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
journeyman	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
rightly	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
ten	O
sacks	O
of	O
soot	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
live	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
Bligh	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
our	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
men	O
took	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
men	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
other	O
house	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
called	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
eight	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
church	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
every	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
happen	O
to	O
you	O
after	O
you	O
are	O
dead	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
persons	O
who	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
when	O
they	O
have	O
taken	O
an	O
oath	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
go	O
to	O
Heaven	O
,	O
they	O
always	O
go	O
to	O
Hell	O
.	O
(	O
Sworn	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
Foxley	O
:	O
On	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
or	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Bligh	O
take	O
ten	O
sacks	O
of	O
soot	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
sack	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
soot	O
was	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
sacks	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
whistle	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Bligh	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
Foxley	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
Bligh	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
come	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
Bligh	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
soot	O
in	O
sacks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
BERRY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
twelve	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
Foxley	O
and	O
Davis	O
:	O
On	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
Bligh	O
took	O
ten	O
sacks	O
away	O
;	O
a	O
whistle	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
Bligh	O
called	O
us	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
whistle	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Bligh	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
us	O
up	O
to	O
send	O
us	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
us	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
Berners-street	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
soon	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
Bligh	O
fill	O
the	O
sacks	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
;	O
Bligh	O
held	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
filled	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
Bligh	O
carried	O
the	O
sack	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
sack	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
Bligh	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
us	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOODWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
these	O
boys	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
times	O
missed	O
soot	O
:	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
soot	O
from	O
the	O
front	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
the	O
cellar	O
was	O
filled	O
up	O
with	O
soot	O
as	O
full	O
as	O
it	O
could	O
hold	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
soot	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
months	O
all	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sooner	O
be	O
hanged	O
than	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
helped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
filled	O
the	O
cellar	O
up	O
from	O
Swallow-street	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Tucker	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Confined	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
69.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
REARDON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
six	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
galls	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
HENRY	O
MATTHEWS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
assistant	O
elder	O
in	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
at	O
Horslydown	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
:	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
property	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
insist	O
upon	O
his	O
stripping	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
particularly	O
;	O
he	O
saved	O
me	O
that	O
trouble	O
,	O
by	O
confessing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
galls	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
canvas	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
,	O
in	O
Billiter-lane	O
;	O
Rigge	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
another	O
bag	O
of	O
galls	O
,	O
very	O
similar	O
to	O
the	O
one	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
quality	O
with	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RIGGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
Aldgate	O
ward	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Billiter-lane	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
after-part	O
of	O
his	O
small	O
clothes	O
this	O
bag	O
of	O
galls	O
,	O
weighing	O
three	O
pounds	O
six	O
ounces	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
in	O
Horslydown-court	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
pepper	O
,	O
indigo	O
,	O
borax	O
,	O
loose	O
galls	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
)	O
Those	O
are	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
articles	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
articles	O
of	O
that	O
description	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
blue	O
galls	O
,	O
and	O
correspond	O
exactly	O
with	O
the	O
galls	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
close	O
by	O
this	O
heap	O
of	O
galls	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
31	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
before	O
the	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
Cree	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
70.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
96	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
flax	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
the	O
charge	O
as	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
All	O
Three	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
71.	O
ARTHUR	B-pers
M'GINNIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
indigo	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
SHILLETO	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
assistant	O
elder	O
in	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouses	O
in	O
Seething-lane	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
usual	O
time	O
of	O
discharging	O
the	O
labourers	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
indigo	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
indigo	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
pockets	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Billiter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
half-a-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
his	O
loss	O
by	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
that	O
indigo	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
quality	O
with	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Rigge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
indigo	O
.	O
)	O
Shilleto	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
indigo	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
ten	O
shillings	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
ever	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipped	O
before	O
the	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouse	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Allhallows	O
Barking	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
72.	O
SARAH	B-pers
CHESHIRE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Half-Moon-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
,	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
children	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
one	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
another	O
six	O
years	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
about	O
fifteen	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Police-Office	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HARDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
children	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
made	O
herself	O
known	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
mentioning	O
some	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
recollected	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
my	O
mother	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
two	O
days	O
work	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
engaged	O
at	O
Dr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
in	O
Hog-lane	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
my	O
mother	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
directly	O
I	O
cleared	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
bundles	O
of	O
clothes	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Half-Moon-alley	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
chairwoman	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
back	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
tea	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
find	O
where	O
my	O
mother	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
mother	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
chairwoman	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
to	O
Hog-lane	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
spoons	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
apron	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
's	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HARDING	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
bad	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
swear	O
false	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
Hell	O
:	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
,	O
Half-Moon-alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
mother	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
discourse	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
little	O
brother	O
opened	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
my	O
mother	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
not	O
long	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
her	O
bonnet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
her	O
cap	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
towards	O
the	O
fire-place	O
,	O
and	O
scraped	O
her	O
feet	O
on	O
the	O
stove	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
reading	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
jingling	O
the	O
glass	O
that	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
spoon	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
what	O
my	O
mother	O
drank	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
particular	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bottle	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
something	O
against	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
bottle	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
spoons	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MITFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
teaspoon	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
any	O
tea-spoons	O
;	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
seeing	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
on	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
more	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
WILLIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
two	O
spoons	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
sold	O
the	O
evening	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoons	O
and	O
apron	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
for	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
mother	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
73.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
pounds	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
cocoa	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
eighty-nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
mustard	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
four	O
pounds	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
starch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
blue	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
pepper	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
eight	O
ounces	O
of	O
orange	O
peppermint	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
lemon	O
lozenges	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
currants	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
thirty	O
lemons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILCOX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
79	O
,	O
Tower-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
chest	O
on	O
my	O
knot	O
to	O
Craven-street	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
waggon	O
in	O
Watling-street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
waggoner	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
lift	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
it	O
past	O
the	O
Bolt-in-Tun	O
,	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
forward	O
from	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
to	O
the	O
waggoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
about	O
Craven-street	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
court	O
,	O
named	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
men	O
sitting	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
pushed	O
his	O
legs	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHERRING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Fisher's-alley	O
with	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbott	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
lugging	O
a	O
chest	O
down	O
a	O
court	O
;	O
Wilcox	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
chest	O
and	O
prisoner	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
TEMPLEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
lump	O
against	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
chest	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
chest	O
and	O
articles	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
LAWRENCE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
plying	O
at	O
Blackfriars-stairs	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
chest	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Pepper-alley	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
too	O
heavy	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
mind	O
it	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
frightened	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
nine	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
74.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HASELDINE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
80	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William-Storrs	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
HALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
in	O
the	O
employ	O
of	O
William-Storrs	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
with	O
my	O
cart	O
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Castle	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
cart	O
with	O
the	O
chest	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
book	O
signed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
copse	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
chest	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
cord	O
catching	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
irons	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
removed	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
side	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
standing	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LINGALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
standing	O
under	O
the	O
cart	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
copse	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
the	O
carter	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
discharged	O
by	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
copse	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
chests	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
move	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Hall	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
more	O
chest	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
75.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
eight	O
quarts	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
76.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WOODBOURNE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
block	O
hammer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
head-stake	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
punch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
flat	O
punches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
,	I-place
Wilderness-row	I-place
,	I-place
Goswell-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tin-plate	O
worker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
tool	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
head-stake	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
our	O
line	O
of	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
block	O
hammer	O
,	O
three	O
punches	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
another	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
officers	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Marshalman	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
Silk-street	O
,	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
tools	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Old-street-square	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
work-shop	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
master	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
inform	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
square	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
he	O
placed	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
himself	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
caught	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
Silk-street	O
,	O
Cripplegate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
slept	O
with	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
officer	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
wife	O
lent	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
a	O
shopman	O
in	O
the	O
jewellery	O
line	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
near	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
respectable	O
character	O
he	O
is	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
five	O
weeks	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
very	O
regular	O
hours	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
bringing	O
this	O
hammer	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
hammer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
articles	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
very	O
badly	O
off	O
for	O
tools	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
own	O
tools	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
apprentices	O
worked	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
dispute	O
about	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
work	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
77.	O
ANN	B-pers
ROUND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
WHITEHEAD	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3	I-place
,	I-place
Houndsditch	I-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
other	O
partner	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
purchase	O
a	O
gown	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
they	O
looked	O
at	O
a	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
pitched	O
upon	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
leave	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
projecting	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
dropped	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dragged	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
;	O
Ikept	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
dropped	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
myself	O
and	O
two	O
sons	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
she	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman-servant	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITEHEAD	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sixteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
about	O
fifteen	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
front	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
during	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
customer	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
bulk	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
stepped	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
more	O
she	O
thought	O
than	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
dragged	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
almost	O
two	O
doors	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOFT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
following	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
wrenching	O
something	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strike	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
some	O
resistance	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
tore	O
her	O
cloak	O
in	O
the	O
neck	O
;	O
some	O
abusive	O
language	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
taking	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
manner	O
of	O
twisting	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
property	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
an	O
officer	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
from	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
cloak	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
use	O
her	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
gun	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
file	O
for	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gown-piece	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
several	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
lady	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
78.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
cocoa	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Barbe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
.	O
Charging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
upon	O
Ralph's-quay	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
labourer	O
upon	O
the	O
quay	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
under	O
the	O
fore-sheet	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
mending	O
some	O
bags	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
coat	O
under	O
the	O
fore-sheet	O
,	O
with	O
cocoa	O
in	O
the	O
pockets	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
bags	O
over	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
coat	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
lighter	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
cocoa	O
and	O
coffee	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
charge	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
fustian	O
jacket	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wore	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
lighter	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
regular	O
bag-mender	O
.	O
-	O
HARDING	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
cocoa	O
,	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
cocoa	O
)	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
other	O
ways	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
job	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BIGNELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Messrs.	O
John	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Barbe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
broker	O
s	O
employed	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
:	O
the	O
lighter	O
was	O
laden	O
with	O
cocoa	O
in	O
part	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
36	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
79.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
two	O
seven-shilling	O
pieces	O
;	O
a	O
half-crown	O
,	O
twenty-two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	O
CHADWICK	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
47	I-place
,	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew's-street	I-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
ten	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
accuse	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
unjust	O
thing	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
party	O
of	O
friends	O
to	O
dine	O
;	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
attended	O
to	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
a	O
customer	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
A	O
on	O
the	O
crown	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
beer	O
machine	O
,	O
andwent	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
till	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
gentleman	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
change	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
recollected	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
off	O
the	O
beer	O
machine	O
;	O
no	O
one	O
had	O
been	O
inside	O
the	O
bar	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Joseph	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
off	O
the	O
beer	O
machine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
sir	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
but	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
particular	O
in	O
sweeping	O
out	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Lambeth	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
whose	O
company	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
shun	O
;	O
the	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
money	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ATKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
produce	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
A	O
marked	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
money	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
was	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
80.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
pounded	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Barbary	O
comfits	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Alley	O
.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
BARNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
and	O
confectioner	O
in	O
Princes-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
servants	O
a	O
supper	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
twice	O
into	O
the	O
confectionary	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rustling	O
of	O
paper	O
among	O
the	O
confectionary	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
jar	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
confectionary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
parcel	O
from	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sometime	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
,	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
81.	O
JOHN-WILSON	B-pers
HATFIELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
ninety-seven	O
files	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BLIGH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Richard	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
ironmongers	O
,	O
in	O
Foster-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
threw	O
a	O
lock	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
with	O
keys	O
to	O
fit	O
a	O
key	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
sometime	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
towards	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
some	O
more	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
parcels	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
other	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
files	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
bundle	O
of	O
files	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bligh	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
reach	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
keys	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
reaching	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
accompting-house	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
Mr.	O
Bligh	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bligh	O
ran	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
more	O
keys	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
files	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
produced	O
three	O
parcels	O
of	O
files	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
48	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
82.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PUGH	I-pers
and	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
eight	O
gallons	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garcias	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
,	O
and	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GARCIAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Finsbury-square	B-place
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
I	O
employed	O
Mess	O
.	O
Wild	O
to	O
bottle	O
off	O
three	O
pipes	O
of	O
port	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
work	O
bottling	O
the	O
wine	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
careful	O
in	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
ullage	O
,	O
or	O
thick	O
part	O
,	O
into	O
bottles	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
draw	O
off	O
the	O
wine	O
clearer	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
the	O
pipe	O
edgeways	O
;	O
they	O
pointed	O
out	O
thirteen	O
bottles	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
ullage	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
pipes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Miller	O
particularly	O
officious	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
drinking	O
too	O
much	O
wine	O
;	O
thepipes	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Miller	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
no	O
particular	O
directions	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
manner	O
the	O
wine	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
men	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
did	O
they	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
the	O
binns	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
marked	O
it	O
with	O
chalk	O
on	O
the	O
binns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
examining	O
those	O
binns	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
quantity	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
numbers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
With	O
twenty-two	O
broken	O
bottles	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
binns	O
,	O
it	O
corresponds	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
;	O
the	O
twenty-two	O
broken	O
bottles	O
might	O
be	O
accident	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
in	O
the	O
binns	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty-one	O
dozen	O
and	O
nine	O
bottles	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
twenty-two	O
broken	O
ones	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
are	O
wine-merchants	O
and	O
wine-coopers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
our	O
servant	O
s	O
;	O
Pugh	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
nearly	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
Miller	O
upwards	O
of	O
six	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Garcias	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
pipes	O
were	O
full	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
yield	O
fifty-two	O
dozen	O
for	O
each	O
pipe	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty-six	O
dozen	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
grounds	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
found	O
three	O
times	O
thirteen	O
bottles	O
of	O
ullage	O
or	O
grounds	O
at	O
least	O
;	O
I	O
speak	O
within	O
compass	O
when	O
I	O
say	O
thirteen	O
bottles	O
a	O
pipe	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SELLWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
carman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
employed	O
by	O
them	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Garcias	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Finsbury-square	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
empty	O
pipes	O
,	O
baskets	O
,	O
and	O
tools	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
masters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
John	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
servants	O
of	O
my	O
masters	O
,	O
one	O
foreman	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
porter	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
employed	O
to	O
bottle	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
finished	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
helped	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
one	O
pipe	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
pipe	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
cart	O
first	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Garcias	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
that	O
pipe	O
up	O
stairs	O
first	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Garcias	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
discover	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
wine	O
shake	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
Miller	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
Miller	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Pugh	I-pers
and	O
Mattew	O
Miller	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
got	O
one	O
pipe	O
up	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
others	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
After	O
Mr.	O
Garcias	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
surprised	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
thirteen	O
bottles	O
of	O
ullage	O
out	O
of	O
three	O
pipes	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
pipes	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
discover	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Miller	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Halfmoon-street	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
Miller	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Pugh	O
came	O
just	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
there	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
cart	O
stopped	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
as	O
much	O
wine	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
pipe	O
with	O
a	O
crane	O
into	O
a	O
wooden	O
can	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
wine	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
drawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
did	O
they	O
fill	O
the	O
can	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
Miller	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
can	O
contain	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
can	O
held	O
four	O
gallons	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
miller	O
's	O
wife	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
employed	O
by	O
Mess	O
.	O
Wild	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
their	O
carman	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
came	O
from	O
prison	O
to-day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Ten	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
you	O
told	O
your	O
masters	O
what	O
passed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
wrong	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
you	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
confessed	O
all	O
I	O
knew	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
in	O
carrying	O
away	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
gallons	O
of	O
wine	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
wrong	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
moment	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
wrong	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
then	O
consider	O
it	O
was	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
wrong	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
discover	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
understood	O
it	O
was	O
wrong	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
before	O
you	O
discovered	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Once	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Not	O
more	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
say	O
you	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
transaction	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
then	O
delivered	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
by	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
undergone	O
private	O
confinement	O
,	O
you	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
accuse	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
confessed	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
disclose	O
a	O
single	O
tittle	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
said	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
had	O
undergone	O
the	O
discipline	O
of	O
private	O
confinement	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
Wootton	O
Basset	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
line	O
of	O
life	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
publican	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
better	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
leave	O
him	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
accusation	O
of	O
your	O
having	O
made	O
free	O
with	O
something	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
make	O
free	O
with	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
mutton	O
or	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
his	O
service	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
theft	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
come	O
here	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
being	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
were	O
examined	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
disclose	O
the	O
circumstances	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
you	O
did	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
PARISH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Halfmoon-street	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
opposite	O
Miller	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
cleaning	O
my	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Sellwood	O
bring	O
a	O
cart	O
to	O
Miller	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pipes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Wild	O
on	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
the	O
cart	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
single	O
knock	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
confusion	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pipes	O
was	O
removed	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
by	O
the	O
cops	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
thing	O
with	O
a	O
cock	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
bung-hole	O
;	O
two	O
pails	O
lined	O
with	O
copper	O
were	O
then	O
brought	O
;	O
Miller	O
filled	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
assisting	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
Pugh	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
Miller	O
scolded	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
pan	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pail	O
emptied	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
while	O
Pugh	O
was	O
drawing	O
another	O
;	O
a	O
knock	O
was	O
made	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
pails	O
drawn	O
full	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
hurried	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
drove	O
off	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
my	O
husband	O
sent	O
information	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
cart	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
opposite	O
Miller	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
always	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Parish	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
our	O
real	O
name	O
is	O
Parish	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
mother	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
former	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
in	O
December	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
took	O
place	O
in	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
For	O
a	O
particular	O
reason	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
obliged	O
to	O
state	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
read	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
might	O
the	O
cart	O
stand	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
nook	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
horses	O
heads	O
were	O
towards	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pipes	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
former	O
transaction	O
,	O
stated	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
two	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
recollection	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
two	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
my	O
oath	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Pugh	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
and	O
Miller	O
two	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Pugh	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Miller	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
83.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
CARROL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
;	O
a	O
Bank-note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
other	O
Banknotes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
each	O
;	O
three	O
2	O
l.	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
1	O
l.	O
Bank-notes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
employment	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
silversmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
No	O
.	O
71	O
,	O
Oxford-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
parish	O
is	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-bone	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
way	O
were	O
you	O
employed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
As	O
shopman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Near	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
December	O
last	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
miss	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
that	O
standing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen-stairs	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
kitchen-door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
the	O
pocketbook	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
locked	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
key	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
hadlost	O
the	O
key	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
ten-pound	O
note	O
,	O
two	O
five-pound	O
notes	O
,	O
three	O
two-pound	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
one-pound	O
notes	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
all	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
notes	O
,	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
missing	O
them	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
this	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
mean	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
missed	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
key	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Near	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
your	O
pocket-book	O
or	O
key	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
possession	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Hole-in-the-Wall	O
,	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
key	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
key	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
by	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
notes	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Eleven	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
woman	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
making	O
her	O
presents	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
give	O
her	O
possession	O
of	O
your	O
key	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
boxes	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
with	O
my	O
clothes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
that	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
of	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
slept	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
box	O
below	O
contained	O
my	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
left	O
unlocked	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
carelessly	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
happened	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
gave	O
her	O
permission	O
to	O
use	O
your	O
key	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
;	O
the	O
Sunday	O
preceding	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
herself	O
;	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
all	O
out	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
conductors	O
of	O
the	O
patrol	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
the	O
Hole-in-the-Wall	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
produce	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
two-pound	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
one-pound	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
her	O
pockets	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
keys	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
Produces	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Davis	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
book	O
you	O
missed	O
from	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
key	O
you	O
left	O
in	O
your	O
great	O
coat	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
notes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
body	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
your	O
master	O
as	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
searched	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
pocket-book	O
delivered	O
to	O
Davis	O
