TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1805	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
PETER	B-pers
PERCHARD	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
RAMSEY	O
AND	O
BLANCHARD	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
.	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
W.	O
WILSON	O
,	O
St.	O
Peter's-Hill	O
,	O
Little	O
Knight-Rider-Street	O
,	O
Doctors	O
'	O
Commons	O
.	O
1805	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
PETER	B-pers
PERCHARD	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
NASH	O
GROSE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRING	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
BROOK	O
WATSON	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
and	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STAINES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Alderman	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROWCROFT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
CLAUDIUS	B-pers
STEPHEN	I-pers
HUNTER	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
JOSIAH	B-pers
BOYDELL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
NEWMAN	O
KNOWLYS	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peris	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Elisha	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Judkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Dismoor	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spalton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hardesty	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dobins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sambrook	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Crump	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Olendale	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burrell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Winkworth	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
.	O
361.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
ham	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Frisby	I-pers
Howis	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Howis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Howis	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
a	O
printer	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howis	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
ham	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Howis	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
some	O
matting	O
;	O
the	O
ham	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
ham	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
matting	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Howis	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
back	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Howis	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
FRISBY	I-pers
HOWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oilman	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Piccadilly	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Howis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Howis	I-pers
my	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
ham	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
carman	O
we	O
usually	O
employ	O
to	O
cart	O
our	O
goods	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
strongly	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
past	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Frisby	O
Howis	O
to	O
load	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
before	O
the	O
shop	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
load	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
for	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
whip-maker	O
and	O
fetched	O
my	O
whip	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
ham	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
thought	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
362.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
BUCKNELL	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Macaulay	I-pers
.	O
BETTY	B-pers
BEAUMONT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopwoman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Macaulay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
lady	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
British	O
lace	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
adjoining	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
glass	O
I	O
saw	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
passed	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
her	O
a	O
draw	O
of	O
British	O
lace	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
real	O
lace	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
shewed	O
her	O
a	O
draw	O
of	O
real	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
choice	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
shewed	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
card	O
from	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
made	O
choice	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
cut	O
off	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
by	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
boy	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
towards	O
the	O
payment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
lace	O
lying	O
about	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
sat	O
upon	O
two	O
stools	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
drawer	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
cheapened	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
offer	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
lace	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
bought	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
gave	O
the	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
intoxicated	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
behaviour	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
action	O
with	O
her	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
genteel	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
dressed	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
white	O
dress	O
and	O
long	O
sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
feather	O
in	O
each	O
of	O
their	O
hats	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
MACAULY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
might	O
you	O
shew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Several	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
or	O
were	O
they	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
most	O
dealing	O
for	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
cheapened	O
.	O
-	O
KINCADE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fort-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
Artillery-ground	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
manufacturer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
,	O
Iassed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
White-Lion-street	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
apparently	O
very	O
well	O
dressed	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
abused	O
the	O
passengers	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
;	O
it	O
attracted	O
my	O
attention	O
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
woman	O
so	O
well	O
dressed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
or	O
what	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
;	O
knowing	O
where	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
district	O
lived	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
on	O
suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
shop-lifter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
lace	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
ticket	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
shop-mark	O
,	O
was	O
hanging	O
somewhere	O
under	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
ticket	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
particular	O
charge	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
drop	O
the	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
which	O
the	O
officer	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
COWLING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
headboroughs	O
of	O
Norton-Falgate	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
fetched	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
shop-lifter	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Kincade	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
lace	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
robbery	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
place	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
the	O
Office	O
being	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
two	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kincade	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BISHOP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
duplicate	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
34	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
363.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ALDRICH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
thirty-three	O
silver	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
eight	O
plated	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
salvers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
three	O
silver	O
gravy-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
desert-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
fish-trowel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
ladles	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
plated	O
branches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
bread-basket	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DENNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bentinck-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
footman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
quit	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
in	O
Passion-week	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
answered	O
me	O
;	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
I	O
rang	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
no	O
person	O
answering	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
servant	O
above	O
stairs	O
neither	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ring	O
at	O
the	O
bell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
house-maid	O
;	O
I	O
reprimanded	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
induced	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
absent	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
servant-maid	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
chest	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
that	O
plate	O
in	O
use	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
chest	O
of	O
plate	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
the	O
whole	O
course	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
had	O
several	O
articles	O
of	O
plate	O
in	O
use	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
last	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
those	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
bedroom	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
common	O
use	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
both	O
these	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
common	O
use	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
few	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Soley	O
,	O
a	O
milkman	O
,	O
on	O
Lisson-green	O
;	O
I	O
traced	O
him	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SOLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Lisson-green	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Soley	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
leave	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
coat	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
wife	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
consent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
dress	O
yourself	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Lisson-green	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
dressed	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
with	O
the	O
coach	O
but	O
the	O
coachman	O
and	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
ride	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
boxes	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
drove	O
on	O
down	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
feed	O
his	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
advise	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
another	O
coach	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
horses	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
got	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
was	O
put	O
alongside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boxes	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
into	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
;	O
the	O
helper	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
shifted	O
the	O
boxes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
touch	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
;	O
he	O
pressed	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Islington	O
turnpike	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
him	O
a	O
pleasant	O
journey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
tell	O
the	O
postillion	O
where	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
Waltham-cross	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
farther	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
the	O
post-boy	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
for	O
the	O
clothes	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
places	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
the	O
right	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
got	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
PATMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Puckeridge	O
,	O
twenty-seven	O
miles	O
from	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
come	O
through	O
Waltham-cross	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Coffin	O
,	O
at	O
Puckeridge	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
Easter	O
,	O
before	O
dinner	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
bring	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
he	O
alighted	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
post	O
lad	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
boxes	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
not	O
present	O
;	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
boxes	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boxes	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
particular	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
parlour-door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
obedience	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
ale	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
fetched	O
the	O
ale	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
cooked	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
directions	O
about	O
these	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
dinner	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
tea	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
drank	O
tea	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
to	O
let	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
hired	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
white	O
deal	O
box	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
would	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
goodness	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
boxes	O
till	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
the	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
deal	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
middle	O
box	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
stairs	O
for	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
whatever	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
it	O
the	O
middle	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
smaller	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
white	O
deal	O
box	O
was	O
larger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
large	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
shifting	O
his	O
box	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
branches	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
particularly	O
see	O
that	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
afterwards	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
branches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
silver	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Apparently	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
silver	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
silver	O
spoons	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
remarked	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
middle	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lock	O
up	O
both	O
the	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
other	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
box	O
he	O
took	O
into	O
his	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
lad	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
bed-room	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understood	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
keep	O
these	O
boxes	O
till	O
he	O
returned	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
large	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
middle	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
your	O
bed-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
kept	O
in	O
your	O
bed-room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fair-day	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
from	O
London	O
about	O
tea-time	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
but	O
very	O
few	O
words	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
busy	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
after	O
his	O
journey	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
his	O
journey	O
for	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
still	O
left	O
his	O
boxes	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
boxes	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
O	O
yes	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rivett	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
bar-door	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
landlady	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
left	O
two	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
show	O
him	O
the	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
both	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
unlocked	O
the	O
bed-room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
the	O
boxes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
rather	O
confused	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
somebody	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
into	O
trouble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
delivered	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rivett	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
voice	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rivett	O
returned	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understood	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
boxes	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
boxes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
any	O
boxes	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
them	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
gave	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
body	O
else	O
might	O
have	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull	O
,	O
at	O
Royston	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Good	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
from	O
Puckeridge	O
;	O
he	O
changed	O
the	O
chaise	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
only	O
one	O
stage	O
from	O
Royston	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
thirteen	O
miles	O
;	O
my	O
chaise	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
deal	O
box	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
(	O
the	O
box	O
produced	O
)	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
box	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
return	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
box	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
chaise	O
of	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
from	O
Cambridge	O
in	O
my	O
chaise	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
fresh	O
pair	O
of	O
horses	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Puckeridge	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
requested	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
there	O
receive	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
plenty	O
of	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
double	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
unlocked	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
bread-basket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rivett	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
came	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
the	O
bread-basket	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
till	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
him	O
giving	O
you	O
the	O
bread-basket	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
one-pound	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
one-pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
chaise	O
as	O
well	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to-bed	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rivett	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
Puckeridge	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
plate	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bread-basket	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
bread-basket	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
bread-basket	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RIVETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Public-office	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
to	O
Puckeridge	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
boxes	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Patmore	O
's	O
bed-room	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
identified	O
this	O
box	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
box	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
wished	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
recognised	O
it	O
immediately	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Patmore	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
unlocked	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
this	O
one	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Patmore	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
that	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
lostin	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
his	O
travelling	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
goodness	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
directly	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Aldrich	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Rivett	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
articles	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
identified	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
there	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
plate	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Patmore	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
box	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
box	O
under	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
likewise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Having	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
you	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
took	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Royston	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
plate	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
large	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
replied	O
he	O
had	O
pledged	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
duplicates	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
replied	O
they	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
at	O
Puckeridge	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
keys	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Puckeridge	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
that	O
opened	O
the	O
smaller	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
pointed	O
out	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
the	O
duplicates	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
shewed	O
you	O
the	O
box	O
himself	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
chaise-door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
found	O
the	O
duplicates	O
where	O
he	O
shewed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
at	O
Royston	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
bread-basket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
plate	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
immediately	O
answered	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
bread-basket	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
bread-basket	O
that	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
Royston	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
weight	O
is	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
weighs	O
thirty-two	O
ounces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
us	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
forty	O
shillings	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
doubt	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
deposited	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
deposited	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
that	O
was	O
deposited	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
must	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
JOEL	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
produce	O
these	O
dishes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Are	O
those	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
taken	O
any	O
pains	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
is	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
respectable	O
family	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
other	O
persons	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
depredation	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
364.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FAGAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
brand-mark	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
locks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
steel	O
ruler	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
)	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
HICKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
calico	O
printer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Old	O
Ford	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
our	O
watchman	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
proceeded	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
EWERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Fagan	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
locks	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
chamber	O
;	O
the	O
brand-mark	O
,	O
the	O
shovel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
wash-house	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
OLIVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
as	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
I	O
met	O
several	O
articles	O
in	O
a	O
wheelbarrow	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
extremely	O
sorry	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
considered	O
that	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
box	O
has	O
been	O
about	O
the	O
factory	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
locks	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
that	O
is	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
365.	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
KELLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
three	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
nankeen	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
sheeting	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
satin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
bed	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Axe	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
eating-house	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Castle-place	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Kelley	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
as	O
cook	O
;	O
on	O
searching	O
her	O
we	O
found	O
forty-two	O
duplicates	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
for	O
property	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
between	O
the	O
sacking	O
and	O
the	O
bed	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
;	O
we	O
also	O
found	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
21	O
,	O
Castle-place	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
City	O
porter	O
,	O
she	O
takes	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
in	O
searching	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
produce	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pockets	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
resisted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
in	O
struggling	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
search	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
pockets	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
forty-two	O
duplicates	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
searched	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
trunks	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Lambeth-street	O
Office	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
those	O
things	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Spinkes	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
master	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
rings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
very	O
valuable	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spinkes	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Gracechurch-street	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
pledged	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
pledged	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
three	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
these	O
pledges	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
myself	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
No	O
person	O
has	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
those	O
tickets	O
but	O
myself	O
,	O
excepting	O
what	O
belongs	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
wages	O
for	O
six	O
months	O
that	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
39	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
366.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DUCKHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
twenty-nine	O
bonnets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	O
Turner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
)	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
5	I-place
,	I-place
Long-lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
bolted	O
and	O
chained	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
;	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
all	O
my	O
bonnets	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
till	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
shop	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
straw	O
bonnet	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
bolted	O
nor	O
chained	O
,	O
it	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
single	O
lock	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
lodgers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
your	O
lodgers	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
in	O
when	O
they	O
like	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GEARY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
coming	O
through	O
Cowheel-alley	O
with	O
this	O
bag	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
but	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
hay	O
for	O
his	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
two	O
keys	O
under	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
other	O
keys	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
some	O
persons	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Cowheel-alley	O
,	O
we	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
securedhim	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
this	O
skeleton-key	O
under	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
threw	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
it	O
let	O
a	O
man	O
get	O
in	O
after	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
bolted	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
forty	O
pound	O
reward	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
spoken	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
39	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
367.	O
ANN	B-pers
MAGRATH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
eighteen	O
yards	O
of	O
chamberry	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS-	O
CHRISTIAN	B-pers
CORKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
some	O
person	O
passing	O
by	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
chamberry	O
muslin	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
knowing	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
chamberry	O
muslin	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
LEADBETTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
chamberry	O
muslin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Corker	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Somerset-house	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
small	O
remittance	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
too	O
freely	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
368.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GENTRY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
four	O
fowls	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
seven	O
chickens	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Barnabas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
BARNABAS	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carrier	O
,	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
waggon	O
from	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Stebbing	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Essex	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
hens	O
and	O
seven	O
chickens	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
waggon	O
from	O
the	O
hind	O
ladder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Romford	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
accuse	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
man	O
passed	O
me	O
till	O
after	O
daylight	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Rutter	O
's	O
possession	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
comes	O
with	O
a	O
one-horse	O
cart	O
from	O
Palley	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
RUTTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
at	O
Hackney	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
buying	O
some	O
pigeons	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
seven	O
chickens	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
basket	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Allen	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
basket	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
being	O
tied	O
up	O
here	O
with	O
some	O
strings	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
basket	O
was	O
not	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
you	O
only	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
string	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
basket	O
by	O
the	O
shape	O
and	O
the	O
make	O
.	O
-	O
SAMPSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Rutter	O
pay	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
four-pence	O
a-piece	O
for	O
seven	O
chickens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
whom	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
some	O
fowls	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
poulterer	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Hackney	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
fowls	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
by	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
fowls	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
369.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BRIGGS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
eight	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
pewter	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Keux	I-pers
.	O
PETER	B-pers
LE	I-pers
KEUX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
Sun-street	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
information	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
breakfast	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
breakfast	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
suspicion	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
pot	O
handles	O
and	O
bottoms	O
that	O
weighed	O
four	O
pounds	O
eight	O
ounces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
weeks	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
search	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
breeches	O
were	O
partly	O
full	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
coat	O
pockets	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
pot	O
handles	O
and	O
bottoms	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
amuse	O
my	O
children	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
dumps	O
and	O
cocks	O
for	O
my	O
children	O
to	O
shy	O
at	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
three	O
children	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
34	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
weeks	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
370.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
seven	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
flour	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Richard	O
Richardson	O
,	O
a	O
corn-factor	O
,	O
in	O
Goulston-square	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
flour	O
that	O
was	O
concealed	O
in	O
another	O
bag	O
under	O
the	O
straw	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
he	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
about	O
seven	O
pounds	O
of	O
flour	O
in	O
this	O
bag	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
bag	O
between	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
walked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Police-Office	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
flour	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
flour	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
carman	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
seventeen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
pounds	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
here	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
locked	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
adjoining	O
building	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
crevice	O
of	O
a	O
slight	O
partition	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
flour	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
straw	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
your	O
master	O
keeps	O
flour	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Neither	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
flour	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
flour	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
that	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
straw	O
was	O
seventeen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
just	O
so	O
much	O
flour	O
as	O
is	O
in	O
this	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
your	O
master	O
missed	O
any	O
flour	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
spilt	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
Counsel	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
371.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BEALS	I-pers
and	O
ESTHER	B-pers
MERRYMAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenwell	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GREENWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
liner-draper	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
for	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
was	O
shewing	O
them	O
the	O
print	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
very	O
suspicious	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
stepped	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
print	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
it	O
was	O
warm	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
print	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
found	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
between	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Beal	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
offer	O
to	O
lay	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hard-working	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
family	O
of	O
children	O
.	O
Merryman	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
brother	O
accidentally	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gown	O
against	O
Whitsuntide	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
there	O
looked	O
at	O
some	O
prints	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
off	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
was	O
I	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
four-pence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
how	O
many	O
yards	O
did	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
six	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
in	O
measuring	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
he	O
shoved	O
that	O
piece	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
here	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
truth	O
about	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
that	O
week	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
pay	O
for	O
all	O
.	O
Beals	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Beals	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Merryman	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
372.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PLUMPTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
check-brace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
groom	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Oliver	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hart-street	B-place
:	O
he	O
unbuckled	O
the	O
check	O
brace	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
other	O
blind	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
brace	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
brace	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
business	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
china	O
painting	O
line	O
;	O
we	O
always	O
work	O
by	O
day	O
and	O
burn	O
our	O
china	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
at	O
ten	O
;	O
being	O
rather	O
late	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
this	O
carriage	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
jumped	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Great	O
Russel-square	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
brace	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
vindicate	O
myself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
that	O
night	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
373.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CROOKSHANKS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
daughter	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	O
WYGATE	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
being	O
concealed	O
in	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
's	O
daughter	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hands	O
lying	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
very	O
much	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
;	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
bed-room	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
servant-maid	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
hearth	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
was	O
a	O
gown	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
the	O
daughter	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
,	O
alarmed	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
supposing	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
a	O
gown	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
paid	O
him	O
justly	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
articles	O
missing	O
which	O
were	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
right	O
to	O
suspect	O
them	O
as	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
always	O
open	O
.	O
Q.What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
bag	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
first	O
wife	O
's	O
bag	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
bag	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
pieced	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
32	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
bag	O
only	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
374.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
LEONARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
ANN	O
THOMPSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
35	I-place
,	I-place
Monmouth-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
quite	O
the	O
reverse	O
way	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
child	O
setting	O
at	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
your	O
child	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
she	O
talk	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
Ann	O
Hughes	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
child	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
here	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
them	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shoe-cellar	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
nice	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
just	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
woman	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
child	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
red	O
cloak	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
cloak	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
over	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
she	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
walked	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
hussey	O
,	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
steal	O
that	O
child	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
having	O
increasedthey	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
lame	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
dog	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
state	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
that	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
through	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
door	O
where	O
there	O
fat	O
a	O
child	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
girl	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
directed	O
me	O
the	O
nearest	O
way	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
market	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
foot	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
small	O
of	O
my	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Hughes	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
your	O
foot	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
neither	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
girl	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
375.	O
JANE	B-pers
HETHERALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Leman	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
;	O
one	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
LEMAN	O
OAKLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pattern	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
gowns	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
room-door	O
been	O
locked	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
double-locked	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
charged	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
duplicates	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
articles	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
scattered	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GILMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Oakley	O
,	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
duplicates	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicates	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
property	O
lost	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
CHARLTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
counterpane	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
each	O
.	O
-	O
HARRIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
gowns	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Turner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
passage	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
trailed	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
distress	O
made	O
me	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
will	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
Almighty	O
's	O
sake	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
49	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
376.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
braces	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
seven-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Plaistow	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Plaistow	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Barlow	B-place
Mow	I-place
,	I-place
Turnham-green	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to-bed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
tick	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to-bed	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
awoke	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
stockings	O
and	O
shoes	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
small	O
clothes	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
pillow	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
landlord	O
for	O
a	O
hammer	O
to	O
open	O
my	O
box	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
more	O
things	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
except	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
A	O
fellow-workman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
lent	O
me	O
some	O
clothes	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
overtook	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
every	O
thing	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to-bed	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
MARTIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
377.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
PERKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-master	O
,	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
preparing	O
to	O
leave	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
coach-maker	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
employ	O
in	O
my	O
work-shop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
coach	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pots	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
pots	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
charge	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Mr	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
)	O
Were	O
the	O
pots	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bruised	O
situation	O
then	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
bent	O
quite	O
flat	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
45	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
378.	O
MARY	B-pers
FOWLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
sole-leather	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Murray	B-pers
Eldred	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
.	O
MURRAY	B-pers
ELDRED	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
leather	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
for	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
past	O
,	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
information	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
brought	O
back	O
and	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
sole-leather	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
leather	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
leather	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
made	O
on	O
purpose	O
like	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
stoop	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leather	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
over	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Eldred	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
leather	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
myself	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Eldridge	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
leather	O
taken	O
out	O
from	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
made	O
on	O
purpose	O
round	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
53	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
379.	O
ANN	B-pers
PERCY	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
CURETON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
bed-furniture	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Penelope	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
PENELOPE	B-pers
DRUMMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Chapel-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
let	O
lodgings	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
furnished	O
apartment	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
what	O
apartments	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
let	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
over	O
every	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
fixed	O
upon	O
the	O
front	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bed-chamber	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
for	O
these	O
rooms	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Sunderland	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
settle	O
in	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
these	O
rooms	O
for	O
three	O
months	O
certain	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
reference	O
for	O
their	O
character	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
reference	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
probably	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
order	O
in	O
some	O
coals	O
for	O
her	O
use	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
address	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
respectable	O
reference	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Pilkington	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pilkington	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
require	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
refresh	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
bed-furniture	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
might	O
she	O
lay	O
herself	O
down	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fatigued	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
bed-room	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cornhill	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Pilkington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
might	O
that	O
be	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
person	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
friend	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
completely	O
stripped	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
furniture	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
curtains	O
and	O
trimmings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
information	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
Office	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Public-office	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
there	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
informing	O
me	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
was	O
pledged	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
property	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
bed-furniture	O
there	O
;	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
had	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
Q.Are	O
both	O
these	O
pawnbrokers	O
here	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
is	O
here	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
the	O
bed-furniture	O
and	O
trimmings	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DORRINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
from	O
our	O
Office	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
her	O
down	O
so	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
private	O
boxes	O
;	O
I	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
Wilson	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sure	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
frequently	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
your	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
nails	O
and	O
every	O
other	O
description	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
one	O
duplicate	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
duplicate	O
was	O
to	O
Collins	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
shop	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
gown	O
or	O
petticoat	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pledged	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
intimated	O
the	O
circumstance	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Cureton	O
.	O
After	O
being	O
committed	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
re-examination	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
bed-furniture	O
was	O
pledged	O
at	O
Matthews	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
likewise	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
duplicates	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
fetched	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Solomons	O
,	O
the	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
duplicates	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
duplicates	O
were	O
for	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
Solomons	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
the	O
duplicate	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
a	O
summons	O
to	O
produce	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
these	O
duplicates	O
pointed	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
's	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SIMMONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
sheets	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
sheets	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
the	O
sheets	O
that	O
you	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
sheets	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
saw	O
your	O
bed-furniture	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
Matthews	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
bed-furniture	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
the	O
curtains	O
and	O
the	O
trimmings	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
clear	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
you	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
that	O
bed	O
furniture	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
to	O
speak	O
within	O
compass	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
a	O
deal	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
widow	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
380.	O
JOHN	B-pers
APLYN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
OWEN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
apartment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
shelf	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
bedroom	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
entered	O
his	O
bedroom	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
become	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
surprize	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
now	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
here	O
last	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
requested	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
foreigner	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
me	O
no	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pledged	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
it	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Brewer-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Brewer-street	O
;	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
pledged	O
for	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
duplicate	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
Owen	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
36	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
381.	O
MARY	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moxley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MOXLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brick-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
lodging	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
another	O
lodger	O
's	O
door	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
articles	O
which	O
are	O
in	O
another	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
delivered	O
up	O
both	O
the	O
keys	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
duplicate	O
for	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
from	O
that	O
same	O
man	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Fothergill	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MORRITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
two	O
sheets	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
certain	O
to	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Moxley	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
be	O
favourable	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
29	O
.	O
Confined	O
six	O
calendar	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
382.	O
MARY	B-pers
JASPER	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Chipperfield	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
CHIPPERFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
43	I-place
,	I-place
George's-court	I-place
,	I-place
Red	I-place
Lion-street	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
CHIPPERFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walk	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LAMSEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
shop	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Chipperfield	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
passed	O
by	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
person	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
so	O
gently	O
down	O
stairs	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
lap	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
