TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1806	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SIXTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	O
SHAW	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT	O
HAND	O
BY	O
JOB	O
SIBLY	O
,	O
FOR	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
1806	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	O
SHAW	O
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
LE	I-pers
BLANC	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALAN	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
Watkin	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
Harvey	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Combe	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Perring	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Smith	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Princep	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
Newman	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Boggis	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gast	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Brede	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Dolphin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Puckeridge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pikes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Evan	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
FIRST	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Manson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blease	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fyson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Senior	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lacomb	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fosbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Buckmaste	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ansley	I-pers
.	O
SECOND	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chaoman	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
Hulme	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
ton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sadford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ayre	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ashnell	I-pers
.	O
357.	O
MARY	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
tea	O
caddy	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
writing	O
desk	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
ink	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
lump	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
MACKENNA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
13	I-place
,	I-place
Finsbury	I-place
Square	I-place
.	O
Through	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
clerk	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
AUGUSTUS	I-pers
FRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
clerks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
back	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
bulky	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
another	O
clerk	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
speaking	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
lady	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
;	O
we	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
servants	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
different	O
ways	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
property	O
the	O
caddy	O
and	O
the	O
desk	O
were	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
the	O
person	O
whom	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
desk	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SNELL	I-pers
YOUNG	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
speaking	O
with	O
the	O
lady	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
lady	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
something	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
projecting	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicions	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
witness	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
missed	O
the	O
tea	O
caddy	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tea	O
caddy	O
and	O
the	O
writing	O
desk	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
Bishop	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
and	O
the	O
desk	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mackenna	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Mackenna	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
tea	O
caddy	O
immediately	O
the	O
alarm	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
she	O
morning	O
before	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
seals	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
W	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
a	O
wafer	O
stamp	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
the	O
whole	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
entirely	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
four	O
small	O
children	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
left	O
me	O
quite	O
in	O
distress	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
]	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
358.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HEWSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
five	O
pound	O
eight	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
flax	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
HENRY	B-pers
BASTIN	I-pers
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
YATES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Russia	O
merchant	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hewson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
as	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
servant	O
of	O
the	O
firm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
means	O
of	O
being	O
his	O
servant	O
had	O
he	O
access	O
to	O
your	O
flax	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
whenever	O
he	O
pleased	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
is	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
son	O
,	O
my	O
flax	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
wharf	O
at	O
Brown	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	I-place
Hermitage	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
caused	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hewson	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Pennington	O
street	O
,	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bastin	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
rags	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
three	O
farthings	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
elderly	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
jacket	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hewson	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
backward	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
wanting	O
to	O
go	O
backward	O
,	O
Bastin	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
her	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
Hewson	O
then	O
pulled	O
the	O
flax	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
jacket	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
;	O
Bastin	O
weighed	O
the	O
flax	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
Hewson	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
rags	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
Hewson	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
;	O
Bastin	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
Hewson	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
immediately	O
after	O
this	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bastin	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
some	O
flax	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
at	O
Bastin	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
livelihood	O
,	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Pennington	O
street	O
,	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
last	O
session	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
flax	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
ELLIOT	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
flax	O
dresser	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
Crown	O
court	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
said	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Bastin	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
Bastin	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
heads	O
of	O
Dutch	O
flax	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
;	O
Bastin	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
flax	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bastin	O
I	O
am	O
looking	O
for	O
some	O
property	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
something	O
here	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
barber	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
gone	O
somebody	O
has	O
thrown	O
this	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
property	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
my	O
son	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
son	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
flax	O
with	O
Bastin	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
:	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
these	O
heads	O
of	O
flax	O
were	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
could	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
from	O
any	O
person	O
throwing	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
placed	O
there	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
son	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
went	O
to	O
Hewson	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
directly	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
flax	O
was	O
not	O
your	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
this	O
rag	O
shop	O
is	O
like	O
all	O
other	O
rag	O
shops	O
,	O
an	O
open	O
rag	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
flax	O
away	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
whatever	O
suspicions	O
you	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
flax	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
returned	O
and	O
sent	O
your	O
son	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
was	O
time	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
flax	O
to	O
be	O
removed	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
there	O
might	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
distance	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
from	O
where	O
Bastin	O
lives	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
thirty	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
made	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
flax	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
STANLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
partner	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bastin	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Bastin	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
heads	O
of	O
flax	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
flax	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
property	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
examining	O
it	O
closely	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
match	O
with	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
information	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
afterwards	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
police	O
office	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
flax	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
largely	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
so	O
far	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
own	O
flax	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
possession	O
till	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
possession	O
till	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
JOHN	O
FOX	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Thames	O
police	O
officer	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hewson	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
first	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
'	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
police	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
flax	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
three	O
heads	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
and	O
my	O
partners	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
Dutch	O
flax	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
compared	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
flax	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agree	O
exactly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Hewson	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
HEWSON	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
67	O
.	O
Confined	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
BASTIN	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
359.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
RYAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
indictment	O
stated	O
that	O
she	O
at	O
the	O
general	O
quarter	O
sessions	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
forty-fifth	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
common	O
utterer	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sentenced	O
to	O
one	O
year	O
's	O
imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
sureties	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
unlawfully	O
did	O
utter	O
to	O
Isabella	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
money	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
sixpence	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
CALEB	B-pers
EDWARD	I-pers
POWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
solicitor	O
of	O
the	O
mint	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
produce	O
the	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
original	O
record	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Marlborough	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
convicted	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
in	O
April	O
1805	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sessions	O
there	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
her	O
person	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
the	O
trial	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
halfpence	O
to	O
produce	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
about	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
uttered	O
the	O
bad	O
sixpence	O
.	O
ISABELLA	O
BROWN	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
your	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
Poland	O
street	O
,	O
Oxford	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
her	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
half	O
a-pint	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
penny	O
farthing	O
,	O
she	O
tendered	O
me	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
that	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
sixpence	O
into	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
only	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
sixpence	O
into	O
your	O
pocket	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
witness	O
Foy	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
Foy	O
came	O
in	O
did	O
you	O
shew	O
Foy	O
the	O
sixpence	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
the	O
lady	O
gave	O
for	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
you	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
sixpence	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
sixpence	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
one	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
keep	O
the	O
sixpence	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
by	O
itself	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
.	O
Q.	O
Foy	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
sixpence	O
then	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Foy	O
at	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
had	O
been	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
attended	O
at	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
quite	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
sixpence	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
sixpence	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
to	O
Foy	O
at	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FOY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
on	O
this	O
day	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
speaking	O
of	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
where	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Portland-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
Poland-street	O
,	O
she	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Poland-street	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
putting	O
her	O
hands	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
walked	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Poland-street	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
out	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
enquired	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
there	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
produced	O
this	O
sixpence	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
this	O
sixpence	O
was	O
the	O
sixpence	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
sixpence	O
.	O
I	O
rubbed	O
the	O
sixpence	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
,	O
to	O
ascertain	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
marked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
by	O
itself	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
in	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
brown	O
paper	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
struggling	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
paper	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
contained	O
two	O
more	O
sixpences	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
produce	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
red	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
tooth	O
brush	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
thirteen	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
new	O
halfpence	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Jackson	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
good	O
copper	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
discourse	O
who	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
liked	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
rest	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
who	O
conducted	O
the	O
mint	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
I	O
received	O
that	O
sixpence	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
court	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
when	O
sentence	O
was	O
passed	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NICHOLL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
moniers	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mint	O
,	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
will	O
trouble	O
you	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
this	O
sixpence	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
good	O
or	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
sixpence	O
are	O
also	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
mixed	O
with	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
brass	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
silver	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
36	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
360.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JARRARD	I-pers
,	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ALTHORPE	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAXTER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Barnabas	B-pers
Carolan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
BARNABAS	B-pers
CAROLAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Holloway	B-place
,	O
laying	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
hay	O
stack	O
,	O
when	O
four	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
hay	O
stack	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
hay	O
stack	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
enclosed	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
paling	O
round	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
I	O
was	O
between	O
asleep	O
and	O
awake	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
woman	O
yourself	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bright	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
field	O
me	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
knees	O
on	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
trowsers	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
trowsers	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
canvas	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
in	O
penny	O
pieces	O
and	O
halfpence	O
,	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
trowsers	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
these	O
trowsers	O
you	O
put	O
under	O
your	O
head	O
.	O
A.Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
these	O
three	O
prisoners	O
were	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
stands	O
outside	O
took	O
the	O
trowsers	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
others	O
doing	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
one	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
talked	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
desired	O
no	O
name	O
to	O
be	O
expressed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
trowsers	O
what	O
did	O
they	O
do	O
next	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
said	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
good	O
piece	O
of	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
trowsers	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
doing	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
about	O
fifteen	O
minutes	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
talking	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
me	O
was	O
hurting	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
struggled	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
very	O
odious	O
expressions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
star	O
light	O
or	O
moon	O
light	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
moon	O
light	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
bright	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
their	O
faces	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
held	O
me	O
had	O
a	O
smock	O
frock	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
dressed	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
white	O
jacket	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
had	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
a	O
year	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
over	O
into	O
another	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
gathering	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
hay	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
meadows	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
follow	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
any	O
alarm	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
was	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
waiter	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
am	O
asking	O
of	O
them	O
three	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
big	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
hay	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sleeping	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
where	O
they	O
abused	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
robbed	O
me	O
while	O
you	O
held	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
they	O
wrought	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Small	O
's	O
that	O
lives	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
master	O
that	O
they	O
wrought	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
abused	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
justice	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Thursday	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
master's-yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
between	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
presume	O
that	O
you	O
(	O
from	O
your	O
dialect	O
)	O
are	O
an	O
Irish	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
work	O
at	O
one	O
place	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
understand	O
that	O
these	O
men	O
are	O
tried	O
for	O
their	O
lives	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
reward	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
told	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
for	O
my	O
loss	O
of	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
hay	O
yard	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
Irish	O
labourers	O
sleep	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
slept	O
there	O
besides	O
yourself	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
hay	O
that	O
saw	O
every	O
thing	O
they	O
did	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
you	O
in	O
taking	O
up	O
these	O
persons	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
These	O
men	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
from	O
the	O
Thursday	O
to	O
the	O
Monday	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
women	O
enough	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
yard	O
.	O
-	O
COX	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
conductors	O
of	O
the	O
patrole	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Baxter	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Jarrard	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Small	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
Althorpe	O
I	O
apprehended	O
in	O
a	O
foot	O
path	O
opposite	O
Mr	O
Small	O
's	O
gate	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
pointed	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Jarrard	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Althorpe	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Baxter	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
361.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	B-place
Four	I-place
Queen	I-place
's	I-place
Heads	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
received	O
some	O
information	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wished	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
lay	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
,	O
he	O
rather	O
hesitated	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pot	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
single	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
basket	O
containing	O
six	O
more	O
pots	O
belonging	O
to	O
different	O
publicans	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
pot	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
the	O
six	O
pots	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
coverered	O
over	O
with	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
pot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
basket	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Stewart	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
362.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
BEDFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wrighthorpe	B-place
's	I-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
Old	I-place
Gravel	I-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	O
the	O
East	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
as	O
lodgers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
your	O
own	O
family	O
consist	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Myself	O
and	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
then	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
house	O
with	O
only	O
three	O
rooms	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
and	O
the	O
top	O
room	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
to	O
Bow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
absent	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Till	O
near	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
both	O
my	O
room	O
doors	O
and	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
returned	O
did	O
you	O
return	O
alone	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
returned	O
with	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
she	O
would	O
meet	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shut	O
my	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
unlocked	O
my	O
lower	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
refreshment	O
;	O
after	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
lower	O
room	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
neighbours	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
somebody	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
top	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
did	O
you	O
perceive	O
any	O
alteration	O
.	O
-	O
A.	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Webb	I-pers
and	O
another	O
gentlewoman	O
ran	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
my	O
box	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
entirely	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
few	O
pieces	O
of	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
mode	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
pink	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
stockings	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
gown	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
French	I-pers
was	O
on	O
the	O
dark	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
head	O
against	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
are	O
you	O
courting	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
my	O
Bill	O
has	O
lost	O
his	O
ship	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
out	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
goodness	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
leave	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
her	O
daughter	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
is	O
your	O
mother	O
coming	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
I	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
particularly	O
my	O
dirty	O
shift	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
what	O
the	O
Hell	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
lost	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
your	O
green	O
gown	O
is	O
hanging	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
cupboard	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
abused	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
and	O
told	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
find	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
liquor	O
shop	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
dressed	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
dress	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
(	O
her	O
pockets	O
appeared	O
very	O
bulky	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
officer	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
turned	O
round	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
and	O
fainted	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
since	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
my	O
shift	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
pan	O
of	O
water	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
an	O
Irish	O
woman	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
daughter	O
mention	O
the	O
shift	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
two	O
Danes	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
board	O
a-ship	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
nights	O
before	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
police	O
office	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
place	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
shew	O
me	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
,	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
together	O
;	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bedstead	O
I	O
perceived	O
some	O
dirty	O
linen	O
,	O
under	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
hammer	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
jar	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
top	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
jar	O
I	O
perceived	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
drawers	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
foul	O
linen	O
;	O
it	O
smelled	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
hammer	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
with	O
the	O
claws	O
of	O
a	O
hammer	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
hammer	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
fitted	O
the	O
claws	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
corresponded	O
exactly	O
in	O
two	O
different	O
places	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
examined	O
the	O
door	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
the	O
claws	O
of	O
the	O
hammer	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
down	O
stairs	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
followed	O
us	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Palmer	O
came	O
over	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
hammer	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
borrowed	O
the	O
hammer	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
hammer	O
had	O
broken	O
open	O
this	O
box	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
box	O
,	O
hammer	O
,	O
and	O
shift	O
,	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
conversation	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
shift	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
state	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
make	O
awaywith	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
premises	O
again	O
at	O
her	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
premises	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
jar	O
where	O
the	O
soul	O
linen	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
shift	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
thigh	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flannel	O
drawers	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Webb	O
took	O
the	O
shift	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
knife	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
across	O
the	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Webb	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
clean	O
she	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
if	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
right	O
,	O
the	O
shift	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
thigh	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
trowsers	O
;	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
pitcher	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shift	O
lost	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
awkward	O
situation	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Irish	O
woman	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hands	O
in	O
,	O
it	O
smelt	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
round	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WEBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
right	O
opposite	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
;	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
abuse	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
the	O
green	O
gown	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
shift	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shift	O
out	O
and	O
washed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
30th	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
whatever	O
was	O
necessary	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
big	O
Irish	O
woman	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
bundle	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
I	O
received	O
of	O
the	O
Irishwoman	O
who	O
had	O
gone	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
this	O
pan	O
as	O
described	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
that	O
looked	O
like	O
drawers	O
,	O
it	O
smelt	O
so	O
bad	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
Brown	O
went-up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
dirty	O
shift	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
wet	O
disagreeable	O
state	O
(	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
shift	O
)	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
cut	O
this	O
mark	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
to	O
mark	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
stitched	O
some	O
yellow	O
thread	O
in	O
the	O
breast	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
clean	O
state	O
and	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
that	O
mark	O
you	O
find	O
there	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
you	O
made	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Exactly	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
also	O
the	O
yellow	O
thread	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
Irishwoman	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
shift	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
you	O
cut	O
a	O
mark	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
made	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
mark	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
for	O
my	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
43	O
,	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
,	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
'	O
door	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
hammer	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
borrowed	O
the	O
hammer	O
of	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
bedstead	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
her	O
husband	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
afterwards	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
proper	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
one	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
till	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shift	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
French	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
alarm	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
and	O
I	O
well	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
ever	O
since	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
people	O
sitting	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
left	O
her	O
nothing	O
,	O
what	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
they	O
left	O
you	O
nothing	O
,	O
why	O
the	O
green	O
gown	O
that	O
you	O
pulled	O
off	O
is	O
there	O
hanging	O
up	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
left	O
me	O
that	O
to	O
change	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
came	O
I	O
had	O
borrowed	O
a	O
washing	O
tub	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
stood	O
there	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
tub	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
this	O
jar	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Bedford	O
's	O
room	O
being	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
foreigners	O
that	O
slept	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
William	B-pers
French	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
hammer	O
that	O
is	O
produced	O
here	O
was	O
borrowed	O
to	O
mend	O
the	O
hinge	O
of	O
the	O
bedstead	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
French	I-pers
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BOTH	O
-	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
363.	O
MARY	B-pers
BLAKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
four	O
gold	O
watch	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tegg	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TEGG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Marylebone	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
passing	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
my	O
wife	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Marlborough	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
gold	O
keys	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LITTLEWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
an	O
umbrella	O
maker	O
in	O
Oxford	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
back	O
wards	O
and	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
four	O
gold	O
keys	O
and	O
one	O
seal	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tegg	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
articles	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
364.	O
MARY	B-pers
BLAKE	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
parasol	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
umbrella	O
shop	O
in	O
Oxford	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
parasols	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
one	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
the	O
remainder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
purchase	O
the	O
one	O
you	O
shewed	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
stairs	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
my	O
lad	O
was	O
gone	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
accused	O
her	O
of	O
taking	O
away	O
something	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Littlewood	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
gold	O
keys	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
parasol	O
from	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
wife	O
here	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
365.	O
ANN	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hat	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Union	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Marylebone	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
late	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
property	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
three	O
one	O
pound	O
notes	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
napkin	O
;	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
flannel	O
,	O
the	O
purse	O
had	O
the	O
three	O
guineas	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bank	O
notes	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
under	O
my	O
bed	O
on	O
Thursday	O
before	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
lives	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
besides	O
yourself	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
breaking	O
open	O
her	O
box	O
except	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
with	O
great	O
persuasion	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
flannel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
searched	O
without	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
flannel	O
,	O
I	O
wore	O
it	O
about	O
my	O
legs	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
living	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
four	O
years	O
as	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
these	O
flannels	O
were	O
hanging	O
on	O
the	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
kick	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
:	O
I	O
tore	O
my	O
clothes	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
and	O
these	O
flannels	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
trunk	O
ever	O
since	O
last	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
mad	O
and	O
jealous	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
366.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRITTEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Grain	I-pers
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
GRAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
to	O
rest	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
path	O
going	O
from	O
Brom	B-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
Old	I-place
Brentford	I-place
,	O
to	O
Ealing	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
walked	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rascal	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
eye	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
at	O
Brentford	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Quite	O
sober	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
my	O
case	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
poor	O
and	O
friendless	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
will	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
declare	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
367.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
CROSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Keef	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
violently	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Keef	I-pers
violently	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
did	O
ravish	O
and	O
carnally	O
know	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
368.	O
MARY	B-pers
MULLINS	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
RASBERRY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair	O
dresser	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Butcherhall	O
lane	O
,	O
Newgate	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Hammersmith	O
)	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
crossed	O
Fleet	B-place
market	I-place
to	O
Ludgate	O
hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Rasberry	O
and	O
Mullins	O
walking	O
together	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Rasberry	O
came	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
either	O
put	O
her	O
arms	O
round	O
me	O
or	O
forced	O
my	O
hands	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
directly	O
said	O
youhave	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
Mullins	O
ran	O
away	O
down	O
Fleet	O
market	O
;	O
Rasberry	O
says	O
,	O
Polly	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
served	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
Rasberry	O
called	O
out	O
Pretty	O
Polly	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
knew	O
who	O
Pretty	O
Polly	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
down	O
Fleet	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
but	O
Rasberry	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
I	O
care	O
,	O
you	O
stopped	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
keep	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
While	O
your	O
arms	O
was	O
so	O
pinioned	O
by	O
Rasberry	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Rasberry	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
she	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
property	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
.	O
Mullins	O
'	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
RASBERRY	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
MULLINS	O
-	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
369.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAWLINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
nine	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-pers
Company	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East	I-pers
Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
for	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NORDERBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
assistant-elder	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
company	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
Jewry-street	B-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
employed	O
in	O
their	O
service	O
for	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
past	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
,	O
I	O
rubbed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
taking	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
shaking	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Hyson	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
Lawrence	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
more	O
Hyson	O
tea	O
from	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
custom-house	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
and	O
breeches	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
tea	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Hyson	O
tea	O
,	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
lord	O
mayor	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
my	O
fault	O
;	O
I	O
maintained	O
my	O
character	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
employ	O
;	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
Confined	O
one	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
370.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MACDONALD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clitter	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CLITTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lion	O
,	O
Dean	O
street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
beer	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
.	O
DANIEL	O
POWEL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Queenhithe	O
ward	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Wright	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
using	O
her	O
ill	O
with	O
her	O
tongue	O
in	O
indecent	O
hours	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
basket	O
in	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
containing	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lion	O
,	O
Dean	O
street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
she	O
struggled	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Wright	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dropped	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
brought	O
in	O
ten	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
speak	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
Labour	O
in	O
Vain	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
come	O
home	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
abuse	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
basket	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
work	O
basket	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
it	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
basket	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BOURNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Queenhithe	O
ward	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
pots	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
an	O
iron	O
pot	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
solder	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
we	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
melting	O
pots	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Wright	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
basket	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
iron	O
pot	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rented	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
cleaned	O
that	O
pot	O
out	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
metal	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
metal	O
in	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pots	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Wright	O
twenty-four	O
years	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
always	O
good	O
friends	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
the	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
iron	O
pot	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
indeed	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
371.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lamb	B-place
farm	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surveyor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
Lamb	O
farm	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
Kingsland	O
and	O
Hackney	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
town	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Worship	O
street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
shewed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
being	O
a	O
dishonest	O
boy	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
SCULTHORPE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
Church	O
street	O
,	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
broken	O
in	O
three	O
parts	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
and	O
his	O
employer	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
lived	O
in	O
Hackney	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Brown	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
together	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
lived	O
some	O
distance	O
farther	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Worship	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
there	O
who	O
knew	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
very	O
quietly	O
to	O
the	O
Northumberland	O
Arms	O
in	O
Worship	O
street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Northumberland	O
Arms	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
Vickery	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
broken	O
spoon	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
lad	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
VICKERY	O
sworn	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
magistrate	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
pen	O
,	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
write	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
if	O
you	O
write	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
goes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Young	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Lamb	O
farm	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
spoon	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hog	O
tub	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
his	O
master	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
any	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
372.	O
ANN	B-pers
TYLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fetton	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
being	O
therein	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
five	O
silver	O
handled	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
seven	O
silver	O
handled	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cruets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Tellear	I-pers
,	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
three	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pocket	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dufour	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
DUFOUR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
6	I-place
,	I-place
Short	I-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Fetton	I-pers
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
to	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
particularly	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
double	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Ann	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
an	O
aged	O
mother	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
my	O
landlady	O
was	O
below	O
serving	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
my	O
front	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
push	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
unlocked	O
,	O
I	O
pushed	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
stamped	O
and	O
screamed	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Fetton	O
came-up	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
bring	O
somebody	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
shawl	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
the	O
publican	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
FETTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Fetton	I-pers
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
is	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
she	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
.	O
On	O
being	O
alarmed	O
by	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
sister	O
outside	O
holding	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
neighbours	O
were	O
alarmed	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
observed	O
any	O
body	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
somebody	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
an	O
apron	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
before	O
my	O
sister	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
HARRIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
on	O
hearing	O
the	O
alarm	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Dufour	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
holding	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
laying	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
silver	O
handled	O
knives	O
and	O
seven	O
silver	O
handled	O
forks	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stud	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
,	O
two	O
cruets	O
,	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
keys	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
MORGAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchhouse	O
keeper	O
,	O
theprisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
these	O
two	O
keys	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dufour	O
's	O
door	O
and	O
both	O
these	O
two	O
keys	O
opened	O
that	O
front	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
property	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
Mrs.	O
Dufour	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
OFFICER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
hearing	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Dufour	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
clothes	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
articles	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
Who	O
does	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
belong	O
to	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
belong	O
to	O
Francis	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Tellear	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
lodges	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
knife	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
cruets	O
,	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
sleeve	O
button	O
,	O
belong	O
also	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
are	O
mine	O
except	O
the	O
curtain	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
shawls	O
worth	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
this	O
petticoat	O
,	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
muslin	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
ROBERT	I-pers
TELLEAR	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
recommend	O
her	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
make	O
soldier	O
's	O
coats	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
these	O
people	O
's	O
stairs	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
old	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
it	O
lay	O
these	O
white	O
handled	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
whom	O
I	O
supposed	O
had	O
dropped	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
good	O
woman	O
in	O
black	O
came	O
in	O
apparently	O
with	O
some	O
steakes	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
door	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
blackguard	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
48	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
373.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Littlejohn	I-pers
,	O
violently	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
carnally	O
did	O
ravish	O
and	O
know	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
374.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
four	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pantaloons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Arms	I-place
,	I-place
Coal-yard	I-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
keeping	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
for	O
the	O
brewer	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
no	O
rent	O
,	O
nor	O
taxes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
afternoon	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
robbery	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
unfasten	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
afternoon	O
taken	O
the	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
brush	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
down	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
coats	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
coats	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
under	O
coats	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pantaloons	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
man	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Grey	O
,	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
got	O
my	O
pantaloons	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
prison	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
heard	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Grey	O
,	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pantaloons	O
on	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
FLEMING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
ticket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
coat	O
was	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
perfect	O
recollection	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
another	O
coat	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
exactly	O
recollect	O
the	O
pledging	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
pledged	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
Skinner-street	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pawned	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
bringing	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
hat	O
he	O
brought	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
coats	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pantaloons	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
before	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
overnight	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
resign	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
altogether	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
375.	O
LEWELLIN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
14.	O
a	O
plain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
chisels	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
locks	O
and	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
ladle	O
bowl	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
brass	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
gimblet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
files	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
hundred	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DAVIES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
John-street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
barwas	O
my	O
journeyman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
miss	O
any	O
tools	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
obtained	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
St.	O
John-street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
he	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HANCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
premises	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
property	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
saw	O
pledged	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
's	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
He	O
applied	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
loan	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
refused	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
this	O
gentleman	O
above	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
tools	O
;	O
his	O
tools	O
and	O
my	O
tools	O
I	O
carried	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
sometimes	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
wanted	O
them	O
we	O
fetched	O
them	O
.	O
we	O
used	O
each	O
other	O
's	O
tools	O
,	O
his	O
tools	O
were	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
some	O
tools	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
some	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
very	O
imprudent	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
his	O
not	O
lending	O
me	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
376.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
ENGLISH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
eight	O
loaves	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lindoras	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LINDORAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
loose	O
any	O
bread	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Oxford	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
from	O
the	O
basket	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
loaf	O
and	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
bill	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
basket	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
bread	O
or	O
your	O
basket	O
again	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
suffered	O
your	O
bread	O
to	O
remain	O
exposed	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
you	O
being	O
absent	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MARKHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
Oxford	O
street	O
when	O
Lindoras	O
lost	O
his	O
bread	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
set	O
the	O
basket	O
down	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
pass	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
from	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
enquiring	O
for	O
work	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hollis	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
English	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
first	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Oxford	O
street	O
into	O
Hollis	O
street	O
,	O
they	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
Cavendish	O
square	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Lindoras	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
both	O
journeymen	O
bakers	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
you	O
know	O
Hopkins	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
journeyman	O
baker	O
,	O
Hopkins	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
Hollis	O
street	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
perhaps	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
more	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
besides	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
LINDSEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cavendish	O
square	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Mortimer	O
street	O
;	O
Thomas	O
Hopkins	O
had	O
a	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
quartern	O
bricks	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
were	O
they	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
several	O
yards	O
behind	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
377.	O
MARY	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Curling	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CURLING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
yellow	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
hang	O
below	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
robbed	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
shift	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
hanging	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
42	O
.	O
Privately	O
Whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
378.	O
JUDITH	B-pers
LOW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
KELLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
slop	O
and	O
sale	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
her	O
nephew	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
boots	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
moved	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
she	O
first	O
stood	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
where	O
this	O
gown	O
hung	O
;	O
a	O
short	O
interval	O
of	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
I	O
noticed	O
her	O
staying	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
bought	O
the	O
boots	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
