TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1806	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SECOND	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT	O
HAND	O
BY	O
JOB	O
SIBLY	O
,	O
FOR	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
By	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
1806	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
MACDONALD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
SOULDEN	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ALAN	B-pers
CHAMBRE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
Watkin	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Harvey	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Combe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Perring	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prinsep	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
Newman	B-pers
Knowlys	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Ezra	B-pers
Levermore	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Peppercorn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Moffat	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brogden	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kasent	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Peele	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Erwood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hose	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lockit	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Vince	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jessop	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Crump	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Younie	I-pers
,	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Few	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Pile	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Murril	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
76.	O
MARY	B-pers
BENNET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HIGGINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
working	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
2	I-place
,	I-place
Willow	I-place
Walk	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
white	O
cambric	O
muslin	O
gown	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
perceived	O
my	O
muslin	O
gown	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
through	O
her	O
pocket-hole	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
gown	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
knowing	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
that	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
gown	O
ever	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PUTTIFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
Grub-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
her	O
bonnet-box	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
cambric	O
muslin	O
gown	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
her	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
spite	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
44	O
.	O
Confined	O
Six	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
77.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRYCE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
canvas	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
laying	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
and	O
Dennis	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
and	O
Co.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
any	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
October	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
any	O
canvas	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Castle	O
Lee	O
canvas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
peculiar	O
colour	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
here	O
to	O
shew	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
from	O
any	O
other	O
cloth	O
made	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
manufacturer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
foreman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
the	O
warehouse	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
27th	O
and	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
Wapping	B-place
Wall	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
canvas	O
in	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Castle	O
Lee	O
canvas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
them	O
pieces	O
taken	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
warehouse	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Thames	O
police	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
and	O
measured	O
it	O
with	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
canvas	O
that	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
Castle	O
Lee	O
was	O
cut	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
2996	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
number	O
that	O
is	O
put	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
excise	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
police	O
office	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bryce	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
tallow	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
bolts	O
of	O
canvas	O
that	O
were	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
remnants	O
were	O
laying	O
alongside	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
apparently	O
cut	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
bolt	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
the	O
magistrate	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
while	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
ask	O
Bryce	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
objection	O
to	O
your	O
searching	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
say	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
canvas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Watson	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
examined	O
them	O
pieces	O
of	O
canvas	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
measured	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
corresponds	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
canvas	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
measure	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
measured	O
thirty-nine	O
yards	O
each	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
remnant	O
,	O
I	O
chalked	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
erased	O
by	O
being	O
handled	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
?	O
A.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
my	O
belief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
canvas	O
that	O
you	O
lent	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
belief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
belief	O
only	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Castle	O
Lee	O
fell	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
canvas	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
thirty-nine	O
yards	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
bolt	O
;	O
but	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
circumstance	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
we	O
bought	O
the	O
canvas	O
off	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
quaker	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
the	O
London	O
number	O
of	O
their	O
stamp	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
books	O
what	O
canvas	O
we	O
buy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
shewed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
all	O
bolts	O
of	O
canvas	O
run	O
nearly	O
those	O
yards	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
run	O
from	O
thirty-nine	O
to	O
forty	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
anything	O
particularly	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
In	O
respect	O
to	O
my	O
stealing	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
stole	O
an	O
article	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
of	O
Captain	O
Sharp	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
traded	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
soap	O
and	O
candles	O
;	O
unfortunately	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
up	O
the	O
Straits	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bring	O
him	O
forward	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
.	O
78.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRYER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
seven	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
four	O
pound	O
eight	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Devey	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
Devey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Devey	I-pers
.	O
ROGER	B-pers
DEVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass	O
founder	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
18	I-place
,	I-place
Shoe-lane	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
your	O
partners	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Roger	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
Devey	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Devey	I-pers
.	O
From	O
information	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
my	O
men	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
breakfast	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
]	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
metal	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
skirts	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
his	O
pockets	O
loaded	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
metal	O
by	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
the	O
ingot	O
piece	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
pointed	O
to	O
his	O
stomach	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
ingot	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
his	O
stomach	O
,	O
the	O
prince	O
's	O
metal	O
was	O
principally	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
pieces	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
set	O
the	O
value	O
,	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
more	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Devey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
metal	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
premises	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
eight	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
metal	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
inside	O
and	O
outside	O
pockets	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
metal	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
metal	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
was	O
the	O
metal	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
premises	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
cut	O
off	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
masters	O
.	O
-	O
TEMPLEMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
metal	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
four	O
children	O
,	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
Gaol	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
79.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DUNGWORTH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
term	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ALPORT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
certificate	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Shelton	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
certificate	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
certify	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
gaol	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
42d	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
before	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
justices	O
then	O
present	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dungworth	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Marylebone	O
,	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
labourer	O
,	O
otherwise	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
in	O
due	O
form	O
of	O
law	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
upon	O
a	O
certain	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
42d	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
one	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
night	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
pin	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
night-caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dungworth	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Thomas	O
Powell	O
,	O
was	O
thereupon	O
ordered	O
and	O
adjudged	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
beyond	O
the	O
seas	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
such	O
place	O
as	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
his	O
privy	O
counsel	O
should	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
declare	O
and	O
appoint	O
,	O
Dated	O
January	O
1	O
,	O
1806	O
,	O
signed	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Alpoat	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
tried	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
court	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
just	O
read	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
turnkey	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
being	O
at	O
large	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bow-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
December	O
,	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
about	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bow-street	B-place
,	O
just	O
going	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
Piazza	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
large	O
and	O
at	O
liberty	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
29	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
80.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
CARROL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Chilvers	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
cookery	O
instrument	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Chilvers	I-pers
,	O
one	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scizzars	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
chisel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
marking	O
instrument	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
CHILVERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Coach	I-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
,	I-place
Grovesnor-square	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
quartered	O
upon	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
did	O
he	O
sleep	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
attic	O
story	O
;	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
fortwo	O
watchmen	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Chilvers	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
bed	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
two	O
clothes	O
brushes	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
lodge	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
these	O
articles	O
that	O
you	O
found	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
underneath	O
the	O
mattress	O
upon	O
the	O
sacking	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Smith	O
was	O
written	O
upon	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
dark	O
velveteen	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
lodging	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
two	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
articles	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Five	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
dark	O
velveteen	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
small	O
articles	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MORTIMER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
trunk	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Chilvers	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
locked	O
and	O
corded	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
scissars	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
chisel	O
,	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stamp	O
.	O
RACHAEL	B-pers
LONGWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
an	O
armourer	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
evening	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
lodgings	O
for	O
his	O
order	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
guard	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
the	O
chair	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
bundle	O
till	O
Christmas	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
husband	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
the	O
pay	O
serjeant	O
,	O
the	O
bundle	O
contained	O
a	O
fustian	O
jacket	O
,	O
a	O
nankeen	O
jacket	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MURRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
bundle	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Longwell	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
armourer	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
two	O
jackets	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
articles	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
looking	O
glasses	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
brass	O
cookery	O
instrument	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
marking	O
stamp	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
broke	O
,	O
as	O
your	O
lordship	O
sees	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
chisel	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
laying	O
on	O
Smith	O
's	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
from	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
two	O
brushes	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
this	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
velveteen	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Smith	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
screw	O
that	O
fastened	O
the	O
padlock	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
off	O
by	O
some	O
instrument	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
lower	O
drawers	O
in	O
Smith	O
's	O
room	O
were	O
forced	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
scissars	O
and	O
the	O
chisel	O
to	O
the	O
drawers	O
that	O
were	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
fit	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
drawers	O
that	O
were	O
cut	O
;	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
cut	O
terribly	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
witnesses	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witness	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
,	O
aged	O
29	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
81.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
FLETCHER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
upon	O
Margaret	B-pers
Croydon	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
counterpane	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
value	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	B-pers
Croydon	I-pers
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
CROYDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
coming	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Bream	O
's	O
Buildings	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Little	O
Coram-street	O
,	O
Russel-square	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Guilford-street	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
opposite	O
of	O
the	O
Foundling	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
bundle	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
knocked	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
snatched	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
distinctly	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
under	O
your	O
arm	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
condition	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
observation	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
or	O
dress	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
Stop	O
thief	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
direction	O
did	O
he	O
run	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
towards	O
Guildford	O
Place	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
strait	O
forward	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
that	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Guildford-street	O
.	O
Some	O
persons	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
court	O
heard	O
me	O
cry	O
out	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
early	O
part	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
returning	O
home	O
from	O
Lamb's-conduit	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
call	O
out	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
Guildford	O
Place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Guildford	O
Place	O
a	O
square	O
or	O
a	O
street	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
joins	O
Lamb's-conduit-street	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
street	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
houses	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
towards	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
neighbours	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
of	O
us	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
course	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
strait	O
down	O
Guildford-street	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
or	O
how	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
stepped	O
over	O
it	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watchouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
set	O
about	O
pursuing	O
him	O
after	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
obstructed	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Foundling	O
wall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
that	O
interruption	O
continue	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
had	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
could	O
see	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
opportunity	O
of	O
observing	O
his	O
dress	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
a	O
cloudy	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
moon	O
was	O
shining	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
bright	O
.	O
MATHEW	B-pers
MURPHY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watchbox	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
directly	O
towards	O
Guildford	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
catch	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
past	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
he	O
see	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
attempting	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
halloed	O
out	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
behind	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
is	O
this	O
from	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
lane	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
far	O
distant	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
turnings	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
servant	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
family	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
waiting	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
moment	O
that	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
family	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
scuffile	O
of	O
taking	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
blow	O
upon	O
the	O
nose	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
effusion	O
of	O
blood	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
yourself	O
struck	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
my	O
nose	O
bled	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemanthat	O
employed	O
me	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
.	O
Murphy	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JESSOP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
assisted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
A.	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
Heron	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
You	O
have	O
told	O
us	O
what	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
your	O
bundle	O
,	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
yours	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
bundle	O
that	O
was	O
snatched	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
table	O
cloth	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
sheets	O
,	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
note	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
only	O
pinned	O
,	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DAWES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
Fox's-court	O
,	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
lane	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
generally	O
shut	O
up	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
on	O
other	O
nights	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
shuts	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
road	O
from	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
understand	O
.	O
Is	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
the	O
direct	O
road	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
from	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
that	O
road	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ECTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Slade	O
,	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
pay-table	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Rising	O
Sun	O
,	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
direct	O
road	O
to	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
lane	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
the	O
strait	O
way	O
from	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
to	O
Gray's-inn	O
lane	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
answer	O
that	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
direct	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
Carolina	O
Place	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
pay-table	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
down	O
Guildford-street	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
my	O
landlady	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
.	O
82.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
MAZZONI	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Egyptian	O
plaster	O
figure	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
two	O
plaister	O
figures	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
statuary	O
and	O
mason	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
162	I-place
,	I-place
Sloane-street	I-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1804	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
situation	O
was	O
he	O
employed	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
journeyman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
authority	O
from	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
,	O
not	O
even	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
loose	O
these	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
;	O
these	O
articles	O
are	O
,	O
the	O
cobler	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Egyptian	O
mummy	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
eleven	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
last	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
figures	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Sloane-street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
brought	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
mistake	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cobler	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
is	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mummy	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
standing	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
bust	O
of	O
Homer	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
to	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
before	O
your	O
servant	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
sold	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
cobler	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
or	O
the	O
mummy	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
warrant	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
surrendered	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
describe	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
the	O
marks	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
two	O
crosses	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
mark	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
each	O
about	O
eleven	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
own	O
dwelling-house	O
that	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Const	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
I	O
understand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
business	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
account	O
entirely	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
man	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
gave	O
him	O
twenty-eight	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
thirty	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
task	O
work	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
rather	O
low	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
nothing	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
wages	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
your	O
debtor	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
every	O
farthing	O
that	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
generally	O
over	O
drew	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
fact	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
disatisfied	O
with	O
his	O
conduct	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
owes	O
me	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
make	O
a	O
demand	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
ever	O
employ	O
an	O
attorney	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
196	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
make	O
a	O
public	O
charge	O
against	O
him	O
previous	O
to	O
his	O
leaving	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
depended	O
too	O
much	O
upon	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Had	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
dealt	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
for	O
figures	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
demand	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
attorney	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
discharge	O
him	O
or	O
he	O
leave	O
your	O
service	O
voluntarily	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
figures	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
made	O
this	O
demand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
prosecute	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
errand	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
small	O
figures	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
drawing	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Egyptian	O
figure	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
laid	O
claim	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
figures	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
word	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
respectable	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
)	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
We	O
understand	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Sloane-street	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
that	O
are	O
now	O
produced	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
purchased	O
them	O
of	O
Mazzoni	O
.	O
I	O
purchased	O
the	O
cobler	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
Mazzoni	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
makes	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mazzoni	O
,	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bust	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
bronzed	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
reply	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
figures	O
,	O
describing	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
demur	O
at	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
shop	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
home	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
figure	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
Mazzoni	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
figures	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
figures	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
cobler	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
my	O
proposal	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
or	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
the	O
figures	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mazzoni	O
told	O
me	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
dry	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
bronze	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
Hamilton	O
at	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
hear	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
large	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
never	O
moved	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
the	O
large	O
mummy	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
purchased	O
a	O
bust	O
of	O
Homer	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mazzoni	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Sloane-street	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
stand	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
stand	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
charge	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
twenty-nine	O
or	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
different	O
times	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
shop	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
servant	O
called	O
Mazzoni	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
once	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
Mazzoni	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
down	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
stand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
either	O
about	O
the	O
cobler	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
or	O
the	O
mummy	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
employing	O
his	O
father	O
near	O
seventeen	O
years	O
to	O
some	O
considerable	O
amount	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
yard	O
one	O
time	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
rude	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
shy	O
with	O
Young	O
Hamilton	O
after	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
cobler	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
you	O
by	O
Mazzoni	O
by	O
an	O
order	O
which	O
you	O
gave	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
that	O
mummy	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
mummy	O
was	O
making	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
as	O
you	O
had	O
done	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
see	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
must	O
,	O
Mazzoni	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
converse	O
together	O
in	O
whispers	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
By	O
no	O
means	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
figure	O
,	O
and	O
Mazzoniwas	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
bronzing	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
dry	O
enough	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
Mazzoni	O
's	O
conduct	O
that	O
appeared	O
he	O
was	O
telling	O
any	O
thing	O
secret	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
considered	O
him	O
the	O
principal	O
in	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Hamilton	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
branch	O
of	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
Hamilton	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
account	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
Mazzoni	O
was	O
there	O
Hamilton	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
fitted	O
out	O
as	O
a	O
mason	O
's	O
with	O
marble	O
chimney	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
Hamilton	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
examined	O
at	O
Marlborough-street	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
could	O
be	O
his	O
motive	O
in	O
taking	O
these	O
steps	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
reply	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
bill	O
above	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
what	O
could	O
he	O
do	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
employment	O
did	O
you	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
under	O
Hamilton	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
making	O
these	O
figures	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
should	O
engage	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
first	O
connection	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
was	O
through	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
repeatedly	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
leave	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
in	O
partnership	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
to	O
work	O
as	O
journeyman	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
partnership	O
I	O
would	O
leave	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
;	O
under	O
that	O
colour	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
previous	O
to	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
met	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
in	O
Sloane-street	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
bronze	O
a	O
head	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
bronzed	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
like	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
figures	O
,	O
the	O
cobler	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
moulds	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
bought	O
the	O
moulds	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Blore	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
deal	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
executed	O
the	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
ordered	O
the	O
mummy	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
cast	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
shop	O
when	O
Mazzoni	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
stand	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
large	O
figure	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
recollection	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
shop	O
along	O
with	O
Mazzoni	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
conversation	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chambre	O
.	O
83.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NICHOLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
being	O
such	O
servant	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
one	O
bushel	O
of	O
beans	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
master	O
,	O
fraudulently	O
did	O
embezzle	O
,	O
secrete	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
only	O
varying	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
charging	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
CARELESS	I-pers
WEBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
carter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
my	O
team	O
to	O
fetch	O
corn	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
cornchandler	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
dealt	O
in	O
Oxford-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kilburn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
so	O
employed	O
by	O
you	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
consumption	O
of	O
corn	O
in	O
the	O
early	O
part	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
suspicion	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
something	O
was	O
wrong	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
beans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
chaff	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
usual	O
quantity	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
about	O
once	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
since	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
particular	O
written	O
order	O
each	O
time	O
;	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
team	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
back	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
chaff	O
,	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
beans	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
beans	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
order	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
had	O
no	O
beans	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
any	O
beans	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
;	O
being	O
surprised	O
at	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
parlour	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
minute	O
in	O
my	O
day	O
book	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
not	O
receiving	O
any	O
beans	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
finding	O
no	O
beans	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
for	O
my	O
bill	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
having	O
brought	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
and	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
chaff	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
written	O
order	O
for	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
beans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
chaff	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
question	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
had	O
no	O
beans	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
man	O
stated	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
beans	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
neverhad	O
any	O
beans	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Pinner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
him	O
in	O
Marybone	O
watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
with	O
any	O
order	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
kept	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
recollect	O
his	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
each	O
time	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
chaff	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
beans	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
they	O
accuse	O
me	O
of	O
is	O
quite	O
wrong	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
that	O
job	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
.	O
84.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
twopence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Kenny	I-pers
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
KENNY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Yorkshire	I-place
Grey	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
King's-road	I-place
,	I-place
Gray's-inn-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
I	O
applied	O
for	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
trunks	O
,	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
clean	O
shirt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
another	O
shirt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
trunk	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
at	O
Hatton-garden	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
two	O
chests	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
officers	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
chest	O
;	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
first	O
chest	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
from	O
the	O
mark	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
one	O
pound	O
bank	O
note	O
was	O
found	O
laying	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
that	O
bank	O
note	O
before	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
that	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
one	O
shirt	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
know	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
close	O
examination	O
,	O
I	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
almost	O
taken	O
the	O
mark	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Two	O
days	O
afterwards	O
I	O
brought	O
Stanton	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
last	O
shirt	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Cross-Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
are	O
both	O
carpenters	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
both	O
work	O
for	O
Messrs.	O
Wig	O
and	O
Mansfield	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
people	O
of	O
respectability	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
discharged	O
from	O
their	O
service	O
since	O
you	O
made	O
this	O
accusation	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
always	O
mark	O
your	O
notes	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
spare	O
note	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
accordingly	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
these	O
notes	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
communicated	O
your	O
loss	O
to	O
your	O
fellow	O
lodger	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
privately	O
,	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
note	O
before	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
warrant	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
accuse	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
mention	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
your	O
first	O
shirt	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
lost	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
every	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
week	O
after	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
another	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
every	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
heard	O
of	O
that	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
your	O
loss	O
must	O
be	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
quarrel	O
before	O
you	O
made	O
this	O
accusation	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
remember	O
bringing	O
some	O
window	O
lead	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
which	O
was	O
common	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
complaint	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
was	O
common	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
clothes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
clothes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
key	O
of	O
that	O
chest	O
was	O
always	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
these	O
shirts	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
your	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
shirts	O
in	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
magistrate	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
aked	O
some	O
questions	O
about	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
you	O
might	O
put	O
some	O
clothes	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
chest	O
in	O
which	O
these	O
shirts	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
clothes	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
But	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
warrant	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
taking	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
shirts	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
lost	O
the	O
note	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STANTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Hancock	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
chest	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shirt	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
claimed	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
directly	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
behind	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
First	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
shirt	O
Stanton	O
took	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
shirt	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
D.	O
K	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
the	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
in	O
red	O
ink	O
,	O
in	O
full	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
shirt	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
may	O
be	O
dimly	O
seen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
4793	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Stanton	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
number	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
ROSOMON	B-pers
MYERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
wash	O
the	O
linen	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Denny	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
shirt	O
that	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
almost	O
rubbed	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
shirt	O
was	O
in	O
King	O
's	O
bundle	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
washed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
in	O
King	O
's	O
bundle	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
their	O
linen	O
was	O
tied	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
of	O
course	O
that	O
red	O
ink	O
will	O
wash	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
that	O
is	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
of	O
one	O
article	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
chest	O
till	O
near	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
in	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
putting	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
linen	O
and	O
his	O
clothes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
landlady	O
said	O
that	O
Kenny	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
girls	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suppose	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
shirts	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
85.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PRIOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
cambric	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
warehouse	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
?	O
-	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
85	I-place
,	I-place
Watling-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Manchester	O
warehouse	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
shutting	O
the	O
door	O
firmly	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
inner	O
door	O
fastened	O
by	O
jamming	O
very	O
tight	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
spring	O
lock	O
nor	O
latch	O
to	O
that	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
I	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
91	O
,	O
Watling-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
proceeding	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
day-light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
features	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
supposing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
lamps	O
or	O
candles	O
in	O
the	O
windows	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
white	O
goods	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
dragged	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
alone	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
one	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
observing	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
running	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
goods	O
still	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
about	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
premises	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
claimed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
's	O
warehouseman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
WOODBRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
goods	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
thegoods	O
back	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
piled	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
the	O
door	O
have	O
been	O
left	O
a	O
jar	O
,	O
by	O
somebody	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
left	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
but	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
went	O
out	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
minutes	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
does	O
not	O
latch	O
,	O
it	O
fastens	O
very	O
tight	O
,	O
it	O
requires	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
force	O
to	O
push	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
piece	O
besides	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
piece	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
was	O
partly	O
in	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
out	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
pieces	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
's	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Woodbridge	O
)	O
Are	O
they	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
goods	O
,	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cambric	O
muslin	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
not	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
this	O
parcel	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Of	O
Stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
only	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
86.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHURCHILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
KNOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
30	I-place
,	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
we	O
are	O
slop-seller	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
loose	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
our	O
service	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
stopped	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
warehouse	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
from	O
information	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
particularly	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
au	O
article	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
by	O
fair	O
means	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
satisfy	O
myself	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
warehouse	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
first	O
be	O
satisfied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
them	O
about	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
apparently	O
from	O
the	O
forepart	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
could	O
he	O
earn	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
standing	O
wages	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
besides	O
an	O
handsome	O
acknowledgement	O
at	O
Christmas	O
;	O
his	O
pay	O
was	O
constant	O
,	O
whether	O
ill	O
or	O
well	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
TILER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
trowsers	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
ours	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
trowsers	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
one	O
hand	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
use	O
at	O
this	O
present	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
51	O
.	O
Whipped	O
in	O
Gaol	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
87.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BOYNTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
five	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Phil	B-place
's	I-place
Buildings	I-place
,	I-place
Hounsditch	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
side	O
carpet	O
on	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
underneath	O
the	O
carpet	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
contained	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
duplicates	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
whose	O
property	O
these	O
duplicates	O
related	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
meant	O
to	O
replace	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Forrester	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
duplicates	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Lambeth-street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Baylis	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
about	O
forty-six	O
duplicates	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
duplicates	O
.	O
-	O
YOUNG	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
of	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
frequented	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
REECE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
gown	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
lend	O
her	O
that	O
gown	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
88.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
KIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
HEWITT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Castle	O
at	O
Moorgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
pots	O
from	O
the	O
manufactory	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
;	O
the	O
pot	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
VAUGHAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
,	O
mangle	O
manufacturer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
had	O
suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
Batho	O
the	O
constable	O
followed	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hewitt	O
's	O
directions	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
pot	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hewitt	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
bent	O
quite	O
flat	O
.	O
-	O
BATHO	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
pots	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
pot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
89.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
KIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
five	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
KNIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Golden	O
Hind	O
,	O
Little	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
serve	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
manufactory	O
with	O
beer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Having	O
frequently	O
lost	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
pot	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
pots	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hewitt	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
there	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HANCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
in	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Mitchell	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
we	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
three	O
pots	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Vaughan	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Batho	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
his	O
lodgings	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
90.	O
MARY	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HAYWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tailor	O
and	O
salesman	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
rather	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
seeing	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
run	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
mind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
cloak	O
of	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pinned	O
a	O
few	O
inches	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
string	O
went	O
over	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
-	O
TURNER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
waistcoat	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Barbican	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
women	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
court	O
and	O
dropped	O
that	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
What	O
pace	O
was	O
she	O
walking	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Very	O
quick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
by	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Positively	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
suspicion	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
91.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
sixty	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
96	I-place
,	I-place
Fore-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
employ	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
the	O
halfpence	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
I	O
had	O
suspicions	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
several	O
papers	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
some	O
half-crown	O
papers	O
,	O
some	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
one	O
half-crown	O
paper	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
paper	O
might	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
having	O
wrapped	O
up	O
halfpence	O
in	O
this	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
half-crowns	O
tied	O
in	O
such	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
such	O
paper	O
as	O
all	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
use	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
all	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
buy	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
other	O
cheesemongers	O
buy	O
all	O
sorts	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
you	O
can	O
say	O
merely	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
wrapped	O
up	O
some	O
halfpence	O
in	O
some	O
waste	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
paper	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
description	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
paper	O
is	O
yours	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
other	O
papers	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
correspond	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
kind	O
of	O
paper	O
was	O
laying	O
about	O
your	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
therefore	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
any	O
purpose	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HEDGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
paper	O
parcels	O
of	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
parcel	O
of	O
copper	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
he	O
unlocked	O
the	O
box	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
strange	O
of	O
him	O
having	O
this	O
quantity	O
of	O
halfpence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
on	O
business	O
for	O
himself	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
in	O
payment	O
;	O
the	O
master	O
said	O
then	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
tie	O
up	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
pounds	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
parcels	O
was	O
the	O
parcel	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Judgment	O
respited	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
92.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOROUGHS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
broach	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Star	I-place
and	I-place
Garter	I-place
in	I-place
Panton-street	I-place
;	O
John	B-pers
Boroughs	I-pers
was	O
quartered	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Having	O
lost	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas	O
night	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
marked	O
dollar	O
in	O
my	O
breches	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
broach	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
bed-room	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
run	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
dollar	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
dollar	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
broach	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
regiment	O
does	O
he	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
drum	O
boy	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLEMENTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
dollar	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
dollar	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
an	O
hammer	O
.	O
MORGAN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
broach	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
four-shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
broach	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
dollar	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
broach	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
nobody	O
enquired	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
13	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
93.	O
MARY	B-pers
BURCHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
neck	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
PHOEBE	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
,	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
from	O
the	B-place
Bull	I-place
and	I-place
Gate	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
in	O
Grace-church-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Windsor	O
.	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
coachman	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
with	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
nine	O
shifts	O
,	O
nine	O
gowns	O
,	O
thirteen	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
four	O
white	O
petticoats	O
,	O
one	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
six	O
neck	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
white	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
white	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
neck	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
guard	O
of	O
a	O
mail	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
they	O
slept	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
till	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
clothes	O
might	O
remain	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
I	O
shall	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
before	O
it	O
is	O
dark	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
not	O
Phoebe	O
?	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
things	O
themselves	O
,	O
being	O
dusk	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
whether	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hackney-coachman	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
came	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
her	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RIMINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
to	O
Holborn	O
from	O
the	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
that	O
comes	O
with	O
the	O
Boston	O
coach	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Windsor	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Gerard's-hall	O
,	O
Basing-lane	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SUDBURY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
property	O
I	O
produce	O
at	O
Gerard's-hall	O
,	O
Basing-lane	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
Windsor	O
coach	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
RUSSEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
turnkey	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry	O
compter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
custody	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
locked	O
her	O
up	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
this	O
property	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
her	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
finding	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
box	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
,	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
Now	O
look	O
at	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
yours	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
person	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
walk	O
London	O
streets	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
character	O
at	O
Feversham	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
a	O
mother	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
blackguard	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
putting	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
.	O
94.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WEEDON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
seventy-two	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
.	O
NEEDLER	B-pers
GREENFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
at	O
Tooting	O
in	O
Surrey	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
calf	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
in	O
Leadenhall	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
calf	O
was	O
slaughtered	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
chopped	O
down	O
in	O
two	O
sides	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
weighed	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
's	O
man	O
put	O
a	O
ticket	O
on	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
employed	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
cart	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
standing	O
very	O
near	O
the	B-place
Spread	I-place
Eagle	I-place
in	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
our	O
lad	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
veal	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
at	O
Lambeth-street	O
office	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
ticket	O
was	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
breast	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
veal	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
matched	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NOWLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
police	O
officer	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
side	O
of	O
veal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
the	O
veal	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
anybody	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nobody	O
but	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
veal	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
veal	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
At	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Greenfield	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
he	O
examined	O
it	O
with	O
another	O
breast	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
of	O
veal	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
veal	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Julian	O
's	O
,	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
this	O
side	O
there	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Nowland	O
knows	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
rent	O
them	O
rooms	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
that	O
Merrick	O
rents	O
them	O
two	O
rooms	O
.	O
NOWLAND	O
.	O
Merrick	O
rents	O
the	O
two	O
rooms	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
back-room	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
Merrick	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
95.	O
ANN	B-pers
BARRET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FOWLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
rooms	O
.	O
She	O
missed	O
some	O
sheets	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
sheets	O
to	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
without	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
leave	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
lived	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
things	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
fetched	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
vast	O
number	O
of	O
duplicates	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
duplicates	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
of	O
sheets	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bunch	I-place
of	I-place
Grapes	I-place
,	I-place
Albemarle-street	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
.	O
JANE	B-pers
FOWLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
publican	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
sheets	O
from	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
knowing	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
she	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
