TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1806	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT	O
HAND	O
BY	O
JOB	O
SIBLY	O
,	O
FOR	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
BUTTERS	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
1806	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	O
GROSE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
Glynn	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowcroft	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Hankey	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Domville	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
Newman	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bagnell	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodall	I-pers
,	O
Harry	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lefevre	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bethel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
FIRST	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Buddle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Elsdon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Handy	I-pers
.	O
SECOND	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godbolt	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Tray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prudence	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Bier	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Seward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
312.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BASSET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ibbett	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
IBBETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ibbett	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
8	I-place
,	I-place
Church	I-place
Row	I-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
;	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
funeral	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
three	O
blankets	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
bed	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
found	O
your	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
after	O
the	O
blankets	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
from	O
work	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
you	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
paid	O
regularly	O
for	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
beds	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
beds	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
people	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
mostly	O
had	O
a	O
bed	O
to	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
asked	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
blankets	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
blankets	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
complained	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
cold	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CASTLETINE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Ibbett	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
funeral	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
.	O
(	O
witness	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
opposite	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ibbetts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
holes	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
large	O
might	O
the	O
bundle	O
be	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
this	O
size	O
.	O
(	O
witness	O
extending	O
her	O
arms	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
in	O
length	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
in	O
width	O
.	O
)	O
PATRICK	B-pers
MACKCALLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
Edward	B-pers
Bassett	I-pers
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
a	O
bustle	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
my	O
landlady	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
funeral	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
left	O
two	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Solafont	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
agreeable	O
lodging	O
.	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
fire	O
when	O
we	O
want	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
out-pensioner	O
of	O
Chelsea	O
Hospital	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
washes	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
his	O
drinking	O
tea	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
tea	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
tea	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
his	O
tea	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
313.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fitzwilliam	I-pers
Vandercombe	I-pers
;	O
a	O
gold	O
broach	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FITZWILLIAM	I-pers
VANDERCOMBE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bush-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Cannon-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
cook	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
ago	O
;	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
we	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
property	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
dismissed	O
from	O
my	O
service	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
1805	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
ago	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1805	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
information	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
police	O
office	O
,	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
silver	O
teaspoon	O
,	O
the	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
towel	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
property	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
-	O
PURWELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Finsbury-square	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
living	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tablecloth	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
box	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
Finsbury	O
Square	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tea	O
spoon	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
.	O
Purwell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
this	O
pocket	O
book	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
with	O
this	O
gold	O
broach	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
sweeping	O
the	O
floor	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
broach	O
and	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
the	O
tablecloth	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
napkin	O
.	O
Ray	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
inthe	O
morning	O
,	O
her	O
box	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
spoons	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
linen	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
pocket	O
book	O
and	O
the	O
broach	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
and	O
the	O
broach	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
sweeping	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Red	O
cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
five	O
shillings	O
or	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
linen	O
from	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
an	O
aunt	O
of	O
hers	O
;	O
the	O
letters	O
has	O
been	O
picked	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
very	O
plain	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
V	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
tablecloth	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
towel	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
the	O
V	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
number	O
18	O
,	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Are	O
these	O
things	O
your	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
With	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
linen	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
spoons	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
linen	O
any	O
mark	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
towel	O
has	O
a	O
V	O
and	O
the	O
figure	O
18	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
surname	O
does	O
begin	O
with	O
a	O
V.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
your	O
linen	O
was	O
so	O
marked	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
having	O
your	O
linen	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
your	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
numbered	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
being	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
V	O
and	O
numbered	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
yours	O
.	O
A.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
positively	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
that	O
the	O
table-cloth	O
and	O
the	O
napkin	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
we	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
identical	O
pattern	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
in	O
use	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
own	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
decisive	O
;	O
the	O
spoons	O
I	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
particularly	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
their	O
faces	O
from	O
the	O
frequent	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
desert	O
spoon	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
crest	O
of	O
a	O
mermaid	O
,	O
the	O
tea	O
spoon	O
has	O
a	O
Roman	B-pers
V	I-pers
under	O
the	O
Hall	O
mark	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
practise	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
plate	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
particular	O
place	O
every	O
night	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vandercombe	O
and	O
reside	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
broach	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
confident	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
broach	O
was	O
enclosed	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
worn	O
since	O
and	O
defaced	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
shortly	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Vandercombe	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
my	O
drawers	O
were	O
always	O
locked	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
up	O
the	O
room	O
after	O
the	O
carpenters	O
had	O
done	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
gentleman	O
moved	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
consider	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
of	O
any	O
value	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
gold	O
pin	O
I	O
never	O
noticed	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
spoons	O
I	O
gave	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
ninepence	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
near	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Red-cross-street	O
,	O
the	O
table	O
linen	O
has	O
been	O
mine	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Vandercombe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Whether	O
this	O
is	O
possible	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
she	O
states	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
linen	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
possibly	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
spoons	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
April	O
1805	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
she	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
314.	O
CORNELIUS	B-pers
DONNOHEW	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CONNER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
water	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Weldy	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WENDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Hewitt	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
late	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Conner	O
,	O
Donnohew	O
tried	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
overtaken	O
by	O
Hewitt	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
water	O
cask	O
upon	O
Conner	O
,	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blue	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
water	O
cask	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WELDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
Highway	I-place
;	O
that	O
water	O
cask	O
stood	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
the	O
cask	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
shillings	O
.	O
-	O
HEWITT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
police	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
questioned	O
the	O
prisoners	O
how	O
these	O
things	O
came	O
in	O
their	O
possession	O
;	O
Donnohew	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
tea	O
tray	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
DONNOHEW	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
CONNER	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
32	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
315.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Boffy	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOFFY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	B-place
Fox	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Wardour-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
near	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Margate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
property	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
clean	O
striped	O
cotton	O
shirt	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
striped	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
orhandkerchiefs	O
pawned	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
fetched	O
out	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
were	O
fetched	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
left	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
pawned	O
them	O
and	O
send	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Marlborough-street	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
shirts	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
-	O
ROBERTS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
Great	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
check	O
shirt	O
,	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
enough	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
ticket	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
bringing	O
three	O
she	O
brought	O
but	O
two	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
to	O
eat	O
for	O
my	O
child	O
nor	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Privately	O
Whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
316.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RUGGLES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
being	O
servant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
employed	O
and	O
entrusted	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
such	O
servant	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
and	O
take	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
;	O
27	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
an	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
fraudulently	O
did	O
embezzle	O
,	O
and	O
secrete	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
WILLIM	O
BENTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
the	O
sheriff	O
of	O
Surry	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
monies	O
he	O
got	O
under	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
(	O
accepted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
)	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
John-street	O
,	O
Edgware	O
Road	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
Whitechaple	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
coach	O
with	O
a	O
w	O
-	O
e	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
that	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Benton	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sheriff	O
's	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
employed	O
by	O
you	O
as	O
your	O
assistant	O
as	O
sheriff	O
's	O
officer	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
mean	O
what	O
is	O
commonly	O
termed	O
a	O
bailiff	O
's	O
follower	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
arrests	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
him	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fee	O
to	O
every	O
caption	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
speak	O
that	O
the	O
16th	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
some	O
days	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
be	O
due	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
After	O
it	O
became	O
due	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
endorsed	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
came	O
due	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
presented	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
went	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
awake	O
now	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
endorsed	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
paying	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
present	O
it	O
but	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
threatened	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
on	O
the	O
over-night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
drew	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
informing	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
by	O
some	O
w	O
-	O
s	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
drunk	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
John-street	O
;	O
Edgware	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
presented	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
bill	O
,	O
drawn	O
upon	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
payable	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
accompting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
ten	O
pound	O
notes	O
and	O
two	O
five	O
pound	O
notes	O
;	O
the	O
bill	O
with	O
the	O
interest	O
is	O
twenty-seven	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
five	O
pound	O
note	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
change	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Benton	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
receipt	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
bill	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
directions	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
pay	O
that	O
money	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PRENTICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Grey	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
(	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
night	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
accompanied	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
bad	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
drank	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
boil	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
eggs	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
good	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
shillingsworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
some	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
drank	O
some	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
eggs	O
were	O
eat	O
and	O
the	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
drank	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
serving	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
out	O
privately	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
my	O
customers	O
,	O
and	O
shenever	O
returned	O
;	O
I	O
awoke	O
him	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
near	O
all	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Q.Had	O
you	O
any	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
property	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
notes	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Langhurst	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Carter-street	O
,	O
Tooley-street	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
but	O
a	O
silver	O
pencil	O
case	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
result	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
examined	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
317.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FLYNN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
upon	O
George	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BEDFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
late	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
hustled	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
persons	O
and	O
knocked	O
down	O
in	O
Field-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Saffron	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
noticed	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
dark	O
blue	O
clothes	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
take	O
your	O
hat	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
tumbled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
hat	O
with	O
the	O
crown	O
hanging	O
only	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
blue	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
dressed	O
in	O
blue	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
his	O
coat	O
was	O
blue	O
or	O
brown	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
jacket	O
and	O
trowsers	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
hat	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
on	O
your	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
saucy	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
hat	O
worth	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
shillings	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
attacked	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
the	O
officers	O
stepped	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
and	O
glazier	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
change	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
I	O
lost	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
TROTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
myself	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Stanton	O
and	O
Wood	O
,	O
two	O
brother	O
officers	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
Irish	O
people	O
collected	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
informed	O
my	O
brother	O
officers	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
amongst	O
the	O
Irish	O
people	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
quell	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
tell	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tried	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
word	O
,	O
police	O
officers	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Irish	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
standing	O
around	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
around	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
through	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
told	O
Wood	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
see	O
what	O
marks	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
Stanton	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
led	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
paint	O
dropped	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
scraped	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
so	O
marked	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
described	O
;	O
I	O
handcuffed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
secure	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
we	O
caught	O
him	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
handcuffs	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
hat	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
behind	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
hat	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
place	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
described	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Field-lane	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
row	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
hat	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
318.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HAMERTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
thirteen	O
cheeses	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Walduck	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WALDUCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
the	O
property	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
these	O
cheeses	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
thirteen	O
cheeses	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
9	I-place
,	I-place
High-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
rented	O
the	O
bottom	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sleep	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
rented	O
it	O
at	O
thirty-five	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
slept	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
though	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
sleep	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
occupied	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
parlour	O
,	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
back	O
rooms	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Walduck	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cheeses	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
I	O
lockedthe	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
on	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
past	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
fastened	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
any	O
more	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
LANGFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
creditors	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
inventory	O
of	O
his	O
goods	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
somebody	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Walduck	O
who	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
away	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
moon	O
shiny	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
moon	O
shine	O
in	O
through	O
the	O
crevice	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
stop	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
forced	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
bad	O
lock	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
could	O
lock	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
missed	O
nothing	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOWNSHEND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patroles	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Crown-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
finding	O
the	O
cheeses	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
cheese	O
and	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
cheese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
cheese	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
turned	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
cheese	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
for	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
words	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cheese	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Mary	O
Green	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
We	O
have	O
heard	O
something	O
about	O
creditors	O
,	O
when	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
your	O
assignment	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
cheeses	O
were	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
assignment	O
was	O
not	O
till	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
cheeses	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
More	O
than	O
four	O
pounds	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
319.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BLAKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
three	O
window	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
white	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
brown	O
Holland	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mill	B-place
Bank	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
black	O
ash	O
maker	O
(	O
pot	O
ash	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
leaving	O
your	O
service	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
-	O
A.Yes	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
prior	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
inebriated	O
,	O
I	O
detected	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
rum	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
kitchen	O
secreted	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Morocco	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
trifling	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
bank	O
note	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
bank	O
note	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
number	O
is	O
29613	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
detected	O
it	O
she	O
said	O
ma'am	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Nelson	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
MATILDA	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
adjoining	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
factory	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
bringing	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
bag	O
tied	O
up	O
with	O
packthread	O
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
leave	O
it	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
that	O
day	O
or	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
luggage	O
than	O
she	O
could	O
take	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
parcel	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
neck	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
took	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
liked	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
acquainted	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
lady	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
warning	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
kicked	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
violent	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
walked	O
like	O
a	O
rotten	O
hedge	O
w	O
-	O
e	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
from	O
ear	O
to	O
ear	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
lay	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Matilda	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
lighterman	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KIRBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
true	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
paid	O
any	O
money	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
320.	O
MARY	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
bedgown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Benbow	B-place
's	I-place
Rents	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
.	I-place
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
dwelling	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
took	O
outof	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
gown	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
willingly	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Very	O
willingly	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
neighbours	O
came	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
PRINCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Confined	O
Six	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
321.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRADDOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
fourteen	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Alliston	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Somers	I-pers
,	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
called	O
a	O
slaughtering	O
house	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Stating	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
building	O
generally	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ALLISTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
52	O
,	O
Marshall-street	O
,	O
Carnaby	O
Market	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
partner	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
James	B-pers
Somers	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
slaughterhouse	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
of	O
having	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
affixed	O
to	O
the	O
slaughtering	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
put	O
under	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
affixed	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
moved	O
without	O
some	O
force	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PRING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
repaired	O
the	O
slaughterhouse	O
last	O
August	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
gutter	O
,	O
the	O
end	O
was	O
cut	O
of	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
about	O
two	O
foot	O
long	O
,	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
the	O
gutter	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
and	O
beat	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
away	O
without	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
moved	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
fitted	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
that	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SLADE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
fitted	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
fitted	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
fit	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KIRVEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
easing	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
spout	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lamp	O
lighter	O
's	O
ladder	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
slaughter	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
spout	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
shoes	O
on	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
near	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
without	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
for	O
the	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shoes	O
under	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
ladder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
that	O
lead	O
being	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
few	O
relations	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
pulled	O
my	O
shoes	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
so	O
bad	O
with	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
bowels	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
my	O
breeches	O
unbuttoned	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Confined	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
322.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
night	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
dimity	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
gaiter	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Marquis	B-pers
of	I-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WOODHOUSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Abercorn	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
his	O
premises	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
night	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
cotton	O
bed	O
furniture	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Abercorn	O
live	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Harlow	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
from	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STONWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Abercorn	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
clothes	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
coming	O
from	O
his	O
poultry	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
clothes	O
from	O
the	O
laundry	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
clothes	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Woodhouse	O
)	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
right	O
in	O
his	O
intellects	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
speak	O
from	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
your	O
mind	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
333.	O
JOHN	B-pers
O'BRIAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
twelve	O
months	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
his	O
taking	O
any	O
velvet	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
stating	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
recollect	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
lengths	O
he	O
took	O
cut	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
Clift	O
and	O
Cockhill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
takingit	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
particularly	O
,	O
he	O
generally	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Produce	O
the	O
entry	O
made	O
by	O
himself	O
on	O
his	O
return	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
entry	O
there	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
writing	O
(	O
witness	O
producing	O
a	O
book	O
)	O
;	O
Clift	O
,	O
six	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
yards	O
of	O
velvet	O
,	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
would	O
be	O
three	O
pound	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
accounted	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
velvet	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
supposing	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
you	O
sent	O
in	O
your	O
account	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Clift	O
and	O
Cockhill	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
made	O
a	O
discovery	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
pretence	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
Clift	O
and	O
Co.	O
that	O
turned	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
false	O
pretence	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
So	O
it	O
appears	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
you	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
false	O
pretence	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
goods	O
to	O
customers	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
other	O
times	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
goods	O
to	O
customers	O
,	O
stating	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
ordered	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
COCKHILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Miss	O
Clift	O
,	O
we	O
carry	O
on	O
business	O
in	O
Titchfield-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
dealt	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
called	O
on	O
you	O
with	O
articles	O
of	O
sale	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
before	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
any	O
order	O
for	O
six	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
velvet	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
bring	O
you	O
six	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
velvet	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
notice	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
of	O
his	O
supposing	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
that	O
velvet	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
then	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
incorrect	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
CLIFT	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
milleners	O
and	O
dress	O
makers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
given	O
any	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
for	O
six	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
velvet	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
he	O
brought	O
you	O
any	O
velvet	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
receiving	O
orders	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
whatever	O
order	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Miss	O
Clift	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
's	O
order	O
,	O
I	O
entered	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
;	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Thresher	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
connection	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
one	O
customer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
even	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
public	O
company	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
introduced	O
me	O
into	O
company	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
singing	O
)	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
ruin	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
324.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PENNINGTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tray	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
assistant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Tray	I-pers
,	O
Sun-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
cottons	O
,	O
she	O
objected	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
too	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
turning	O
round	O
to	O
reach	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
previously	O
shewn	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
more	O
pieces	O
,	O
she	O
objected	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
too	O
light	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
down	O
at	O
tea	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
the	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
any	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
JOYCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe	O
binder	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
16	O
,	O
Peter-street	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
Without	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
buy	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
bought	O
things	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tray	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
taken	O
down	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
young	O
master	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
home	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
cotton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Phillips	O
)	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
gown	O
to	O
pay	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
this	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
underneath	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
Phillips	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Confined	O
Three	O
Months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
325.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FROST	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
FROST	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Robert	O
Brown	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Pink	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
jennet	O
,	O
value9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Joblin	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
feloniously	O
did	O
receive	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
jennet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
being	O
part	O
and	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
aforementioned	O
goods	O
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
,	O
declining	O
to	O
offer	O
any	O
evidence	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
BOTH	O
-	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
326.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLAKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
tanned	O
hide	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OSBORNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
its	O
being	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
warehouseman	O
at	O
Leadenhall	O
market	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
bought	O
thirty-seven	O
hides	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
habits	O
of	O
carting	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
thirty-six	O
.	O
-	O
FREEMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
leather	O
factor	O
in	O
Leadenhall	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
thirty-seven	O
hides	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
GIBBONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
leather	O
cutter	O
,	O
Church	O
row	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
bought	O
thirty-seven	O
hides	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
only	O
thirty	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Into	O
whose	O
care	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
convey	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Osborne	O
)	O
You	O
received	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
some	O
hides	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
putting	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
the	O
loading	O
book	O
;	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
I	O
carted	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
load	O
them	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
doing	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
cart	O
began	O
to	O
load	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
cart	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
things	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
cart	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
to	O
go	O
its	O
rounds	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
with	O
thirty	O
seven	O
hides	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
I	O
counted	O
only	O
thirty	O
six	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BULLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Blake	O
come	O
through	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
called	O
Bullen	O
Alley	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
fortnight	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
between	O
Skinner	O
street	O
and	O
Angel	O
alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BILLINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
60	O
,	O
Skinner	O
street	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
fortnight	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
my	O
back	O
window	O
that	O
looked	O
into	O
Acorn	O
alley	O
,	O
it	O
joins	O
Bullen	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Blake	O
with	O
the	O
leather	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Bullen	O
yard	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pitch	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Blake	O
.	O
I	O
admit	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
leather	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
impossible	O
from	O
where	O
she	O
represents	O
she	O
lives	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
Bullen	O
alley	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
any	O
gentleman	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
to	O
see	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ribbon	O
weaver	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	O
court	O
,	O
Angel	O
alley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
through	O
Bullen	O
yard	O
with	O
the	O
leather	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pitch	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Richardson	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
afterwards	O
with	O
a	O
knot	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SAPWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
in	O
Angel	O
alley	O
;	O
Dodson	B-pers
looks	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
while	O
Richardson	O
is	O
bad	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Dodson	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
playing	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
for	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
pointed	O
to	O
Shephard	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
pull	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
boards	O
a	O
bullock	O
's	O
hide	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
produce	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
Dodson	O
,	O
and	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
saw	O
Blake	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
Dodson	O
how	O
the	O
leather	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Blake	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
Blake	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
handcuffed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Dodson	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
once	O
a	O
respectable	O
man	O
in	O
our	O
parish	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
braces	O
now	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
while	O
this	O
poor	O
man	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
concealed	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
sand	O
bin	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SHEPHARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
a	O
hide	O
of	O
leather	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
this	O
alley	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Blake	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Dodson	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sapwell	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Dodson	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Dodson	O
was	O
then	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hide	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
two	O
shutters	O
and	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
hide	O
up	O
;	O
Sapwell	O
instantly	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Dodson	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
instant	O
of	O
securing	O
him	O
,	O
Blake	O
made	O
his	O
appearance	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Sapwell	O
also	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
hide	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hide	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Blake	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Bilingsgate	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
at	O
various	O
markets	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
at	O
Bilingsgate	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
three	O
small	O
children	O
)	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
basket	O
at	O
Bilingsgate	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
says	O
,	O
porter	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
job	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shillings	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Blue-Coat	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
at	O
my	O
leisure	O
;	O
I	O
goes	O
home	O
to	O
leave	O
what	O
supply	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
is	O
totally	O
innocent	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
potatoes	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
my	O
children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
you	O
this	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
;	O
frequently	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
carry	O
things	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
.	O
Dodson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
liberty	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
while	O
he	O
lookedfor	O
his	O
children	O
,	O
it	O
remained	O
there	O
during	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Sapwell	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Blake	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
seems	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
as	O
how	O
the	O
hide	O
was	O
secreted	O
and	O
covered	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
pitched	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
assure	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
officer	O
you	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
agitation	O
of	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
Blake	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
Dodson	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BLAKE	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
37	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
Whipped	O
in	O
Gaol	O
.	O
DODSON	O
-	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
327.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tuff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TUFF	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Harp	O
lane	O
,	O
Tower	O
street	O
.	O
Last	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
arrived	O
from	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
passage	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
aft	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
vessel	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
aft	O
cabin	O
and	O
came	O
upon	O
deck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
friends	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
replied	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
pump	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
Billingsgate	O
boat	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
mistake	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
from	O
Chatham	O
to	O
the	O
Gravesend	O
boat	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
half	O
tipsey	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
taking	O
my	O
own	O
bundle	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
own	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
captain	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
bundle	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
vessel	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
328.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NIX	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
pound	O
seven	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
united	B-pers
merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East	I-pers
Indies	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
like	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
ELY	B-pers
SOUL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
commodore	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
Crutched	B-place
Friars	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
gang	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
command	O
of	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
observed	O
any	O
Mocoa	O
coffee	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
bale	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
gone	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rub	O
our	O
gang	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
confused	O
in	O
my	O
rubbing	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
small	O
pockets	O
hanging	O
quite	O
behind	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
like	O
coffee	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
elder	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
answered	O
,	O
pray	O
Mr	O
.	O
Soul	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
on	O
being	O
taken	O
there	O
an	O
officer	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
one	O
pound	O
seven	O
ounces	O
of	O
coffee	O
.	O
-	O
BURGESS	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
locker	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
coffee	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
weighs	O
one	O
pound	O
seven	O
ounces	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Mocoa	O
coffee	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
hung	O
up	O
my	O
coat	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nigh	O
it	O
till	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
coffee	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
coffee	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
Whipped	O
.	O
in	O
Goal	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
329.	O
DAVID	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GUEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair	O
dresser	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
16	I-place
,	I-place
Bear-street	I-place
,	I-place
Liecester-square	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
shirt	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
accuse	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Clarence	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
was	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
he	O
found	O
was	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
with	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
shirt	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
razors	O
and	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
razors	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
shirt	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
my	O
wages	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
46	O
.	O
Confined	O
Fourteen	O
Days	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
330.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HURST	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
twelve	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
flour	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shephard	I-pers
Killock	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SHEPHARD	I-pers
KILLOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	O
mills	O
,	O
Lea	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
flour	O
dresser	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
Hackney	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
patrole	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
man	O
into	O
custody	O
with	O
some	O
flour	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisonertold	O
me	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
mill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
man	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
IVES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
of	O
Hackney	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
this	O
man	O
about	O
twenty-five	O
minutes	O
before	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Brooksby	O
's	O
Walk	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
from	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
property	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
says	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
a	O
little	O
dust	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
God	O
Almighty	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
five	O
shillings	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
trustees	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
Lea	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Killock	O
's	O
premises	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
three	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
of	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
mill	O
called	O
the	O
mill	O
tail	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
Hackney	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mill	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
flour	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
flour	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
34	O
.	O
Confined	O
Six	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
331.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
RUSSEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
POCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Robert	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
One	B-place
Tun-court	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
.	I-place
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
22nd	O
,	O
I	O
arose	O
from	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
two	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
clean	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
opened	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
servant	O
maid	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
George	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
gone	O
like	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
shirts	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
examined	O
my	O
box	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
watch	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
Christopher	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Panton-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COPE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Panton-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
described	O
it	O
as	O
her	O
husbands	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
twenty-seven	O
shillings	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lodger	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
being	O
sick	O
,	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
asked	O
any	O
questions	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
now	O
denies	O
he	O
ever	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
332.	O
ANN	B-pers
SLOCOMB	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
close	O
to	O
our	O
window	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
linen	O
drapery	O
goods	O
hanging	O
about	O
your	O
window	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
suddenly	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
the	O
printed	O
cotton	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
measured	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
it	O
measured	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
suddenly	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
ran	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
she	O
without	O
being	O
confused	O
admitted	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
confused	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
property	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Although	O
you	O
were	O
attending	O
to	O
her	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
property	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
gone	O
into	O
any	O
place	O
whatever	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
this	O
cotton	O
produced	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
have	O
ventured	O
to	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
had	O
my	O
employer	O
's	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
confident	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
sold	O
but	O
by	O
yourself	O
,	O
other	O
persons	O
sell	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
yourself	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
shopmen	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
nor	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
girl	O
in	O
custody	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
cotton	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
I	O
produce	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
defence	O
to	O
her	O
counsel	O
;	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
youth	O
.	O
]	O
Confined	O
Six	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
334.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLEMENTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Buckhart	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
tenat	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Buckhart	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHRISTIAN	I-pers
BUCKHART	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
14	I-place
,	I-place
Northumberland-street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
servant	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
:	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
best	O
silver	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
mahogany	O
wardrobe	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
empty	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
were	O
full	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
indictment	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
in	O
the	O
commitment	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
small	O
clothes	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
article	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
articles	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
patent	O
cord	O
small	O
clothes	O
,	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
between	O
forty	O
and	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
different	O
offices	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
learn	O
any	O
thing	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
thief	O
or	O
what	O
has	O
became	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
lead	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
where	O
three	O
people	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
as	O
housebreakers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
wore	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
small	O
clothes	O
which	O
attracted	O
my	O
notice	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
examined	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
lined	O
with	O
white	O
calico	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
large	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buttons	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
gallowses	O
were	O
fastened	O
were	O
white	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
spot	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
knee	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
them	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
wore	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Was	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
out	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
spoken	O
of	O
their	O
value	O
,	O
may	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Upwards	O
of	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
worn	O
them	O
twice	O
and	O
injured	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
purchaser	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
might	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
These	O
breeches	O
are	O
a	O
common	O
colour	O
,	O
you	O
stated	O
that	O
you	O
knew	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
white	O
calico	O
lining	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
spot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
metal	O
button	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
any	O
breeches	O
lined	O
with	O
any	O
other	O
calico	O
than	O
white	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
peculiar	O
in	O
their	O
having	O
white	O
calico	O
lining	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
wore	O
them	O
I	O
rode	O
to	O
Windsor	O
and	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
lining	O
doubled	O
under	O
my	O
seat	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
inconvenience	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
wore	O
them	O
higher	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
front	O
button	O
was	O
torn	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
torn	O
out	O
now	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
very	O
common	O
sort	O
of	O
breeches	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
except	O
from	O
the	O
circumstances	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
RUSSEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Buckhart	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
recollect	O
happening	O
on	O
this	O
Sunday	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
half	O
after	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
every	O
door	O
and	O
window	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
on	O
returning	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
single	O
lock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
two	O
cupboards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
state	O
that	O
you	O
supposed	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
directly	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
drawers	O
of	O
the	O
wardrobe	O
were	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
empty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
What	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
them	O
drawers	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Plate	O
and	O
linen	O
were	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
others	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Russel	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
them	O
drawers	O
were	O
broken	O
open	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
different	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
opened	O
every	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
four	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
table	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
LAVENDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patroles	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
we	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
breeches	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
detained	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
your	O
loss	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
less	O
than	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
observed	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
button	O
which	O
is	O
nearly	O
coming	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
supports	O
the	O
gallowses	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
wearing	O
his	O
breeches	O
so	O
high	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
breeches	O
this	O
button	O
was	O
perfectly	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
lose	O
now	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
heavy	O
irons	O
they	O
put	O
on	O
me	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
purchased	O
these	O
breeches	O
promiscuously	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
hanging	O
across	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
they	O
attracted	O
my	O
attention	O
seeing	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
I	O
gave	O
twenty-three	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
stole	O
it	O
is	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Lavender	O
.	O
)	O
Had	O
he	O
heavy	O
irons	O
on	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
iron	O
on	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wore	O
these	O
breeches	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
breeches	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
334.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BURTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
Banes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Dean	I-place
's	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
housekeeper	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
Banes	I-pers
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
boarding-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
live	O
with	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
family	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
fix	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
dustmanbringing	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
ticket	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
shirt	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Broomfield	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shirt	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
shirts	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
permanent	O
ink	O
Thompson	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
officer	O
to	O
search	O
Broomfield	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
some	O
information	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
this	O
search	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
