TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1806	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	O
SHAW	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORTHAND	O
BY	O
JOB	O
SIBLY	O
,	O
FOR	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
BUTTERS	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
1806	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
SHAW	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
ELLENBOROUGH	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
GILES	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
Alexander	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
William	I-pers
Anderson	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Eamer	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bloxham	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
George	O
Scholey	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
Newman	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bott	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Vandome	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowgin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pim	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairbould	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
FIRST	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
Rogers	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Claridge	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ager	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tegg	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Folkes	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
,	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Anstead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
.	O
SECOND	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Newport	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
Ludland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lathe	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
.	O
560.	O
MARY	B-pers
BLACKSLEY	I-pers
,	O
ELIZEBTH	B-pers
SIMMONDS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARTHA	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Blacksley	O
and	O
Simmonds	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
bargaining	O
with	O
my	O
shopman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
Blacksley	O
stood	O
with	O
her	O
back	O
against	O
some	O
calico	O
placed	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
some	O
wire	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
attention	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
some	O
customers	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
Blacksley	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
missed	O
her	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Simmonds	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
hiding	O
herself	O
at	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
steps	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
cotton	O
to	O
Wood	B-pers
the	O
moment	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Wood	O
was	O
waiting	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Wood	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
Blacksley	O
said	O
where	O
the	O
print	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
ANTHONY	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
all	O
you	O
know	O
is	O
finding	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Windmill	O
street	O
.	O
Blackley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
women	O
are	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
BLACKSLEY	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
SIMMONDS	O
,	O
WOOD	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
561.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ASKEW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
five	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
two	O
pocket	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
;	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
two	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
.	O
And	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ASKEW	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
PRICE	I-pers
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
WALTER	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robert	O
Lomas	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
,	I-place
Tabernacle	I-place
Walk	I-place
,	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
this	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eight	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
single	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
surprised	O
at	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
state	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
double	O
locked	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
double	O
locked	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
point	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Susannah	O
Miles	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
two	O
rooms	O
above	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
missed	O
nothing	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
did	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
by	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
.	O
-	O
A.Nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Only	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
finding	O
the	O
door	O
single	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
double	O
locked	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
else	O
,	O
my	O
apartments	O
were	O
all	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Q.Therefore	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
all	O
as	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
except	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Miles	O
's	O
apartments	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Curwood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
circumstance	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
MILES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
eight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
before	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
chapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
articles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
remember	O
these	O
particularly	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
these	O
since	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
gowns	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
cloak	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
six	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
your	O
box	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
box	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
few	O
things	O
they	O
left	O
were	O
thrown	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
articles	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
some	O
gowns	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
three	O
gowns	O
,	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
nightcap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Worship	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
search	O
with	O
Ray	O
;	O
Ray	O
produces	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
Vickery	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
stockings	O
and	O
the	O
cap	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
stockings	O
and	O
cap	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
gowns	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
VICKERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
gowns	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Noah	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
jew	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
Ray	O
,	O
Bishop	O
,	O
and	O
Noah	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Hatfield	O
street	O
,	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
shewed	O
to	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
by	O
Noah	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
apartments	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
is	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Price	O
.	O
Armstrong	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
we	O
must	O
search	O
his	O
place	O
;	O
we	O
proceeded	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
was	O
these	O
implements	O
of	O
house	O
breaking	O
-	O
three	O
crows	O
,	O
one	O
large	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
small	O
ones	O
,	O
two	O
large	O
picklock	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
small	O
picklock	O
keys	O
for	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
cupboard	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
In	O
another	O
cupboard	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
file	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
file	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
cupboard	O
was	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
putty	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
impression	O
of	O
a	O
key	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
putty	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
when	O
they	O
get	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
key	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
impression	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
said	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
some	O
place	O
which	O
she	O
mentioned	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
belief	O
.	O
This	O
handkerchief	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Susannah	O
Miles	O
)	O
Whose	O
property	O
is	O
that	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Vickery	O
)	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
yellow	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
was	O
this	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
was	O
the	O
stockings	O
and	O
the	O
cap	O
belonging	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoners	O
apartments	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
me	O
with	O
Armstrong	O
and	O
another	O
officer	O
;	O
we	O
examined	O
the	O
box	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
boxes	O
were	O
broken	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
boxes	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
boxes	O
were	O
these	O
(	O
to	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
)	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
one	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
was	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Mine	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
that	O
box	O
you	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
A.Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
Vickery	O
.	O
The	O
boxes	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
these	O
tools	O
,	O
we	O
fitted	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
tool	O
has	O
a	O
jagged	O
edge	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
this	O
tool	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
exactly	O
,	O
this	O
tool	O
was	O
rusty	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
the	O
rust	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fitted	O
the	O
impression	O
exactly	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
strong	O
elm	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
took	O
some	O
force	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
comparing	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
tools	O
with	O
the	O
impression	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rust	O
that	O
you	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
by	O
that	O
tool	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
has	O
a	O
notch	O
,	O
a	O
jagged	O
edge	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
that	O
jagged	O
edge	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
is	O
a	O
stout	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
painted	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
box	O
belonged	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
the	O
tool	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
box	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
this	O
large	O
box	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
much	O
larger	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
thinner	O
.	O
To	O
that	O
box	O
they	O
have	O
used	O
this	O
tool	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
.	O
These	O
gowns	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Noah	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
cloak	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
I	O
had	O
against	O
another	O
house	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
searching	O
that	O
house	O
Noah	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
searched	O
his	O
bag	O
,	O
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
articles	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
bag	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
silk	O
cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
)	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
silk	O
cloak	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Vickery	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
)	O
Is	O
that	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
worth	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
gave	O
four	O
pounds	O
for	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Above	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
worth	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
more	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Vickery	O
.	O
Noah	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
the	O
following	O
day	O
produced	O
these	O
gowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
therethere	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
following	O
day	O
these	O
gowns	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
after	O
that	O
produced	O
the	O
gowns	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
gowns	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
gowns	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
pieces	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
new	O
topped	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Speak	O
within	O
the	O
mark	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
two	O
pounds	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Curwood	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Vickery	O
)	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
only	O
heard	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
could	O
discover	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
than	O
what	O
are	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
NOAH	B-pers
AARON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
cloak	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
would	O
I	O
buy	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
clothes	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
that	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
would	O
I	O
buy	O
any	O
clothes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
tomorrow	O
;	O
he	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
boy	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
woman	O
;	O
they	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
seven	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q.What	O
things	O
did	O
they	O
shew	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
four	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
cloak	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
Vickery	O
took	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
gowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
else	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
altogether	O
of	O
a	O
lump	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
lot	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
pound	O
fifteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
it	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Vickery	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
never	O
recovered	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Aaron	O
)	O
Are	O
there	O
four	O
gowns	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
one	O
I	O
sold	O
in	O
Rag	O
fair	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
now	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
suit	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
four	O
pound	O
ten	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
concluded	O
the	O
bargain	O
at	O
four	O
pound	O
fifteen	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
AARON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
going	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
12th	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
what	O
your	O
father	O
said	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
what	O
he	O
say	O
pass	O
in	O
your	O
presence	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Curwood	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
bringing	O
up	O
to	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
watch-motion	O
maker	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MILES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
them	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
one	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
box	O
locked	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
come	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
sister	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
just	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sister	O
to	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
alarmed	O
indeed	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
apartment	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
is	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
strong	O
deal	O
box	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
strongish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
tool	O
which	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
with	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
evident	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
thing	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
watch-maker	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
allow	O
me	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
mentioned	O
,	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
or	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
that	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
pattern	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
a	O
French	O
watch	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TIDMARSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q.	O
Yours	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
a	O
common	O
strong	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
mentioned	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
return	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
on	O
looking	O
in	O
your	O
box	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Aaron	O
)	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
place	O
that	O
yousaw	O
this	O
man	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
Q.Where	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
Mitre-Court	O
,	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
let	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Price	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ASKEW	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
,	O
ELIZABETH	O
ASKEW	O
,	O
alias	O
PRICE	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
562.	O
HENRY	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hembrow	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hembrow	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HEMBROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
197	I-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
ringing	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
quitted	O
my	O
service	O
I	O
believe	O
nine	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
knife	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
T.	O
H.	O
the	O
letters	O
were	O
burnt	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
handle	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
cutting	O
knife	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
my	O
cellar	O
door	O
and	O
my	O
house	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
Adjoining	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
the	O
accompting	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
iron	O
chest	O
fixed	O
in	O
the	O
accompting	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
forced	O
with	O
a	O
hook	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
with	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
large	O
choppers	O
;	O
the	O
wall	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
stone	O
work	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
through	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
we	O
shall	O
hear	O
,	O
in	O
fact	O
you	O
missed	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
HAYDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
that	O
walk	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
lives	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
first	O
I	O
slapp	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
all	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
shoved	O
my	O
hand	O
against	O
it	O
and	O
it	O
gave	O
way	O
and	O
opened	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
this	O
good	O
man	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
yes	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
answer	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
far	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
forward	O
and	O
said	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
very	O
well	O
if	O
all	O
is	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
thought	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
if	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
hurrying	O
out	O
for	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
satisfied	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
his	O
hat	O
that	O
laid	O
behind	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
wrist	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
long	O
carving	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
rescuing	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
fall	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
struggled	O
for	O
a	O
minute	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
old	O
of	O
,	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
tore	O
a	O
piece	O
from	O
the	O
flap	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
,	O
struggling	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A.It	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
his	O
coat	O
was	O
torn	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
piece	O
I	O
tore	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
I	O
halloed	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SEDDALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coal	O
merchant	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Union	O
street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
mentioned	O
,	O
were	O
you	O
passing	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
supposed	O
as	O
butchers	O
were	O
early	O
risers	O
,	O
they	O
perhaps	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
past	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
halloa	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
immediately	O
afterwards	O
a	O
scuffle	O
between	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
,	O
whoever	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
no	O
questions	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Vigo	O
Lane	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watchman	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
by	O
the	O
dirtiness	O
of	O
his	O
stockings	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
's	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
watchman	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
watchman	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Haydon	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
that	O
his	O
coat	O
was	O
torn	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
the	O
watchman	O
mentioned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
coat	O
which	O
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
,	O
matched	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
us	O
into	O
his	O
accompting-house	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
forcing	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
New	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
springing	O
of	O
the	O
rattles	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
Bond-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
Grafton-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PETHERICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
I	O
borrowed	O
a	O
coat	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
own	O
coat	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
kept	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
compared	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
matched	O
the	O
place	O
exactly	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GREGORY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
catch	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Hembrow	O
's	O
accompting	O
house	O
and	O
perceived	O
the	O
wood	O
work	O
round	O
the	O
iron	O
chest	O
was	O
broken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
stone	O
and	O
bricks	O
were	O
broken	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
iron	O
chest	O
was	O
not	O
broken	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
cleavers	O
that	O
were	O
bent	O
,	O
with	O
mortar	O
and	O
brick	O
dust	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
pushed	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
some	O
person	O
asked	O
me	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
answered	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
Thomas	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
pushed	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shut	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
block	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
and	O
leaned	O
upon	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
very	O
well	O
recollect	O
my	O
hat	O
falling	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
answered	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
knife	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
recollect	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
563.	O
ANN	B-pers
MOLLINEUX	I-pers
and	O
CORNELIUS	B-pers
LEARY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
accosted	O
me	O
with	O
open	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
clasped	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
body	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
on	O
to	O
Villiers	B-place
Street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
Villier-street	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
and	O
she	O
stood	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
only	O
a	O
four	O
halfpence	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
While	O
you	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
your	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
while	O
you	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A.I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
hip	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
conceived	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Leary	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
directly	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
or	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
stand	O
at	O
Villier-street	O
,	O
who	O
proposed	O
stopping	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
proposal	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
stopped	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
both	O
must	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
both	O
go	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
pass	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
spoke	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Leary	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Pilgrim	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Pilgrim	O
do	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Pilgrim	O
searched	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
cuffs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
situation	O
were	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
just	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
glasses	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
last	O
perceive	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Pall	O
Mall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pocket	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
guineas	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
PILGRIM	O
sworn	O
.	O
Your	O
wife	O
searched	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
abot	O
her	O
person	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
cuff	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
cuff	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Leary	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
knows	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
conveyed	O
into	O
my	O
cuff	O
.	O
MOLLINEUX	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
LEARY	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
564.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
DUDDERIDGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
six	O
brass	O
bosses	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
brass	O
knocker	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
hook	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
brass	O
carriages	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
bolt	O
staple	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
thirty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marriott	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARRIOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
and	O
ironmonger	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old	O
Broad	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
sixteen	O
years	O
as	O
my	O
foreman	O
.	O
The	O
occasion	O
of	O
my	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
with	O
some	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
ninety	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
paper	O
boxes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
not	O
yours	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
any	O
gold	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
things	O
in	O
iron	O
and	O
brass	O
that	O
I	O
recognised	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
articles	O
you	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Brass	O
bosses	O
,	O
parts	O
of	O
brass	O
door	O
knockers	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
bell	O
carriages	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
These	O
articles	O
are	O
not	O
peculiar	O
to	O
your	O
warehouse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
bosses	O
are	O
old	O
bosses	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
crane	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
of	O
Snowhill	O
;	O
strictly	O
speaking	O
they	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
my	O
account	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
allowed	O
for	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
these	O
articles	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
speaking	O
of	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
arms	O
of	O
the	O
crane	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
placed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
them	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
laying	O
on	O
his	O
vice	O
board	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
you	O
say	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
so	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
who	O
died	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
after	O
twenty	O
years	O
servitude	O
,	O
bound	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
son	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
freeman	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
forty	O
pounds	O
odd	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
instructed	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
glad	O
if	O
this	O
had	O
not	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
pleased	O
to	O
have	O
sacrificed	O
five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mason	O
,	O
a	O
brother	O
officer	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
Purl	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
bag	O
he	O
shot	O
into	O
a	O
scale	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
seventy	O
pounds	O
of	O
lead	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
immediately	O
with	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
lead	O
;	O
he	O
hesitated	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship	O
street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
last	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marriott	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
perquisite	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marriott	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marriott	O
appeared	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
-	O
BISHOP	O
sworn	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Marriott	O
,	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
Ray	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
apartments	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Little	O
Purl	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
searching	O
his	O
back	O
room	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
brass	O
articles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
bosses	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Marriott	O
speaks	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marriott	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
bosses	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
worn	O
by	O
friction	O
;	O
these	O
six	O
bosses	O
belonged	O
to	O
one	O
frame	O
,	O
which	O
composes	O
the	O
crane	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
those	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
day	O
by	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
new	O
iron	O
ones	O
in	O
the	O
crane	O
for	O
those	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
these	O
bosses	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
article	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
allowing	O
them	O
as	O
perquisites	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
stated	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
a	O
forge	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
ways	O
always	O
a	O
rule	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
almost	O
nineteen	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
old	O
brass	O
and	O
lead	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
right	O
person	O
had	O
them	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
,	O
Skinner	O
street	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HILLSLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
brass	O
which	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
crane	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
,	O
Skinner	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
any	O
perquisites	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
always	O
understood	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
perquisites	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
's	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
perquisites	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
understood	O
the	O
old	O
brass	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
lead	O
,	O
iron	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
not	O
,	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
job	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
understand	O
all	O
the	O
old	O
materials	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
master	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
brass	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
lead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
work	O
done	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
worth	O
something	O
to	O
a	O
foreman	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
brass	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
lead	O
must	O
be	O
worth	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
principal	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
or	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
master	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
565.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
HOGG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
eight	O
brass	O
escutcheons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
plate	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
sixpences	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marriott	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARRIOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
live	O
in	O
Old	O
Broad	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
a	O
former	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
shop	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
law	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
of	O
robbing	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
particularly	O
two	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
merely	O
suspicion	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Merely	O
suspicion	O
;	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
articles	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
bell	O
carriages	O
and	O
cranks	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
searched	O
him	O
inmy	O
presence	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
brass	O
escutcheons	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
plate	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
work	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
lackerers	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
to	O
be	O
lackered	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
lackerers	O
without	O
my	O
orders	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
escutcheons	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
articles	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
stated	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
lackered	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
you	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
without	O
your	O
leave	O
,	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
taking	O
them	O
without	O
your	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
;	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
articles	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
value	O
would	O
not	O
exceed	O
three	O
pence	O
or	O
four	O
pence	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Does	O
your	O
lackerer	O
work	O
in	O
your	O
premises	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
of	O
this	O
side	O
Tower	O
hill	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
never	O
our	O
custom	O
to	O
send	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
without	O
writing	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
lackered	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BISHOP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
police	O
constable	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
in	O
Worship	O
street	O
office	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
eight	O
brass	O
escutcheons	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brass	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
a	O
beer	O
barrel	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
lackered	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mason	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
law	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
small	O
bags	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
bags	O
contained	O
about	O
seven	O
pound	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
bag	O
containing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
bags	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
articles	O
in	O
brass	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
work	O
bench	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
the	O
escutheons	O
.	O
Privately	O
Whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
566.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CONNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jeremy	I-pers
;	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jeremy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
JEREMY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
in	O
Southampton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
that	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
keep	O
brooms	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
some	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
conveying	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
too	O
,	O
leaving	O
my	O
nephew	O
,	O
my	O
shopman	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
waited	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
distance	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
way	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
drew	O
nearer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
off	O
were	O
you	O
then	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
ten	O
to	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
requested	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
bundle	O
contained	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
a	O
bundle	O
then	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Oh	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
at	O
broad	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
ringing	O
the	O
bell	O
he	O
disentangled	O
himself	O
by	O
twisting	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
across	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
escaping	O
his	O
arm	O
came	O
across	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
ran	O
down	O
Southampton-street	O
towards	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
see	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
my	O
nephew	O
's	O
possession	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Southampton-street	O
not	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
.	O
It	O
contained	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
our	O
furniture	O
cotton	O
,	O
about	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JEREMY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
finding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
in	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
contains	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
covering	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bundle	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
hair	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
contents	O
is	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
cotton	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SHERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
passing	O
in	O
Southampton-street	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
past	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
like	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeremy	I-pers
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
bundle	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
567.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ARROW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
.	O
LEONARD	B-pers
CROWDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ditcham	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
,	I-place
Sherborn	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
carpenter	O
and	O
boxmaker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
carcase	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
carcase	O
saw	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
pistols	O
he	O
took	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
boxmaker	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
the	O
pistols	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
having	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
251	O
,	O
Borough	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
saws	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
the	O
shopman	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
carcase	O
saw	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Arrow	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistols	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Reaves	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Privately	O
Whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
568.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SHIPLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Hoye	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lydia	B-pers
Bourden	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Michael	B-pers
Hoye	I-pers
,	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
9	I-place
.	I-place
Size	I-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Antling	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
dinner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
door	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
door	O
go	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
street	O
door	O
is	O
always	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
undid	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
coat	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
DANIEL	O
LEADBETTER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
this	O
coat	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Vine	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
marked	O
in	O
the	O
sleeve	O
lining	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
overpowered	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
my	O
faculties	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
55	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
Whipped	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
569.	O
SARAH	B-pers
SAMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
IRELAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
78	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
bridge	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
stockings	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
shewn	O
a	O
parcel	O
containing	O
three	O
pair	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
at	O
a	O
lower	O
price	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
second	O
parcel	O
was	O
getting	O
she	O
purloined	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
persisted	O
in	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
lad	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
produced	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
men	O
's	O
ribbed	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Peat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
express	O
some	O
approbation	O
of	O
that	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
case	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
some	O
better	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
the	O
stocking	O
;	O
she	O
concealed	O
the	O
stockings	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
having	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
she	O
produced	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ireland	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
defence	O
to	O
her	O
counter	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
46	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
570.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COOKMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
fir	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
deal	O
board	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Perrot	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
.	O
PERROT	O
FENTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
a	O
workman	O
employed	O
in	O
repairing	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
wood	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
;	O
on	O
opening	O
it	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
quartering	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
I	O
selected	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
joined	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
quartering	O
and	O
a	O
deal	O
board	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
call	O
them	O
chips	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Laurence	O
was	O
the	O
master	O
carpenter	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
work	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
superintend	O
the	O
work	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
wood	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
better	O
employed	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
men	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
talk	O
of	O
agreements	O
I	O
must	O
state	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
explain	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
must	O
know	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
agreed	O
to	O
allow	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
men	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
agreement	O
with	O
these	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
stated	O
to	O
the	O
carpenter	O
that	O
I	O
employed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
any	O
wood	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
other	O
buildings	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
taking	O
away	O
wood	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
iron	O
and	O
lead	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
these	O
men	O
will	O
be	O
discontented	O
unless	O
you	O
let	O
them	O
take	O
some	O
chips	O
for	O
firing	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
what	O
beer	O
you	O
like	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
encouraging	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
extent	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
general	O
system	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
cut	O
pieces	O
of	O
oak	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
wood	O
and	O
iron	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
allow	O
no	O
more	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
splinter	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
out	O
any	O
I	O
will	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
that	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
call	O
an	O
agreement	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
men	O
they	O
must	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
In	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
general	O
allowance	O
of	O
beer	O
was	O
stopped	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
carrying	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
persisted	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
man	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
issue	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Laurence	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Laurence	O
says	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
will	O
allow	O
you	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
take	O
no	O
chips	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
not	O
stopped	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
stopped	O
the	O
men	O
began	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
chips	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
basket	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
I	O
met	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haslem	I-pers
with	O
a	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
your	O
chips	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haslem	I-pers
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
chips	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
old	O
rotten	O
stuff	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
your	O
part	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
basket	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
alderman	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
whispering	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
my	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
serve	O
my	O
king	O
and	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sit	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
fourteen	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
French	O
prison	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
my	O
trial	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Confined	O
Two	O
Months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
571.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GLOVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Tomson	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
ROGER	B-pers
DEVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass	O
founder	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
week	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
metal	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
emptied	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
the	O
metal	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
an	O
old	O
rag	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Shoe-lane	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
shop	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
metal	O
must	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
but	O
her	O
shop	O
was	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
certain	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
some	O
founder	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
along	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Robin	O
Hood	O
court	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
into	O
Dean-street	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
repeatedly	O
requested	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
whose	O
metal	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
metal	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
after	O
his	O
master	O
came	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
part	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
ELISHA	B-pers
WESTWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
caster	O
for	O
Messrs.	O
Warner	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
founders	O
,	O
they	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
Jewin-street	O
,	O
Crescent	O
,	O
Cripplegate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
the	O
metal	O
belong	O
to	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
these	O
three	O
pieces	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
firmly	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
572.	O
MARY	B-pers
YOKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
frying	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
ABIGAIL	B-pers
SUMNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	B-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Green-yard	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
proved	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
continued	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
was	O
he	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
horse	O
line	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
Little	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
me	O
pretty	O
well	O
for	O
several	O
weeks	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
owed	O
me	O
something	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
they	O
leave	O
your	O
lodgings	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
month	O
last	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
is	O
out	O
,	O
oh	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
home	O
presently	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
let	O
your	O
lodgings	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
you	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	O
HENRY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
there	O
is	O
two	O
frying	O
pans	O
,	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
and	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Clark	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
me	O
up	O
the	O
duplicates	O
directly	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
entirely	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
distressed	O
woman	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
573.	O
MARY	B-pers
HINTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
five	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
children	O
's	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gershen	I-pers
.	O
LUCY	B-pers
GERSHEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gershen	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
near	O
thirteen	O
weeks	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
from	O
market	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
fruit	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
porter	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
fruit	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
porter	O
had	O
gone	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
property	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
these	O
articles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
STANCEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
30	O
,	O
Red	O
Lion-street	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
petticoat	O
,	O
pledged	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
for	O
eightpence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
a	O
frock	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
She	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hinton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
belief	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
is	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
,	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
gown	O
pledged	O
for	O
eight-shillings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hinton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
myself	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SIMMONDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Windsor	O
,	O
105	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
six	O
pledges	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
three	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
face	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
574.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
RICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	O
,	O
Jones	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
bedgown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
habit	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
muslins	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
ribbon	O
,	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
did	O
steal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3	I-place
,	I-place
Williams	I-place
's	I-place
Buildings	I-place
,	I-place
Brompton	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
laundry	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
other	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
three	O
washerwomen	O
that	O
were	O
washing	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
to	O
serve	O
them	O
out	O
with	O
soap	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
necessary	O
when	O
they	O
wanted	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
off	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
particular	O
care	O
over	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
were	O
the	O
woman	O
there	O
washing	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
order	O
before	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
order	O
not	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
after	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
look	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
late	O
before	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
home	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
way	O
from	O
Brompton	O
to	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
return	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
barrow	O
and	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
candle	O
alight	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
window	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
left	O
burning	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
we	O
always	O
live	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
that	O
laid	O
over	O
the	O
washhouse	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
board	O
that	O
we	O
lift	O
up	O
to	O
letthe	O
steam	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
going	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
afraid	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
possible	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
you	O
take	O
another	O
candle	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
is	O
there	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
through	O
every	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
beds	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
we	O
sleep	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
nobody	O
but	O
the	O
dogs	O
,	O
one	O
large	O
one	O
and	O
one	O
little	O
one	O
that	O
we	O
keep	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
that	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
leave	O
Margaret	O
Rrice	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
my	O
wife	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
some	O
person	O
has	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
one	O
candle	O
and	O
she	O
with	O
another	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
the	O
caps	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
your	O
husband	O
searched	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
missed	O
was	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
was	O
two	O
habit	O
shirts	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
gowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
the	O
caps	O
at	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
caps	O
are	O
valued	O
at	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
piece	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
habit	O
shirts	O
they	O
are	O
valued	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
them	O
at	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
value	O
them	O
at	O
ten	O
shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
petticoats	O
at	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
valued	O
at	O
sixpence	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
the	O
bedgown	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
at	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
bonnet	O
at	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
worth	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
worth	O
about	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
worth	O
five	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
.	O
A.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
that	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
new	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
four	O
pounds	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
receipt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
particular	O
marks	O
it	O
has	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
lately	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
to	O
town	O
I	O
gave	O
she	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
drawers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
traced	O
her	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
Bow	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
eighth	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
No	O
.	O
73	O
,	O
Great	O
Peter	O
street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
clothes	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
and	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
master	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
bonnet	O
the	O
officer	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
afterwards	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Barrow	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
what	O
parish	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Kensington	O
,	O
in	O
Brompton	O
division	O
,	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
collect	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
Kensington	O
parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Kensington	O
parish	O
.	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
further	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
particular	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
examine	O
where	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
other	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
reason	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
recollecting	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
separate	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
With	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
that	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
down	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
tea	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
,	O
Peggy	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
found	O
the	O
bonnet	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
bonnet	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
what	O
the	O
officer	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
this	O
girl	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
five	O
pound	O
note	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
till	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
suspect	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
call	O
five	O
hundred	O
witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
away	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
is	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
DRYDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
below	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
as	O
to	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
over	O
the	O
washhouse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
door	O
fastened	O
below	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
double	O
lock	O
and	O
and	O
two	O
bolts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
leaving	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
my	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
the	O
dogs	O
in	O
to	O
protect	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
the	O
gates	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
defence	O
to	O
her	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
youth	O
and	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
]	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
575.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
forty-fourth	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Mac	O
Felon	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
and	O
take	O
to	O
wife	O
one	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pooley	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pooley	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
register	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
register	O
of	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
1804	O
.	O
-	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
of	O
this	O
parish	O
,	O
bachelor	O
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
parish	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
this	O
church	O
by	O
banns	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
1804	O
,	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
rector	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
bachelor	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
and	O
Sophia	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
were	O
present	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
parties	O
yourself	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pooley	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Watts	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
at	O
Whitechapel	O
church	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
witnessed	O
that	O
marriage	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pooley	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
lately	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
