TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1807	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT	O
HAND	O
BY	O
JOB	O
SIBLY	O
,	O
FOR	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
117	O
,	O
ALDERSGATE-STREET	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right-honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
Soulden	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
Simon	B-pers
Le-Blanc	I-pers
,	O
knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Newnham	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
Glynn	O
,	O
bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
bart	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bloxand	I-pers
,	O
knt	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Scholey	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
Newman	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beeby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buzzard	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Utting	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bolden	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Lethbridge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Somers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
FIRST	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maine	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Berrow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
Clement	B-pers
Chaple	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wardle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Aquilla	I-pers
Brown	O
,	O
Bennet	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	I-pers
William	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
.	O
SECOND	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Ivey	B-pers
Aires	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cuthurst	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Tullett	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
523.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROSE	I-pers
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Skegil	I-pers
.	O
MARY	O
SKEGIL	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
,	O
at	O
Spring-gardens	B-place
,	I-place
under	I-place
Spring-garden-chapel	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Spring-garden	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
my	O
apartments	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
left	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
apartment	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
his	O
coat	O
of	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
and	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
abusive	O
language	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
things	O
against	O
a	O
Greenwich-coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
drop	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
dropt	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
coach-office	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Treadway	O
the	O
officer	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
office	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
your	O
room	O
locked	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
partly	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Scotland-yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
running	O
up	O
Scotland-yard	O
towards	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Northumberland-street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach-office	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
bundle	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
office	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
DALLAS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Northumberland-street	O
,	O
Scotland-yard	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
stop	O
and	O
talk	O
to	O
a	O
publican	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
following	O
him	O
calling	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
broke	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
office	O
;	O
Treadway	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
Chiswick	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plasterer	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
cousin	O
in	O
Tothil-street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Coming	O
into	O
Spring-gardens	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
passage	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
Cockspur-street	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
past	O
Charing-cross	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
Northumberland-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
publican	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
524.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROSE	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
shawls	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
525.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
hundred	O
wine	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
twenty	O
wine	O
glass	O
decanters	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
snuffers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
copper	O
boilers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
reside	O
at	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tavern	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
this	O
indictment	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
glasses	O
and	O
decanters	O
,	O
and	O
boilers	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
either	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
or	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
deposited	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
adjoining	O
the	O
bowling-green	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
servant	O
Haley	O
.	O
MATHEW	B-pers
REDWOOD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ostler	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
boilers	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
bowling-green	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HALEY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
one	O
approach	O
towards	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
flag	O
basket	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
which	O
turned	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sack	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
hedge	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
those	O
boilers	O
were	O
concealed	O
;	O
he	O
hid	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
boilers	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
hid	O
behind	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
opposite	O
where	O
the	O
boilers	O
were	O
concealed	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
field	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
boilers	O
immediately	O
from	O
his	O
shoulders	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
boilers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
letter	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
;	O
Haley	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Haley	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
pushed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
charge	O
of	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
sack	O
and	O
the	O
boilers	O
on	O
his	O
shoulders	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gardener	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Haley	O
)	O
Are	O
they	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
you	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
boilers	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
glasses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
first	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
of	O
your	O
bowling	O
green	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
first	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
the	O
usual	O
hour	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Stoke	O
Newington	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
by	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
by	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
you	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
a-bed	O
by	O
ten	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
perfectly	O
recollected	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
by	O
himself	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
while	O
we	O
had	O
our	O
supper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
last	O
seen	O
these	O
boilers	O
on	O
your	O
premises	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
affixed	O
in	O
brickwork	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Homerton	O
going	O
along	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
edge	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
yours	O
,	O
lay	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
41	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
one	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
526	O
MARY	B-pers
DUFFY	I-pers
alias	I-pers
BRALEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
indictment	O
stated	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
general	O
quarter	O
sessions	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
holden	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Kent	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
46th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
common	O
utterer	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
in	O
the	O
goal	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
county	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
one	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
find	O
sureties	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
two	O
year	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
indictment	O
further	O
stated	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
money	O
,	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
shilling	O
;	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
utter	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
she	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
only	O
stating	O
that	O
she	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
utter	O
a	O
counterfeited	O
shilling	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
CALEB	B-pers
EDWARD	I-pers
POWELL	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
produce	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
the	O
clerk	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Kent	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
copy	O
(	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
NICHOLAS	I-pers
MASTER	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
quarter	O
sessions	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
,	O
January	O
28th	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
witness	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
sentence	O
pronounced	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Perfectly	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
purchase	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
she	O
bargained	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
in	O
consideration	O
of	O
her	O
poor	O
appearance	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
her	O
worth	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
sounded	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
,	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
back	O
the	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
shilling	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
gave	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
itself	O
on	O
the	O
ledge	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
laid	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
woman	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
purchased	O
a	O
lamb	O
's	O
heart	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
four	O
pence	O
;	O
she	O
tendered	O
another	O
shilling	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
being	O
tendered	O
to	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
:	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
officer	O
Franklin	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
here	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
indeed	O
madam	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
here	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
look	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
here	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
article	O
that	O
you	O
purchased	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
basket	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
Oh	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
basket	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
articles	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
We	O
gave	O
both	O
the	O
shillings	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
shilling	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ledge	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
shilling	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
that	O
the	O
shilling	O
that	O
you	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
ledge	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
shilling	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
shilling	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
my	O
servant	O
changing	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
your	O
reason	O
for	O
saying	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
shilling	O
;	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
your	O
man	O
would	O
change	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WORREL	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
servant	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
giving	O
you	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
part	O
with	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
that	O
shilling	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
returned	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
by	O
itself	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
the	O
lady	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
examined	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
pay	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
for	O
a	O
lamb	O
's	O
heart	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
steel	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
this	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
bad	O
shilling	O
just	O
now	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
tried	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
steel	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
bad	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Franklin	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
Franklin	O
came	O
did	O
any	O
conversation	O
take	O
place	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
your	O
wife	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
veal	O
that	O
she	O
purchased	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
veal	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
purchased	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
When	O
Franklin	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
what	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
called	O
a	O
smasher	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
chin	O
and	O
she	O
swallowed	O
something	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
searchedher	O
pockets	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
basket	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
sugar	O
,	O
potatoes	O
,	O
spinage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
veal	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
'the	O
basket	O
in	O
small	O
quantities	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
both	O
the	O
shillings	O
to	O
Franklin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FRANKLIN	I-pers
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
woman	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
called	O
a	O
smasher	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
separate	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
spinage	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
veal	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
veal	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
ten	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
all	O
good	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
,	O
send	O
her	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
right	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
after	O
me	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
mouth	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
why	O
;	O
she	O
swallowed	O
very	O
hard	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
nick	O
against	O
her	O
teeth	O
.	O
Going	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
she	O
said	O
why	O
should	O
you	O
wish	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
does	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
you	O
sending	O
me	O
to	O
goal	O
for	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
you	O
another	O
day	O
and	O
make	O
you	O
amends	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
more	O
in	O
my	O
mouth	O
than	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
gentlemen	O
have	O
.	O
MR.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NICOLLS	I-pers
-	I-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
monier	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
mint	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
tell	O
us	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
good	O
or	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
both	O
counterfeits	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
appear	O
different	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
more	O
bad	O
shillings	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
bring	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
than	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
sixteen	O
weeks	O
in	O
goal	O
and	O
fed	O
upon	O
bread	O
and	O
water	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
527.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BOWERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sizer	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Sizer	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sizer	I-pers
and	O
others	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sizer	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Sizer	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
count	O
the	O
same	O
offence	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
only	O
stating	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sizer	I-pers
only	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOODSON	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Coventry	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
close	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sizer	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
drawing	O
something	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
at	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
drawed	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
EDWARD	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
live	O
in	O
Coventry-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
any	O
alarm	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
pick	O
up	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
witness	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
moment	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
such	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
all	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
window	O
when	O
you	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
then	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
glass	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
spot	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
appear	O
cut	O
or	O
broke	O
by	O
violence	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
put	O
two	O
hands	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
528.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLACKMORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HILLIARD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Green's-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
Edward	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
when	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
five	O
pound	O
bank	O
note	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
my	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
when	O
I	O
shifted	O
myself	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
then	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
by	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
soldier	O
had	O
not	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
tape	O
that	O
I	O
tied	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
handkerchief	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wipe	O
my	O
razor	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
to	O
some	O
jew	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
.	O
JAMES	O
GILLMORE	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
or	O
landlady	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
turn-screw	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
instrument	O
made	O
useof	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
exactly	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
lined	O
with	O
blue	O
paper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
turn	O
screw	O
was	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
blue	O
paper	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
slept	O
with	O
a	O
girl	O
the	O
very	O
night	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
red	O
tape	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
pounds	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
that	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
change	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
RENNY	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
three	O
shirts	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
of	O
corporal	O
Bates	O
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
NATHAN	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
private	O
unless	O
he	O
brought	O
his	O
serjeant	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
serjeant	O
before	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
serjeant	O
:	O
the	O
corporal	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
BATES	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
corporal	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
Nathan	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
serjeant	O
Ball	O
's	O
apartment	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
CORBITT	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
private	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
regiment	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
desert	O
the	O
regiment	O
,	O
a	O
sea	O
officer	O
had	O
offered	O
him	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
recruit	O
house	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Tothil-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
five	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
shillingsworth	O
of	O
gin	O
and	O
rasberry	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
drink	O
together	O
before	O
we	O
parted	O
;	O
he	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
five	O
pound	O
note	O
changed	O
at	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
's	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
Princes-street	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
report	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
regiment	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
corporal	O
Lovey	O
.	O
RICHARD	O
GRIFFITHS	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Richard	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
-	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Hilliard	O
lodges	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
quartered	O
upon	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
Hilliard	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
Hilliard	O
complained	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
529.	O
ANN	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Craig	I-pers
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
ROBERT	O
ROBERTS	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Craig	I-pers
,	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
516	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
walk	O
down	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
calicoes	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
there	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
her	O
occasionally	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
make	O
motions	O
with	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
shop	O
as	O
if	O
her	O
legs	O
were	O
tied	O
close	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
serve	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Craig	O
said	O
one	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
print	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
OWEN	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Craig	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
lad	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
examined	O
telling	O
you	O
his	O
suspicions	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taking	O
something	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
print	O
actually	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
lad	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
warm	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
young	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
engaged	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
nothing	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
530.	O
PETER	B-pers
BURKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Macarty	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
twenty-four	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
SIMON	B-pers
WALSH	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
reside	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
Ratcliffe	O
Highway	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Macarty	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
,	I-place
Ratcliffe-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
remained	O
there	O
till	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
property	O
in	O
your	O
possession	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
fifty-two	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
sixty	O
pounds	O
in	O
bank	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
twenty	O
pound	O
,	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
,	O
two	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
bank	O
note	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
had	O
you	O
that	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
brewer	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
notes	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Boyle	O
,	O
a	O
seaman	O
,	O
that	O
lodged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Bell	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
room	O
would	O
be	O
vacant	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
settle	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
money	O
accounts	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
private	O
room	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
ale	O
.	O
Me	O
and	O
Boyle	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
were	O
together	O
then	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
shortly	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
continue	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
Boyle	O
stopped	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
toss	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
ofwine	O
;	O
we	O
tossed	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dispute	O
in	O
tossing	O
,	O
and	O
Boyle	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
finished	O
one	O
bottle	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
persons	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
remained	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
remain	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Boyle	O
out	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
)	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
conversation	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
slept	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
remained	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
your	O
money	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
where	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
awoke	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
twenty	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
thirty-five	O
pounds	O
in	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
awoke	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Nobody	O
but	O
myself	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
sweeping	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
Boyle	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
Boyle	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
particular	O
of	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
soon	O
recollect	O
the	O
indorsement	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
endorsed	O
RAB	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
recollection	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
;	O
the	O
landlady	O
and	O
Burke	O
shewed	O
me	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
underneath	O
the	O
new	O
clothes	O
there	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
purse	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
,	O
1713	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
dent	O
on	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
lay	O
no	O
claim	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
landlady	O
examined	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
guinea	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
there	O
was	O
twenty	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
chiefly	O
in	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
gold	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
discovered	O
these	O
new	O
clothes	O
and	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
them	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
A	O
R	O
B	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
in	O
payment	O
for	O
his	O
porter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
examination	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
restitution	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
this	O
pocket	O
book	O
and	O
that	O
card	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
that	O
he	O
changed	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
note	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Spaniard	O
by	O
birth	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
navy	O
thirteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
the	O
Superb	O
.	O
Since	O
then	O
I	O
served	O
in	O
the	O
Invincible	O
of	O
Deptford	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
alledges	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
change	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
assert	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
untill	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
found	O
me	O
on	O
any	O
day	O
or	O
hour	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
probable	O
that	O
I	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
changed	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
also	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seventeen	O
pounds	O
prize	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
doubloons	O
I	O
brought	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saved	O
up	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
.	O
Under	O
all	O
these	O
circumstances	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
acquit	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
all	O
my	O
clothes	O
and	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
will	O
shew	O
where	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
531.	O
LOUISA	B-pers
BRIAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LAWSON	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
to	O
John	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Upper	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
and	O
clasped	O
her	O
hand	O
round	O
my	O
waist	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
she	O
walked	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
made	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
dragged	O
her	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
was	O
dragging	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
being	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
your	O
watch	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
she	O
clasped	O
her	O
hand	O
round	O
your	O
waist	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
feel	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
down	O
my	O
thigh	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
you	O
felt	O
caused	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
your	O
hand	O
down	O
directly	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOWLER	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
this	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
dragging	O
the	O
woman	O
along	O
towards	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
her	O
hands	O
were	O
liberated	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
keeper	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SANDERS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchhouse	O
keeper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
that	O
man	O
accosted	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
close	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
one	O
guinea	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
take	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
thewatch	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
brutal	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
dragged	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q.to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
532.	O
SOPHIA	B-pers
HUBBARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Did	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DID	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
9	I-place
,	I-place
Saffron-place	I-place
,	I-place
Saffron-hill	I-place
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A.He	O
lets	O
the	O
house	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
one	O
adjoining	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
Sophia	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
apartment	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
slight	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
her	O
excuse	O
was	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
staid	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
dinner	O
was	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
staid	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
stop	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
a	O
stranger	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
two	O
nights	O
and	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
drowsy	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
liquor	O
,	O
not	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
nobody	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
slept	O
till	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
I	O
awoke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
hung	O
my	O
key	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
altogether	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
hung	O
in	O
its	O
usual	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
From	O
information	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Little	O
Saffron-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
fetched	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
strip	O
her	O
to	O
see-whether	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
on	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
counted	O
out	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
she	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
new	O
money	O
except	O
one	O
seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
bent	O
one	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
frequently	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
After	O
several	O
times	O
threatening	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
she	O
pulled	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
counted	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HANCOCK	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
constable	O
delivered	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
me	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
asleep	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sophia	B-pers
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
gin	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
to	O
dinner	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
he	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
came	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
searched	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hancock	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Baylis	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
any	O
purpose	O
.	O
-	O
A.No	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
533.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GARLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
KINDER	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kinder	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
opening	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
iron	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
from	O
a	O
pile	O
of	O
goods	O
that	O
stood	O
right	O
opposite	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
very	O
quick	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
covered	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
a	O
morning	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
foot	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
reprimanded	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
64	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
534.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RICHARDS	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
watch	O
manufacturer	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridgwater-square	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
employ	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
principally	O
to	O
melt	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
his	O
leisure	O
hours	O
at	O
his	O
trade	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
case	O
maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
years	O
had	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
aknowledge	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
numbers	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
underneath	O
the	O
desk	O
in	O
the	O
accounting	O
house	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
the	O
dates	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
value	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
book	O
here	O
.	O
Having	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
dates	O
and	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
tin	O
box	O
which	O
was	O
underneath	O
the	O
desk	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
some	O
information	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
did	O
you	O
examine	O
your	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
immediately	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
and	O
examined	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
notes	O
there	O
,	O
wanting	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
nearest	O
his	O
dwelling	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Milley	O
keeps	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
second	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
corresponded	O
to	O
the	O
date	O
,	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
amount	O
of	O
that	O
note	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
the	O
note	O
(	O
note	O
produced	O
)	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
dated	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
35,100	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
What	O
year	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
taken	O
the	O
date	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
35,100	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
my	O
note	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
coin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
coin	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
entrusted	O
to	O
melt	O
two	O
quantities	O
of	O
that	O
coin	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BENBY	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
apprentice	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
do	O
you	O
recollect	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
being	O
absent	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
accompting	O
house	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
keep	O
watching	O
the	O
accompting	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
who	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
accompting	O
house	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
eight	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
accompting	O
house	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
hours	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
watching	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MILLEY	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hare	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
publican	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
book	O
among	O
other	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
But	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gleed	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
'	O
belonging	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
I	O
received	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Milley	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
I	O
deny	O
ever	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
555.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Firmin	B-pers
de	I-pers
Taster	I-pers
.	O
FERMIN	B-pers
DE	I-pers
TASTER	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
-	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
footman	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
de	O
Taster	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
inventory	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
counted	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
inventory	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
missing	O
from	O
that	O
inventory	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
cream	O
jug	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
:	O
I	O
counted	O
all	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
inventory	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
CARTWRIGHT	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
city	O
constable	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
de	O
Taster	O
's	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
his	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
searching	O
a	O
cupboard	O
in	O
his	O
apartment	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
hats	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
undermost	O
hat	O
had	O
the	O
duplicates	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
produced	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
one	O
duplicate	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
1807	O
,	O
one	O
spoon	O
for	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
pledged	O
at	O
Barker	O
's	O
,	O
91	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
agitated	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
hats	O
situated	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
pantry	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sleeps	O
and	O
keeps	O
his	O
clothes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TOTTERY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
91	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
duplicate	O
produced	O
by	O
Cartwright	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
your	O
duplicate	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
spoon	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
34	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
556.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
carpet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Herbert	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
HERBERT	B-pers
BROOM	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partners	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
we	O
are	O
carpet	O
manufacturers	O
,	O
our	O
warehouse	O
is	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
a	O
carpet	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
Crabb	O
the	O
officer	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
carpets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
any	O
transactions	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
frequently	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
proceeding	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
requested	O
permission	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
our	O
porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
porter	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
John	B-pers
Daniels	I-pers
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
sent	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
the	O
tender	O
.	O
ELISHA	B-pers
CRAB	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
Cutler's-street	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
carpet	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
officers	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
carpet	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
five	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
first	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
sudden	O
spring	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
his	O
jacket	O
,	O
the	O
jacket	O
tore	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
the	O
jacket	O
gave	O
way	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
into	O
Cammomile-street	O
into	O
a	O
mews	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
property	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
hit	O
me	O
down	O
when	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
hit	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
could	O
till	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
carpet	O
you	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
same	O
carpet	O
you	O
shewed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Broom	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
carpet	O
before	O
he	O
sat	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
for	O
him	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HART	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
also	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
carpet	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
paper	O
is	O
our	O
clerk	O
's	O
writing	O
,	O
it	O
certifies	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
carpet	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
557.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
twenty	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stirtevant	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STIRTEVANT	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
flannel	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MEAD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Angel-alley	O
,	O
Bishopgate-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Angel-passage	O
,	O
Angel-alley	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
for	O
God	O
sake	O
let	O
me	O
pass	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shephard	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SHEPHARD	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
flannel	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Confined	O
Two	O
Months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
558.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PETHER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
to	O
the	O
jurors	O
unknown	O
.	O
THOMAS	O
BRERETON	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Downes	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
past	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
alternately	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
they	O
followed	O
it	O
till	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
then	O
the	O
tallest	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
jumped	O
up	O
and	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
by	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
perhaps	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
suppose	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
returned	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
,	O
called	O
some	O
name	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
come	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
through	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
into	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
patrol	O
stood	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
of	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
patrol	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
coat	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
The	O
patrol	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
Chancery-lane	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Towards	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
duskish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Therefore	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
might	O
not	O
hand	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
coat	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
driver	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
empty	O
chaise	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
driver	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
men	O
went	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
ANTHONY	O
M'DONALD	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Chancery-lane	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
up	O
a	O
dark	O
court	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
out	O
into	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
that	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
,	O
he	O
kicked	O
his	O
foot	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
559.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
ROBERT	I-pers
UTTING	I-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
general	O
quarter	O
sessions	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
forty	O
sixth	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
common	O
utterer	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
money	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
shilling	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
sentenced	O
and	O
adjudged	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
one	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
money	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
shilling	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
did	O
utter	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
for	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
only	O
varying	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
charging	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
CALEB	O
EDWARD	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
produce	O
the	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
original	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
copy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
his	O
conviction	O
.	O
(	O
Copy	O
of	O
record	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BEEBY	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newport	O
,	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
court	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
mentioned	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
receive	O
sentence	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
afterwards	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
he	O
remained	O
there	O
for	O
one	O
year	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	O
Sweedish	O
Crowns	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
he	O
tendered	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
gin	O
came	O
to	O
two	O
pence	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
ten	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
came	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
copper	O
enough	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
taking	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
another	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
colleague	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Charlton	B-pers
the	O
headborough	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wished	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
supposed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
he	O
shook	O
very	O
much	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
agitation	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Mr	O
Charlton	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
getting	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
unsuccessful	O
;	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
other	O
shillings	O
that	O
were	O
like	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
he	O
tendered	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
sixpence	O
and	O
ten	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Charlton	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
step	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
road	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
shilling	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
separate	O
,	O
I	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
shilling	O
that	O
was	O
tendered	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
separate	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
desk	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
shilling	O
that	O
was	O
tendered	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
taken	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
shillings	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
my	O
sister	O
in	O
law	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
left	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
your	O
sister	O
in	O
law	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
shilling	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
While	O
you	O
were	O
gone	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
put	O
that	O
shilling	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
magistrate	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
mixed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
magistrate	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
my	O
teeth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
altogether	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
feel	O
a	O
difficulty	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
magistrate	O
I	O
could	O
discover	O
that	O
one	O
by	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
my	O
teeth	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
see	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
B	O
put	O
upon	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
magistrate	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
mark	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
try	O
them	O
with	O
your	O
teeth	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
shilling	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
shilling	O
.	O
MR.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NICOLL	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
piece	O
he	O
uttered	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
offered	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
counterfeited	O
one	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
has	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
put	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
are	O
all	O
counterfeits	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
all	O
alike	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
they	O
vary	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
vary	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
crooked	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
intoxicated	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
few	O
friends	O
;	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
requisite	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
that	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
coachman	O
:	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
can	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
560.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
HAYWARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Case	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
MARY	O
ORE.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Myers	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Church-row	O
,	O
Islington	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
leave	O
Islington	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
Brighton	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
health	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
early	O
part	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Myers	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
during	O
your	O
absence	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
return	O
did	O
you	O
perceive	O
any	O
wine	O
missing	O
from	O
your	O
cellar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Before	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
repeatedly	O
mentioned	O
the	O
circumstance	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
drinking	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Brighton	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
your	O
cellar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
entrusted	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
discover	O
after	O
your	O
return	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
your	O
garden	O
gate	O
would	O
open	O
your	O
wine	O
cellar	O
.	O
-	O
A.Afterwards	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
unlock	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
DOBSON	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ore.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
During	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Ore	O
's	O
absence	O
at	O
Brighton	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
visit	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
wine	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
took	O
a	O
key	O
from	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
wine	O
cellar	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Ore	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
wine	O
cellar	O
door	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
whenever	O
she	O
pleased	O
;	O
the	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
stock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
large	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
wine	O
and	O
spirits	O
of	O
every	O
sort	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
wine	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
my	O
mistress	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
intimate	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
further	O
than	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
seem	O
very	O
comely	O
and	O
well	O
made	O
-	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
friar	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
singular	O
she	O
made	O
this	O
free	O
confession	O
to	O
you	O
-	O
she	O
knew	O
you	O
were	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
fond	O
of	O
drinking	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
character	O
you	O
deserve	O
-	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
called	O
in	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Although	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
sober	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
wine	O
cellar	O
and	O
show	O
you	O
how	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
-	O
you	O
never	O
tasted	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
wine	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
Because	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
copper	O
hole	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Ore	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
the	O
information	O
from	O
this	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
defence	O
to	O
her	O
counsel	O
,	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
561.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
HAYWARD	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
three	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
white	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ore	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
,	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
,	O
declining	O
to	O
offer	O
any	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
562.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HYLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
chaise	O
harness	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Westall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WESTALL	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Westall	I-pers
,	O
144	B-place
Long	I-place
Acre	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
harness	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
parts	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
peg	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
calling	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
dropped	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
harness	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
harness	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
peg	O
;	O
the	O
bridle	O
of	O
the	O
harness	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
peg	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
harness	O
was	O
not	O
complete	O
without	O
the	O
bridle	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
563	O
MARGARET	B-pers
HOLMES	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
FRAINE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
sixty	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ALEXANDER	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
128	B-place
Brick-lane	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Matthew	I-place
Bethnal	I-place
Green	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
printed	O
cottons	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Holmes	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
in	O
Church-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
there	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
I	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
;	O
they	O
separated	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
Worship-street	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
the	O
officer	O
found	O
upon	O
Holmes	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
persons	O
belonging	O
to	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
;	O
a	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
girls	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Gill	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
Holmes	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
Gill	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Holmes	O
outside	O
of	O
your	O
door	O
,	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
might	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Gill	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
MARIA	O
FRITH	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
near	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
speaking	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
baby	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
gown	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
some	O
cloth	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
.	O
-	O
A.No	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
no	O
women	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
that	O
gave	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
Holmes	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
LAMLY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
:	O
we	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
turned	O
down	O
Church-street	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
women	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Holmes	O
walking	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
before	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
if	O
that	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
before	O
Holmes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
holding	O
her	O
apron	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
corners	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
on	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
own	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
instant	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
lap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
three	O
women	O
and	O
MargaretHolmes	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
speak	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
Holmes	O
.	O
JOHN	O
VICKREY	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
The	O
Irish	O
linen	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
cap	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
whom	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
afterwards	O
by	O
Hancock	O
.	O
JAMES	O
HANCOCK	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
that	O
Gill	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
duplicates	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
together	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
Frith	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
these	O
women	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
None	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
three	O
women	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
:	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
three	O
women	O
talked	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Gill	O
introduced	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
as	O
customers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
looked	O
at	O
ribbands	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
HOLMES	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
27	O
.	O
GILL	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
justice	O
Le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
564.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
O'BRIAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
upon	O
Hannah	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
three	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
DAVEY	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Starch-green	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
a	O
blacksmith	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
gardens	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
gardens	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
William	O
Sparks	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
