TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1807	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT	O
HAND	O
BY	O
JOB	B-pers
SIBLY	I-pers
,	O
FOR	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
1807	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LORD	I-pers
ELLENBOROUGH	I-pers
,	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
SIR	O
GILES	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
Harvey	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Combe	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perring	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowcroft	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Claudius	B-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
Newman	B-pers
Knowlys	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nottingham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Kippen	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hoppey	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Stanfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allwinkle	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brander	I-pers
.	O
FIRST	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Antell	I-pers
,	O
Wiliam	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maycock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lapworth	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Speare	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gomm	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pater	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fawcett	I-pers
.	O
SECOND	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mullet	I-pers
,	O
Allen	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Speare	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Faulkener	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cofton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Nathan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
254.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
EVE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RYAN	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
's	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
2	I-place
,	I-place
Short's-lane	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
bed	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
by	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
I	O
awoke	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
necessary	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
coat	O
to	O
a	O
jew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
crown	O
piece	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coat	O
pocket	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
the	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
DONALDSON	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
necessary	O
in	O
Pipe-maker	O
's	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
duplicates	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
down	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
key	O
;	O
on	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
duplicates	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
this	O
poor	O
fellow	O
's	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
jew	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
dollar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
brought	O
the	O
lock	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
key	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fits	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
25	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
255.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
THORPE	I-pers
and	O
ZACHARIAH	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Devitt	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Dutch	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Pile	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
ten	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
ten	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
sauce	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
eleven	O
silver	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Devitt	I-pers
,	O
esquire	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DUTCH	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Landsdowne-place	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Devitt	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
step	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
there	O
is	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
chimney-sweeper	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
that	O
plate	O
been	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
steps	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
hat	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
step	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
for	O
the	O
beadle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
other	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
what	O
Thorpe	O
said	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
the	O
beadle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PILE	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Devitt	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
witness	O
Dutch	O
bring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
bring	O
the	O
hat	O
with	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Thorpe	O
's	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
farthest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LILLYWHITE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
beadle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Devitt	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Thorpe	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
plate	O
delivered	O
into	O
your	O
charge	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
ten	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
eleven	O
forks	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
sauce	O
spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Pile	O
)	O
You	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
plate	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
Mr.	O
Devitt	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Devitt	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
marked	O
with	O
my	O
crest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Pile	O
)	O
Who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
you	O
and	O
Dutch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
maid	O
servants	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
boy	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
employed	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thorpe	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
worked	O
very	O
heard	O
for	O
my	O
living	O
.	O
Fisher	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
THORPE	O
-	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
12	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
FISHER	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Thorpe	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
]	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
256.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TODD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hollister	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
broach	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
pin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hollister	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HOLLISTER	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
21	I-place
,	I-place
Charlotte-street	I-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
road	I-place
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Charles	B-pers
Hollister	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
fine	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
immediately	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
rushed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
another	O
at	O
the	O
handles	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
drawers	O
open	O
and	O
shut	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
see	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
rushed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
cill	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
from	O
me	O
through	O
a	O
court	O
that	O
is	O
facing	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
fallen	O
down	O
.	O
Immediately	O
another	O
man	O
rushed	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
stepped	O
upon	O
me	O
in	O
getting	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
recovered	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
discription	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clitherow	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
time	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
that	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
man	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
afterwards	O
is	O
he	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
altered	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
like	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
my	O
gloves	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
for	O
many	O
days	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
he	O
same	O
drawer	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
this	O
public	O
house	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Hollister	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Pretty	O
nigh	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
CLITHEROW	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
About	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Hollister	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
description	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
-	O
KENNEDY	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
fourteen	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
off	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
257.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
.	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
waiscoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Quirk	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
QUIRK	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
8	I-place
,	I-place
Spread-Eagle	I-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
Gray's-Inn	I-place
lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Marybone	O
infirmary	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
that	O
I	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
infirmary	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
property	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
wore	O
it	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Devil	O
tempted	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
besides	O
your	O
coat	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
24	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
258.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SIMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
five	O
bibles	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STOCKDALE	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
'	I-place
.	O
The	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
stolen	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
auction	O
room	O
,	O
adjoining	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
dwell	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
son	O
that	O
sleeps	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
close	O
of	O
the	O
sale	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
tying	O
some	O
books	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
tying	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
tying	O
up	O
a	O
bible	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
clerk	O
that	O
takes	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
delivers	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
watch	O
over	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
finding	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
,	O
untied	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
which	O
contained	O
a	O
large	O
quarto	O
bible	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
sale	O
had	O
closed	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
auctioneer	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
detected	O
a	O
person	O
stealing	O
a	O
bible	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Bow	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
duplicates	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
duplicates	O
led	O
to	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
books	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Those	O
books	O
were	O
not	O
taken	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Confine	O
yourself	O
to	O
the	O
bible	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
sold	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
therefore	O
whether	O
he	O
sold	O
books	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
possibly	O
know	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
rather	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
only	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
this	O
bible	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prior	O
lots	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
twenty-four	O
shillings	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
bought	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
who	O
bid	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HURL	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
occasion	O
I	O
officiated	O
as	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stockdale	O
's	O
sale	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
his	O
selling	O
any	O
bible	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
bible	O
sold	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
of	O
that	O
size	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
demy	O
quarto	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
sale	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
bid	O
for	O
that	O
bible	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taffey	O
for	O
one	O
pound	O
five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
this	O
book	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Stockdale	O
speaking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
book	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
one	O
pound	O
four	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
lot	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taffey	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
pound	O
five	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
bible	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
259.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HOUGH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Maycock	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MAYCOCK	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
purchased	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
flannel	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
cotton	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
untied	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
her	O
apron	O
was	O
folded	O
up	O
on	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
woman	O
put	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
the	O
flannel	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
untied	O
my	O
apron	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
36	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
260.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SUTTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
gold	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edney	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	O
EDNEY	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
auctioner	O
and	O
appraiser	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
.	O
My	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Philip	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
watch	O
or	O
seals	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
and	O
two	O
gold	O
seals	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
a	O
silversmith	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Emanuel	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
sold	O
in	O
the	O
sale	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
sale	O
we	O
generally	O
returned	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
some	O
lots	O
that	O
were	O
unsold	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
returned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
made	O
application	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
account	O
;	O
he	O
suggested	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbrokers	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
immediately	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WINFIELD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
178	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
hatter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bristol	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
business	O
very	O
slack	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
is	O
own	O
watch	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Emanuel	O
called	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
EMANUEL	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Winfield	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
purchase	O
some	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Edney	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
when	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Edney	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Generally	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
particularly	O
by	O
the	O
chain	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
jack	O
chain	O
than	O
a	O
watch	O
chain	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Emanuel	O
)	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
chain	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
you	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edney	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
book	O
here	O
I	O
could	O
produce	O
the	O
number	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
without	O
entering	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
chain	O
only	O
.	O
Privately	O
Whipped	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
261.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GUN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
three	O
barrels	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
hundred	O
gallons	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
Villebois	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Villebois	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sampson	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOWSER	I-pers
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
EWINGS	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
Mile	O
End	O
New-town	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
turn	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
continued	O
there	O
till	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
my	O
round	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
ale	I-place
house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Pelham-street	I-place
,	O
there	O
stood	O
a	O
dray	O
with	O
seven	O
barrels	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
fronting	O
the	O
George	O
ale	O
house	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
standing	O
with	O
the	O
dray	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
whip	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
curb	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
dray	O
and	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Gun	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
bottle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
off	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
store	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
seven	O
barrels	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
starting	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
beat	O
.	O
The	O
store	O
house	O
belongs	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Hanbury	O
and	O
Co	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Gun	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
empty	O
dray	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
set	O
there	O
for	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
and	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
might	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
finger	O
wanting	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
drove	O
off	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
the	O
brew-house	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
five	O
o'clock	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
dray	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
store	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
barrel	O
go	O
off	O
the	O
dray	O
into	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
barrel	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
offside	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
chalk	O
to	O
mark	O
the	O
dray	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
then	O
with	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
dray	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
shafts	O
of	O
the	O
dray	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
mark	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
two	O
crosses	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
one	O
cross	O
and	O
a	O
stroke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
chalk	O
fell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
barrels	O
were	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
dray	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Seven	O
remained	O
on	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
I	O
saw	O
carried	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
walked	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Gun	O
quickly	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
and	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
before	O
five	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Gun	O
said	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
there	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
come	O
and	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Where	O
they	O
were	O
starting	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
drove	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
my	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
store	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
brewer	O
s	O
men	O
there	O
pumping	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
Gun	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
handed	O
me	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
,	O
Gun	O
was	O
serving	O
out	O
some	O
gin	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Bowser	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BUTTS	I-pers
AVELING	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
principal	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
The	O
partners	O
are	O
John	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
Villebois	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Villebois	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sampson	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
any	O
information	O
from	O
Ewings	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
make	O
a	O
minute	O
investigation	O
of	O
the	O
drays	O
that	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
marks	O
on	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
drays	O
,	O
and	O
state	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
those	O
marks	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
off-shaft	O
of	O
a	O
dray	O
two	O
crosses	O
in	O
chalk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
drove	O
that	O
dray	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
had	O
driven	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
magistrates	O
of	O
Worship	O
street	O
office	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
two	O
officers	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Armstrong	O
and	O
Vickery	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
can	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
Gunn	O
who	O
drove	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
was	O
at	O
work	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
two	O
horses	O
and	O
his	O
dray	O
that	O
was	O
allotted	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Gunn	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
and	O
the	O
dray	O
at	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
or	O
the	O
storehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
horses	O
that	O
Gunn	O
drove	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
chalked	O
dray	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
.	O
-	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
proceed	O
with	O
Vickery	O
and	O
Armstrong	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
officers	O
.	O
We	O
next	O
proceeded	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
public-house	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
William	B-pers
Bowser	I-pers
;	O
when	O
we	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
return	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
our	O
drays	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
very	O
early	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
men	O
left	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
hesitated	O
for	O
an	O
instant	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
two	O
barrels	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
casks	O
where	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
one	O
barrel	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
cask	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
place	O
,	O
broke	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
staves	O
and	O
hoops	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
the	O
staves	O
and	O
the	O
hoops	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
cask	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
but	O
full	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
the	O
but	O
was	O
empty	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
put	O
the	O
beer	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
empty	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
from	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
third	O
barrel	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
drayman	O
brought	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
third	O
cask	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
that	O
the	O
staves	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
staves	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
barrels	O
;	O
he	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
beer	O
of	O
the	O
drayman	O
Gunn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
three	O
one	O
pound	O
notes	O
for	O
three	O
barrels	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
three	O
barrels	O
of	O
beer	O
worth	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Six	O
pounds	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
each	O
cask	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
One	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
One	O
cask	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
whose	O
property	O
was	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Messrs.	O
Trueman	O
,	O
Hanbury	O
and	O
Co.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
beer	O
of	O
the	O
quality	O
which	O
you	O
usually	O
furnish	O
the	O
publicans	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
store	O
beer	O
not	O
of	O
age	O
for	O
selling	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Bowser	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
line	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
quite	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
answer	O
to	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
shewed	O
you	O
this	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
induced	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
drayman	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
perquisite	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BISHOP	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moser	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Gunn	O
signed	O
any	O
paper	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Take	O
that	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
mark	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Gunn	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
examination	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moser	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
(	O
examination	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Aveling	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bowser	O
deal	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
any	O
beer	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
orders	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
police	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Gunn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
Bowser	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
cask	O
and	O
staves	O
there	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
three	O
pounds	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
perquisites	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
ADAM	B-pers
TINSLEY	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
shew	O
you	O
a	O
cask	O
and	O
some	O
staves	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
a	O
cask	O
with	O
one	O
head	O
in	O
it	O
and	O
some	O
staves	O
,	O
the	O
cask	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
Trueman	O
and	O
Hanbury	O
's	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
out	O
the	O
staves	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
two	O
complete	O
barrels	O
.	O
Gunn	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Bowser	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
Gunn	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
ale	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
civil	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
well	O
liked	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhhood	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
and	O
have	O
his	O
beer	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
home	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
wanted	O
to	O
say	O
something	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
secret	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
barrel	O
of	O
stout	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
perquisites	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
charge	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
waste	O
but	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
help	O
the	O
waste	O
but	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
time	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
start	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
should	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
my	O
attention	O
to	O
be	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
at	O
any	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
cask	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
store-house	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
orders	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
barrel	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
be	O
could	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
each	O
turn	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
horses	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
empty	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
tools	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
up	O
the	O
hoops	O
so	O
as	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
knock	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
knocking	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
the	O
beer	O
flew	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
on	O
.	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
skimmed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
froth	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
brew	O
it	O
all	O
like	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
gave	O
for	O
a	O
but	O
of	O
other	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
near	O
six	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
that	O
for	O
nine	O
pounds	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
nearly	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
four	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
one	O
barrel	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
why	O
was	O
I	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
four	O
for	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
then	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
pocket	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
three	O
pound	O
and	O
the	O
seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
supposing	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
change	O
to	O
divide	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
only	O
three	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
called	O
again	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
him	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
came	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
.	O
Gunn	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
Bowser	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUNN	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
50	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
BOWSER	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
43	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
262.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SWASH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
February	O
,	O
three	O
bird	O
cages	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
birds	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hagger	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HAGGER	I-pers
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
sign	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Blakeney	I-place
's	I-place
head	I-place
,	I-place
Norton	I-place
falgate	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
birds	O
and	O
the	O
cages	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
tap	O
room	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
cages	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
birds	O
,	O
(	O
witness	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
cages	O
and	O
my	O
birds	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
goldfinch	O
,	O
a	O
linnet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chaffinch	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
goldfinch	O
first	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
linnet	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
chaffinch	O
.	O
From	O
information	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Finsbury	O
square	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
tied	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
cages	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
birds	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
three	O
birds	O
and	O
my	O
three	O
cages	O
,	O
each	O
bird	O
was	O
in	O
its	O
own	O
cage	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
birds	O
and	O
my	O
cages	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
cages	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
shillings	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
chaffinch	O
and	O
a	O
linnet	O
in	O
cages	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
goldfinch	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
the	O
birds	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
chaffice	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hagger	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
bird	O
and	O
a	O
linnet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
goldfinch	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
Finsbury	O
square	O
with	O
three	O
birds	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
cages	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
three	O
cages	O
only	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Lord	O
Ellenborough	O
.	O
263.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLARKSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
'	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
and	O
wittingly	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
and	O
possession	O
divers	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
four	O
bank	O
notes	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
each	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
for	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
indictment	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
264.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLARKSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
governor	O
and	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
for	O
feloniously	O
disposing	O
of	O
and	O
putting	O
away	O
a	O
like	O
forged	O
note	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
intention	O
.	O
And	O
two	O
other	O
counts	O
for	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
only	O
stating	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
,	O
declining	O
to	O
offer	O
any	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
this	O
charge	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
265.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BENNS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
eighty	O
bushels	O
of	O
beans	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
nine	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brickwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
PIKE	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
carman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brickwood	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brickwood	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
order	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
draw	O
ten	O
quarters	O
of	O
beans	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Keeps	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
order	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
sacks	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Brickwood	O
's	O
storehouse	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
loaded	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
sacks	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Twenty	O
sacks	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
New	B-place
Cut	I-place
windmill	I-place
,	I-place
Blackfriar's-road	I-place
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Keep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
paper	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
folded	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Keep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
the	O
beans	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Keep	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
beans	O
and	O
the	O
sacks	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
shooting	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
BRICKWOOD	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cornfactor	O
and	O
corn-merchant	O
living	O
at	O
Broken	O
wharf	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
foreman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
beans	O
in	O
your	O
granary	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
had	O
made	O
this	O
discovery	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
endeavour	O
to	O
ascertain	O
what	O
quantity	O
was	O
deficient	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
my	O
deficiency	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
above	O
forty	O
quarters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Forty	O
shillings	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Keep	O
were	O
examined	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
paper	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
Keep	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
corn	O
is	O
delivered	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
granary	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
usual	O
to	O
give	O
written	O
bills	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
instances	O
where	O
there	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
any	O
printed	O
bills	O
ready	O
at	O
hand	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
foreman	O
never	O
fills	O
up	O
notes	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
filled	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
clerk	O
or	O
myself	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
your	O
foreman	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
out	O
any	O
corn	O
without	O
your	O
knowledge	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
clerk	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Certainly	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whenever	O
he	O
sends	O
out	O
any	O
corn	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
the	O
custom	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
his	O
duty	O
to	O
enter	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
delivery	O
book	O
;	O
the	O
clerk	O
usually	O
fills	O
up	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
enters	O
it	O
in	O
another	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
check	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
entry	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
of	O
beans	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Keep	O
,	O
New	O
Cut	O
windmill	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
this	O
transaction	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
able	O
to	O
ascertain	O
any	O
loss	O
of	O
your	O
sacks	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
particularly	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nine	O
sacks	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
brought	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
beans	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partners	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understood	O
you	O
to	O
state	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
bills	O
of	O
sale	O
are	O
usually	O
printed	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
tickets	O
that	O
are	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
carman	O
are	O
usually	O
printed	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
sometimes	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
twice	O
in	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
clerk	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
bills	O
at	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
wrote	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
clerk	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Corn-exchange	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
wrote	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
foreman	O
is	O
positively	O
ordered	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
any	O
goods	O
without	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
me	O
or	O
the	O
clerk	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LOCKEY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
police	O
officer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
the	O
New	O
Cut	O
,	O
Keep	O
's	O
mill	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
nine	O
sacks	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
Mr.	O
Brickwood	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
in	O
full	O
length	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOODCOCK	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Cut	O
mill	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
twenty	O
sacks	O
of	O
whole	O
beans	O
come	O
in	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
split	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Brickwood	O
's	O
sacks	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
267.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
seven	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
LATTER	I-pers
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
four	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOSLING	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church-street	O
,	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
building	O
line	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
long	O
retired	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
ordered	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
hay	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
cut	O
a	O
load	O
and	O
three	O
trusses	O
;	O
half	O
a	O
load	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
partners	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remainder	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
where	O
your	O
stack	O
of	O
hay	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
your	O
hay	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
At	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
nine	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
the	O
rest	O
home	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
your	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
twelve	O
trusses	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
twelve	O
trusses	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
twelve	O
,	O
there	O
seems	O
a	O
small	O
quantity	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
turned	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
but	O
somebody	O
came	O
and	O
prevented	O
me	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
twice	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
loft	O
,	O
I	O
counted	O
only	O
eighteen	O
instead	O
of	O
twenty-one	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
loading	O
the	O
hay	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
the	O
haybinder	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
twenty-one	O
on	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
Ward	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
Ward	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
leave	O
the	O
three	O
trusses	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
twenty-one	O
trusses	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ARNOLD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Angel-alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
Ward	O
was	O
my	O
carter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gosling	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
return	O
home	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
hay	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gosling	O
till	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
so	O
late	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
trusses	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
eighteen	O
trusses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
loft	O
;	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cart	O
there	O
and	O
the	O
hay	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
quantity	O
that	O
I	O
expected	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
thirteen	O
trusses	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
eighteen	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
horses	O
had	O
eat	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
eat	O
five	O
trusses	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
with	O
what	O
the	O
horses	O
had	O
eat	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
loose	O
,	O
another	O
truss	O
;	O
reckoning	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
fourteen	O
trusses	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
nothing	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
foreman	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
hay	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
hay	O
at	O
the	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
and	O
Trimmings	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
Kingsland-road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Six	O
trusses	O
altogether	O
and	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
like	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
might	O
be	O
outside	O
trusses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Four	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
missed	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
seven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
twenty-one	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
missed	O
four	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
up	O
eighteen	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ostler	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
there	O
(	O
Latter	O
)	O
told	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
Ward	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
hay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Ward	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
this	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
another	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Ward	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Latter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Ward	O
that	O
Ward	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
hay	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
mentioned	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
six	O
trusses	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
WARD	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
19	O
.	O
Fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
LATTER	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Rooke	O
.	O
268.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MANNING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
was	O
clerk	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Hasletine	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
employed	O
and	O
entrusted	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
and	O
valuable	O
securities	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
such	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
employed	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
and	O
take	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
six	O
pounds	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
his	O
said	O
masters	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
feloniously	O
did	O
embezzle	O
and	O
secrete	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HASLETINE	I-pers
PEPYS	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Comyn	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
Edward	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
24	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
we	O
are	O
surgeons	O
'	O
instrument	O
makers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
collecting	O
clerk	O
and	O
bookkeeper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
receive	O
payments	O
due	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
your	O
different	O
customers	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
duty	O
to	O
account	O
daily	O
to	O
the	O
shopman	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
an	O
entry	O
in	O
a	O
receipt	O
book	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
your	O
business	O
use	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
your	O
accounts	O
with	O
your	O
shopman	O
weekly	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Weekly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
June	O
1806	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
paper	O
of	O
names	O
in	O
your	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
William	O
Williams	O
has	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
that	O
any	O
money	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
accounted	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1807	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
collect	O
your	O
debts	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
account	O
always	O
to	O
the	O
shopman	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
responsibility	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
These	O
sums	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
in	O
pencil	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
in	O
red	O
ink	O
in	O
the	O
regular	O
receipt	O
book	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Comyn	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
shopman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Pepys	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
account	O
to	O
you	O
daily	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
make	O
an	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
your	O
business	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
master	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
direction	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
any	O
person	O
for	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
received	O
instructions	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Hasledine	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
this	O
order	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
him	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
making	O
preparations	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
attend	O
business	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
wished	O
me	O
to	O
step	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
;	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
secret	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
business	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
presented	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
paper	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
hand	O
writing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
requested	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
call	O
upon	O
those	O
people	O
whose	O
names	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
list	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
placing	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
unpleasant	O
situation	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
happy	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
upon	O
Messrs.	O
Green	O
of	O
Leadenhall	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
receipt	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
Messrs.	O
Green	O
,	O
of	O
Leadenhall	O
street	O
.	O
MR.	O
CHARLES	O
GREEN	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Comyn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
merchant	O
in	O
Leadenhall	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
deal	O
with	O
Messrs.	O
Pepys	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
owe	O
them	O
any	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
June	O
1806	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
,	O
six	O
pound	O
thirteen	O
,	O
that	O
receipt	O
was	O
given	O
for	O
the	O
draft	O
on	O
our	O
bankers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
draft	O
was	O
returned	O
cancelled	O
by	O
our	O
bankers	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
draft	O
and	O
the	O
receipt	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Williams	O
)	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
receipt	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
hand	O
writing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
account	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
six	O
pound	O
thirteen	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
W.	O
H.	O
Pepys	O
)	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
account	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
E.	O
Pepys	O
)	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
account	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
six	O
pound	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
transaction	O
at	O
all	O
passed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
lose	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
recovered	O
this	O
money	O
till	O
such	O
times	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
come	O
forward	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
defraud	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
45	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
269.	O
ROSEY	B-pers
LOVETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
two	O
tippets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Giesler	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ANDREWS	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
yard	I-place
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
her	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
some	O
French	O
cambrics	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
joined	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
standing	O
outside	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
a	O
dozen	O
doors	O
down	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
stopped	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
parley	O
.	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
after	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
across	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Giesler	O
's	O
the	O
furrier	O
.	O
I	O
crossed	O
over	O
and	O
passed	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
home	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Giesler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
was	O
still	O
standing	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
crossed	O
over	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
crossed	O
again	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
station	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
stool	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
standing	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
saw	O
her	O
stoop	O
down	O
and	O
pull	O
up	O
her	O
petticoats	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
her	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
apparently	O
put	O
something	O
up	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
patten	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
tie	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
see	O
her	O
put	O
something	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
stood	O
up	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
back	O
towards	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
steps	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
tippet	O
hanging	O
down	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
came	O
another	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
stole	O
the	O
tippets	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
going	O
past	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Giesler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
the	O
tippets	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
them	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
ROBSON	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
serve	O
these	O
women	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
this	O
property	O
being	O
gone	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
taken	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
serving	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
wet	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pattens	O
on	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
this	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
patten	O
felt	O
very	O
heavy	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
dirt	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
stoop	O
down	O
to	O
knock	O
the	O
dirt	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pattens	O
,	O
that	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
270.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PURDON	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welldon	I-pers
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
boot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welldon	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WELLDON	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welldon	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
by	O
trade	O
but	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
follow	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
he	O
entered	O
as	O
a	O
marine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
sell	O
shoes	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
57	I-place
.	I-place
Goswell	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
that	O
house	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
and	O
the	O
shutters	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
whether	O
I	O
secured	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
had	O
you	O
left	O
any	O
shoes	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
placed	O
in	O
rows	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
hooks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
window	O
glass	O
all	O
whole	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
windows	O
cracked	O
but	O
no	O
glass	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
lodgers	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
the	O
lodgers	O
have	O
a	O
back	O
door	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
alarm	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
apprehension	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
ratling	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
cat	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
use	O
glass	O
in	O
our	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
cat	O
had	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
seat	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
adjoining	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
the	O
watchman	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
I	O
saw	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
five	O
pair	O
and	O
one	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
child	O
's	O
boot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
what	O
state	O
the	O
windows	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
shutter	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
shoes	O
were	O
all	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
spot	O
where	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broken	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
shoes	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Worship	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
some	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
pair	O
with	O
the	O
half	O
boot	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
cut	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
pair	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
with	O
the	O
half	O
boot	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
that	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
four	O
pair	O
found	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HEARNE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
my	O
box	O
is	O
in	O
Goswell	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
lives	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
box	O
is	O
between	O
thirty	O
and	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
her	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
to	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Welldon	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
stoop	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
glass	O
crack	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
within	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
separated	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
Purdon	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
suddenly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
nothing	O
particular	O
.	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
bringing	O
him	O
along	O
I	O
perceived	O
Taylor	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
willow	O
walk	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
gaiters	O
on	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
Purdon	O
.	O
Taylor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
Purdon	O
round	O
Old	O
street	O
corner	O
,	O
he	O
shammed	O
very	O
drunk	O
;	O
we	O
perceived	O
him	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
symptoms	O
did	O
he	O
show	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
staggered	O
and	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
large	O
enough	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
a	O
witness	O
here	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
burglary	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
once	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
burglary	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
these	O
men	O
are	O
convicted	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
reward	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
forty	O
pound	O
reward	O
upon	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
y	O
them	O
twto	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
court	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
there	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HEADBERRY	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Pitt	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Old	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
Taylor	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
Hearne	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Taylor	O
seemed	O
rather	O
fuddled	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
solid	O
afterwards	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BOYLE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
rope	O
maker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
61	O
,	O
Noble	O
street	O
,	O
Goswell	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
your	O
road	O
lay	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Down	O
the	O
willow	O
walk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
somewhere	O
about	O
Goswell	O
street	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
you	O
went	O
through	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
shoes	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
on	O
a	O
dunghill	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Three	O
pair	O
and	O
one	O
odd	O
child	O
's	O
half	O
boot	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
good	O
woman	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
shoes	O
of	O
Boyle	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Purdon	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
brought	O
up	O
under	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
support	O
my	O
mother	O
that	O
is	O
blind	O
.	O
Purdon	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Taylor	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BOTH	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
271.	O
LYDIA	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
for	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
not	O
stating	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
4	I-place
,	I-place
Philips	I-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
Grub	I-place
street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
apartments	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
back	O
room	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
rent	O
did	O
she	O
pay	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Four	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
them	O
blankets	O
with	O
your	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
Three	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
happening	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
take	O
out	O
some	O
bundles	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
blanket	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
you	O
know	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
found	O
a	O
blanket	O
of	O
yours	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
but	O
very	O
industrious	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PERRYMAN	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pledged	O
a	O
blanket	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
pledged	O
the	O
blanket	O
,	O
I	O
owed	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
one	O
weeks	O
rent	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
pay	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
I	O
hoped	O
it	O
made	O
no	O
odds	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
out	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
some	O
money	O
for	O
a	O
child	O
out	O
to	O
nurse	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
they	O
were	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
constables	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
pawned	O
the	O
blanket	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
The	O
sheets	O
were	O
out	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
secure	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
rent	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
her	O
hand	O
writing	O
for	O
the	O
rent	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
paper	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
36	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Month	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
272.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
OLAFF	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
OLIFFE	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
PATCHELL	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COX	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
bother	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
he	O
resides	O
at	O
Wickham	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
farm	O
at	O
Totteridge	O
,	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
your	O
brother	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Swan	I-place
inn	I-place
,	I-place
Wickham	I-place
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
with	O
some	O
corn	O
which	O
it	O
brought	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
corn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
servant	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
to	O
Totteridge	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
horse	O
since	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford	O
street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
bringing	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
black	O
gelding	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witnesses	O
'	O
house	O
,	O
home	O
to	O
Totteridge	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Thursday	O
night	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
missed	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
that	O
you	O
brought	O
him	O
from	O
Wickham	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
at	O
Totteridge	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
or	O
evening	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
the	O
night	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
gelding	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
gelding	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
communicated	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Moxon	I-pers
was	O
applied	O
to	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
last	O
see	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
to	O
day	O
and	O
yesterday	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
custody	O
is	O
he	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
now	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
horse	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
till	O
yesterday	O
or	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
yesterday	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Moxon	O
sold	O
your	O
master	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
horse	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Moxon	O
sold	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MOXON	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
High	O
Wickham	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
having	O
sold	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
applied	O
to	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
gelding	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
saddle	O
on	O
my	O
horse	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
brought	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
stand	O
a	O
pint	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
two-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
you	O
proposed	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
horse	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
speak	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Varney	O
about	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
Varney	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
suited	O
myself	O
with	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
horse	O
I	O
want	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
horse	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
learn	O
where	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Varney	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
horse	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
whose	O
horse	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
purchased	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
you	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
VARNEY	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
horse-dealer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Paddington	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
call	O
upon	O
you	O
with	O
any	O
horse	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
was	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
black	O
gelding	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
tail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
did	O
he	O
bring	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
sell	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
price	O
did	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Two	O
pound	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Cowley	O
,	O
by	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
buy	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
thirty-three	O
shillings	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
meet	O
his	O
master	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
horse	O
behind	O
you	O
at	O
Paddington	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
do	O
you	O
recollect	O
meeting	O
Mr.	O
Moxon	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Moxon	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
accompanied	O
me	O
to	O
Paddington	O
:	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
in	O
Oxford	O
street	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Mr.	O
Moxon	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
detained	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
at	O
Paddington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
suppose	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
pound	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
really	O
made	O
a	O
bargin	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
thirty	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
bought	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
price	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
expect	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
price	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
That	O
made	O
me	O
doubt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
detained	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
apprehend	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
Paddington	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
premises	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
conntry	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
proved	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
horse	O
the	O
prisoner	O
agreed	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
thirty	O
three	O
shillings	O
.	O
Dunn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
from	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
to	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Moxon	O
)	O
You	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
agreed	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
Varney	O
in	O
his	O
stables	O
in	O
Paddindton	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
see	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
master	O
's	O
or	O
the	O
servant	O
's	O
possession	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Johnson	O
)	O
You	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
from	O
Cox	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Cox	O
's	O
for	O
corn	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
locked	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fastened	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
undone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
being	O
undone	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
barred	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
undone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
more	O
private	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
unfastened	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
unbarred	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Totteridge	O
from	O
Wickham	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Moxon	O
)	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
sold	O
this	O
horse	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
for	O
in	O
December	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Seven	O
guineas	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
22	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
.	O
273.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STANLEY	I-pers
was	O
