TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
THE	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1807	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
Days	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
IN	O
THE	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT	O
HAND	O
BY	O
JOB	B-pers
SIBLY	I-pers
,	O
FOR	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
By	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
CORPORATION	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
LONDON	O
,	O
By	O
R.	O
BUTTERS	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
1807	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
On	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
AND	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
AND	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEIGHTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
Sir	O
NASH	B-pers
GROSE	I-pers
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sir	O
Brook	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Staines	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ainsley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Joshua	B-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Princep	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Domville	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
Newman	B-pers
Knowlys	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common-Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bolcot	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bridger	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hopwood	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Heaton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Leeks	I-pers
.	O
FIRST	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hulston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mangham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hullam	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Goldicutt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pinney	I-pers
.	I-pers
SECOND	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Fontaine	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Strachn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowey	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
.	O
356.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
ALLISON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
1	I-place
,	I-place
Cross-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lace-maker	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
good	O
nature	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
destitute	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
had	O
turned	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
by	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
this	O
person	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
all	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
my	O
shift	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
left	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
neither	O
shoes	O
nor	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pursue	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
early	O
hour	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
about	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
election	O
at	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
some	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
she	O
had	O
wore	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
till	O
last	O
Friday	O
.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
CORDING	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
High-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
pledge	O
;	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
20	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
356.	O
PETER	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
epaulets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DELANEY	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
respecting	O
this	O
accusation	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
officers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
London	O
regiment	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
putting	O
on	O
our	O
regimentals	O
on	O
parade	O
days	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Swan	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
,	I-place
Bunhill-row	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Charles	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
changed	O
my	O
clothes	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
servant	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
trunk	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
keeping	O
these	O
regimentals	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
following	O
Friday	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
servant	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
epaulets	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
leather	O
small	O
clothes	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
lock	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JAMES	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
servant	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Delaney	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Bunhil-row	O
,	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
master	O
having	O
a	O
trunk	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
I	O
received	O
some	O
regimentals	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
that	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
Swan	O
public-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
epaulets	O
on	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
epaulet	O
on	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
The	O
captain	O
keeps	O
one	O
key	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
trunk	O
again	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
epaulets	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
leather	O
small-clothes	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
had	O
been	O
fastened	O
on	O
again	O
by	O
two	O
small	O
nails	O
and	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
since	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
small	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
epaulets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
regiment	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
the	O
East	O
London	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
company	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
captain	O
Delaney	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
King-street	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
duplicates	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
duplicates	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
moved	O
a	O
jar	O
on	O
the	O
mantle	O
piece	O
;	O
under	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
pledged	O
for	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
moment	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
ticket	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
alarmed	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
the	O
captain	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
epaulets	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
the	O
ticket	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
many	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
I	O
tie	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
sticking	O
in	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
357.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
PEELEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
she	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
eight	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
five	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
eleven	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
five	O
habit	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
seven	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
two	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
about	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
hour	O
,	O
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
66	I-place
,	I-place
Chiswell-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Charles	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
my	O
servant	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
wash	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
tea	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
went	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
woke	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
inform	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
clothes	O
missing	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
things	O
you	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
wash.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ray	B-pers
the	O
officer	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
office	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fothergill	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
advantage	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
57	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
359.	O
MARY	B-pers
BENNARY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Rupert	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
RUPERT	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
18	B-place
,	I-place
John	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Holywell	I-place
Mount	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
articles	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BISHOP	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
office	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
shawl	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
POPE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
shawl	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
MR.	O
COTTON	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
pledged	O
a	O
bed	O
gown	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
shawl	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bed	O
gown	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
I	O
pledged	O
them	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gown	O
with	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Cotton	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
that	O
gentleman	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
foot-marks	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
with	O
blue	O
pantaloons	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
360.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
three	O
sets	O
of	O
cart	O
harness	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
three	O
cart	O
ropes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodbridge	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRAINGER	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Woodbridge	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodbridge	I-pers
,	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Greenford	B-place
Green	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Willsdon	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
benefit	O
club	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bacon	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
my	O
horses	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
benefit	O
club	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
bacon	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
lost	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dunghill	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
left	O
shut	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
shut	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
trace	O
chains	O
for	O
cart	O
horses	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
it	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
dung	O
hole	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
the	O
sack	O
was	O
tied	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
ropes	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
loose	O
on	O
the	O
dunghill	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hat	O
full	O
of	O
horse	O
hair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
been	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
always	O
hang	O
the	O
harness	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
the	O
back	O
band	O
straps	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
chains	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
dung	O
fork	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
try	O
to	O
wrench	O
the	O
bin	O
open	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
dung	O
hole	O
window	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
follow	O
servant	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
loft	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
man	O
been	O
about	O
the	O
parish	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Boram	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
loft	O
into	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
distress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
stable	O
or	O
loft	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
stable	O
is	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
join	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
loft	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
with	O
Grainger	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
farm	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
called	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
loaded	O
my	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
be	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
said	O
here	O
I	O
be	O
,	O
set	O
a	O
ladder	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
without	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
think	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
place	O
open	O
and	O
cutting	O
the	O
leather	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
a	O
begging	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
begging	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Christian	O
country	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
case	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
relieve	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
on	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
would	O
you	O
like	O
to	O
strip	O
yourself	O
naked	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
till	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
at	O
four	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
dog	O
's	O
collar	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
threatened	O
me	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
remember	O
the	O
dog	O
's	O
collar	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
collar	O
I	O
thought	O
might	O
lead	O
to	O
some	O
discovery	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
up	O
from	O
Colchester	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
stable	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
alarm	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
frightened	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
loft	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
38	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
361.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RUTTIFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Joseph	B-pers
Firth	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
an	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FIRTH	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
baker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
South-molton-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
James-court	B-place
,	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
with	O
his	O
snatching	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
the	O
case	O
flew	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
standing	O
at	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
towards	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
the	O
watch	O
nor	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
do	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Young	O
man	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
serious	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
clear	O
in	O
your	O
recollection	O
-	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
snatched	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
people	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
nigh	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Only	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
holding	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
wanted	O
to	O
rescue	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
recovered	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
use	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
watchman	O
here	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
rescue	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
held	O
up	O
your	O
arm	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
insulted	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
court	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
are	O
there	O
any	O
improper	O
houses	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
there	O
might	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
or	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
girls	O
in	O
that	O
court	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
standing	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
girl	O
standing	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Am	O
I	O
to	O
understand	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
any	O
girl	O
in	O
that	O
court	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
intoxicated	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
let	O
me	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
accompany	O
her	O
home	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
talking	O
with	O
two	O
bad	O
girls	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
breeches	O
were	O
unbuttoned	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
16	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
Confined	O
Six	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
362	O
JOHN	B-pers
BREWSTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
thirty-eight	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
building	O
of	O
his	O
called	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
for	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
only	O
stating	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
building	O
generally	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Mary-le-bone	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
taking	O
some	O
lead	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
Montague-square	B-place
,	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
inhabited	O
by	O
colonel	O
St	O
.	O
Ledger	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
plumber	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
compared	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WILD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
Mary-le-bone	O
parish	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
a	O
dunghill	O
where	O
this	O
lead	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gloucester-place	O
to	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
going	O
on	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
right	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
mews	O
again	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
dropping	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
into	O
the	O
mews	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
George-street	O
,	O
Portman-square	O
;	O
I	O
hallooed	O
to	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
dropped	O
a	O
great	O
knife	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
knife	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
lamplighter	O
was	O
lighting	O
the	O
lamps	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
burner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
knife	O
fixed	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
rails	O
and	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
knife	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
mews	O
where	O
the	O
dunghill	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
dunghill	O
(	O
the	O
lead	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
thirty-eight	O
pound	O
.	O
I	O
fitted	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
lead	O
cut	O
from	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
kitchen	O
flat	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
lead	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
nigh	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
partner	O
was	O
receiving	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
no	O
reason	O
though	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
partner	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
partner	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
John	B-pers
Brewster	I-pers
,	O
my	O
partner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
knife	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
rails	O
and	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
a	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
lead	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
dunghill	O
after	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justise	O
Grose	O
.	O
363.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BULL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
serge	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
other	O
white	O
serge	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
blue	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
blue	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
blue	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
brown	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thrupp	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MAIZE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
private	O
road	O
,	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
passed	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
bulk	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
flannel	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
paid	O
a	O
penny	O
a-yard	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
walked	O
to	O
Oxford-street	O
to	O
buy	O
flannel	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
George-street	O
,	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thrupp	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
untied	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
serge	O
and	O
broad	O
cloth	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
cuttings	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
Mr.	O
Thrupp	O
gave	O
him	O
these	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
o	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
cautious	O
of	O
telling	O
an	O
untruth	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
should	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
not	O
hear	O
that	O
,	O
only	O
what	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
43	O
.	O
Confined	O
Two	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
364.	O
BARBARA	B-pers
BARLOW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
SARAH	B-pers
LINCH	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
10	I-place
,	I-place
Cohen	I-place
's	I-place
Rents	I-place
,	I-place
New-Inn-yard	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
out	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
tickets	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOCKLEY	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
the	O
articles	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
365.	O
ANN	B-pers
BANNISTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lea	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
LEA	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Hart	I-place
in	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
liberty	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
Le	I-place
Grand	I-place
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
our	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
George-street	O
,	O
Foster-lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
pots	O
off	O
the	O
strap	O
;	O
she	O
crossed	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pots	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
53	O
.	O
Confined	O
Two	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
366.	O
MORRIS	B-pers
CAVEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Montrose	I-pers
.	O
MR.	O
DENNIS	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
mews	O
where	O
the	O
duke	O
keeps	O
his	O
carriage	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
past	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
glimpse	O
of	O
the	O
crest	O
on	O
the	O
button	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
suffered	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
coat	O
with	O
the	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
this	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
my	O
reply	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
coat	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
conducted	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
duke	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
domestics	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
in	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BULLOCK	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
duke	O
's	O
coachman	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
coat	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
house	O
door	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
26	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
367.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STOKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
floor	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BARNES	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
floor	O
cloth	O
manufacturer	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
City	B-place
Road	I-place
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
printer	O
for	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
suspected	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
missed	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
thousand	O
pound	O
in	O
one	O
year	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
employed	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apprentice	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
informed	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
property	O
afterwards	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Most	O
assuredly	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOW	I-pers
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hill-street	O
,	O
Finsbury-square	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
manufactory	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
floor	O
cloth	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Gee-street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
floor	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Walford	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
carry	O
was	O
floor	O
cloth	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
factory	O
.	O
MRS.	O
BENSON	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
14th	O
or	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
floor	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
purchased	O
it	O
of	O
Stokes	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
floor	O
cloth	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Walford	O
.	O
You	O
bargained	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
for	O
the	O
floor	O
cloth	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
purchase	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
carpet	O
painted	O
;	O
Mrs	O
Fisher	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
LOCK	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Eleven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
learned	O
your	O
catechism	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
good	O
thing	O
or	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
bad	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
people	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
Hell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
purchasing	O
any	O
floor	O
cloth	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Benton	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Walford	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
about	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
very	O
little	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
floor	O
cloth	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
happened	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
mother	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
bought	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
it	O
or	O
your	O
mother	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Me	O
sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
for	O
my	O
mother	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
agreed	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Benson	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
floor	O
cloth	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
Benson	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
of	O
floor	O
cloth	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
Vickrey	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
VICKREY	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
floor	O
cloth	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
's	O
in	O
Gee-street	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Benson	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
Benson	O
went	O
over	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
's	O
mother	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
floor	O
cloth	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
368.	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brinklett	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRINKLETT	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brinklett	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
kept	O
the	B-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
at	I-place
Fulham	I-place
.	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
had	O
borrowed	O
of	O
me	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bar	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
ordered	O
sixpennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
some	O
brandy	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
to	O
mix	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
her	O
six	O
doors	O
from	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
were	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
glass	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
liquor	O
more	O
than	O
did	O
me	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
parting	O
with	O
my	O
friends	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
serving	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Betsy	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
serve	O
me	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
this	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
thought	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
39	O
.	O
Confined	O
Two	O
Months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
Whipped	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
369.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
THORN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FROST	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
last	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
I	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
hesitated	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
boy	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
duplicates	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pawned	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NEAVES	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
and	O
a	O
tea	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
tea	O
spoon	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
of	O
replacing	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
Confined	O
Six	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
370.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LOVETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
thirty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
woolen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
l.	O
seventy	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
baize	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HILTON	I-pers
.	O
My	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Henry	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
woolen	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
the	O
robbery	O
from	O
information	O
The	O
warehouse	O
is	O
in	O
Cullum-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
warehouse	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
;	O
the	O
padlock	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
goods	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
has	O
none	O
been	O
found	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BARTON	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Davison	O
and	O
Newman	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
Cullum-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Darby	O
and	O
Hilton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
each	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
with	O
goods	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
first	O
men	O
passed	O
me	O
with	O
very	O
little	O
notice	O
;	O
I	O
noticed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
bags	O
with	O
goods	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
some	O
reply	O
similar	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
struck	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
go	O
up	O
Lime-street	O
for	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
concluded	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
men	O
employed	O
by	O
Messrs.	O
Darby	O
and	O
Hilton	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
employ	O
and	O
took	O
no	O
further	O
notice	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
smith	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
learned	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
who	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
CARTWRIGHT	I-pers
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Holdsworth	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
afternoon	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Haswell	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Hartshorn-court	O
,	O
leading	O
into	O
Fenchurch	O
street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
one	O
pound	O
notes	O
,	O
a	O
two	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
canvass	O
bags	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
described	O
the	O
bags	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
charge	O
against	O
the	O
man	O
for	O
stealing	O
bank	O
notes	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
searched	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
you	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
a	O
door	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HASWELL	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
foreman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Holdsworth	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
directly	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
on	O
but	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
the	O
spring	O
lock	O
;	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
did	O
you	O
perceive	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
perceive	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
snowy	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
some	O
footsteps	O
of	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
flakes	O
of	O
snow	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
on	O
seeing	O
them	O
footsteps	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
idea	O
the	O
depredators	O
were	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
one	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
question	O
;	O
the	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
from	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
goods	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
About	O
forty	O
pound	O
altogether	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Barton	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
bags	O
,	O
are	O
they	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
bags	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
many	O
hundreds	O
have	O
bags	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BAGLEY	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
53	O
,	O
in	O
Church-street	O
,	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
this	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
make	O
shoes	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
meeting	O
him	O
any	O
morning	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
will	O
make	O
all	O
the	O
difference	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
rather	O
nearer	O
six	O
than	O
seven	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
a	O
load	O
upon	O
his	O
knot	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
that	O
would	O
satisfy	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
word	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
good	O
strong	O
shoes	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
nearest	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
measured	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
all	O
you	O
say	O
is	O
very	O
correct	O
,	O
when	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
till	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
shoes	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
recollect	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
birth-day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
be	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
coloured	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
satisfied	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
umbrella	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
coarse	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
company	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
you	O
applied	O
to	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
before	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Because	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
birth-day	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
material	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
day	O
on	O
which	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
-	O
are	O
you	O
quite	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
prison	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Cartwright	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
last	O
session	O
;	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
session	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
the	O
session	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
33	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
371.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BURRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
fourteen	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
building	O
of	O
theirs	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
for	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
only	O
stating	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
building	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
stated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FLETCHER	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
employ	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Holmes	O
and	O
Hall	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
occupy	O
Porter	B-place
's	I-place
quay	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
further	O
back	O
garret	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
gib-head	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
lead	O
off	O
.	O
communicated	O
it	O
to	O
Stapp	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
STAPP	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
;	O
from	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
Fletcher	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
beating	O
the	O
lad	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
pin	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Henry	O
Hall	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
hammering	O
the	O
lead-closer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
an	O
iron	O
pin	O
from	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
William	O
Hall	O
;	O
his	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
they	O
occupy	O
Porter	O
's	O
quay	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Stapp	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
beating	O
the	O
lead	O
up	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
pin	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
about	O
fourteen	O
pound	O
of	O
lead	O
from	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
fall	O
the	O
iron	O
pin	O
from	O
his	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
newly	O
cut	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WYE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
measured	O
the	O
place	O
with	O
a	O
string	O
,	O
the	O
lead	O
exactly	O
corresponded	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
want	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
sick	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
small	O
children	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
Publickly	O
Whipped	O
on	O
Porter	O
's	O
Quay	O
,	O
and	O
confined	O
in	O
Newgate	O
One	O
Month	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Sergeant	O
.	O
372.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
NOWLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
thirty	O
four	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
ash	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Devey	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
Devey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Devey	I-pers
.	O
ROGER	B-pers
DEVEY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass	O
founder	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
your	O
partners	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Robert	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
Devey	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Devey	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
evening	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
move	O
aukwardly	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
way	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
pass	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Mich	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
heavy	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
metal	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
metal	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
ingot	O
of	O
ash	O
metal	O
;	O
it	O
weights	O
thirty	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
twenty	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
this	O
ingot	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Devey	O
call	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
metal	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
40	O
.	O
Confined	O
in	O
Newgate	O
One	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
Whipped	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
373.	O
SARAH	B-pers
SHARP	I-pers
and	O
HANNAH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
twenty	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
calico	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elsworth	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRAY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elsworth	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
linen	O
draper	O
s	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Twenty	O
eight	O
yards	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eleven	O
pieces	O
of	O
goods	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
counter	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
them	O
,	O
Armstrong	O
served	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
persons	O
left	O
your	O
shop	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
Sharp	O
till	O
such	O
times	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Sharp	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Gleed	I-pers
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
sent	O
over	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
men	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
left	O
the	O
three	O
ladies	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
up	O
Rose-alley	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Sharp	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Sharp	O
with	O
the	O
print	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
print	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
Jones	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Jones	O
till	O
the	O
following	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
certain	O
that	O
the	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
speaks	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
stay	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
ten	O
minutes	O
to	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
counter	O
to	O
your	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
small	O
side	O
counter	O
,	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
laving	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
at	O
that	O
counter	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
serving	O
them	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
close	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Jones	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
callico	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
serving	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
me	O
and	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
ladies	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
this	O
print	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
We	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
rather	O
more	O
-	O
ARMSTRONG	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
servant	O
to	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
doing	O
of	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
ladies	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
serving	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
dimity	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
several	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
which	O
pleased	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
immediately	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
Jones	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
from	O
information	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Sharp	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
Jones	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
the	O
same	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
callico	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
these	O
women	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
counter	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
main	O
counter	O
.	O
BARNARD	B-pers
GLEED	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
Worship-street	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Jones	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
child	O
was	O
playing	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Sharp	O
by	O
a	O
sadler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
off	O
near	O
Devonshire-street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
New-street	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
carts	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
.	O
Jones	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
duffell	O
cloak	O
on	O
;	O
directly	O
these	O
women	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Sharp	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
New-street	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
together	O
up	O
Rose-alley	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
narrow	O
alley	O
and	O
thoroughfare	O
into	O
New-street	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Rose-alley	O
Jones	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Sharp	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
tie	O
up	O
my	O
stocking	O
,	O
Jones	O
and	O
Sharp	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
face	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
pass	O
from	O
Jones	O
to	O
Sharp	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
joined	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
distinctly	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
something	O
under	O
Sharp	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
know	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
rolled	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
loose	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Sharp	O
,	O
Jones	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Sharp	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
print	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Rose-alley	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
it	O
back	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
in	O
Rose-alley	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
callico	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
Jones	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
took	O
Sharp	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
;	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Jones	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Rose-lane	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shopman	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Jones	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
sells	O
fruit	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Orange-lane	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
oranges	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Whitechapel	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
then	O
;	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Rose-lane	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
people	O
a	O
quarreling	O
,	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
parted	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
an	O
odious	O
thing	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
women	O
to	O
quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
officers	O
came	O
,	O
one	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
print	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Sharp	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Rose-alley	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
print	O
lay	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
one	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
man	O
not	O
woman	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Rose-alley	O
,	O
that	O
gentleman	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
this	O
woman	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
compter	O
.	O
Sharp	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
SHARP	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
JONES	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
47	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
London	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
374.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Mauclark	I-pers
.	O
LUKE	B-pers
MAUCLARK	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Coram-street	I-place
.	O
From	O
information	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
MR.	O
BISHOP	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
42	O
,	O
Great	O
Coram-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
No	O
.	O
36	O
or	O
37	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
this	O
person	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
over	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Coram-street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
one	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
houses	O
had	O
paper	O
in	O
their	O
windows	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
houses	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
tied	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
that	O
bundle	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
35	O
.	O
Confined	O
Six	O
Months	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
375.	O
MARY	B-pers
COY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
80	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkinson	I-pers
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
DOUGLAS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
in	O
Jermyn-street	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rochford	O
,	O
Jermyn-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
Mary	B-pers
Coy	I-pers
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WATKINSON	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
Bedford-court	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
dish	O
back	O
that	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
some	O
victuals	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
identified	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pledge	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
distress	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
28	O
.	O
Confined	O
One	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
.	O
376.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALSGROVE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
leaden	O
stink	O
trap	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
eight	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
pipe	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
affixed	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
count	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
32	I-place
,	I-place
Frith-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
entered	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
lead	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
stink	O
trap	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
pipe	O
had	O
been	O
fixed	O
that	O
day	O
by	O
the	O
plumber	O
's	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
house	O
was	O
under	O
repair	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
my	O
furniture	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MEDLAM	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Frith	O
street	O
every	O
night	O
after	O
the	O
workmen	O
had	O
done	O
their	O
work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
from	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
From	O
No	O
.	O
21	O
,	O
Church-street	O
,	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
Frith-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
doors	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
all	O
fastened	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
at	O
21	O
,	O
Church-street	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Frith-street	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lead	O
pipe	O
,	O
a	O
stink	O
trap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
place	O
open	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
lighted	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
fastened	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
not	O
lit	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
saying	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
you	O
fastened	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
quite	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
open	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
WILKINS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Frith-street	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
rather	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Being	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
knock	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
door	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
knocked	O
he	O
crossed	O
over	O
opposite	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
height	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
I	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
door	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
towards	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
watching	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
might	O
occur	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
touched	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
meaning	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
on	O
our	O
return	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
watching	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
more	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
from	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
through	O
the	O
crevice	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
being	O
dark	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
the	O
lady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
21	O
,	O
Church-street	O
.	O
Cross-examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alley	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
crossing	O
the	O
street	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
distinctly	O
see	O
his	O
features	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
dining	O
room	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
seen	O
his	O
features	O
distinctly	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
-	O
MOODY	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
house	O
in	O
Frith-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
thieves	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
climb-over	O
from	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
railing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
'	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
made	O
my	O
way	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
On	O
looking	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
I	O
distinctly	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
scaling	O
the	O
iron	O
railings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
now	O
in	O
question	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
attempting	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
pulling	O
me	O
from	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
struggling	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILKINS	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
the	O
lady	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
examined	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
witness	O
Medlam	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
some	O
persons	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
being	O
called	O
by	O
Moody	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
securing	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
violence	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
by	O
false	O
keys	O
,	O
or	O
picking	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SHARP	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
copper	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
pipe	O
and	O
the	O
copper	O
.	O
-	O
CRAYDEN	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
searched	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
common	O
latch	O
key	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
Frith-street	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
area	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
iron	O
crow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
whatever	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
passing	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
aged	O
30	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
only	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Grose	O
.	O
377.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DUNCAN	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
liberty	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Rolls	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
spent	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
a	O
friend	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
stop	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
before	O
dinner	O
I	O
was	O
shewing	O
him	O
several	O
watches	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
the	O
gold	O
repeater	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
replaced	O
it	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
valuable	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
stands	O
me	O
in	O
upwards	O
of	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
in	O
to	O
dinner	O
with	O
my	O
friend	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
called	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
till	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
your	O
shop	O
immediately	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
this	O
gold	O
repeater	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
common	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Perfectly	O
so	O
.	O
After	O
consulting	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
my	O
friend	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
there	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
business	O
done	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
names	O
and	O
the	O
numbers	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
him	O
whether	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
watches	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
pledged	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
certain	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
)	O
for	O
one	O
pound	O
fifteen	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
called	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
immediately	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Southgate	O
came	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
ticket	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
had	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
any	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
ticket	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Tabernacle-square	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Southgate	O
to	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
office	O
,	O
from	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Southgate	O
and	O
Stanton	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SOUTHGATE	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisonor	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
By	O
sight	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
aukward	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
did	O
he	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
ticket	O
,	O
a	O
one	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
ticket	O
on	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
the	O
man	O
from	O
whom	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
true	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tabernacle	O
row	O
,	O
City	O
Road	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Southgate	O
brought	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
gold	O
repeater	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
-	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
this	O
business	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
interrogated	O
her	O
concerning	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
respectable	O
inhabitant	O
of	O
this	O
parish	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
parish	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
and	O
regular	O
visitor	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ladies	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
question	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
person	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
answered	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
added	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
all	O
was	O
perfectly	O
right	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
eight	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
course	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
ticket	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
following	O
afternoon	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Stanton	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
entered	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
produced	O
the	O
ticket	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
shewing	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
claimed	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
the	O
number	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
MRS.	O
SOUTHGATE	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Southgate	I-pers
are	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
particulars	O
about	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
his	O
bringing	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
last	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
eight	O
pounds	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Walker	B-pers
a	O
great	O
falsity	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
got	O
a	O
ticket	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
STANTON	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
remember	O
apprehending	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
containing	O
four	O
one	O
pound	O
notes	O
and	O
three	O
tickets	O
;	O
one	O
ticket	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
pledged	O
for	O
eight	O
pounds	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
Tabernacle-walk	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
gave	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
he	O
claimed	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
,	O
look	O
first	O
at	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
your	O
property	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
my	O
case	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
-	O
DEATH	O
,	O
aged	O
23	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
jury	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
recommended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
]	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Graham	O
.	O
378.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
BRAND	I-pers
and	O
JANE	B-pers
HOBBS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
of	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
and	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
