TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1735	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	O
BELLAMY	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reeve	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Urlin	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Leadbeater	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffries	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Middleson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chisholm	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Carns	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Howard	B-pers
Deezly	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Deardsley	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waist-coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
others	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
seventeen	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	O
Adamson	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
three	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lansdale	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brooks	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Crone	I-pers
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
Compter	I-place
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
William	B-pers
Crone	I-pers
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
Robert	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Wigs	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Macnamar	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hartford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Bulbrook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Currier	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
7.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
lb	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sculthorp	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Farling	I-pers
,	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dormer	O
,	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Ipswich	B-place
Arms	I-place
in	O
Cullum-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Gutter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Barbican	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Martha	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
,	O
December	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
sending	O
a	O
Letter	O
dated	O
February	O
30	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Name	O
subscribed	O
,	O
to	O
Dorothy	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Penson	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
four	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
threatning	O
if	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
left	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
.	O
March	O
2d	O
,	O
1733	O
.	O
John	O
Penson	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
my	O
Maid	O
deliver	O
'd	O
this	O
Letter	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
directed	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
contains	O
Threatnings	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
therein	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Shot	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Discovery	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
some	O
Relations	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
lurking	O
there	O
abouts	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
upon	O
some	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
his	O
Cousin	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Letter	O
was	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
People	O
(	O
John	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
)	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
.	O
For	O
Mrs.	O
Penson	O
,	O
in	O
Silvuer-Street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury-Market	O
,	O
Feb.	O
30	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Penson	O
if	O
you	O
dont	O
put	O
four	O
Pound	O
within	O
your	O
Rails	O
by	O
your	O
Bones	O
by	O
God	O
we	O
will	O
burn	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
Family	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
dam	O
our	O
Sols	O
if	O
we	O
dont	O
by	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
set	O
a	O
Watch	O
the	O
furst	O
time	O
we	O
Litt	O
of	O
you	O
we	O
will	O
murder	O
you	O
dam	O
our	O
Eyes	O
if	O
we	O
dont	O
put	O
the	O
Munnuy	O
We	O
will	O
murder	O
you	O
by	O
God	O
by	O
us	O
J.H	O
Im	O
TG	O
TH	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Penson	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
watch	O
'd	O
till	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Penson	O
.	O
We	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
writ	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Post-house	O
in	O
Wild-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
light-headed	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Letter	O
was	O
sent	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
writing	O
a	O
Letter	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
Letter	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand	O
-	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
Hester	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Guineas	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
-	O
As	O
for	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
they	O
threatned	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
Hearing	O
that	O
Hester	O
Robinson	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
Letter	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
durst	O
do	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Penson	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
five	O
Guineas	O
to	O
swear	O
away	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Boy	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
unhandsome	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
honourable	O
Gentlemen	O
will	O
allow	O
the	O
Law	O
to	O
be	O
suborned	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
to	O
be	O
bought	O
when	O
the	O
whole	O
Neighbourhood	O
cry	O
out	O
shame	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
prosecuting	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
innocent	O
manner	O
-	O
Innocent	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
an	O
innocent	O
thing	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Blood	O
for	O
Money	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
boldly	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
swore	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
to	O
clear	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Penson	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
four	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Penson	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bear	O
my	O
Charges	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
9.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Lownds	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
November	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Fream	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Chandois	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
and	O
looked	O
upon	O
some	O
striped	O
Thread	O
Sattins	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
bought	O
14	O
Yards	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Piece	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
shuffling	O
something	O
under	O
their	O
Riding-hoods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
presently	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sattin	O
upon	O
Ward	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
noon	O
.	O
Hezekiah	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
Fream	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
nothing	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Sattin	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
carried	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
Round-house	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
examined	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
,	O
who	O
granted	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
commiting	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
thither	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Constables	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
behind	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
rescued	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
Men	O
.	O
We	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
for	O
a	O
Fact	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
at	O
the	O
Rescue	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Ward	O
Guilty	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Fream	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
.	O
Matth.ias	O
Fream	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
rescuing	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Fream	I-pers
out	O
of	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
,	O
April	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
to	O
carry	O
two	O
Shop-lifters	O
,	O
Ann	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Fream	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Round-house	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
their	O
Commitment	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
A	O
Coach	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
:	O
The	O
Coach-man	O
drove	O
down	O
Rose	O
Street	O
,	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
where	O
a	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
a	O
Stop	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
more	O
attacked	O
us	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Coach-Doors	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
rescued	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
My	O
Hat	O
was	O
beat	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
when	O
several	O
others	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Parr	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
the	O
last	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
:	O
The	O
rest	O
were	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
up	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
his	O
Wife	O
bid	O
him	O
make	O
haste	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
warrant	O
ye	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
your	O
Business	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
December	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Billings	I-pers
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Byrne	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buck	O
Skin	O
Breeches	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
28	O
Moidores	O
,	O
9	O
Quarter	O
Moidores	O
,	O
6	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
each	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Chest	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Byrne	O
is	O
my	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
absconding	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
gone	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
publish	O
'd	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
at	O
Huntington	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Huntington	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
passing	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
suspected	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
seen	O
at	O
Godmanchester	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
pursued	O
'em	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
Wood	O
side	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
'em	O
back	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
where	O
Byrne	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
were	O
Irish	O
Rogues	O
who	O
had	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoe-makers	O
Pincers	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Chest	O
open	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
of	O
Huntington	O
.	O
Byrne	O
had	O
these	O
Buck-skin	O
Breeches	O
on	O
;	O
these	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
which	O
is	O
30	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
in	O
this	O
other	O
Paper	O
is	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Bateman	O
;	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Clark	O
.	O
Byrne	O
confest	O
all	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Confession	O
in	O
writing	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Breeches	O
and	O
my	O
Spoons	O
-	O
Then	O
Byrne	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
proved	O
and	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Byrne	O
.	O
I	O
confess	O
my	O
self	O
Guilty	O
-	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
and	I-place
Pye	I-place
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
Clark	O
and	O
Bateman	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
egg	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
any	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
me	O
from	O
one	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoemakers	O
Pincers	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Chest	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
two	O
Guineas	O
to	O
fetch	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
-	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Dublin	O
where	O
I	O
should	O
live	O
without	O
working	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Common	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
-	O
They	O
had	O
between	O
them	O
26	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
that	O
Clark	O
and	O
Bateman	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
Principals	O
but	O
Accessary	O
's	O
in	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
must	O
therefore	O
acquit	O
them	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
may	O
indict	O
them	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Clark	O
and	O
Bateman	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Byrne	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
16.	O
William	B-pers
Wardlow	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wadlow	B-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Wadlow	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
,	O
November	O
28	O
.	O
and	O
Daniel	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
whatever	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
a	O
strange	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Gray	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
The	O
Cloaths	O
are	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
before	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
or	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
be	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Martha	O
Daniel	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
enquired	O
for	O
them	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Stranger	O
was	O
her	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Husband	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
.	O
(	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Maid	O
)	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
Wardlow	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
had	O
not	O
you	O
acquainted	O
your	O
Mistress	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Pattison	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Pippin	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
sworn	O
falsly	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
in	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
ask	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
Mistress	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Name	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
pledged	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
Truth	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
M.	O
Pattison	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
afterwards	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
Wardlow	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Black	O
Suit	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Wardlow	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Daniel	O
.	O
Wardlow	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wollard	I-pers
,	O
December	O
10	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Black	O
Suit	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
Frogs	O
,	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
seven	O
Shirts	O
,	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
280	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Partner	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
live	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Black	O
Hood	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
asleep	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
came	O
home	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
before	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
no	O
longer	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pacify	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
stay	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
provided	O
with	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
We	O
at	O
last	O
agreed	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sup	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pattisons	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Shop	O
in	O
Great	O
Queen	O
Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
God	O
send	O
that	O
nothing	O
else	O
may	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
lock'd-	O
The	O
Lock	O
goes	O
with	O
a	O
Spring	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
fast	O
without	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
it	O
after	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
our	O
Box	O
and	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
all	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Chimnies	O
in	O
every	O
Room	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Garret	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
.	O
Her	O
Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
without	O
side	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Box	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
were	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
.	O
We	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
this	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Needham	O
,	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Maker	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
the	O
Latch	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
come	O
here	O
!	O
They	O
have	O
begun	O
to	O
fire	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
God	O
's	O
Mercy	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
all	O
burnt	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Stairs	O
where	O
the	O
Board	O
was	O
burnt	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
was	O
hot	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
her	O
doing	O
since	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
cold	O
.	O
But	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
was	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
Beast	O
?	O
Then	O
we	O
locked	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
too	O
.	O
Her	O
Box	O
was	O
then	O
open	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
Garret	O
Window	O
.	O
She	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Thieves	O
must	O
be	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Gowns	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
afterwards	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
those	O
Gowns	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
pledg	O
'd	O
these	O
Gowns	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Needham	O
.	O
An	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
Gowns	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Burt	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
House	O
I	O
then	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Gowns	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
lost	O
too	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Burt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
with	O
us	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gate	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
pawn	O
the	O
Gowns	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Husband	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Gowns	O
were	O
at	O
Burt	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Burt	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
advertised	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Needham	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Sweet-heart	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Wilson	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Widower	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
100	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
present	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
fine	O
Cloths	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Cause	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Parliament	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
to	O
get	O
himself	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
marry	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Love	O
Letter	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
a	O
vile	O
Fellow	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
if	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
I	O
'll	O
get	O
somebody	O
to	O
swear	O
your	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Needham	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Master	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Lock	O
back	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
no	O
Fire	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Burts	O
in	O
the	O
Broad	O
Way	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
ajar	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
mist	O
was	O
the	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
run	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
my	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Cloak	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Burt	O
's	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
If	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
to	O
frighten	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
has	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
ruin	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
Masters	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
'em	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
Tinder	O
that	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
fire	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
fright	O
,	O
I	O
forgot	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
before	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Coals	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
back	O
till	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
there	O
being	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
for	O
Supper	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
three	O
Ribs	O
of	O
a	O
Neck	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
besides	O
Bread	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
cold	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Hood	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
at	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
twice	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
Several	O
in	O
whose	O
Families	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
18.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Fisher	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
Linnen	O
Covers	O
for	O
Chairs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Fisher	O
Tench	O
,	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
January	O
24	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Devy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Sir	O
Fisher	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Hatton	B-place
Garden	I-place
.	O
His	O
Garret	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
three	O
Aprons	O
,	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
eight	O
Mobs	O
,	O
twelve	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Eastall	I-pers
.	O
And	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
and	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
likewise	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garret	O
twelve	O
Linnen	O
Covers	O
for	O
Chairs	O
and	O
a	O
Frize	O
Gown	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
twenty	O
fourth	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
self	O
and	O
Byrom	O
went	O
into	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Ladder	O
with	O
a	O
Board	O
upon	O
it	O
standing	O
against	O
Sir	O
Fisher	O
Tench	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Byrom	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Top	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Garret	O
Window	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
Moonlight	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
down	O
two	O
Bundles	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
both	O
waited	O
below	O
.	O
We	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Richard	O
's	O
in	O
Thatched	O
Alley	O
,	O
near	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
.	O
Being	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
who	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
Hannah	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
wanted	O
something	O
for	O
Supper	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Chap	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Leadbeater	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Oads	O
's	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Byrom	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mother	O
Richards	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Bob	O
Carter	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
looking	O
over	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Womens	O
Apparel	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
.	O
Several	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
(	O
not	O
then	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
January	O
24	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Parlor	O
in	O
Green	B-place
Arbour	I-place
Court	I-place
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Old	B-place
Baily	I-place
,	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Byrom	O
went	O
into	O
Green	O
Arbour	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushed	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
carried	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Oads	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
plain	O
Shirts	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Leadbeater	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
ruffled	O
Shirts	O
we	O
wore	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Shirts	O
to	O
Sam	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
for	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
five	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Wet	O
Linnen	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Oads	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Maid	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Mothers	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hayden	I-pers
,	O
Carter	O
brought	O
two	O
Shirts	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
(	O
not	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
abed	O
,	O
but	O
)	O
to	O
two	O
Men	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Carter	O
's	O
Company	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oades	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Goat	O
and	O
Leek	O
in	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Man	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
Cartar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Carter	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Jail	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
run	O
of	O
his	O
Errants	O
and	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Carter	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Lad	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
delighted	O
in	O
Cudgel	O
Playing	O
and	O
Bear	O
Gardens	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
resisted	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
strugling	O
,	O
this	O
Chissel	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Stocking	O
Weaver	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Seat	O
that	O
I	O
sit	O
upon	O
at	O
Work	O
being	O
very	O
uneasy	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
the	O
Chissel	O
to	O
rectify	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Carter	O
say	O
,	O
Damn	O
it	O
there	O
is	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
and	O
twenty	O
in	O
my	O
Information	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
enough	O
of	O
them	O
taken	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wish	O
the	O
rest	O
may	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
B	O
-	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
a	O
Thieving	O
again	O
the	O
Minute	O
that	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
Liberty	O
.	O
Several	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
19.	O
John	B-pers
Balm	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dowle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hamper	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
Fowls	O
,	O
the	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smithers	I-pers
,	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Martland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Soop	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Carbonel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
December	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
Smith	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
fixt	O
to	O
several	O
Houses	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Tillard	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Thompson	O
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bars	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Smith	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Thompson	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bolder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Charles	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
of	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
January	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Monteth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
Mitchel	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
12lb	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Nov	O
,	O
22	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14lb	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Anterac	I-pers
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Morter	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
January	O
16	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
28lb	O
of	O
Lead	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Henning	I-pers
,	O
December	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
these	O
Boys	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Boys	O
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
themselves	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
these	O
Felonies	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Game	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Herlow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Vallens	O
,	O
Sheets	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
John	B-pers
Barkshire	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
William	O
,	O
Earl	B-pers
Cowper	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
lodge	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Nights	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
over	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cowper	O
's	O
Stables	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
eleven	O
Guineas	O
in	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
and	O
wrapt	O
the	O
remaining	O
ten	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Pocket	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
my	O
Bed	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Beds	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
seventeenth	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
where	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Whore	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
12	O
s.	O
left	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
sign	O
'd	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
told	O
him	O
Life	O
was	O
sweet	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ranby	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
afterwards	O
at	O
York	O
Stairs	O
;	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
Whore	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
12	O
s.	O
left	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pukford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Latter	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Latty	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gettings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
and	O
Will	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Botreau	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
John	O
Botreau	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
by	O
two	O
such	O
Boys	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Shop	O
in	O
Earl	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mulatto	O
Boy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
Bently	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Pickle	O
Coucumbers	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
,	O
Dwyer	O
stept	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
stick	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Body	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
Bentley	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
Box	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
our	O
Lodging	O
at	O
-	O
Bedfords	O
,	O
in	O
Well	O
's	O
Yard	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Pound	O
.	O
That	O
House	O
harbours	O
none	O
but	O
such	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Truth	O
was	O
known	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
21	O
d.	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
7	O
d.	O
a	O
Piece	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3lb	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
John	O
Clements	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
3lb	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
off	O
my	O
Counter	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
going	O
along	O
Leather	B-place
Lane	I-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Dwyer	O
stept	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
and	O
a	O
Sugar	O
Loaf	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
'em	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
'em	O
to	O
Jack	O
Oliver	O
,	O
who	O
bit	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
Bentley	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Dwyer	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Dwyer	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Bently	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Philadelphia	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
February	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Quarter	O
Guineas	O
,	O
four	O
Portugal	O
thirty	O
six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Sil-	O
ver	O
,	O
with	O
Child	O
Bed	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
;	O
and	O
ten	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Howit	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Howit	O
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
advertised	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discovered	O
and	O
Confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beckwith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Will	O
.	O
Cummings	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Errand	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Mother	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Baron	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
Case	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Half	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Polack	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
William	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber	O
Pot	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Mary	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pickard	B-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
three	O
Petticoats	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
de	I-pers
Leon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boon	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Call	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Goswell	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
Metal	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Pinchbeck	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
About	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
down	O
New	O
street	O
to	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Court	I-place
.	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
presently	O
mist	O
my	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
comes	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sacheveral	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
dropt	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
four	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
passage	O
in	O
Gunpowder	O
Alley	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Case	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
I	O
nor	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
liberty	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
.	O
Who	O
then	O
to	O
plain	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Yard	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
came	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
her	O
Smock	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
size	O
and	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
Grenadier	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
aside	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
together	O
it	O
would	O
signify	O
nothing	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
back	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Case	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
32.	O
L-	B-pers
R-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
December	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Frances	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
in	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
34.	O
William	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Leghorn	O
Hats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Feb	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
alias	O
Fielder	B-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
not	O
then	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
twelve	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
.	O
six	O
Towels	O
,	O
six	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
fifteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
three	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
Feb.	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
above	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Fielder	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
in	O
Blew	O
:	O
He	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
Nine	O
Pin	O
and	O
Bowl	O
at	O
Edgware	B-place
the	O
Day	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
Lawrence	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
His	O
House	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
mine	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
at	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
five	O
.	O
Their	O
Horses	O
stood	O
the	O
while	O
in	O
my	O
Yard	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
Hay	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
Horses	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
Fielder	O
and	O
Wheeler	O
there	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
Fielder	O
and	O
Wheeler	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Resistance	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pistols	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
in	O
Westminster	O
to	O
the	O
Nine	O
Pin	O
and	O
Bowl	O
at	O
Edgware	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
near	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Lawrences	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
eight	O
or	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Fielder	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
Hatch	O
into	O
the	O
Sheep	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sheep	O
Boy	O
and	O
bound	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
speak	O
when	O
we	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
frighted	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
Gregory	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
A	O
Servant	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
Pistols	O
in	O
our	O
Hands	O
.	O
We	O
bound	O
the	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
and	O
Maid	O
.	O
Turpin	O
pulled	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Breeches	O
down	O
and	O
dragged	O
him	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
discover	O
where	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
.	O
Gregory	O
took	O
the	O
Maid	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
afterwards	O
told	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
away	O
what	O
Money	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
Plate	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
Guineaa	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
any	O
more	O
they	O
cheated	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Share	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
them	O
bound	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
,	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Key	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
,	O
Westminster	O
Wheeler	O
and	O
Rose	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
lodged	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
Fielder	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
twice	O
.	O
Their	O
Horses	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
Stables	O
.	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
a	O
Bay	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
They	O
had	O
such	O
colour	O
'd	O
Horses	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Edgware	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
Black	O
.	O
Bowler	O
.	O
They	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
away	O
together	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
Inn	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Wheeler	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
six	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
his	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boy	O
.	O
That	O
Man	O
in	O
Blue	O
(	O
Fielder	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Sheep	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Garter	O
and	O
tyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
what	O
Servants	O
my	O
Master	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
So	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
Pistols	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threw	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
over	O
my	O
Face	O
-	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Coat	O
(	O
Rose	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Evidence	O
(	O
Wheeler	O
)	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
off	O
my	O
Face	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
Fire	O
Arms	O
my	O
Master	O
kept	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Gun	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Gun	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
Rose	O
took	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Throat	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
it	O
was	O
Rose	O
when	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Person	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
such	O
an	O
offer	O
made	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
that	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
Rose	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pate	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
some	O
body	O
knocked	O
;	O
I	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
Pistols	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Blood	O
!	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
here	O
?	O
We	O
had	O
two	O
Candles	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
their	O
Faces	O
plainly	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
a	O
Cloth	O
over	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Minutes	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
tyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
me	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
and	O
hoodwink	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
-	O
They	O
opened	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Elder	O
Wine	O
and	O
made	O
us	O
drink	O
twice	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Plate	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Resistance	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
paid	O
some	O
Workmen	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Boy	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
!	O
My	O
Man	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
rushed	O
five	O
Men	O
with	O
Pistols	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
Fielder	O
,	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
in	O
Blue	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
:	O
They	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Neckcloth	O
and	O
tyed	O
it	O
over	O
my	O
Eyes	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
down	O
my	O
Breeches	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
six	O
and	O
thirty	O
Shilling	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
shew	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
.	O
They	O
drove	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
my	O
Breeches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
Closet	O
they	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
though	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
thirteen	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
what	O
else	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
all	O
my	O
Linnen	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
Napkins	O
and	O
Shirts	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Sheets	O
off	O
the	O
Beds	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
trod	O
the	O
Beds	O
about	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Money	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
whipt	O
me	O
with	O
their	O
bare	O
Hands	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
strike	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
black	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
my	O
Head	O
with	O
their	O
Pistols	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Kettle	O
of	O
Water	O
off	O
the	O
Fire	O
and	O
threw	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
scalding	O
Water	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
cold	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
me	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
haul	O
'd	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
burn	O
me	O
alive	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
a	O
Bill	O
to	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
chop	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
a	O
Knife	O
under	O
my	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
.	O
Some	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
dragged	O
me	O
about	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
My	O
Breeches	O
were	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
blind	O
folded	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Dorothy	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
House	O
a	O
churning	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
I	O
put	O
out	O
my	O
Candle	O
.	O
They	O
rushed	O
in	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
tyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
.	O
They	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
shew	O
him	O
where	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
Violence	O
-	O
He	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Son	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Son	O
would	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
Yes	O
-	O
Then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
nezt	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
return	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
:	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
any	O
body	O
loose	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
-	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Chest	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Linnen	O
and	O
twenty	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
throw	O
Fielder	O
down	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Rose	O
in	O
Thieving	O
Lane	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
what	O
Resistance	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pullen	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Duck	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
Thieving	O
Lane	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
Rose	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
Thieving	O
Lane	O
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
goes	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Walker	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
found	O
in	O
Rose	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
Fielder	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
talking	O
about	O
.	O
Rose	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
neither	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
alias	O
Saunders	B-pers
alias	O
Schooling	B-pers
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Picture	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
I.	O
washed	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Strainer	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
a	O
Coral	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Mourning	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Cypher	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
enamel	O
'd	O
Blue	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Angels	O
holding	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
and	O
four	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
with	O
Posies	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hat	O
,	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
with	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
thirty	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
Inn	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Marybone	B-place
Park	I-place
;	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
Cow	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Servant	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
another	O
Servant	O
whom	O
we	O
likewise	O
bound	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
seiz	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
Men	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
Bush	O
and	O
Turpin	O
to	O
stand	O
over	O
them	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
four	O
others	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
knocked	O
:	O
The	O
Maid	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
pushed	O
in	O
and	O
bound	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Daughter	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
Gentlewoman	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Fielder	O
broke	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
Gregory	O
stood	O
over	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
quiet	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Silver	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
Cup	O
and	O
Strainer	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Picture	O
,	O
four	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
ten	O
Pound	O
all	O
but	O
eighteen	O
Pence	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Guineas	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
they	O
sunk	O
them	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
we	O
threatned	O
the	O
Family	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
we	O
could	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
all	O
bound	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
thirty	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Pound	O
in	O
Silver	O
besides	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
-	O
They	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
.	O
Three	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
clam	O
'd	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
some	O
Game	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Methinks	O
you	O
are	O
mighty	O
funny	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
they	O
presented	O
their	O
Pistols	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
bound	O
me	O
with	O
my	O
Men	O
.	O
My	O
Eyes	O
are	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
Persons	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
some	O
body	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Wheeler	O
entered	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
followed	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
my	O
Tongue	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
bound	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
set	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
risied	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
:	O
They	O
knocked	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
They	O
cock	O
'd	O
their	O
Pistols	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
manfully	O
to	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
ye	O
done	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Knock	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
struck	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
old	O
Mistress	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
!	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
an	O
old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Coat	O
[	O
Rose	O
]	O
I	O
'll	O
stop	O
your	O
Mouth	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
broke	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
tyed	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
Blood	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cow-House	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
two	O
Fellows	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
bound	O
me	O
,	O
Bush	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
smutted	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
stood	O
sentry	O
over	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
feeding	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
two	O
Fellows	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
his	O
Face	O
all	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
untyed	O
my	O
Garter	O
and	O
bound	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
Bush	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
Manning	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
stood	O
over	O
us	O
with	O
Pistols	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
House	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
Bullets	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
with	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Walker	O
in	O
the	O
Gate	O
House	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Fathers	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
eyes	O
.	O
Keeper	O
.	O
This	O
Medal	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Rose	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
Rings	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Rose	O
himself	O
self	O
-	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
That	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
when	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
And	O
this	O
other	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
with	O
the	O
Posey	O
is	O
my	O
Mothers	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
This	O
Cup	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Walker	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Francis	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Punch	O
Cup	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bartram	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Pistols	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Rose	O
-	O
And	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
within	O
a	O
Pistols	O
length	O
of	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
Trigger	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
Finger	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
Hammer	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
so	O
prevented	O
his	O
firing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
Walker	O
resisted	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
shot	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
.	O
-	O
Harrowfield	O
,	O
a	O
Coachman	O
.	O
Walker	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Pistol	O
and	O
was	O
pulling	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
hung	O
by	O
something	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
knockd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Inn	O
Keeper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
Bush	O
nor	O
Walker	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
others	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
About	O
fifteen	O
Pistols	O
with	O
Bullets	O
,	O
a	O
Bullet-Mould	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Powder	O
Horns	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Fielder	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Rose	O
.	O
Nor	O
I.	O
Walker	O
.	O
Nor	O
I.	O
Bush	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Indictment	O
against	O
Field	O
,	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
Rose	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
to	O
try	O
them	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
37	O
,	O
38	O
,	O
39.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Gulliford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ridgley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Locket	O
,	O
eleven	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Milk	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
Decembber	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ridgly	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Ball	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
abed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
A	O
Square	O
Hole	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
my	O
Shutter	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Pin	O
was	O
unkey	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Shutter	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
,	O
with	O
above	O
fifty	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Rope	O
Walk	O
,	O
in	O
Old	O
Street	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Gulliford	O
cut	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Shutter	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
.	O
Isaacson	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
to	O
Williams	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
took	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
for	O
our	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Silver	O
and	O
the	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
fifty	O
Shillings	O
for	O
the	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Pound	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
for	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fifty	O
four	O
Ounces	O
,	O
at	O
four	O
Shillings	O
an	O
Ounce	O
.	O
-	O
Plaxton	O
.	O
Williams	O
threw	O
this	O
Pistol	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
and	O
Frank	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Williams	O
and	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
our	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
this	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
to	O
shoot	O
the	O
Thief	O
Takers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Jacks	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ivon	B-pers
Lenain	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
lb	O
of	O
Sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
twenty	O
four	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Ferris	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Tape	O
,	O
January	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Ivon	B-pers
Lenain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
against	O
the	O
Knave	O
of	O
Clubs	O
in	O
Club	B-place
Row	I-place
,	O
Spittle	B-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Isaacson	O
got	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Mill	O
(	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
)	O
drew	O
the	O
Hooks	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
one	O
Shutter	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
one	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
Jacks	O
looked	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Whitehead	O
for	O
thirty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jacks	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
any	O
Robbery	O
besides	O
this	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
.	O
We	O
became	O
acquainted	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Whiteheads	O
.	O
She	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Jewin	O
Street	O
and	O
sold	O
Greens	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pretence	O
that	O
People	O
might	O
not	O
suspect	O
that	O
she	O
dealt	O
in	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
Jacks	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
40.	O
John	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
nine	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
Punch	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Ale	O
House	O
at	O
Mile	O
End	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
sixteen	O
Pence-a-piece	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
away	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
went	O
foremost	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
hindmost	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
done	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
I	O
past	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
Rich	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
fluced	O
the	O
Link	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
prick	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
prick	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
prick	O
'd	O
,	O
Tom	O
.	O
Johnson	O
tript	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Heels	O
.	O
John	O
Rich	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Maid	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
I	O
flurried	O
the	O
Link	O
over	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
nor	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
surprised	O
at	O
his	O
Sword	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
two	O
Wounds	O
in	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
told	O
me	O
was	O
three	O
Inches	O
deep	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
wounded	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
fifty	O
Yards	O
behind	O
when	O
Rich	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Maid	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
Noise	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
saw	O
Rich	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
Jack	O
Rich	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
prick	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
over	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
by	O
the	O
Bridge	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Knight	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
Rich	O
when	O
he	O
whisked	O
the	O
Link	O
over	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Neither	O
he	O
nor	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
Rich	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
came	O
Johnson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Rich	O
both	O
tumbled	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
ten	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Yards	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
Johnson	O
did	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
Rich	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
prick	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
swear	O
that	O
Johnson	O
did	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
Johnson	O
himself	O
has	O
sworn	O
that	O
he	O
trip	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fairfax	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Rich	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
them	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
himself	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
prick	O
'd	O
Johnson	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
assaulted	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
one	O
was	O
pricked	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
forced	O
Johnson	O
over	O
the	O
Ditch	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Rich	O
,	O
Ye	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
thrust	O
my	O
Sword	O
down	O
your	O
Throat	O
.	O
The	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
.	O
Rich	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
the	O
Link	O
into	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
shut	O
the	O
Hatch	O
when	O
Rich	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
burn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
the	O
Link	O
to	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pushed	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
leaned	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Link	O
under	O
my	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
and	O
pitched	O
my	O
Petticoat	O
-	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
.	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Knock	O
the	O
Bitch	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Cane	O
within	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
forced	O
the	O
Hatch	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
the	O
Cane	O
you	O
Bitch	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
fetch	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watmore	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
and	O
Daughter	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Grandson	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
Supper	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Maid	O
cry	O
Murder	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
my	O
Grandson	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
of	O
swearing	O
at	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Fellows	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Link	O
and	O
struck	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
pushed	O
us	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
same	O
Fellow	O
flurried	O
his	O
Link	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Goslin	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Maid	O
as	O
bad	O
or	O
worse	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
scream	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
lean	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
the	O
Link	O
downwards	O
-	O
The	O
Captain	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Henson	O
got	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Captain	O
down	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Henson	O
trip	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Link	O
Boy	O
's	O
Heels	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Captain	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Link	O
Boy	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
you	O
deserve	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
Link	O
run	O
down	O
your	O
Throat	O
:	O
Come	O
back	O
and	O
make	O
my	O
Servant	O
Recompence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Henson	I-pers
,	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
Johnson	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
along	O
of	O
Rich	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
the	O
Link	O
in	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Captain	O
came	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
Fist	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
Sword	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
says	O
Parker	O
,	O
You	O
tript	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
says	O
Johnson	O
,	O
But	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Knock	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
la	O
Motte	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
peaceable	O
,	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
's	O
Verdict	O
was	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
41.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Knight	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
to	O
Edith	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooms	I-pers
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
43.	O
James	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Saws	O
,	O
two	O
Plains	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Oakly	I-pers
;	O
and	O
five	O
Books	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
January	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ream	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Guillims	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Francis	B-pers
Fort	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
for	O
one	O
Hundred	O
Pound	O
each	O
,	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
fifty	O
Pound	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
two	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
each	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
forty	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
Decem	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
a	O
Cheesmonger	O
in	O
King	B-place
street	I-place
Westminster	I-place
)	O
laid	O
the	O
Bag	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
upon	O
a	O
Pile	O
of	O
Cheshire	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
and	O
forgot	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Bag	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Porter	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Bag	O
lay	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Bag	O
was	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
Notice	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
stop	O
such	O
Notes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
three	O
Notes	O
were	O
sent	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
Penny	O
Post	O
Letter	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Doyle	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Apparrel	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
lb	O
of	O
Lead	O
fix't	O
to	O
Lincolns	B-place
Inn	I-place
Playhouse	I-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Linwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
seven	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
three	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Immings	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Feb	O
20	O
.	O
John	O
Immings	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Ratsy	I-pers
.	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
my	O
Master	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Acton	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
Tick	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
where	O
my	O
Mistress	O
was	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
Ratsy	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
stop	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Mistress	O
liked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
better	O
than	O
she	O
did	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
shabby	O
Fellow	O
before	O
she	O
run	O
my	O
Master	O
in	O
Debt	O
to	O
maintain	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Shirt	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
upon	O
Tick	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
must	O
be	O
forced	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
frequently	O
a	O
Junketting	O
together	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
in	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
absence	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Master	O
coming	O
home	O
one	O
time	O
sooner	O
than	O
was	O
expected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Alley	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
wash	O
his	O
Linnen	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
me	O
once	O
to	O
pawn	O
forty	O
four	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
extravagant	O
Ways	O
had	O
made	O
my	O
Master	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
It	O
's	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
business	O
to	O
meddle	O
or	O
make	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
play	O
the	O
Whore	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
answer	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
a	O
Green	O
Purse	O
of	O
Gold	O
in	O
a	O
Bravado	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
visit	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
Market	O
.	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
kept	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
New	O
Oxford	O
Market	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
partners	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
it	O
well	O
enough	O
and	O
and	O
has	O
bought	O
Goods	O
for	O
us	O
both	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
-	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
how	O
things	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
forbid	O
him	O
my	O
House	O
-	O
The	O
Night	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
Night	O
House	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Wife	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
whither	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
value	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Butchers	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Wife	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
and	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
their	O
Journey	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
robbed	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
49.	O
George	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
50.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Blackhorse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Canlestick	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
51.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
Winifred	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
52.	O
John	B-pers
Olyver	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
47	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53	O
,	O
54	O
,	O
55.	O
John	B-pers
Sindal	I-pers
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ethelbert	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Fish	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Frying	O
Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
eighteen	O
Plates	O
,	O
four	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Brass	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
two	O
Wigs	O
,	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Faucet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Madam	O
Love	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
beyond	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Cross	I-place
.	O
The	O
back	O
side	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
fore	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
all	O
abed	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
Ladder	O
next	O
the	O
Sea	O
Side	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Then	O
Nathan	O
and	O
I	O
hoisted	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
or	O
Dining	O
Room	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Hawks	O
got	O
in	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Hawks	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
There	O
stands	O
a	O
great	O
Thief-Catcher	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
contrived	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
knocking	O
at	O
Folk	O
's	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
getting	O
in	O
and	O
robbing	O
their	O
Houses	O
.	O
He	O
robbed	O
Col.	O
Ronaines	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turned	O
Evidence	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
his	O
Comrades	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
's	O
turn	O
'd	O
Thief	O
Taker	O
,	O
and	O
wants	O
to	O
hang	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
