TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1735	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	O
BELLAMY	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Hardwicke	O
,	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Randall	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stringfellow	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Witheridge	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Humblebee	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Picksal	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Casely	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Satchel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Eels	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stockman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Macgwin	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
Pound	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
April	O
7	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
On	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Procession	O
to	O
the	O
Spital	O
Sermon	O
at	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
:	O
And	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
drew	O
my	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
I	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
how	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
Sword	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
handed	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
Henry	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6.	O
Frances	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Gilchrist	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bohea	O
Tea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
East	B-pers
India	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Surbut	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Labourer	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
Ware-house	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Stocking	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Tea	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
sometimes	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
Company	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
Practice	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Tea	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Chests	O
of	O
Tea	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Ware-house	O
belonging	O
to	O
other	O
Merchants	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Tea	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Dakins	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
8.	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
each	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Hester	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
Pound	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Coral	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
Lady	O
coming	O
into	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
wait	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
my	O
Workman	O
(	O
who	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
)	O
appeared	O
in	O
a	O
surprise	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Card	O
of	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
fifteen	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
unlacing	O
her	O
felt	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Plate	O
-	O
She	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hobden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
Card	O
of	O
Rings	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Child	O
's	O
Godfather	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Child	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
ask	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
cost	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10.	O
James	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
Pound	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
Hon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Delawar	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Pierre	O
du	O
Lac	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
Richard	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dennison	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Laced	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rumph	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
13.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
3l	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Banyan	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lew	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lewis	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Porter	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mears	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blewet	B-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Eleazar	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
and	I-place
Coronet	I-place
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Company	O
for	O
her	O
Interest	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
left	O
this	O
Seal	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
pledge	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
obliging	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
being	O
drunk	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Three	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dressing	O
her	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Seal	O
hanging	O
to	O
her	O
Watch	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Low	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
Seal	O
.	O
You	O
lie	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
I	O
'll	O
keep	O
it	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
owe	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
bury	O
you	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
vild	O
Woman	O
and	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afraid	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
House	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Longbotham	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
persuade	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Seal	O
and	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
Fool	O
as	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Kendenell	I-pers
.	O
*	O
I	O
was	O
Drawer	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
charge	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
*	O
Rowland	O
Kendenell	O
was	O
tryed	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
2	O
.	O
Page	O
27.	O
was	O
a	O
lying	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
bury	O
her	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
16.	O
Mary	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramsby	I-pers
alias	O
Bransy	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bays	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Fore	O
Bodies	O
and	O
Backs	O
of	O
a	O
Waist-coat	O
,	O
four	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
for	O
Breeches	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Goose	O
and	O
Cabbage	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Several	O
Persons	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	O
Bays	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Whaile	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Weight	O
,	O
Feb.	O
25.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Walmsley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Walmsley	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
Heels	O
were	O
tripp	O
'd	O
up	O
near	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
honest	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
clean	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Warwick	O
's	O
in	O
Sheer	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Landlady	O
Warwick	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
This	O
Man	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Woman	O
scraped	O
the	O
Dirt	O
off	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
Warwick	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
for	O
the	O
Wine	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
Change	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
that	O
for	O
cleaning	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
held	O
my	O
Hands	O
while	O
Warwick	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
keep	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
We	O
sat	O
down	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Guinea	O
more	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
that	O
again	O
by	O
main	O
force	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
Warwick	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
did	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
only	O
she	O
went	O
twice	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
shut	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
to	O
help	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
bear	O
with	O
this	O
usage	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
mischief	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
Door	O
that	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
House	O
into	O
another	O
as	O
bad	O
(	O
where	O
one	O
Bishop	O
keeps	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
)	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Man	O
is	O
robbed	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Houses	O
,	O
the	O
Thieves	O
whip	O
through	O
this	O
Door	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
escape	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
served	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
Warwick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
got	O
off	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
find	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
Moll	B-pers
Nutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Beck	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Walmsley	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
House	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
21.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sears	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Streeter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Hams	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
Sears	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Flureau	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty	O
six	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Slaughter	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Slaughter	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
had	O
sold	O
thirty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Cuttings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
being	O
examined	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Silver	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Master	O
denying	O
he	O
ever	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Rowen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Roan	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Cornhill	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Habitation	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Grace	B-place
Church	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
crost	O
over	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
invited	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Spread	B-place
Eagle	I-place
.	O
where	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
betwixt	O
'em	O
before	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
were	O
pretty	O
warm	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
:	O
And	O
so	O
says	O
Jenny	B-pers
Roan	I-pers
,	O
What	O
do	O
we	O
come	O
here	O
for	O
?	O
And	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
claps	O
her	O
Hands	O
to	O
my	O
Breeches	O
to	O
unbutton	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
she	O
goes	O
out	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
Peg	B-pers
Young	I-pers
follows	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
they	O
staid	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
and	O
thinking	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Watch	O
could	O
I	O
find	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Women	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
few	O
Nights	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
produced	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Calcot	O
's	O
,	O
)	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
Watch	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Young	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
Owner	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
otherwise	O
they	O
should	O
neither	O
have	O
Money	O
nor	O
Watch	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
advertise	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
strange	O
Uproar	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Common	O
Council	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
Tavern	O
upon	O
Parish	O
Affairs	O
-	O
Peg	B-pers
Young	I-pers
hearing	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
rioted	O
him	O
before	O
all	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
noisy	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Roan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
full	O
Discharge	O
under	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
only	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
March	O
18	O
1734-5	O
.	O
Received	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
one	O
Shilling	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	B-pers
Roan	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
full	O
of	O
all	O
Accounts	O
per	O
me	O
Samuel	O
Cole	O
Margaret	O
Young	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Drawer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
sold	O
fruit	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
Play-house	O
-	O
And	O
so	O
meeting	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
Jenny	B-pers
Roan	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Grace	O
Church	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
persuaded	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Wine	O
mull	O
'd	O
with	O
Eggs	O
.	O
Peggy	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
its	O
bloody	O
cold	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
your	O
Maiden-head	O
and	O
mine	O
will	O
keep	O
one	O
another	O
warm	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
oblige	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
Present	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
oblige	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
ye	O
my	O
Watch	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
he	O
gives	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
accordingly	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
:	O
And	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
comes	O
and	O
demands	O
this	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gives	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
;	O
whereof	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
New	O
Gown	O
he	O
had	O
promised	O
me	O
-	O
Besides	O
he	O
run	O
me	O
to	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
charge	O
in	O
Coach-hire	O
and	O
Wine	O
and	O
Veal	O
Cutlets	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
sworn	O
I	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Mistake	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
his	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
pledged	O
his	O
Watch	O
to	O
be	O
obliged	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
by	O
other	O
Women	O
too	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
makes	O
a	O
common	O
Practice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
25.	O
Martin	B-pers
Fin	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
(	O
his	O
Wife	O
)	O
,	O
Bridget	O
(	O
his	O
Wife	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cacket	I-pers
,	O
from	B-pers
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cacket	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
a	O
Drapers	O
)	O
in	O
Lombard	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
just	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
along	O
and	O
hussled	O
Mrs.	O
Cacket	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
She	O
presently	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Purse	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Six	O
Bell	O
Ale-house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
those	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
were	O
the	O
People	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
Daniel	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
tall	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Whitish	O
Cloak	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Red	O
Cloak	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Six	O
Pence	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
opened	O
her	O
Hand	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
Bridget	B-pers
Fin	I-pers
(	O
the	O
little	O
Woman	O
)	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
jog	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
five	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Yes	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
.	O
A	O
Boy	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
dropt	O
something	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
We	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
six	O
Pences	O
more	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cacket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
assured	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
Persons	O
-	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
joggled	O
in	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
came	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
behind	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
in	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
missing	O
my	O
Purse	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Friend	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Red	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Daniel	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Virtue	O
of	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Purse	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
We	O
neglected	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Purse	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
)	O
Stephen	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taft	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
Foot	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
Girl	O
that	O
sells	O
Oranges	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
accidentally	O
into	O
their	O
Company	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
Se'n-night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Rowland	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
Foot	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Daniel	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Rowland	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Daniel	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
three	O
Years	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Gardener	O
.	O
Griffith	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Journey-man	O
Upholstrer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Call	O
Rowland	O
and	O
Loyd	O
.	O
again	O
-	O
Here	O
Rowland	O
,	O
on	O
what	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
Daniel	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
Tavern	O
?	O
Rowland	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Rowland	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
set	O
Eyes	O
on	O
her	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Discourse	O
with	O
her	O
then	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
know	O
you	O
?	O
Rowland	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
Rowland	O
.	O
Nay	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
subpaena	O
'd	O
by	O
somebody	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
fancy	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
how	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
Loyd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
Loyd	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Rowland	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
talk	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
?	O
Rowland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Loyd	O
?	O
Officer	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
called	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
but	O
have	O
heard	O
no	O
answer	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
's	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
25.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Sacrilegiously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ounces	O
and	O
fourteen	O
Penn	O
Weight	O
of	O
Gold	O
Fringe	O
.	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
,	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Chappel	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Earl	O
of	O
Oxford	O
,	O
called	O
Oxford	O
Chappel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gladwin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
intrusted	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gold	O
Fringe	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
burnt	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foubert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
Ounces	O
and	O
twelve	O
Penny	O
Weight	O
of	O
burnt	O
Silver	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Sacriledge	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
nothing	O
appears	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Chappel	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Fringe	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
private	O
Chappel	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Noble	O
Man	O
's	O
House	O
-	O
Jury-man	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
conse-crated	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Sacriledge	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Jemima	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Plain	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Chrystal	O
Stone	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Red	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Chrystal	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
St.	O
Albans	O
about	O
a	O
Bankruptcy	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
serv	O
'd	O
as	O
I	O
afterwards	O
was	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
Sheer	I-place
Lane	I-place
*	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
together	O
before	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
first	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
My	O
Rings	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
her	O
up	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
hinder	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
*	O
Where	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
N.	O
P.	O
Pallamounter	O
lost	O
above	O
30	O
l.	O
for	O
stealing	O
which	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
Brother	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
seems	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
promised	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
Drawer	O
advised	O
us	O
not	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Smith	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Property	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
again	O
afterwards	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
tipt	O
the	O
wink	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
These	O
two	O
Men	O
drank	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
They	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
oblige	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Rings	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
three	O
Rings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
strange	O
Gentleman	O
followed	O
us	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
token	O
that	O
I	O
stood	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
stroked	O
that	O
little	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Hump	O
for	O
luck	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Hewitson	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
called	O
Of	O
Alley	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hewitson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
St.	O
Patrick	O
's	O
Day	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
Work	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
near	O
Cecil	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
Of	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Mob	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
.	O
My	O
Head	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
hurt	O
and	O
abused	O
in	O
other	O
respects	O
.	O
I	O
cryed	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
followed	O
him	O
without	O
either	O
Cap	O
,	O
Apron	O
,	O
or	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
Apron	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
somebody	O
thrust	O
them	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
as	O
rugged	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
does	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a-top	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
-	O
The	O
Woman	O
complained	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
staggering	O
along	O
as	O
drunk	O
as	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Dram	O
or	O
two	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
her	O
Apron	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
going	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kello	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Graham	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Abraham	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
between	O
twenty	O
and	O
thirty	O
Years	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
modest	O
,	O
virtuous	O
and	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cantillon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
confounded	O
drunk	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Country-men	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
keep	O
within	O
Doors	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bressan	O
.	O
That	O
Night	O
being	O
St.	O
Patrick	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
so	O
drunk	O
in	O
honour	O
of	O
St.	O
Patrick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
.	O
At	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
Morgan	B-pers
Donavin	I-pers
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
that	O
Night	O
as	O
drunk	O
as	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
stand	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
,	O
the	O
Governess	O
of	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
come	O
to	O
out	O
Round-house	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hewitson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
fright	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
more	O
drunk	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
downright	O
Drunkenness	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
,	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
sign	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
Woman	O
.	O
Mac	O
Carthy	O
,	O
Macnamara	O
,	O
Morgan	O
Donavin	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morphy	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
28.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
February	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Richard	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
five	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
,	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
New	B-place
Turn-Stile	I-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
Nov.	O
18.	O
or	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
we	O
lost	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
which	O
stood	O
upon	O
a	O
Dresser	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Shop	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
Rush	O
Candle	O
burning	O
by	O
us	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
left	O
upon	O
the	O
Latch	O
that	O
my	O
Sister	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
without	O
disturbing	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
the	O
least	O
Noise	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
his	O
Son	O
Butler	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
with	O
Sweet	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
both	O
hanged	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Audry	I-pers
(	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Sister	O
)	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
Drawers	O
off	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
which	O
leads	O
into	O
Princes	O
Street	O
half	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
was	O
bolted	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
-	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Back	O
Doors	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Yard	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
Night	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kingston	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
attempt	O
made	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
House	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
Church	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
the	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
Butler	O
Buckley	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Passage	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
My	O
Boy	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Oven	O
to	O
warm	O
himself	O
.	O
My	O
Boy	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Oven	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Butler	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
Bridewell	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Belcher	O
,	O
who	O
examined	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
were	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
first	O
at	O
one	O
place	O
and	O
then	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
both	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
.	O
We	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
Lies	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Stock-house	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
Kingston	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Uncle	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
and	O
Phillip	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
robbed	O
the	O
Church	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Little	O
Turn-Stile	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
House	O
upon	O
Little	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
each	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Banford	O
resolving	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
Horse	O
and	O
rode	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
with	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
Tothill	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
what	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
named	O
the	O
particulars	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
account	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
given	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Butler	O
Buckley	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
Victuals	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Sultana	O
's	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Canister	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Oxenden	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
informed	O
us	O
of	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Banford	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Canister	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Sultana	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
Boy	O
had	O
told	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
Sweet	O
was	O
a	O
notorious	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
enticed	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
Kingston	O
.	O
Richard	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Sweet	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Tothill	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Warrant	O
we	O
then	O
had	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
taking	O
Sweet	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
But	O
next	O
Day	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
went	O
to	O
Kingston	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Richard	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
.	O
His	O
Brother	O
John	O
hearing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
wants	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Who	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
My	O
Name	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
defy	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
.	O
Be	O
ye	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Banford	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Sweet	O
,	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Butler	O
Buckley	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
nine	O
Years	O
old	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
)	O
being	O
examined	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
false	O
Swearing	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
satisfactory	O
Answers	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
admitted	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
Butler	O
Buckley	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
Richard	O
Buckley	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Uncle	O
John	O
Buckley	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Sweet	O
,	O
and	O
Phillip	O
Wilkinson	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
both	O
hang	O
'd	O
at	O
Kingston	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Little	O
Turn-Stile	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Screen	O
was	O
drawn	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
hid	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
till	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Entry	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
leading	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
(	O
Little	O
Turn-Stile	O
)	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
in	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
and	O
Sweet	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
Uncle	O
standing	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
next	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
next	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
and	O
Sweet	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
out	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
nine	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Brussels	O
Laced	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
directly	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
home	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
At	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
forward	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Doyley	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
Green	O
Canister	O
in	O
Piccadily	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
Discovery	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Busby	O
took	O
me	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
force	O
ye	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
turn	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
liberty	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
confess	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
your	O
Father	O
or	O
Uncle	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
named	O
them	O
first	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
I	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
at	O
Kingston	O
mention	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
all	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Busby	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Boy	O
spoke	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Boy	O
whipt	O
and	O
hung	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Heels	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Busby	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bailiff	O
Belcher	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
confess	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
threatned	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
him	O
whipt	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
When	O
and	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
and	O
your	O
Uncle	O
together	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
both	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
that	O
Day	O
as	O
the	O
Church	O
was	O
robbed	O
-	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
March	O
-	O
And	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee	O
House	O
in	O
Coventry	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
,	O
by	O
Woodstock	O
Meuse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
-	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Shoe-maker	O
-	O
And	O
twice	O
at	O
the	O
Canister	O
where	O
we	O
lodged	O
,	O
once	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Besides	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
we	O
carried	O
home	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
us	O
together	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Macrakan	O
's	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Canister	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Sweet	O
or	O
Wilkinson	O
there	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lie	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
Kingston	O
Church	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Waterman	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Kingston	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Busby	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
by	O
the	O
Waterman	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Furniture	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
what	O
care	O
I	O
could	O
in	O
giving	O
my	O
Boy	O
good	O
Instructions	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
care	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
effect	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
perverse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
notorious	O
Lyar	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
corrected	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
with	O
severity	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
hardening	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Cranburn	O
Alley	O
for	O
some	O
Worsted	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
next	O
Day	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Loyd	O
.	O
Butler	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Your	O
Chalks	O
are	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
must	O
reckon	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
;	O
for	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
Sweet	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
had	O
decoyed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Kingston	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Kingston	O
till	O
Sunday	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
swears	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
my	O
Brother	O
John	O
for	O
near	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
word	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Warrant	O
.	O
J.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Sweet	O
nor	O
Wilkinson	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
Day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Buckley	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Macrakan	O
's	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
in	O
Little	O
Earl	O
street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
and	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
to	O
shew	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Little	O
Turn-Stile	O
)	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Buckley	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
*	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
lived	O
at	O
Martha	B-pers
Macrakans	I-pers
a	O
Year	O
and	O
two	O
Months	O
;	O
they	O
moved	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Canister	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Macrakans	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
deposed	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
March	O
:	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
November	O
:	O
The	O
Boy	O
swore	O
I	O
then	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Canister	O
-	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Brother	O
John	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Macrakans	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Macrackan	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
a	O
notorious	O
Lyar	O
.	O
Jemima	B-pers
Covedale	I-pers
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
-	O
next	O
Saturday	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Boy	O
standing	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Gaskins	O
Door	O
,	O
near	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
He	O
pray	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
Mrs.	O
Gaskins	O
her	O
Cousin	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Cousin	O
?	O
She	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
and	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
her	O
Son	O
Bobby	O
.	O
She	O
chid	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gaskin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
all	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
March	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
Kingston	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fromage	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sultana	O
Tavern	O
.	O
Richard	O
Buckley	O
was	O
a	O
Waiter	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
his	O
Glasses	O
came	O
in	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
us	O
from	O
Pontacks	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
fifty	O
,	O
sixty	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
hundred	O
Pound	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
his	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Grief	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
swore	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Kingston	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fromage	O
.	O
That	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
on	O
some	O
Noble	O
Men	O
at	O
my	O
,	O
House	O
and	O
they	O
burnt	O
his	O
Wig	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
amends	O
-	O
He	O
complained	O
that	O
his	O
Boy	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Waiter	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
several	O
Noble	O
Men	O
dined	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
bespoke	O
a	O
Dinner	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
waited	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
at	O
twelve	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Wig	O
was	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Noon	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Bonifaces	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
eleven	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
forget	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Sultana	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
his	O
Glasses	O
were	O
sent	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
waited	O
on	O
some	O
Noble	O
Men	O
.	O
Between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Company	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Wig	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Noble	O
Men	O
had	O
burnt	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Boniface	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Noon	O
,	O
March	O
9th	O
(	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
dyed	O
)	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
Fellow	O
Servants	O
,	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
Morris	O
,	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
drest	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Graves	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Credit	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Maidwell	O
for	O
some	O
Glasses	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
in	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
Mr.	O
Maidwell	O
's	O
Bill	O
for	O
such	O
Glasses	O
,	O
dated	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Father	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
.	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Vipont	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Long	O
Room	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
June	O
last	O
to	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
faithfull	O
and	O
just	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
at	O
Scarborough	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Season	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Waile	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
brave	O
Man	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
hang	O
'd	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Uncle	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
-	O
He	O
's	O
an	O
impudent	O
,	O
lying	O
,	O
mischievous	O
Boy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
,	O
in	O
New	O
Bond-street	O
.	O
John	O
Buckley	O
lodged	O
there	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
Midsummer	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
lived	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
.	O
R.	O
Buckley	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
swore	O
that	O
my	O
Brother	O
lived	O
in	O
Bond	O
street	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
often	O
met	O
together	O
lately	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
difference	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
.	O
Richard	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
John	O
disobliged	O
Richard	O
,	O
by	O
refusing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Richard	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
prest	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
reconcil	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
friends	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Father	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
's	O
an	O
ungratefull	O
Rascal	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
March	O
(	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Boy	O
charges	O
him	O
with	O
being	O
at	O
Kingston	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
four	O
times	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
betwixt	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
for	O
odd	O
things	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
his	O
Brother	O
Richard	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
honest	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
together	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Calder	I-pers
,	O
(	O
on	O
Tower	B-place
hill	I-place
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
six	O
Shifts	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
October	O
23	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
they	O
and	O
Sweet	O
,	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
detected	O
in	O
several	O
Falshoods	O
and	O
Contradictions	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Number	O
of	O
Creditable	O
Witnesses	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
30.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Huggit	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
3	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
R.	O
Brown	O
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Steps	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
in	O
Moor	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
a	O
Sally	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
drunk	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
at	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
White	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
your	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shifted	O
her	O
Hands	O
behind	O
her	O
.	O
Several	O
People	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
dragged	O
her	O
along	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
then	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
two	O
Irish	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scotch	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
all	O
your	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
all	O
again	O
except	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
meeting	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
by	O
the	O
Quarters	O
in	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
,	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
put	O
this	O
bad	O
Money	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Look	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Do	O
I	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
Whore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
But	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
thieving	O
Bitch	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Men	O
stript	O
me	O
naked	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
that	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
Man	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
near	O
the	O
Steps	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Herb	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Court	O
in	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Basket	O
Women	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
32.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Staygold	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Staygold	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
going	O
through	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Passage	O
towards	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
full	O
but	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
plainly	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
at	O
an	O
Apple	B-pers
Stall	I-pers
.	O
He	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
0ut	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Wormwood	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
:	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Standing	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
Wormwood	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
walked	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
Peter	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
Peter	O
Hubbard	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
did	O
I	O
stop	O
him	O
for	O
?	O
But	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
behind	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
34.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kenning	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Campell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Campell	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
About	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
William	I-pers
's	O
House	O
in	O
Hanging	B-place
Sword	I-place
Alley	I-place
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
says	O
Jenny	O
,	O
Let	O
this	O
Woman	O
drink	O
too	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
drunk	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
Jenny	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
when	O
Jenny	O
went	O
home	O
:	O
but	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
mist	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
Newgate-Bird-Son-of-a-Bitch	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
then	O
neither	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Jenny	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
Fellow	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stript	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
Gold	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Warson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
March	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36.	O
Chrisset	B-pers
Quint	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
Charles	B-pers
Noise	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
*	O
In	O
December	O
,	O
1731	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
convicted	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Drague	I-pers
;	O
and	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
1734.	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turlip	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Hens	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38	O
,	O
39	O
,	O
40	O
,	O
41	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Funnel	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42.	O
Ann	B-pers
Blackerby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
43	O
,	O
44.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Quilts	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Door	O
of	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maine	I-pers
,	O
February	O
27	O
.	O
Rice	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
Price	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
James	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Double	O
Deals	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mariner	I-pers
.	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48	O
,	O
49.	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hammers	O
,	O
two	O
Borers	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Leaden	O
Weights	O
,	O
March	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Cordial	O
Water	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50	O
John	B-pers
Spakeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Townly	I-pers
,	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
51.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brasser	B-pers
alias	O
Rose	B-pers
alias	O
Cox	B-pers
alias	O
Head	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
nine	O
Napkins	O
,	O
two	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
one	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
February	O
16	O
.	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
which	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
were	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
with	O
Mottos	O
,	O
a	O
Mourning	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Cypher	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Picture	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
I.	O
washed	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
,	O
February	O
16	O
.	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
stealing	O
which	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
were	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
After	O
John	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
robbed	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
's	O
Lodging	O
near	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
Inn	O
in	O
Dawes	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	B-place
,	O
Westminster	B-place
.	O
We	O
laid	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
and	O
appraised	O
them	O
among	O
our	O
selves	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
price	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
us	O
our	O
Shares	O
:	O
And	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
and	O
how	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
two	O
Days	O
she	O
sold	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
him	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
Box	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Linnen	O
and	O
fifteen	O
Pound	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
farther	O
appeared	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Thieving	O
Lane	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
orders	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Westridge	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gunner	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
These	O
Goods	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
53.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54	O
,	O
55.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hadly	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Adley	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
two	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
Pound	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jukes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jukes	I-pers
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
56.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roly	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
57.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarkland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
58.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Talken	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
59.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lee	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
60.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ghees	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ansley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
61	O
,	O
62.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bushby	I-pers
,	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Start	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Bushby	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Start	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
holp	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
carried	O
me	O
there	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Pouch	O
to	O
pour	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knocked	O
it	O
all	O
off	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Guinea	O
that	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Pouch	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
with	O
one	O
more	O
Guinea	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Taylor	O
knocked	O
me	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
up	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
Taylor	O
picked	O
up	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Te	O
Rascalty	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
skin	O
ye	O
alive	O
if	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
your	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
some	O
Run	O
Brandy	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
;	O
But	O
while	O
they	O
staid	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
above	O
Stairs	O
attending	O
other	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
Black-shoe	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
any	O
Money	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
leaving	O
any	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Some	O
Words	O
arising	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Hastings	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
voluntarily	O
surrendered	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
these	O
Allegations	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
63.	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Fisher	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
January	O
24	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
an	O
Accomplice	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
against	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
)	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
64.	O
Ann	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
65.	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Chancellor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
fourth	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Beatrice	I-pers
Biatard	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
66.	O
William	B-pers
Maze	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Steel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
67.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dawling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blisset	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
April	O
16	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
68.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tharlesworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
promissory	O
Note	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
drawing	O
,	O
for	O
ten	O
Pound	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfyed	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Fitzgerald	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
69.	O
Jarvis	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cassoy	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
.	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
70.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
April	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
71.	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
72,73,74.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hives	I-pers
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
*	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
and	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
Stiles	O
was	O
convicted	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
2	O
.	O
Page	O
26	O
.	O
75.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tea	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
stranging	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Town	I-pers
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
twenty	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
and	O
the	O
Dog	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
to	O
smell	O
at	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sink	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
Disorder	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
run	O
his	O
Nose	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Clout	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
like	O
Disorder	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
my	O
Servant	O
appeared	O
very	O
uneasy	O
at	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
from	O
one	O
Room	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
ail	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
look	O
where	O
I	O
pleased	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
must	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
slight	O
Miscarriage	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
there	O
and	O
seen	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Sink	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
uneasy	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
Work	O
as	O
ever	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
Wages	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
dissatisfied	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
there	O
very	O
clean	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
born	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
because	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
It	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
growth	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Spots	O
nor	O
Marks	O
of	O
violence	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
following	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
her	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
bury	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
come	O
before	O
her	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
76.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Chrystal	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
enamel	O
'd	O
and	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
from	B-pers
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
I	O
wrapt	O
my	O
Rings	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
my	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
staid	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
down	O
my	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Rings	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
down	O
your	O
Bosom	O
?	O
S.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
Nay	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
not	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
surprise	O
at	O
missing	O
my	O
Rings	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Indeed	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Then	O
pray	O
search	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
begun	O
to	O
strip	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Constable	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
into	O
a	O
Skettle	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Milk	O
Womans	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
Justice	O
and	O
Newgate	O
should	O
be	O
her	O
portion	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
afterwards	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
all	O
the	O
Charges	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
throw	O
in	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Rigmaramus	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
Brandy	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
down	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
mist	O
her	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
search	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
Whereof	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
stript	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
her	O
things	O
on	O
again	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
For	O
all	O
your	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
your	O
Husband	O
is	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
this	O
Brandy	O
Woman	O
's	O
Creatures	O
;	O
you	O
owe	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
you	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
she	O
bids	O
you	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
notorious	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Sea	B-place
Coal-Lane	I-place
.	O
She	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
breakfast	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
but	O
took	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
among	O
us	O
besides	O
dry	O
Drams	O
.	O
She	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
heartily	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
beat	O
her	O
Mother	O
.	O
-	O
S.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
Beat	O
my	O
Mother	O
?	O
Lord	O
Jesus	O
!	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
fighting	O
,	O
this	O
Nell	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
her	O
a	O
clean	O
Shift	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
this	O
very	O
Nell	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
with	O
taking	O
her	O
Rings	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
ill	O
thought	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
got'em	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Caterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
drunk	O
Rum	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
Punch	O
.	O
She	O
fell	O
a	O
fighting	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
her	O
Smock	O
was	O
tore	O
all	O
to	O
rags	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Rings	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
'em	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Lord	O
Almighty	O
knows	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
'em	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
Nell	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
and	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
with	O
having	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
stript	O
as	O
naked	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
together	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
all	O
been	O
drinking	O
:	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
you	O
disguis	O
'd	O
?	O
S.	O
Caterson	O
.	O
Disguis	O
'd	O
!	O
Yes	O
,	O
O	O
my	O
conscience	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
disguis	O
'd	O
sure	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
stark	O
naked	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
intorious	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
body	O
suffers	O
for	O
her	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
-	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
dusterous	O
,	O
honest	O
Woman	O
as	O
lives	O
by	O
bread	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Barlin	O
Swash	O
(	O
Baron	B-pers
Suasso	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Beecham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
body	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
los	O
to	O
go	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
untorious	O
House	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
77.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Coltsford	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
78.	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
5.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stockman	I-pers
alias	O
Macquin	O
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tea	I-pers
.	O
Barret	O
and	O
Grindley	O
pleaded	O
there	O
Bellies	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Transportation	O
37.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Casely	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramsby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bays	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
alias	O
Rose	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
Jemima	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
Chrissy	B-pers
Quint	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Noise	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Funnel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Calker	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Jarvis	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brain	I-pers
.	O
Whipt	O
2.	O
Ann	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mare	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
is	O
published	O
in	O
two	O
Volumes	O
in	O
Octavo	O
,	O
price	O
Fourteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
SELECT	O
TRIALS	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
Murders	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
Rapes	O
,	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
Coining	O
,	O
Frauds	O
and	O
other	O
Offences	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Year	O
1720	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
time	O
;	O
chiefly	O
transcribed	O
from	O
Notes	O
taken	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
with	O
genuine	O
Accounts	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
Confessions	O
,	O
and	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
eminent	O
Convicts	O
;	O
These	O
Trials	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Collection	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
Volumes	O
contain	O
the	O
Trials	O
of	O
Hawkins	O
and	O
Sympson	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
Robberies	O
;	O
of	O
Spiggot	O
the	O
famous	O
Highwayman	O
that	O
bore	O
350	O
lb	O
Weight	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
of	O
Butler	O
,	O
Barton	O
,	O
Fox	O
,	O
Hawes	O
,	O
Wright	O
,	O
Colthouse	O
,	O
Drury	O
,	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Yates	O
,	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
Beck	O
,	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
all	O
famous	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
and	O
Street	O
Robbers	O
;	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
the	O
famous	O
Footman	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Ravish	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
;	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Kraaft	O
,	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
Cooke	O
,	O
Ellis	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
for	O
Rapes	O
.	O
all	O
very	O
entertaining	O
;	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Stanley	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
his	O
Whore	O
;	O
of	O
Brinsdon	O
,	O
Crony	O
,	O
Nichol	O
.	O
Mac	O
Gennis	O
,	O
Lutterell	O
the	O
famous	O
Nanny	O
Butler	O
,	O
Vaughan	O
and	O
Cholmly	O
(	O
two	O
Constables	O
)	O
Foster	O
Snow	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
also	O
Major	O
Oneby	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gow	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
of	O
Vesey	O
and	O
Hallam	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
their	O
Wives	O
,	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jane	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
;	O
of	O
Sally	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
for	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
J	O
-	O
F	O
-	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Button	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
for	O
Felony	O
;	O
of	O
Duttus	O
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
others	O
for	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
shewing	O
all	O
the	O
Tricks	O
,	O
and	O
Methods	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
Mollies	O
;	O
of	O
Squire	O
Day	O
alias	O
Davenport	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
for	O
Pilking	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
of	O
two	O
German	O
Counts	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
;	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
for	O
several	O
Felonies	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
particulars	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
published	O
;	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Squire	O
