TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1737	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
M.DCC.XXXVII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Fossey	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
,	O
serv	O
'd	O
on	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fossey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	O
Arnold	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
Edwin	B-pers
Thornicroft	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Winsmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
>	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
sworn	O
on	O
Thursday	O
(	O
instead	O
of	O
Richard	O
Fletcher	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
continued	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
1.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gillam	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brocade	O
Silk	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Tabby	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
spotted	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
Point	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Mob	O
,	O
with	O
Brussel	O
's	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Mob	O
,	O
with	O
Mechlin	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Tucker	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
white	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Neck-Handkerchief	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Ruffle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stepple	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
.	O
About	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
August	O
5	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Stepple	O
's	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
East-Ham	O
Coach	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
Whitechapple	B-place
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Thames-street	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
enquired	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
East-Ham	O
Coach	O
with	O
my	O
Bundle	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
'll	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
is	O
just	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
snatched	O
the	O
Parcel	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
Gulston-street	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
several	O
People	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Gulston-Square	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
three	O
Minutes	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
?	O
Castle	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
excuse	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Bundle	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Castle	O
.	O
No	O
?	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
East-Ham	O
Coach	O
stand	O
?	O
Castle	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
and	O
Three	O
Tobacco	O
Pipes	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapple	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
run	O
towards	O
the	O
Inn	O
?	O
Castle	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
towards	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
from	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Gulston	O
street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
walked	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
pray	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
cry	O
out	O
-	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
?	O
Castle	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Gulston-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
Castle	O
)	O
cry	O
-	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
Elbow	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
-	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
run	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
People	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
flew	O
so	O
swiftly	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
take	O
any	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
you	O
Rascal	O
,	O
how	O
dar	O
'd	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
the	O
Lad	O
?	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
Answer	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Gulston-Square	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
runing	O
along	O
,	O
without	O
either	O
Hat	O
or	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
People	O
cry	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
'till	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Witness	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
(	O
it	O
seems	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Bundle	O
away	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Boy	O
very	O
hard	O
loaded	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
far	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Ham	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Bundle	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Bailiffs	O
following	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
considering	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
a	O
Man	O
5	O
l.	O
I	O
flung	O
down	O
the	O
Bundle	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
my	O
Heels	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
People	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Jones	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Butolph	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
August	O
26	O
John	B-pers
Weldon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Buildings	O
upon	O
ButolphWharf	B-place
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Story	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Sugar	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Apron	O
and	O
his	O
Right	O
Pocket	O
full	O
;	O
we	O
weighed	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
49	O
lb	O
.	O
wanting	O
;	O
sixteen	O
Pounds	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Sugar	O
in	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Capsel	O
Room	O
to	O
my	O
Partners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Sugar	O
belonged	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
fuddled	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
:	O
Weldon	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
most	O
of	O
us	O
thought	O
he	O
only	O
shamm	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Adkins	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sugar	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
Cooper	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Buildings	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
Hoopsticks	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
rapp	O
'd	O
out	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
Weldon	O
take	O
Care	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
shamm	O
'd	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
so	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
very	O
frequently	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Hat-several	O
Times	O
upon	O
the	O
Wharfs	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
several	O
Runs	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
never	O
take	O
him	O
'till	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Witnesses	O
are	O
all	O
dead	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
,	O
4.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Hacker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
Aug.	O
5	O
.	O
Chambers	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
Hacker	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Frances	B-pers
Marlborough	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
3	O
Messuages	O
belonging	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Gillings	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
Shadwell	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gillings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
these	O
Houses	O
are	O
empty	O
;	O
they	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Foxes	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
near	O
Pelican-stairs	B-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Lead	O
carried	O
about	O
16	O
Feet	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
fixed	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
down	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
that	O
Thieves	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Lead	O
ripp	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
the	O
Chimnies	O
.	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
dodg	O
'd	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
Chimnies	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
surrender	O
.	O
The	O
Lead	O
was	O
mov	O
'd	O
16	O
or	O
18	O
Feet	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
fix	O
'd	O
.	O
Another	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
the	O
People	O
say	O
,	O
a	O
Thief	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Chimnies	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
ashore	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
6	O
Feet	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ladder	O
being	O
raised	O
against	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
says	O
he	O
?	O
Come	O
along	O
say	O
's	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
just	O
ready	O
to	O
throw	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Lead	O
fix	O
'd	O
?	O
Gillings	O
.	O
We	O
see	O
it	O
almost	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Shadwell	O
Market	O
to	O
these	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Street	O
being	O
all	O
in	O
an	O
Uproar	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
The	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
somebody	O
was	O
stealing	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Tops	O
of	O
the	O
Houses	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
take	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
set	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Gillings	O
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
Ladder	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
of	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
5	O
Years	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
quiet	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
would	O
be	O
Drunk	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
never	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
This	O
very	O
Day	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
Rabbets	O
to	O
Poplar	O
;	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
One	O
before	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
Tyler	O
.	O
Why	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Brick-layer	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Masters	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
you	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Killet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
in	O
Ratcliffe-Highway	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
.	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Joshua	O
Howard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
3	O
Weeks	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
-	O
before	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
Her	O
going	O
away	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
broke	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
which	O
would	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
or	O
she	O
might	O
watch	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
and	O
take	O
our	O
Keys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
near	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
Holloway	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Shelf	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Justice	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
On-the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
sign	O
'd	O
her	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
one	O
Morning	O
when	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
out	O
every	O
Morning	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
;	O
she	O
goes	O
out	O
with	O
Fruit	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
Milk	O
.	O
Howard	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
having	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Maid	O
liv	O
'd	O
extravagantly	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
enquired	O
into	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Victor	O
,	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Victor	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
Shifts	O
and	O
Aprons	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
-	O
She	O
wished	O
sad	O
Wishes	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
Mistress	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
:	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
Night	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
enquire	O
farther	O
into	O
it	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
-	O
my	O
Maid	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Victor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
any	O
of	O
Howard	O
's	O
Money	O
:	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
true	O
-	O
indeed	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
did	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Linnen	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Fellow-Servant	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
having	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
that	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Linnen	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Victor	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
Howard	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
2	O
Guineas	O
more	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
)	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Howard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Horn	O
Cup	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
her	O
first	O
coming	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
Innocent	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
that	O
you	O
ran	O
from	O
your	O
Service	O
in	O
so	O
abrupt	O
a	O
Manner	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
never	O
threaten	O
'd	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
voluntarily	O
where	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Holborn	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
green	O
Silk	O
tabby	O
Gown	O
,	O
faced	O
with	O
red	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Knolton	I-pers
,	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
William	B-pers
Kitchinman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Printed	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
-	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Movillion	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
5	O
Pieces	O
out	O
of	O
12	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
bleaching	O
Grounds	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
Information	O
concerning	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
:	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gerrard	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Ring	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
Ring	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Vincent	O
over-hearing	O
this	O
Discourse	O
,	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
one	O
Grace	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
secreted	O
.	O
These	O
Pieces	O
now	O
produced	O
,	O
are	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Bleaching	O
Grounds	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
half	O
finished	O
,	O
or	O
whiten	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
are	O
half	O
the	O
Colours	O
in	O
them	O
which	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
lay	O
them	O
as	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Movillion	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
have	O
cut	O
of	O
the	O
Marks	O
at	O
the	O
Ends	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
we	O
know	O
every	O
Man	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Skreen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Ring	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
ask	O
after	O
my	O
Ring	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
7	O
Pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
to	O
dispose	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
one	O
Day	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
7	O
Pieces	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
7	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
it	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
4	O
Pieces	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
bring	O
you	O
them	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
raise	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
but	O
Grace	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
these	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
indeed	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Grace	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
lend	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
would	O
borrow	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
paid	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Grace	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
particular	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
Hold	O
,	O
-	O
by	O
Recollection	O
't	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
6	O
Pieces	O
then	O
pledged	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
(	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
)	O
lives	O
at	O
'Squire	O
Clark	O
's	O
at	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
what	O
's	O
become	O
of	O
this	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
?	O
Skreen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
the	O
very	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
out	O
and	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
saying	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
become	O
of	O
Grace	O
now	O
?	O
Skreen	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
indeed	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
borrow	O
'd	O
the	O
7	O
Guineas	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
upon	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
Grace	O
paid	O
him	O
this	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
Skreen	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
deliver	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Movillion	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Clement	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
's	O
Lodging	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Scotsman	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
traded	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Pieces	O
,	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
4	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
half	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Skreen	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
first	O
2	O
Pieces	O
-	O
then	O
four	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
redeem	O
'd	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
indulged	O
'till	O
to	O
Morrow	O
Morning	O
I	O
will	O
bring	O
my	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
's	O
this	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
she	O
's	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Skreen	O
Has	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
any	O
Endeavours	O
to	O
get	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
?	O
Skreen	O
.	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
4	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gate	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Ring	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
want	O
Money	O
or	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
Councel	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Agent	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
off	O
with	O
Ease	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
drawing	O
(	O
withdrawing	O
)	O
the	O
Cullisses	O
(	O
Recognizances	O
)	O
would	O
not	O
cost	O
above	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
s.	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
my	O
Mark	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Peices	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
came	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
Swear	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
C	O
To	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Your	O
Trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
because	O
your	O
Friends	O
were	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
Linnen	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
come	O
yet	O
.	O
C.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
an	O
Hour	O
allow	O
'd	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
allow	O
'd	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
to	O
produce	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
John	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
Trades	O
over	O
Sea	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
7	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Skreen	O
's	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
produced	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
Goods	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Movillion	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
another	O
Printer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
went	O
suddenly	O
from	O
their	O
Places	O
upon	O
such	O
another	O
Affair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
Body	O
here	O
from	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
say	O
this	O
Johnson	O
deliver	O
'd	O
you	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
not	O
finish	O
'd	O
.	O
Skreen	O
.	O
Adkins	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
2	O
Gowns	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bid	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
Grace	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
Question	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
?	O
Upon	O
my	O
Faith	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Merlin's-Cave	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tore	O
off	O
enough	O
Linnen	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
bind	O
the	O
Bargain	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
several	O
Gowns	O
upon	O
the	O
People	O
's	O
Backs	O
,	O
which	O
Grace	O
Adkins	O
had	O
sold	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
allow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
2	O
Hours	O
more	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lutwych	O
appeared	O
.	O
Lutwych	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
gave	O
me	O
Money	O
for	O
Councel	O
and	O
Subpoena	O
's	O
against	O
to	O
Morrow	O
.	O
Norton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
Agent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Need	O
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
commended	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
Whitster	O
's	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Lutwych	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Subpenae	O
's	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dottery	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
imagine	O
his	O
Trial	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
'till	O
to	O
Morrow	O
Mr.	O
Movillion	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dottery	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother-in-Law	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
a	O
Printer	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
till	O
latterly	O
:	O
't	O
is	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
since	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
first	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
complained	O
the	O
Grounds	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
bid	O
me	O
God	O
b	O
'	O
w	O
'	O
y	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
?	O
Jarvis	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
turn	O
away	O
2	O
Servants	O
for	O
being	O
Acquaintances	O
and	O
Accomplices	O
of	O
his	O
?	O
Jarvis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
any	O
Relation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Sister	O
.	O
He	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
and	O
here	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dottery	O
would	O
have	O
appeared	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dame	O
Mary	B-pers
Abdey	I-pers
,	O
Aug	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
11.	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter-Dish	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Bason	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
3	O
Copper	O
Sance-pans	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Copper	O
Stew-pans	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Jacob	O
Kendall	O
I	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Bason	O
and	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
moved	O
3	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
2	O
Stew-pans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
they	O
broke	O
was	O
adjacent	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
fast	O
.	O
The	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
and	O
Bason	O
they	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
a	O
good	O
Way	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Wash-house	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bundry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Labour	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Howard	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
back	O
and	O
pull	O
too	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
Then	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
pushed	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Stew-pans	O
and	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
all	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
Harrison	O
,	O
but	O
Howard	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
observ	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Face	O
were	O
crock	O
'd	O
and	O
black	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
exactly	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Kendalls	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
opening	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Harrison	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
Wall	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
making	O
water	O
too	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Work	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
Howard	O
;	O
and	O
Harrison	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
ago	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
full	O
of	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
detained	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
remov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
-	O
where	O
did	O
they	O
stand	O
over	O
Night	O
?	O
Kendall	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Wash-house	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
again	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
in	O
King	O
Harry	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Sanders	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Harrison	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
some	O
People	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
one	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
in	O
Maudlin	O
's	O
Rents	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Dust	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Goods	O
being	O
stolen	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
Door	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
rushed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Bundey	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
Howard	O
turn	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
at	O
all	O
passed	O
him	O
.	O
Howard	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
my	O
Hands	O
and	O
Face	O
being	O
crock	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
mending	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
a	O
Porridge-pot	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
C.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
notable	O
Evidence	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
happens	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
.	O
Howard	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
very	O
good	O
Hours	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
this	O
Thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
Watchman	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
)	O
went	O
-	O
past	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
?	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
'till	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
House	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
?	O
Cannon	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Howard	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
whose	O
Porrige-pot	O
I	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
crock	O
'd	O
my	O
Hands	O
and	O
Face	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Howard	O
since	O
Whitsuntide	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Howard	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mend	O
her	O
Porrige-pot	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
?	O
-	O
'T	O
was	O
an	O
Iron	O
Porrige-pot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
mending	O
it	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
-	O
upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Radwell	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Collier	I-pers
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
.	O
Howard	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
he	O
buys	O
and	O
sells	O
Pewter	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
has	O
dealt	O
in	O
Pewter	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
.	O
C.	O
That	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
:	O
'T	O
is	O
sworn	O
upon	O
him	O
here	O
:	O
Tho	B-pers
Colcott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
only	O
this	O
-	O
he	O
will	O
get	O
Drunk	O
and	O
bring	O
himself	O
into	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
not	O
he	O
deal	O
in	O
Pewter	O
?	O
Colcott	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
deals	O
in	O
,	O
-	O
not	O
I.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
enormous	O
Crime	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Seaman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Contrivance	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Franklin	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
this	O
Thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Newcastle	O
upon	O
Tine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Seamen	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Birth	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
past	O
Mr.	O
Kendall	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Hubbub	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
put	O
my	O
Head	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
seized	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Sanders	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
you	O
saw	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
?	O
Sanders	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Kendall	O
.	O
Harrison	O
says	O
now	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Sea-faring	O
Man	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
regular	O
bred	O
Parson	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
worn	O
Canonical	O
Robes	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
3	O
Months	O
.	O
Harrison	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
Time	O
indeed	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
and	O
educated	O
at	O
Eaton	O
College	O
.	O
Howard	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
Harrison	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Ann	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloth	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
a	O
Nutmeg	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weldon	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
though	O
several	O
Times	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Daffon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Daffon	I-pers
,	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
then	O
being	O
)	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Knife	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
held	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
above	O
the	O
Bone	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Hip	O
did	O
strike	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
Danes	O
,	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
languishly	O
lived	O
from	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
to	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Daffon	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Misfortune	O
happen	O
'd	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
Blood	O
Vessel	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Kidneys	O
being	O
cut	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
dressing	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
3	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
dressed	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
;	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
grew	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Place	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
Chiswick	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
too	O
soon	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
cautioned	O
him	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
live	O
regularly	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
any	O
Exercise	O
.	O
The	O
Week	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Way	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Dressings	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
well	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
with	O
some	O
Fidlers	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Flux	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
Danger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
any	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
lost	O
no	O
Blood	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
dressing	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Irregularity	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
the	O
Fever	O
have	O
occasioned	O
his	O
Death	O
without	O
this	O
Wound	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Wound	O
occasioned	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
his	O
Fever	O
was	O
very	O
violent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
.	O
A	O
Fisherman	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
City	O
Marshal	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
Net	O
away	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
beg	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hat	B-place
and	I-place
Feather	I-place
in	O
Milford-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Partner	O
,	O
-	O
come	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
dead-hearted	O
for	O
one	O
Net	O
,	O
-	O
let	O
's	O
have	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
dry	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
in	O
a	O
mouthing	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Way	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
-	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
drunk	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
-	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
People	O
to	O
bring	O
none	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
this	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
dash	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
slid	O
to	O
his	O
Son	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
dash	O
the	O
Knife	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
his	O
Son	O
?	O
Powel	O
.	O
He	O
dash	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Net	O
being	O
Seized	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Net	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
recover	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
returning	O
,	O
the	O
Father	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Come	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
-	O
Shall	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Aye	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Son	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
you	O
are	O
Drunk	O
enough	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
People	O
not	O
bring	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
dash	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
bounc	O
'd	O
against	O
his	O
Son	O
's	O
Side	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
Must	O
I	O
be	O
rul	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
!	O
-	O
Sanger	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
peaceable	O
,	O
quiet	O
Man	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Fault	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
being	O
rather	O
too	O
indulgent	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
Another	O
Witness	O
spake	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Son	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
.	O
14.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Macguire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
August	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Recognizances	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
August	O
29	O
.	O
Richard	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
,	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
'	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
his	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
some	O
body	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
:	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
towards	O
the	O
Necessary-House	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
then	O
button	O
'd	O
up	O
close	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
take	O
your	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
)	O
if	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
Coat	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
am	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
seeing	O
something	O
button	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
Six	O
Plates	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Necessity	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Plates	O
:	O
Says	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
Plates	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Bosom	O
.	O
-	O
Here	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Change	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shilling	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
now	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
Aye	O
,	O
-	O
Here	O
's	O
your	O
Change	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
leaving	O
the	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
behind	O
you	O
.	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
John	B-pers
Totterdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
Victualler	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
August	O
1st	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
of	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
so	O
lying	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
did	O
drag	O
and	O
pull	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Stairs	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
certain	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
drag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
so	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Sides	O
,	O
Belly	O
and	O
Thighs	O
did	O
strike	O
,	O
kick	O
and	O
stampt	O
upon	O
;	O
giving	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
by	O
throwing	O
and	O
dragging	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
said	O
Stairs	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
stricking	O
,	O
kicking	O
and	O
stamping	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
five	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
keeps	O
a	O
Victualing	O
House	O
in	O
Vine-Street	B-place
,	O
Westminister	B-place
,	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Two	B-place
Brewers	I-place
)	O
All	O
then	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
Mind	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
some	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
where	O
or	O
how	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
Mind	O
;	O
-	O
for	O
why	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
's	O
a	O
Witness	O
too	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
it	O
happened	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
indeed	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
Stairs	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Woman	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
Margaret	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
)	O
Lord	O
-	O
Brown	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
in	O
your	O
Room	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
,	O
fight	O
Dog	O
,	O
fight	O
Bear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Devil	O
part	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
parted	O
you	O
too	O
often	O
already	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Woman	O
told	O
me	O
Totterdale	O
was	O
beating	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
But	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
-	O
Murder	O
,	O
-	O
Murder	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
soft	O
,	O
faint	O
Tone	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stamping	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
kicking	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stamp	O
2	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Knife	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
some	O
little	O
Time	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
poor	O
Woman	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Chamber-door	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
my	O
Door	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
bid	O
me	O
ask	O
my	O
Wife	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
break	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
my	O
Bed	O
's	O
Feet	O
and	O
the	O
Curtains	O
were	O
drawn	O
over	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
wav	O
'd	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
to	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
able	O
to	O
stir	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
discovered	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
Cap	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
?	O
'T	O
is	O
below	O
Stairs	O
Johnney	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
You	O
lye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
-	O
indeed	O
Johnney	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
lye	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
of	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
flew	O
at	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
sprung	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Heels	O
,	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
drew	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
't	O
was	O
Head-foremost	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
fell	O
about	O
7	O
Stept	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
lay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
frighted	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
staid	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Minutes	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bolted	O
and	O
barr	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
this	O
Room	O
cry	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
Johnney	O
!	O
Johnney	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
kill	O
me	O
!	O
'T	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
this	O
Room	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
Slight	O
Door	O
,	O
-	O
only	O
Slit-deal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
she	O
was	O
Dead	O
.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
beating	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
Molly	O
,	O
Molly	O
,	O
come	O
hither	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
'd	O
the	O
Curtains	O
over	O
her	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
pull	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Bed-Curtains	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
two	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
haul	O
'd	O
her	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
he	O
stamped	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
stamped	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
their	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
himself	O
and	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Sleep	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
Dead	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
external	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Corps	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
so	O
many	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
,	O
that	O
put	O
me	O
upon	O
being	O
careful	O
and	O
inquisitive	O
in	O
my	O
Search	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Ribs	O
fractured	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Stab	O
in	O
her	O
Right	O
Arm	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Joint	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
The	O
Instrument	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
Nerves	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
cut	O
no	O
Blood	O
Vessel	O
.	O
Upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
nine	O
Ribs	O
fractured	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
broken	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Places	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
two	O
Places	O
,	O
another	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
,	O
another	O
was	O
mash	O
'd	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
;	O
two	O
whereof	O
were	O
beat	O
in	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Kidney	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
something	O
farther	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Rib	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
broken	O
ones	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
fractured	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
which	O
convinced	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
broke	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
imagine	O
with	O
the	O
Heel	O
of	O
his	O
Shoe	O
:	O
for	O
if	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
fractur	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
Instrument	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
broke	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
impossible	O
that	O
this	O
single	O
Rib	O
should	O
have	O
remained	O
unhurt	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
fractur	O
'd	O
ones	O
.	O
This	O
Treatment	O
occasion	O
'd	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Ribs	O
had	O
been	O
fractur	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
that	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
impossible	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Margaret	O
Phillips	O
(	O
my	O
Cousin	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
lies	O
o'Nights	O
.	O
We	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Hurry	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
backward	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
where	O
he	O
keeps	O
Hogs	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
-	O
you	O
Phillips	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
where	O
's	O
my	O
Bitch	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
unless	O
she	O
is	O
among	O
the	O
Hogs	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
hid	O
her	O
in	O
your	O
Room	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
jumbling	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Phillips	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
sit	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
?	O
If	O
I	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
run	O
the	O
Knife	O
into	O
my	O
Guts	O
.	O
The	O
jumbling	O
continued	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
poor	O
Creature	O
come	O
tumbling	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
poor	O
Head	O
came	O
knock	O
,	O
knock	O
,	O
knock	O
,	O
upon	O
every	O
Stair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
(	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
down	O
)	O
upon	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
he	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
dead	O
then	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
faintly	O
,	O
-	O
Oh	O
!	O
-	O
Oh	O
!	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
beat	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
!	O
Oh	O
!	O
-	O
Oh	O
!	O
-	O
dear	O
Johnney	O
,	O
Johnney	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
!	O
do	O
n't	O
!	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
him	O
very	O
plainly	O
,	O
-	O
thump	O
,	O
thump	O
,	O
thump	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Poor	O
old	O
Mother	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
Johnney	O
,	O
Johnney	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Johnney	O
would	O
speak	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
another	O
Door	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
immediately	O
came	O
out	O
crying	O
I	O
'm	O
undone	O
!	O
undone	O
!	O
undone	O
!	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
peep	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
-	O
dead	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
her	O
Jaws	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
Cap	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Phillips	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
speak	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
an	O
honest	O
Cause	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
)	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
never	O
expected	O
to	O
receive	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
(	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
)	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
returning	O
with	O
the	O
Crown	O
:	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Johnney	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Judas	O
's	O
Kiss	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kiss	O
'd	O
and	O
embrac	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
they	O
were	O
Marry	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Cousin	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Bitch	O
was	O
,	O
-	O
There	O
he	O
stands	O
,	O
he	O
ca	O
n't	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
Your	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
your	O
Bitch	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
among	O
the	O
Hogs	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
meant	O
a	O
Bitch	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
Puppies	O
by	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
your	O
Bitch	O
?	O
-	O
God	O
mend	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
just	O
now	O
Kissing	O
her	O
.	O
Aye	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
stamp	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
peep	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
stamping	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
stamp	O
her	O
Guts	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
from	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
your	O
Sister	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
the	O
Devil	O
drove	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
God	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
Power	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Soldier	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Races	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
of	O
August	O
and	O
met	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Totterdale	O
had	O
Murder	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
only	O
half	O
Murder	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
frequentsly	O
did	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Miss	O
he	O
kept	O
forced	O
against	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
hinder	O
me	O
from	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
Murder	O
has	O
been	O
committed	O
?	O
So	O
I	O
threw	O
her	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Back-Room	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Casement	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Murder	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
come	O
yet	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
an	O
own	O
Brother	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
but	O
neither	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
nor	O
Brother	O
will	O
appear	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Helins	O
,	O
Married	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
feloniously	O
Married	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
being	O
in	O
full	O
Life	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Calloway	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wedding	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
William	O
Woodward	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
about	O
7	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Married	O
at	O
Great	O
St.	O
Helens	O
Church	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
and	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
Married	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	B-place
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
;	O
't	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	B-place
and	I-place
Pen	I-place
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
And	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
Wedding	O
Shop	O
too	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Parson	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Person	O
's	O
Name	O
;	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
once	O
belonged	O
to	O
Creed-Church	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
Drink	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
Holmes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Ruth	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
many	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
the	O
Parson	O
's	O
Assistant	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
stand	O
for	O
Clark	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Parson	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
dost	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Parson	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
Gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
Preach	O
at	O
Creed-Church	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
parson	O
himself	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
belonged	O
to	O
that	O
Church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
was	O
performing	O
Hall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
C.	O
What	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
Father	O
I	O
suppose	O
Hall	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
And	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
since	O
this	O
Honour	O
was	O
conferr	O
'd	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
.	O
Coune	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
the	O
Parson	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
lusty	O
jolly	O
Man	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Complaint	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
Court	O
,	O
against	O
a	O
Fleet	O
Parson	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Hell	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
Gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
not	O
incumbent	O
on	O
us	O
to	O
shew	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Orders	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
'	O
Woodward	O
.	O
C.	O
But	O
here	O
's	O
Hall	O
that	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
Father	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
Married	O
at	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
remember	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Pen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
Drunk	O
.	O
C.	O
Drunkenness	O
is	O
no	O
Excuse	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
Crime	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
18	O
,	O
19.	O
Richard	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorrel	B-pers
Smalt	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
Cock	O
fixed	O
thereto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
June	O
4	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Man	O
(	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
came	O
and	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
Several	O
Thefts	O
and	O
Street-Robberies	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
Franklin	O
and	O
Smalt	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
Tom	O
Gale	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
in	O
Black	O
and	O
White-Court	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
entertainment	O
of	O
lewd	O
Women	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
thither	O
from	O
Smalt	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
staid	O
at	O
Gale	O
's	O
'till	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Smalt	O
keeps	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
harbouring	O
of	O
such	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Franklin	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
sat	O
Drinking	O
at	O
Gale	O
's	O
,	O
Smalt	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Tom	O
Gale	O
told	O
Dorrel	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Dorrel	O
)	O
had	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Lead-Lay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
understood	O
that	O
Lay	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Says	O
Dorrel	O
Smalt	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
formerly	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
that	O
Lay	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Custom	O
was	O
to	O
walk	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
observe	O
where	O
Cocks	O
and	O
Pipes	O
were	O
fixed	O
;	O
the	O
Places	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
Smalt	O
)	O
asked	O
me	O
and	O
Franklin	O
,	O
whether	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
rob	O
an	O
adjacent	O
House	O
of	O
a	O
Pipe	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
House	O
inhabited	O
by	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Printer	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Tom	O
Gales	O
House	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
broke	O
down	O
a	O
Partition	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Means	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
this	O
Partition	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
a	O
boarded	O
Partition	O
,	O
and	O
join	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
Partition	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
parted	O
the	O
House	O
from	O
the	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Fence	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
it	O
self	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
By	O
breaking	O
down	O
the	O
boarded	O
Partition	O
:	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Pipe	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
boarded	O
Partition	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Case	O
off	O
the	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
away	O
about	O
2	O
Yards	O
,	O
or	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Tom	O
Gales	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Way	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Pipe	O
in	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
.	O
Smalt	O
and	O
Franklin	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Lead	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
We	O
broke	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
at	O
Tom	O
Gale	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Smalt	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
Black-Boy	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
Gale	O
's	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
Bars	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
in	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Pipe	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
Smalt	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
after	O
this	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
sold	O
for	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Smalt	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
4	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
among	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
self	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
Directions	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
to	O
Smalt	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Pistols	O
loaded	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
Joe	O
Emmerson	O
's	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
given	O
Smalt	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mac	O
Cray	O
's	O
Gang	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Black	B-place
and	I-place
White	I-place
Court	I-place
.	O
The	O
Cock	O
and	O
Pipe	O
which	O
they	O
stole	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
lost	O
as	O
is	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
particular	O
Times	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
that	O
Franklin	O
the	O
Sailor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Board	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
the	O
Cock	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Night	O
that	O
Board	O
was	O
broke	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cock	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Board	O
was	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Inches	O
wide	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Foot	O
,	O
or	O
2	O
Foot	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
high	O
;	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
removed	O
,	O
any	O
Person	O
may	O
enter	O
side-ways	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Bars	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
Pipe	O
as	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
12	O
Yards	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
in	O
Turn-again	O
Lane	O
was	O
the	O
Plumber	O
that	O
put	O
the	O
Pipe	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charges	O
38	O
s.	O
for	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Pipe	O
and	O
a	O
Cock	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
frequently	O
at	O
this	O
Gale	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
there	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
when	O
the	O
2	O
Pistols	O
loaded	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Smalt	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Directions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
comes	O
it	O
that	O
Richard	O
Walker	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Walker	O
only	O
rents	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
publish	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
belongs	O
to	O
Messieurs	O
Hoar	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
as	O
Assignees	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darlow	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
Franklin	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Time	O
they	O
swear	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
confined	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
then	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Prison	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
my	O
Committment	O
,	O
dated	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
June	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
robb	O
'd	O
this	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
you	O
was	O
precise	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
your	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Information	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
Instructions	O
for	O
drawing	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
must	O
fix	O
upon	O
a	O
particular	O
Day	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Turn-key	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
Franklin	O
's	O
Commitment	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Gavannah	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Keeper	O
's	O
)	O
own	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Belt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
mov	O
'd	O
Franklin	O
from	O
New-Prison	O
to	O
Newgate	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Tho.Smith	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
every	O
Thing	O
into	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
prepar	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
exact	O
and	O
particular	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
Commitment	O
;	O
the	O
Book	O
and	O
the	O
Original	O
Commitments	O
are	O
at	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
him	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Custody	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
considerable	O
Time	O
.	O
Mr	O
,	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
His	O
Commitment	O
is	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
our	O
Calender	O
of	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
When	O
they	O
are	O
brought	O
from	O
other	O
Prisons	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
bring	O
Copies	O
of	O
their	O
Commitments	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
enter	O
them	O
in	O
our	O
Calendar	O
.	O
C.	O
To	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Produce	O
the	O
Plumber	O
's	O
Bill	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
almost	O
worn	O
to	O
Pieces	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
no	O
Date	O
-	O
only	O
-	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
new	O
Pipe	O
,	O
I	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
4	O
(	O
something	O
)	O
of	O
Soder	O
,	O
8	O
s.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Time	O
they	O
say	O
Franklin	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
for	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
broke	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
5th	O
or	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
Pipe	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
the	O
Water	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Spiggot	O
and	O
Fosset	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
before	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Franklin	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Windsor	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
paid	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
of	O
stealing	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
.	O
Smalt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
likely	O
I	O
should	O
steal	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Pipe	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Master	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
Every	O
Morning	O
I	O
rose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
Times	O
;	O
was	O
your	O
Shoulder	O
broke	O
after	O
the	O
last	O
Robbery	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
first	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
last	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trow	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Donolly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
checqu	O
'd	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Waistcoat	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d	O
and	O
two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
certain	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pinada	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Shirt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
calling	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
it	O
seems	O
)	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
these	O
Things	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
bellowing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
that	O
Lady	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Girl	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Eyes	O
take	O
the	O
Bundle	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
one	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Parcel	O
in	O
the	O
checqu	O
'd	O
Apron	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
Sick	O
with	O
Drinking	O
some	O
out-of-the-way	O
nasty	O
Stuff	O
.	O
O	O
Pray	O
burn	O
me	O
,	O
burn	O
my	O
Hand	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
send	O
me	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Ginshop	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
wont	O
send	O
me	O
over	O
Sea	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Cotton	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Dobbings	I-pers
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
Transports	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knelham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Launders	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Laundrass	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
August	O
2d	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Potlid	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
Box-iron	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
a	O
Pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kinlinside	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
India	O
work	O
'd	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
August	O
20	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Vintry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rimus	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
John	B-pers
Strut	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
thePerson	O
of	O
Adolphus	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Peter	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wood	O
n	O
Pail	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
August	O
9	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Hattan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
Ton	O
Weight	O
of	O
Pebble-stones	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Mist	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
July	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
John	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Whitechaple	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Steel	O
Tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
my	O
Time	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sculter	O
,	O
a	O
Bookbinder	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Sun-Tavern-Fields	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
some	O
Company	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
'till	O
Night	O
:	O
About	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Home	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
after	O
Ten	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Church-Lane	B-place
,	O
(	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
Home	O
)	O
by	O
Whitechapel	O
Church	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Gardens	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Collar	O
:	O
Damn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
Stand	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laugh	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
-	O
you	O
Monkey	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
stand	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Yes	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
damn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
stand	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
let	O
's	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
your	O
Contentions	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
foolish	O
Traveller	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
carry	O
'd	O
Money	O
about	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
o'Night	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
damn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Money	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
he	O
shook	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Heel	O
slipping	O
on	O
the	O
little	O
low	O
Bank	O
that	O
runs	O
along	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
recover	O
'd	O
myself	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Bank	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Bank	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
there	O
came	O
one	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
my	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
of	O
my	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
-	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
you	O
struck	O
me	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
you	O
Home	O
as	O
bare	O
as	O
Adam	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
sat	O
upon	O
my	O
Belly	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
Farthings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
half	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
Pocket	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
.	O
)	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
sat	O
upon	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoes	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
-	O
Damn	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
rare	O
pair	O
of	O
Wedgers	O
,	O
-	O
Let	O
's	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
good	O
Booty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
?	O
Gale	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
Swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
first	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
upon	O
my	O
Breast	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
Home	O
as	O
bare	O
as	O
Adam	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
strip	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
tore	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Buttons	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
off	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
in	O
stripping	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Company	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
off	O
my	O
Breast	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
you	O
Dogs	O
,	O
push	O
away	O
or	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
nail	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Cloaths	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Gale	O
.	O
A	O
green	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
Wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
the	O
Colour	O
(	O
Green	O
)	O
?	O
Gale	O
.	O
The	O
Moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
.	O
C.	O
'T	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
distinguish	O
Green	O
from	O
Blue	O
,	O
by	O
Night	O
.	O
Gale	O
.	O
The	O
Moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
as	O
bright	O
as	O
Day	O
it	O
self	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
in	O
Church	O
lane	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
described	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
?	O
Gale	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
(	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
just	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
among	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
People	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Billinger	I-pers
.	O
All	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
this	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Golden-Lyon	O
in	O
Goodman's-Yard	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
20	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
dress	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
Wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Billinger	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
running	O
after	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
took	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
got	O
Intelligence	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
Persons	O
were	O
making	O
Sale	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
surly	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
informed	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
to	O
exchange	O
the	O
Buckles	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
among	O
20	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
first	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Swear	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
August	O
1st	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Business	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
4	O
Persons	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
then	O
on	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Wig	O
:	O
Harris	O
had	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
imagined	O
he	O
answered	O
the	O
Description	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Harris	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Harris	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
,	O
(	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
after	O
him	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Chick-Lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Golden-Lyon	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
?	O
Gale	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
'till	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
Gale	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Church	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
Minutes	O
after	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
:	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
all	O
daub	O
'd	O
with	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Nose	O
and	O
Mouth	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Fellow	O
that	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Scar	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
her	O
Forehead	O
)	O
that	O
his	O
Nose	O
turned	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
green	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
natural	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
Wig	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
Colour	O
of	O
the	O
Wig	O
?	O
Kelly	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Wig	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
green	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Gale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hat	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
red	O
Mark	O
,	O
very	O
red	O
upon	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Scar	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bareback	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Blood	O
run	O
down	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
daub	O
'd	O
behind	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
had	O
a	O
Mark	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Nose	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
that	O
some	O
Buttons	O
upon	O
the	O
