TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	O
Barnard	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1737	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Three-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
BARNARD	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Three-Pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
shall	O
contain	O
the	O
usual	O
Quantity	O
sold	O
for	O
Six-Pence	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
past	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
Due	O
such	O
Three-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
further	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNARD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
PAGE	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
,	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminar	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hookman	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carbonel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crouder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Battin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompsons	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ratcliffe	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tuffnel	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Eason	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spices	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Punchin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Watch	O
Cases	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-box	O
with	O
silver	O
Rims	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
's	O
Drawers	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
laid	O
,	O
-	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Watch-cases	O
,	O
a	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-box	O
with	O
silver	O
rims	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch-case	O
was	O
gone	O
likewise	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
this	O
be	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
!	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
your	O
Servant	O
that	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
too	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
't	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
Weather	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
impossible	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
without	O
dirting	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
probably	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
's	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
upon	O
Puddle-Hill	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Watch-cases	O
and	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
apprehend	O
these	O
silver	O
Cases	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Cases	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
this	O
Snuff-box	O
is	O
mine	O
like	O
wise	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Feb.	O
10	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch-case	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
This	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
Case	O
I	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
leather	O
Glove	O
in	O
my	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Kingston	O
,	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
chang	O
'd	O
my	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
behind	O
me	O
backed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
my	O
Closet	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
my	O
Watch	O
to	O
wear	O
at	O
a	O
Ball	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Chest	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Chest	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gitson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Sister	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
's	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
silver	O
Cases	O
,	O
this	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gold	O
Case	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
is	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
no	O
Questions	O
about	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Jane	B-pers
Gitson	I-pers
brought	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
pawn	O
these	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Cases	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
Sister	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
my	O
Mother	O
are	O
no	O
ways	O
confederate	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
which	O
my	O
Master	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
The	O
Gold	O
Case	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
my	O
Family	O
Justice	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Mother	O
has	O
given	O
my	O
Master	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
2.	O
George	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
hundred	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	O
Hind	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
Socks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Cushions	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Mattress	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
2	O
Feather	O
beds	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
when	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Goods	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
one	O
Night	O
took	O
a	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
of	O
Lead	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
we	O
took	O
5	O
Hundred	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Time	O
about	O
6	O
Hundred	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
Mutton-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
equally	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
(	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Malt	O
Loft	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
an	O
inner	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
Parlour	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
some	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Velvet	O
Cushions	O
;	O
some	O
Stocking	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Fringe	O
Then	O
we	O
broke	O
a	O
fine	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
what	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
we	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Mattress	O
and	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hop-lost	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
thus	O
bundled	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
Parlour	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Compting-house	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Truth	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
dying	O
this	O
Moment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
Sister	O
;	O
she	O
died	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Undertaken	O
for	O
the	O
Funeral	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Riggs	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
which	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
burying	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Hands	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
.	O
Berry	O
.	O
Some	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
Wife	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
.	O
This	O
red	O
Silk	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
dy	O
'd	O
a	O
Massareen	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
The	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Mattress	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
or	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
5	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
this	O
Berry	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
Riggs	O
.	O
Riggs	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
Berry	O
,	O
ran	O
from	O
his	O
Work	O
to	O
Berry	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
his	O
Wife	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Riggs	O
,	O
(	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
and	O
Berry	O
.	O
By	O
their	O
Means	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Mattress	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Sheet	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
3.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gittings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hanquets	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hanquets	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
House	I-place
to	O
see	O
his	O
Majesty	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
Parliament	O
House	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
narrow	O
Passage	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
surrounded	O
with	O
a	O
Croud	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
Pickpockets	O
,	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Breeches	O
where	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
Presently	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
stirring	O
under	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
Instant	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
slip	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
And	O
some	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
near	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
fled	O
into	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Entry	O
,	O
where	O
these	O
two	O
Men	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Watch	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Watch	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
draw	O
it	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
Cloth	O
and	O
the	O
Lining	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Skirts	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Hanquets	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Capps	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
a	O
Croud	O
,	O
and	O
observ	O
'd	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
scuffling	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
Way	O
through	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Priory	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Watch	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
Side	O
next	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
Person	O
gathered	O
up	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Skirts	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
Lining	O
and	O
the	O
Outside	O
.	O
The	O
Pocket	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
slipp	O
'd	O
down	O
between	O
the	O
Cloth	O
and	O
the	O
Lining	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hanquets	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
immediately	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wallington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
my	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Court	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
before	O
me	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dirty	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wallington	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
(	O
Jones	O
)	O
told	O
me	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
Dirt	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Capps	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Friends	O
were	O
all	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
treating	O
with	O
the	O
Soldier	O
about	O
a	O
favourable	O
Evidence	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
promis	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
rewarded	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
promise	O
to	O
reward	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
in	O
my	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Capps	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Entry	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
4.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Millegan	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Sword	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
steal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Millegan	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Thigh	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
9	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
6th	O
to	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
for	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Millegan	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
1734	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
's	O
a	O
Distiller	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
go	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
down	O
Windmill-Street	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
stabb	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
-	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Hilliard	O
,	O
has	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Langford	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
wear	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
hid	O
one	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
Popes	O
Eye	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
given	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
about	O
II	O
o'Clock	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
Money	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
Bailiffs	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
bewitch	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
out	O
without	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
aid	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Bit	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Officer	O
attempted	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
go	O
through	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Millegan	O
)	O
brought	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
arrested	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Wratyh	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Sword	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Writ	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
He	O
declar	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
friendly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
safe	O
within	O
the	O
Verge	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Officer	O
attempted	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Prisoner	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
deliver	O
him	O
safe	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
Danger	O
.	O
Upon	O
these	O
Declarations	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
done	O
some	O
other	O
Business	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
arrest	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
getting	O
some	O
Hurt	O
?	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
venture	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
arrest	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
so	O
away	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
.	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Hilliard	O
had	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
the	O
Deceased	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
really	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
expose	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
charge	O
him	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
Things	O
easy	O
.	O
Langford	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
both	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
May	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
1734	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Downing-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
his	O
Buroe	O
.	O
The	O
Messenger	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bent	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Bit	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
together	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
Business	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
Shore	O
ditch	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
damn	O
it	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
arrest	O
Hilliard	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
my	O
Brother-in-Law	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1734	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
wounded	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
He	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
Fellow	O
your	O
Sister	O
saw	O
in	O
Langford	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
,	O
Nat	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
has	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lately	O
a	O
Corporal	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Foot-Guards	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
drumm	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Regiment	O
with	O
a	O
Halter	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
for	O
enlisting	O
Soldiers	O
for	O
the	O
Pretender	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Deceased	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Horseshoe	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
and	O
there	O
his	O
Follower	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Writ	O
;	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
tapp	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
his	O
own	O
Legs	O
he	O
thrust	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
what	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
languished	O
from	O
Monday	O
to	O
Thursday	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Totterdell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
May	O
8th	O
,	O
1734	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
leap	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
jobb	O
'd	O
the	O
Sword	O
into	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Thigh	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Thing	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Writ	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
executing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Itorno	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	B-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Legs	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
:	O
The	O
Sword	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
bent	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
Bone	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
apprehended	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
long	O
to	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Stab	O
?	O
I	O
know	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
when	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
Hilliard	O
had	O
jobb	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
thro	O
'	O
his	O
Thigh	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Hand	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
.	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Orifice	O
was	O
Length-ways	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
upwards	O
a	O
Way	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Sword	O
pass	O
'd	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
downwards	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
great	O
Observation	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
an	O
approaching	O
Mortification	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
downward	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Writ	O
,	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Writ	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
Langford	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
his	O
Follower	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
swears	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
arrest	O
me	O
.	O
Langford	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Writ	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Windmill-Street	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
arrest	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
unwise	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
certainly	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
fear	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Widow	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Writ	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
sworn	O
an	O
Officer	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1733	O
,	O
and	O
continu	O
'd	O
an	O
Officer	O
to	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
1734	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Langford	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
perswade	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Note	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
discharging	O
one	O
Newman	O
whom	O
Langford	O
had	O
arrested	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
in	O
the	O
Marshall	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
afraid	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
owe	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
expos	O
'd	O
.	O
Millegan	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Writ	O
out	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Officer	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
not	O
exposing	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Officer	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Officer	O
was	O
gone	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
return	O
in	O
four	O
Hours	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
conduct	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Verge	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
kindly	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
Punch	O
and	O
Ratafie	O
,	O
promising	O
to	O
be	O
grateful	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Langford	O
's	O
Daughter	O
bid	O
Millegan	O
not	O
trust	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Fellow	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Millegan	O
,	O
-	O
perhaps	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Writ	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
expose	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
civil	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
do	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
God	O
strike	O
me	O
dead	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
past	O
the	O
Opera-house	O
,	O
2	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
asking	O
him	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
left	O
Thumb	O
almost	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
his	O
Followers	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Such	O
Treachery	O
and	O
Barbarity	O
no	O
Man	O
was	O
ever	O
used	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Writ	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
produced	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
3d	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Exercise	O
when	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
knock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
with	O
what	O
Instrument	O
.	O
His	O
Follower	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
md	O
him	O
make	O
sure	O
Work	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
stagger	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thrust	O
among	O
the	O
Poles	O
of	O
the	O
Chairs	O
which	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Opera	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
receive	O
any	O
Wound	O
,	O
or	O
tap	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
underneath	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Arrest	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
any	O
Wound	O
given	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Public	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
following	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
against	O
the	O
Horshoe	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
flung	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Chair	O
Poles	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Hurt	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Villain	O
has	O
murd'red	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Sword	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Wound	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Head	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
used	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
Blow	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complain	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
sent	O
Home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ormerod	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Wound	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
given	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Fall	O
.	O
Baxter	B-pers
Polding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
down	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
on	O
the	O
Shafts	O
of	O
my	O
Dray	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Head	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Arrest	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
the	O
tapping	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
The	O
Widow	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
had	O
no	O
walking	O
Stick	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Tiptaff	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
(	O
the	O
former	O
Witness	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Sword	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
drawn	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
any	O
Wound	O
given	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Joel	B-pers
Fremoult	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
punctur	O
'd	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
under	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
Inches	O
in	O
Depth	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
2	O
Wounds	O
likewise	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
Thumb	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Contusions	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Langford	O
.	O
The	O
Truth	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
bit	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
if	O
any	O
Bailift	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
it	O
should	O
go	O
through	O
him	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
Seth	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gaudy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
as	O
a	O
civil	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
Silvester	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
now	O
without	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Warrington	O
perswade	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Warrington	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Hilliard	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
she	O
might	O
come	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
swear	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
deserves	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
would	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
any	O
Power	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
!	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Officer	O
had	O
Power	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
6.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
Taylor	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
committing	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
horrid	O
and	O
detestable	O
Crime	O
of	O
Buggery	O
.	O
And	O
Berry	O
for	O
wickedly	O
consenting	O
with	O
Taylor	O
the	O
said	O
unnatural	O
Crime	O
to	O
commit	O
and	O
do	O
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Windham	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
live	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Round-Court	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
necessary	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
have	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
,	O
yet	O
is	O
often	O
left	O
unlock	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
my	O
Servant	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
2	O
Fellows	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
Thieves	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Servant	O
following	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
bolted	O
(	O
went	O
hastily	O
)	O
into	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Taylor	O
sitting	O
,	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
open	O
Seat	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
close	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Berry	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
;	O
both	O
their	O
Breeches	O
being	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Mob	O
rose	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
knock	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
seiz	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Shame	O
such	O
Rascals	O
should	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
's	O
)	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Berry	O
made	O
his	O
Confession	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Taylor	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
too	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hilder	O
prov	O
'd	O
Berry	O
's	O
Confession	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
and	O
Confession	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Olave's-street	O
,	O
Southwark.	O
``	O
Who	O
faith	O
,	O
that	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
asked	O
him	O
if	O
``	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
this	O
``	O
Informant	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
``	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Joy	O
Bridge	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Light	O
coming	O
,	O
``	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
a	O
necessary	O
House	O
in	O
``	O
Round-Court	O
,	O
where	O
Taylor	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
``	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
pulled	O
down	O
``	O
their	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
Taylor	O
committed	O
the	O
Act	O
``	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Windham	O
``	O
the	O
2d	O
Time	O
caught	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Windham	O
.	O
Taylor	O
confessed	O
it	O
full	O
as	O
plain	O
,	O
or	O
plainer	O
than	O
Berry	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
(	O
several	O
Times	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Crime	O
with	O
Berry	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
Berry	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
After	O
Berry	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
Taylor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
acted	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Their	O
Breeches	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
up	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Fridenburgh	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
very	O
exactly	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
carrying	O
to	O
Goal	O
,	O
Berry	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
from	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
convenient	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
thought	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
from	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
7	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Catherine	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Pincushion	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Feb	O
18	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Peterson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
7	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
I	O
met	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
working	O
People	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
this	O
Knife	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Oaths	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Pistol	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
defend	O
my	O
self	O
against	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
till	O
some	O
body	O
should	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Pocket	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
kill	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
dar	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
he	O
threw	O
my	O
Hoop	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
Knife	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Guts	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
Book	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Knife	O
run	O
against	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
scream	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Help	O
!	O
help	O
!	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
help	O
!	O
but	O
he	O
lugg	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
Pocket	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
;	O
I	O
continu	O
'd	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Voices	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
stop	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Men	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
'frighted	O
Madam	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
perfect	O
Idea	O
of	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Spot	O
of	O
Ground	O
where	O
he	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
my	O
Pincushion	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Knife	O
that	O
he	O
threat'ned	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
both	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
perhaps	O
meet	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
in	O
any	O
Particular	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
laid	O
Hands	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
Peterson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
calls	O
laying	O
Hands	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ditch	O
and	O
tore	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
defended	O
my	O
self	O
against	O
his	O
Knife	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hearing	O
when	O
these	O
Men	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
as	O
plain	O
when	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
him	O
particularly	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
;	O
or	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Black-Lyon	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Field	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
,	O
-	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
me	O
!	O
-	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
me	O
!	O
We	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Help	O
at	O
Hand	O
,	O
-	O
Help	O
at	O
Hand	O
;	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
full	O
Speed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
trembled	O
and	O
quak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
between	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
'frighted	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
clear	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
enough	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
Men	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
,	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
,	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
her	O
Pocket	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
torn	O
down	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
two	O
Friends	O
had	O
been	O
walking	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
We	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Holloway	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
Lyon	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
Part	O
of	O
five	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
Eight	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
have	O
Mercy	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Help	O
at	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
ran	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Witness	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
some	O
People	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
logg	O
'd	O
him	O
along	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
Penknife	O
to	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
that	O
Moment	O
.	O
We	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
torn	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
the	O
Knife	O
.	O
-	O
Harvey	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
solemnly	O
declare	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
;	O
they	O
swear	O
in	O
spight	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
Lodge	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
debt	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
an	O
Execution	O
out	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
confin	O
'd	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
Goal	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
Watkins	O
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
about	O
3	O
three	O
Years	O
)	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
8.	O
William	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
two	O
Quart	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Micheal	B-pers
Martindale	I-pers
,	O
January	O
10	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
dead	O
Fowls	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
,	O
February	O
2	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
Drab	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pycroft	I-pers
,	O
January	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bygrave	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bottomley	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
James	B-pers
Coulthorp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
wooden	O
Plows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
Steel	O
Saws	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
Mortois	O
Chissels	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
paring	O
Chissel	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
:	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
3	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
cloth	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
15.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather-Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Mark	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hempen	O
Sack	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Walcott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Barley	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
,	O
February	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Stables	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sweeting	I-pers
.	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Peel	I-pers
January	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
about	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
one	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cocoa	O
cup	O
tipp	O
'd	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elliot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chalk	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
5	O
.	O
Dor	O
.	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
out	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
Church	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
People	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
street	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Chamber	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Lock	O
upon	O
a	O
Box	O
where	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
little	O
Substance	O
,	O
quite	O
broke	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Cocoa	O
shell-Cup	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Ring	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Box	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Cup	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
1	O
Guinea	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
five	O
Guineas	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
6	O
Guineas	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Elliot	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
mine	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chalk	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tankard	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
my	O
Sister	O
Elliot	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dobey	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Phillips	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Partners	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Gold	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Feb.	O
5th	O
in	O
the	O
Fore-noon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Dame	O
Elliot	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
toward	O
her	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
dirty	O
Canvas	O
er	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Brother	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
at	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
my	O
Sister	O
who	O
was	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
making	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
somebody	O
was	O
in	O
Dame	O
Elliot	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
make	O
hast	O
and	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
making	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
in	O
Dame	O
Elliot	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
was	O
stuff	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
he	O
ran	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
base	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
up	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Iron	O
Nails	O
;	O
she	O
deals	O
in	O
Iron	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
Leave	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Mob	O
rose	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Mary	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
,	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Yard	O
,	O
to	O
wash	O
some	O
Leeks	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Dame	O
Elliot	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
What	O
at	O
Noon	O
Day	O
says	O
I	O
!	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
rob	O
Neighbour	O
Ellot	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Door	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Nails	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
buy	O
Iron	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
-	O
so	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Drummer	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
Cock	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Tenement	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
22.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wicker	O
Basket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
Quartern	O
,	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
Quartern	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Julian	I-pers
,	O
February	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Hainsworth	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrel	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty-four	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
February	O
5	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
26.	O
,	O
Millicent	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Oakley	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
Feb.	O
1st	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Hollford's-Alley	B-place
,	O
which	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
Great	O
Wild	O
Street	O
,	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
Hoskins	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
Oakley	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Something	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
in	O
Pawn	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
half	O
Guinea	O
chang	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
redeem	O
my	O
Buttons	O
,	O
they	O
demanded	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
the	O
Dram	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
swearing	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Rather	O
than	O
loose	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Back-door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
escape	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
through	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Minutes	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
longer	O
than	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
the	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Civility	O
at	O
all	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Hind	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
young	O
Fellow	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
six	O
Pence	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
through	O
my	O
Backdoor	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
from	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
threaten	O
'd	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
appear	O
'd	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
an	O
Assault	O
:	O
I	O
committed	O
them	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Thoughts	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
Bishop-Gate	B-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Afternoon	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Seals	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Doxen	O
.	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
bid	O
Money	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
jingling	O
of	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Seals	O
with	O
his	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
carefully	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
up	O
another	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
already	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
5	O
Seals	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
struggling	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
tore	O
his	O
Coat	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
My	O
Man	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
much	O
ado	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Seals	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
these	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
gave	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
and	O
deposed	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
convinced	O
by	O
the	O
Resistance	O
he	O
made	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
People	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Liquor	O
disorders	O
me	O
vastly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
entrusts	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
vast	O
Number	O
of	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Goal	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
drunk	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
;	O
he	O
marry	O
'd	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
's	O
in	O
Liquor	O
he	O
's	O
like	O
a	O
Madman	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Man	O
deals	O
in	O
Fruit	O
,	O
-	O
his	O
Wife	O
does	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
does	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
Fruit	O
himself	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Business	O
he	O
follows	O
-	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
John	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
-	O
not	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Porter	O
in	O
Borough	O
Market	O
work	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
deals	O
in	O
Callamancoes	O
,	O
Muslins	O
,	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
-	O
not	O
old	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
new	O
ones	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Porter	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
harm	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
's	O
in	O
Liquor	O
he	O
'll	O
rattle	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
Pewter	O
about	O
like	O
a	O
Madman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dodson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Borrough	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
Good	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
but	O
very	O
indifferent	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
from	O
entering	O
into	O
Particulars	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
because	O
they	O
call	O
me	O
a	O
Molly	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Woman	O
than	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
can	O
I	O
help	O
my	O
Face	O
?	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
William	B-pers
Moreland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Knocker	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coyl	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
Richard	B-pers
Manlove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
;	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Long	B-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone	O
Bottle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Oil	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Pewtor	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
3	O
.	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Stone	O
Mugs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bolt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
7	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Stamford	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	O
.	O
On	O
Christmas-Day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Rogues	O
at	O
Work	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
!	O
-	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
at	O
!	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
at	O
first	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
our	O
Maid	O
got	O
up	O
so	O
early	O
,	O
but	O
looking	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
neither	O
hearing	O
nor	O
seeing	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
Thieves	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Window	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
Hours	O
Time	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Bolts	O
clink	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
!	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
till	O
Morning	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
fast	O
and	O
safe	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Eadon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
.	O
On	O
Christmas	O
Eve	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Stall	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
-	O
(	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Cobler	O
)	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Pinchers	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
to	O
maintain	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Christmas	O
Hollidays	O
,	O
from	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
on	O
the	O
Outside	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
break	O
;	O
Boards	O
from	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
to	O
him	O
We	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Mugs	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
among	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
while	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
2	O
live	O
ones	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
again	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
push	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
The	O
Noise	O
of	O
the	O
Fowls	O
wak	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
.	O
Eadon	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
thrown	O
under	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
ran	O
away	O
)	O
safe	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
no	O
Body	O
stirring	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Pan	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
boil	O
'd	O
Meat	O
and	O
Broth	O
the	O
Meat	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Broth	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
our	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
kill	O
'd	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
bak	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Pye	O
for	O
our	O
Christmas	O
Dinner	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
five	O
Fowl	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
for	O
a	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Pewter	O
we	O
sold	O
at	O
a	O
Pewterer	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
first	O
Shop	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
before	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Whitemore	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
an	O
Infant	O
his	O
Character	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
honest	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Cobler	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
may	O
express	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Tongue	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
Question	O
before	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
only	O
once	O
for	O
a	O
Childish	O
Thing	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
little	O
Fruit	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
's	O
in	O
Liquor	O
he	O
'll	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
indeed	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stark	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Turf	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
spake	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Behalf	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
acquitted	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Indictment	O
.	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Albin	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Allbone	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
Jan	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
James	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
John	O
Brown	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
118	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
Penthouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Jane	B-pers
Monro	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Diana	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Robert	B-pers
Breckens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
Feb	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Felton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Bluegate	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
Design	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
forc	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
forc	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
l'it	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
have	O
Proof	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
what	O
you	O
may	O
say	O
-	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
'll	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
-	O
Why	O
I	O
do	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
more	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
give	O
no	O
(	O
any	O
)	O
farther	O
Account	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
why	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
her	O
Instructions	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
uppermost	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
yes	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
call	O
'd	O
-	O
These	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
forc	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
stay	O
,	O
-	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
;	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
heard	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
my	O
Time	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
said	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
Account	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
10	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Things	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
-	O
and	O
dispatch	O
me	O
-	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
threat'ned	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
she	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
Bluegate	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
so	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
he	O
found	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
Life	O
-	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
Time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Terror	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
frighted	O
for	O
Fear	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
Way	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
indeed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
coming	O
down	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
losing	O
my	O
Life	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
-	O
a-bed	O
-	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
slept	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
came	O
and	O
raised	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
only	O
examine	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
visit	O
Bluegate	O
Fields	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
notorious	O
Place	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Way	O
thither	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
well	O
dressed	O
was	O
fallen	O
into	O
Mall	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
stripp	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
lower	O
Apartment	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
above	O
Stairs	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Cloaths	O
spread	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'waked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
being	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drest	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
People	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
Moll	O
Thomas	O
was	O
at	O
Ray	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Gate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
one	O
Coleman	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
of	O
Whitechappel	O
Court	O
,	O
heard	O
my	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
Beer	O
for	O
my	O
Watchmen	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
Coleman	O
,	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
drink	O
Beer	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
Wine	O
enough	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
ruffled	O
Smock	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
't	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
'wak	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
explain	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Gate	O
,	O
another	O
Woman	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
my	O
threa'ning	O
her	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Bartholing	B-pers
Brinkley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
sell	O
Gin	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
Moll	O
Thomas	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
thinking	O
Informers	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
had	O
more	O
need	O
go	O
to	O
Thomas	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
than	O
come	O
to	O
trouble	O
us	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tumber	I-pers
a	O
Watchman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
in	O
his	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Condition	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
deposed	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Account	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
They	O
,	O
-	O
They	O
had	O
threat'ned	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
fetch	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Pots	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
less	O
than	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
Bed	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
which	O
of	O
these	O
Girls	O
must	O
I	O
lie	O
with	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
lie	O
with	O
any	O
Man	O
besides	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Gate	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
trouble	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
.	O
They	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
yet	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38.	O
William	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cranfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
willful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
in	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
exhibited	O
before	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Information	O
,	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
41.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Margarets	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
Charles	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bembow	I-pers
,	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
43.	O
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Nov	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
feloniously	O
made	O
and	O
forged	O
an	O
Acquittance	O
and	O
Receipt	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
certain	O
Account	O
;	O
which	O
Account	O
and	O
forged	O
Acquittance	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Words	O
and	O
Figures	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Guiren	O
against	O
Bancillion	O
.	O
Bill	O
,	O
23	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
-	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
-	O
10	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
-	O
half	O
Profit	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
-	O
Costs	O
out	O
of	O
Purse	O
,	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
-	O
my	O
Dividend	O
,	O
5	O
l	O
6	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
-	O
17	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
-	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
-	O
Due	O
to	O
me	O
13	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
Contents	O
.	O
R.	O
Gately	O
.	O
With	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Roger	B-pers
Gately	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Solicitor	O
s	O
of	O
the	O
High	O
Court	O
of	O
Chancery	O
.	O
And	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
observ	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
not	O
laid	O
within	O
the	O
Words	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
Chap	O
.	O
25.	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
perpetual	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
farther	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Paper	O
produced	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
rather	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Costs	O
.	O
That	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Receipt	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
express	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
worded	O
,	O
the	O
Receipt	O
could	O
not	O
with	O
any	O
Propriety	O
of	O
Construction	O
be	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Word	O
Costs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Paper	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
Memorandum	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
applicable	O
to	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Councel	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
.	O
I	O
humbly	O
hope	O
these	O
Objections	O
may	O
be	O
wav	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
be	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
Merits	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
.	O
Councel	O
Defendant	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
this	O
Hint	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
neither	O
Mr.	O
Gately	O
's	O
Testimony	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
Affidavits	O
,	O
can	O
be	O
admitted	O
in	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Case	O
between	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Whiting	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Case	O
in	O
Point	O
;	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
that	O
where	O
a	O
Person	O
is	O
concerned	O
in	O
Interest	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
.	O
Councel	O
Plaintiff	O
.	O
I	O
presume	O
Mr.	O
Gately	O
is	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Law	O
;	O
for	O
supposing	O
we	O
convict	O
the	O
Defendant	O
on	O
this	O
statute	O
,	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
is	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Thing	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
forfeited	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
;	O
by	O
his	O
Conviction	O
therefore	O
Mr.	O
Gately	O
loses	O
all	O
Prospect	O
of	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
-	O
'twill	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
Power	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
convicted	O
.	O
The	O
Objection	O
against	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
being	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
arises	O
from	O
his	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
it	O
's	O
being	O
to	O
his	O
Advantage	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
't	O
is	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
disadvantage	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
appears	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
allow	O
'd	O
a	O
legal	O
Evidence	O
;	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
may	O
give	O
a	O
Testimony	O
to	O
charge	O
himself	O
.	O
Now	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
if	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gately	O
's	O
,	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Defendant	O
should	O
be	O
convicted	O
,	O
Gately	O
will	O
be	O
depriv	O
'd	O
of	O
ever	O
having	O
any	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
doing	O
?	O
Why	O
he	O
is	O
prosecuting	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
Offence	O
,	O
which	O
Conviction	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Prospect	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
any	O
Recompence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
44	O
.	O
45.	O
Edward	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Richford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bolster	O
of	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
double	O
Dutch	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Royals	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
38	O
.	O
And	O
46.	O
William	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
moving	O
;	O
perswading	O
,	O
councelling	O
,	O
abetting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Polson	O
and	O
Richford	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Felony	O
to	O
commit	O
and	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Defendants	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
47.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
Malt-loft	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Liberty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Stove	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49	O
.	O
50.	O
John	B-pers
Lovett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
1	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkercheif	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
from	O
her	O
Person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
of	O
Smelts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Codfish	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burrow	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
Martha	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
brass	O
Weights	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Touch-stone	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54.	O
Philip	B-pers
Shovel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bliss	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kinshillug	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
1735	O
.	O
Mary	O
Kinshillug	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
off	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
complaining	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dish	O
to	O
warm	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
some	O
Toast	O
and	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
.	O
In	O
our	O
Conversation	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Brother	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Holland	O
Trader	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
my	O
Civility	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
.	O
Thus	O
we	O
passed	O
away	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
spare	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
Brother	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
should	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
my	O
Dining-Room	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
Fire	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
it	O
against	O
her	O
Brother	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Seventh	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
studied	O
the	O
Planets	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
hidden	O
Treasure	O
in	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
-	O
(	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
she	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Treasure	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
Treasure	O
in	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
take	O
what	O
she	O
pleased	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
bitter	O
Wishes	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Treasure	O
,	O
she	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
an	O
valuable	O
Things	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
16	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bay	O
Salt	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
the	O
Salt	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
Things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
is	O
dirty	O
now	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
clean	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
so	O
aching	O
a	O
Heart	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
remember	O
'd	O
her	O
20	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
remember	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
2	O
Days	O
,	O
a	O
conjuring	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Senses	O
.	O
-	O
Gray	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
2	O
Days	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Kirshillug	O
's	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
good	O
Fire	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Tea	O
in	O
5	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
to	O
trust	O
my	O
Landlady	O
Kinshillug	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dining	O
Room	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
Change	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
below	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Kirshillug	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Soul	O
in	O
the	O
Dining-Room	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
hidden	O
Treasure	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
too	O
.	O
-	O
Galloway	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Kingshillug	O
carry	O
her	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Things	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
