TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
1742	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIMOTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
CHAPPLE	O
,	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
ABNEY	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
++	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Dec.	O
14th	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
was	O
chosen	O
Recorder	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
resign	O
'd	O
that	O
Office	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Figgins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cargill	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Catterns	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Norris	B-pers
John	I-pers
Hancks	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Munro	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wealy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheat	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chesson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skeats	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Everden	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gittings	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Blagrove	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Spenceley	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Creighton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Pumps	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Pumps	O
;	O
they	O
hung	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Turnstile-Alley	B-place
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
somebody	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Snuff-box	O
lined	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Rim	O
and	O
Hinge	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lacour	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lacour	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Brother	O
Dr	O
Lacour	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	B-place
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Fellow	O
fumbling	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
Says	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
only	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
your	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
just	O
dropped	O
your	O
Snuff-box	O
into	O
the	O
Channel	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Channel	O
wet	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
secure	O
the	O
Fellow	O
.	O
+	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
I	O
felt	O
that	O
Fellow	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
immediately	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Brother	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Aldermen	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
Breaks	O
,	O
in	O
This	O
and	O
other	O
Trials	O
,	O
are	O
to	O
shew	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
follows	O
is	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
Questions	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
which	O
Questions	O
are	O
omitted	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Answers	O
sufficiently	O
denote	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Dr	O
Philip	B-pers
Lacour	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
Grocer	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
wet	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
Box	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Box	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Channel	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Pinch	O
a	O
Snuff	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Brown	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
throw	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
this	O
Box	O
by	O
the	O
Sound	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
falling	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Fleet-ditch	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
Walnuts	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Shells	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Walnut-shells	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Dr	O
Lacour	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
found	O
any	O
Thing	O
like	O
Walnuts	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
like	O
something	O
heavy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Porter	O
;	O
I	O
fetch	O
Carcasses	O
from	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
my	O
Trial	O
put	O
off	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
cast	O
without	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Demee	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30th	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
examined	O
a-part	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Demee	O
;	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
fe'nnight	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Shutters	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
holding	O
the	O
Pin	O
for	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
something	O
came	O
trailing	O
against	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
of	O
your	O
Bulk	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
Linnen	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Demee	I-pers
;	O
one	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
trailing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
down	O
Duke's-Place	B-place
,	O
against	O
Mr	O
Smith	O
's	O
Back	O
door	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Mitre-Tavern	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
He	O
ran	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Check	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
are	O
carried	O
back	O
to	O
your	O
Shop	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Check	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Shop	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
Yes	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lacour	I-pers
.	O
[	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
]	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Mr	O
Demee	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Fellow	O
trailing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Check	O
Linnen	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
Look	O
after	O
that	O
Piece	O
of	O
Check	O
Linnen	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
trailing	O
along	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
draw	O
it	O
in	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
trailed	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
Duke's-Place	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
Shop	O
where	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
Piece	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
is	O
like	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
?	O
Lacour	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Check	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Demee	O
's	O
Man	O
says	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
dragging	O
along	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Mr	O
Salter	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
within	O
two	O
Doors	O
of	O
Mr	O
Demee	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Linnen	O
:	O
One	O
End	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
dragging	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
run	O
over	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
:	O
He	O
threw	O
the	O
Check	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Check	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mind	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
,	O
young	O
Man	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
Check	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
hit	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
hit	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
innocent	O
Man	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Check	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Check	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
lie	O
pretty	O
near	O
one	O
another	O
:	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
Demee	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dropp	O
'd	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wardley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
under	O
Aldgate	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
to	O
his	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
acquaint	O
them	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
made	O
Answer	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
pester	O
'd	O
with	O
these	O
Fellows	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
being	O
big	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Male	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Child	O
she	O
did	O
alone	O
and	O
secretly	O
bring	O
forth	O
alive	O
;	O
which	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Land	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Bastard	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
did	O
wrap	O
and	O
fold	O
,	O
by	O
Means	O
of	O
which	O
Wrapping	O
and	O
Folding	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
was	O
choaked	O
and	O
strangled	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
such	O
Choaking	O
and	O
Strangling	O
did	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Sunday	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary-House	O
,	O
at	O
Mr	O
Hughes	O
's	O
in	O
little	B-place
Jermyn-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Necessary-House	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
somewhat	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr	O
Hughes	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
They	O
unrolled	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
*	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
wash	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
in	O
every	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
*	O
21st	O
James	O
I	O
.	O
Cap	O
27	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
Woman	O
be	O
delivered	O
of	O
any	O
Issue	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
should	O
by	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
be	O
a	O
Bastard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
endeavour	O
privately	O
,	O
either	O
by	O
drowning	O
,	O
or	O
fact	O
burying	O
thereof	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Way	O
,	O
either	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
procuring	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
so	O
to	O
conceal	O
the	O
Death	O
thereof	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
light	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
were	O
born	O
alive	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
concealed	O
:	O
In	O
every	O
such	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
so	O
offending	O
,	O
shall	O
suffer	O
Death	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
Case	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
except	O
such	O
Mother	O
can	O
make	O
Proof	O
by	O
the	O
Witness	O
at	O
the	O
least	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
speaks	O
of	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Necessary-Place	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
Common-Sewer	O
)	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
be	O
push	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
.	O
She	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
lie	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
one	O
Linnen	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Hand	O
and	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
)	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
discovered	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
till	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Male	O
Child	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
was	O
wash	O
'd	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
convenient	O
Place	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
examine	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tullock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Midwife	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Appearance	O
of	O
any	O
Violence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
viewing	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
its	O
Death	O
?	O
Tullock	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
indeed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Thing	O
provided	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Tullock	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Things	O
provided	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Tullock	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
to	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
poor	O
Creature	O
was	O
ignorant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Miscarriage	O
?	O
Tullock	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
whether	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
went	O
her	O
full	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
might	O
come	O
pretty	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
owned	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
with	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Tullock	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
herself	O
in	O
Labour	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
a	O
Relation	O
's	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
Brother	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
Serant	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Midwife	O
attended	O
on	O
the	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Tullock	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
carried	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
to	O
avoid	O
her	O
Shame	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Thing	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Yes	O
;	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
Things	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
at	O
her	O
Brother	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
there	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Closet	O
locked	O
?	O
Tullock	O
.	O
Her	O
Brother	O
was	O
mov	O
'd	O
from	O
that	O
House	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
empty	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
these	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
convenient	O
Things	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
those	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Coroner	O
for	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
Westminster	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Examination	O
*	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
before	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
signed	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Substace	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Tullock	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
.	O
*	O
1st	O
&	O
2d	O
,	O
Philip	O
&	O
Mary	O
,	O
Cap	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Sect	O
.	O
5	O
&	O
6	O
.	O
Every	O
Coroner	O
,	O
upon	O
any	O
Inquisition	O
before	O
him	O
found	O
,	O
whereby	O
any	O
Person	O
or	O
Persons	O
shall	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
Murder	O
or	O
Manslaughter	O
committed	O
,	O
shall	O
put	O
in	O
Writing	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
shall	O
also	O
take	O
Examinations	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
certify	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Goal-Delivery	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
James	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
taken	O
this	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1742	O
.	O
This	O
Examinant	O
faith	O
,	O
``	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
``	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Male	O
Child	O
(	O
which	O
``	O
was	O
still-born	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged	O
Staff	O
in	O
``	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
James	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
``	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
``	O
Examinant	O
,	O
unfortunately	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
into	O
``	O
the	O
Bog-House	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
``	O
Hughes	O
,	O
in	O
Li	O
ttle	O
Jermyn	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
``	O
of	O
St	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Mark	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
X	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Taken	O
and	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Coroner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
]	O
When	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
sign	O
her	O
Confession	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
can	O
neither	O
read	O
nor	O
write	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
ignorant	O
Person	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
concerned	O
in	O
Liquor	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
moving	O
from	O
one	O
House	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
heavy	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
hurt	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
my	O
Time	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
near	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Body	O
hear	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
enough	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
Labour	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
born	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Michael	B-pers
Bewley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
after	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25th	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
Weaver	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Key	O
with	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Seven	O
:	O
Seeing	O
a	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Plates	O
rattle	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Holding	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
somebody	O
has	O
not	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
backwards	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
in	O
running	O
away	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
within	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
:	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
Assistance	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
Plates	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
move	O
them	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
from	O
the	O
Shelf	O
to	O
the	O
Table	O
which	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
at	O
;	O
-	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Plates	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
fast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Wind	O
did	O
not	O
blow	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
but	O
lately	O
mended	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Panes	O
of	O
Glass	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Glass	O
gone	O
:	O
-	O
he	O
left	O
nothing	O
behind	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Light	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Minute	O
he	O
heard	O
us	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chissel	O
.	O
They	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
what	O
Answer	O
I	O
made	O
when	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
putting	O
up	O
a	O
Loom	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
work	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
never	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
me	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Hodges	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
jump	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
what	O
for	O
a	O
Place	O
it	O
is	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Haberdashers-Square	B-place
in	O
Grub-Street	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
tumbled	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Body	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
us	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Hodges	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
Judge	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
frightned	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
Mrs	O
Hodges	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
at	O
seeing	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
Face	O
close	O
against	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
looked	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
He	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
saw	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
was	O
four	O
Plates	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
moved	O
from	O
the	O
Shelf	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
supposed	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
long	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
Body	O
knows	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mrs	O
Hodges	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
running	O
down	O
the	O
Gateway	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
Knives	O
and	O
this	O
Chissel	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
borrow	O
'd	O
this	O
Chissel	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
a	O
Loom	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
shov	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
recover	O
my	O
self	O
:	O
Said	O
that	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
have	O
I	O
caught	O
you	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
?	O
said	O
I.	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
charged	O
another	O
Man	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
very	O
quietly	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
broke	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
Judge	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
move	O
his	O
Loom	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
stole	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
House	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
did	O
any	O
Damage	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Bewley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Home	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
till	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Affair	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Hammer	O
and	O
Chissel	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
his	O
Loom	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
stained	O
with	O
any	O
ill	O
Character	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
made	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
said	O
the	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
a	O
Person	O
is	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Alderman	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
stood	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
said	O
otherwise	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty-two	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elisha	B-pers
Impey	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13th	O
.	O
Elisha	B-pers
Impey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
commenced	O
Servant	O
with	O
me	O
last	O
January	O
was	O
Twelve-month	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Soapboiler	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	B-place
;	O
presently	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
Service	O
,	O
abundance	O
of	O
my	O
Customers	O
complained	O
of	O
want	O
of	O
Weight	O
in	O
their	O
Soap	O
;	O
I	O
consulted	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
wait	O
with	O
Patience	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Rogue	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Soap	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
more	O
sent	O
:	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
Men	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Boxes	O
was	O
heavier	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
imagine	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Soap	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Villany	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
Soap	O
weighed	O
;	O
some	O
was	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
wanting	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
all	O
your	O
Boxes	O
examined	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
foremost	O
,	O
opened	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
was	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
secure	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
unlocked	O
another	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Lid	O
about	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Pardon	O
:	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Accomplices	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
any	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Fellow-Servant	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Barrel	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
how	O
much	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
in	O
his	O
Box	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Cask	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Daniel	B-pers
Scorer	I-pers
,	O
desired	O
that	O
Box	O
might	O
be	O
let	O
by	O
my	O
Box	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
Scorer	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Coventry-Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7	O
Henry	B-pers
Cromley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Fustic	O
Wood	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Ticket-Porter	B-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
going	O
up	O
Fresh	B-place
Wharf	I-place
Gateway	I-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Fustic	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Wood	O
for	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Fustic	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
better	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
than	O
to	O
burn	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
here	O
all	O
this	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Victualling-House	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr	O
Fuller	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
missed	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
hundred	O
and	O
odd	O
Weight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Pieces	O
missing	O
:	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Dyers	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Parcels	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whose	O
Property	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
itt	O
off	O
Fresh-Wharf	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Thing	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
October	O
20th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
St	B-place
Clement's-Church	I-place
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
Rascal	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
:	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
Damn	O
my	O
Eyes	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
for	O
another	O
Fellow	O
shov	O
'd	O
me	O
against	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
He	O
run	O
by	O
St	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Mr	O
Wood	O
,	O
stopped	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Constables	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
stay	O
from	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
Ten	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Guard	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Gang	O
of	O
Fellows	O
with	O
Clubs	O
,	O
to	O
rescue	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
near	O
twenty	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
?	O
Higginson	O
.	O
The	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
by	O
St	O
Clement's-Church	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
that	O
Fellow	O
has	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Fellow	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
designed	O
to	O
rescue	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Constable	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
a	O
Guard	O
,	O
for	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
John	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
accidentally	O
hit	O
my	O
Foot	O
against	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
he	O
valued	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
at	O
10	O
d.	O
they	O
kept	O
me	O
from	O
Seven	O
to	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
would	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
Constables	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
God	O
forgive	O
you	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
sworn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Constables	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
doing	O
their	O
Duties	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Neave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Publican	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Goose	B-place
and	I-place
Gridiron	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
12th	O
or	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Thursday	O
following	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Guinea	O
Reward	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Day	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Pot	O
again	O
,	O
Mr	O
Austen	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
show	O
me	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Friday	O
Se'nnight	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ben	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
Wych	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Person	O
that	O
is	O
detained	O
here	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
my	O
Mug	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Indeed	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Brother	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
Mug	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Linnen-Draper	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Austen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Amazement	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
Pot	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Mr	O
Ellis	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
Reward	O
offer	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Cast	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Ellis	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
I	O
believe	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Pot	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	O
Austen	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
being	O
detain	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
could	O
suffer	O
for	O
it	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
said	O
his	O
Brother	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
says	O
the	O
Pot	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
what	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
exactly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
speak	O
before	O
to	O
a	O
particular	O
Hour	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
prove	O
by	O
any	O
Witness	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
-	O
Hutchinson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Grotto	O
in	O
Southampton-Buildings	O
that	O
Day	O
from	O
5	O
till	O
7	O
,	O
then	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
parted	O
by	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
chearful	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Close	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
one	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
:	O
He	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
Money	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Estate	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
Man	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
honestly	O
and	O
justly	O
:	O
He	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
none	O
but	O
Housekeepers	O
Company	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wittingstill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
as	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
Plate	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
several	O
Times	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Things	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
gone	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
when	O
the	O
Drawers	O
have	O
been	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
sometimes	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
Mr	O
Neave	O
,	O
pray	O
stay	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
till	O
I	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
looked	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
two	O
Fits	O
of	O
Illness	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Wyatt	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Baker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Chamberlaine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Wyatt	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
given	O
to	O
any	O
loose	O
Ways	O
.	O
Mr	O
Saffree	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
500	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
,	O
especially	O
latterly	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
a	O
Frenzy	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Parents	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
Memory	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
an	O
unjust	O
Thing	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
entrust	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
Friends	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
Mercers	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
some	O
Money	O
left	O
him	O
lately	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
disappointed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
sometimes	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
:	O
He	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
an	O
Ironmonger	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
Shop-keepers	O
in	O
general	O
;	O
they	O
deal	O
in	O
many	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
faithfully	O
:	O
His	O
Master	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
-	O
His	O
Brother	O
is	O
lifted	O
for	O
a	O
Marine	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nettlefold	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nettlefold	I-pers
.	O
The	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
past	O
me	O
twice	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
on	O
:	O
He	O
followed	O
me	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
go	O
:	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
Fellow	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
between	O
his	O
Legs	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
quietly	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Run	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
besides	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
see	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
free	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rotherford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Hempen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Clement	B-pers
Corderoy	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
Clement	B-pers
Corderoy	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sacking	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
his	O
back	O
Part	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
Boy	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Carman	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
He	O
run	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
between	O
a	O
Cart	O
and	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Duffel	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
this	O
Boy	O
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
this	O
Cloak	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
stole	O
something	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
gave	O
this	O
Cloak	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Woman	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
this	O
Cloak	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Alley	B-place
,	O
three	O
Doors	O
from	O
Mrs	O
Cross	O
's	O
.	O
This	O
Cloak	O
hung	O
a	O
little	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
Boy	O
(	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
*	O
)	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
too	O
tender	O
Years	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Havril	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gloucestershire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
October	O
12	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
perceiving	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
a'Clock	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Go	O
about	O
your	O
Business	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Thought	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sometime	O
afterwards	O
in	O
came	O
Joseph	B-pers
Doody	I-pers
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Gloucestershire	O
Cheese	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
I	O
believe	O
150	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
impeached	O
four	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Doody	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
Cheesemonger	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
a'Clock	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Cheesemonger	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
I	O
dropt	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
Purpose	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
self	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
Lad	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
Mr	O
Harris	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Harris	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Doody	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
with	O
Gold	O
Thread	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Waist-coat	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Berrington	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Berrington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Home	O
into	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
Return	O
,	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Coat	O
with	O
Gold	O
Thread	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Waist-coat	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
a	O
Snuff-colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brown	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
between	O
a	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
and	O
the	O
George	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
young	O
Fellow	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
.	O
Mr	O
Satchel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
flung	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
George	O
and	O
a	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King's-Road	O
,	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Theobald's-Row	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Things	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Snuff-colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
with	O
twelve	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brown	B-pers
Waistcoat	I-pers
.	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
-	O
Anne	B-pers
Reynardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr	O
Berrington	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Instant	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
running	O
with	O
his	O
Apron	O
full	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Thing	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Reynardson	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Girl	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Belott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
26th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Bird-Cage	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
and	O
four	O
Six-pences	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
weekly	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
Threatnings	O
or	O
Promises	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
Hunt	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
Servant	O
's	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Promises	O
of	O
Favour	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Callimanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richford	I-pers
,	O
October	O
5th	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
winding	O
of	O
Silk	O
;	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Groat	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Mr	O
Warner	O
's	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
Things	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Warner	O
's	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
indeed	O
.	O
Bambridge	O
Cresswell	O
.	O
This	O
good	O
Woman	O
left	O
some	O
Things	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
after	O
Mrs	O
Richford	O
had	O
fetched	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Gown	O
that	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
:	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Trowels	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
Hammer	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Trowel	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
Hammer	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scammell	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6th	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Trowels	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
Metcalf	O
's	O
Yard	O
in	O
Shad-Thames	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
Cook	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Brushes	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
my	O
Basket	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
.	O
Middleton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
serve	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
that	O
Trade	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Harps	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Quilt	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Blanket	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Feather	O
Pillow	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Pillow-cases	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Calbreath	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
October	O
24th	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Calbreath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
robbed	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
'till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Foley	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
going	O
there	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
ever	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Harps	I-pers
,	O
but	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Beane	I-pers
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
in	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Candle-stick	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Susannah	B-pers
Beane	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
Pillow	O
and	O
this	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
know	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Beane	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
take	O
in	O
Things	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
brings	O
them	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
We	O
take	O
in	O
Goods	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
own	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
altered	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
new	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
Matter	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
Things	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
Design	O
of	O
Fraud	O
:	O
She	O
begged	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Hair	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
hurt	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Creech	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
this	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Smallpiece	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodges	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
another	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Concern	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Concern	O
!	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Emmet	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
her	O
so	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
[	O
Consort	O
or	O
Companion	O
]	O
which	O
was	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
and	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
above	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
my	O
Side	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
I	O
started	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
put	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
under	O
the	O
Bolster	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
ten	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
was	O
married	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
prov	O
'd	O
since	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
married	O
by	O
jumping	O
over	O
a	O
Mop-stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
when	O
you	O
fell	O
asleep	O
?	O
Emmet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
before	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
awake	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
all	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
:	O
She	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
)	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bolster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
she	O
said	O
so	O
?	O
Emmet	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
May	O
it	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
Story	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
Man	O
is	O
my	O
Kinsman	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
from	O
the	O
India	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
:	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
through	O
Devonshire-Square	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
several	O
Houses	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
We	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
Husband	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pretended	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
betray	O
her	O
:	O
We	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
show	O
her	O
Mercy	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Power	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
promis	O
'd	O
her	O
Mercy	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Both	O
my	O
Kinsman	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
:	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
or	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
People	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Bernard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
there	O
sat	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
we	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
sell	O
a	O
Dram	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
a	O
Watch	O
that	O
is	O
pawn	O
'd	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
credibly	O
informed	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Constable	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
too	O
.	O
Said	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
aware	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Woman	O
the	O
Story	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
again	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
lent	O
me	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Tap	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
led	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
narrow	O
Passage	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
narrow	O
Passage	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Person	O
put	O
a	O
Brown	B-pers
Paper	I-pers
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Paper	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
called	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
directly	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Take	O
this	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
Six-pence	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
was	O
asleep	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
speak	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
:	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Dwelling-House	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nineteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
a	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
this	O
Piece	O
was	O
mine	O
?	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
my	O
Mark	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Wm	O
Edwards	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
into	O
Wales	O
:	O
he	O
swore	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
this	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
and	O
his	O
Answer	O
was	O
,	O
Nothing	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
another	O
Expression	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
stole	O
any	O
Thing	O
before	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Value	O
:	O
Edwards	O
is	O
bound	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
ordered	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
21.	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
,	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Southerton	I-pers
,	O
November	O
24	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Southerton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Right	O
Hand	O
Pocket	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Postern	O
of	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
towards	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
Men	O
by	O
,	O
besides	O
myself	O
?	O
Southerton	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
Ludgate	O
Prison	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Stall	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Stop	O
in	O
the	O
Postern	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
take	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
Ogilby	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Officers	O
,	O
caught	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
Men	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
knows	O
between	O
God	O
and	O
his	O
Conscience	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Southerton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
off	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bradfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Sheet	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
Things	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Sheet	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Landlord	O
's	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Velvet	O
Manteels	O
,	O
fifteen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Kid	O
Gloves	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
white	O
Damask	O
Shoes	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flowered	O
Silk	O
Shoes	O
,	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
one	O
Rowler	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
one	O
Brocaded	O
Shoe	O
,	O
several	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lenson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
November	O
25	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
25.	O
Patience	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
white	O
Damask	O
Shoes	O
laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
one	O
Brocaded	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Gloves	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lenson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
Sash-Window	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
before	O
would	O
push	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Velvet	O
Manteels	O
,	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
Kid	O
Glove	O
s	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
put	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
than	O
the	O
Evidence	O
confessed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
therein	O
mentioned	O
;	O
these	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Manteel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
who	O
will	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
inform	O
you	O
concerning	O
your	O
Goods	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Eckley	I-pers
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Patience	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Forrester	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Shoes	O
,	O
one	O
Brocaded	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Gloves	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
three	O
Pair	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
were	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
Lenson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
the	O
Gloves	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
Gloves	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
that	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
mine	O
;	O
said	O
Mrs	O
Forrester	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
the	O
Gold	O
Laced	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Velvet	O
Manteel	O
to	O
Duke	O
William	O
's	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
Care	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
give	O
for	O
these	O
?	O
Lenson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
eleven	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eckley	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
St	O
Giles	O
,	O
Campbell	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
our	O
Hands	O
to	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
a	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
easily	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
put	O
a	O
Panen	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
got	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Delavry	O
stood	O
by	O
to	O
watch	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
agreed	O
upon	O
before-hand	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
stand	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
by	O
while	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Velvet	O
Manteels	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
one	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Gloves	O
,	O
in	O
running	O
along	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
fifteen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
to	O
that	O
Gentle-woman	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff	O
box	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
Shoe	O
,	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Brigade	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
)	O
[	O
Brocade	O
]	O
and	O
a	O
Pudding	O
done	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
they	O
put	O
round	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
Gold	O
Laced	O
Shoes	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
at	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
:	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
shared	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
divided	O
20	O
d.	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Manteel	O
;	O
but	O
Delaney	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
:	O
Campbell	O
and	O
I	O
shared	O
that	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
that	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
makes	O
nine	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
:	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Forrester	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
,	O
Whether	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
all	O
from	O
one	O
Person	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
several	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
We	O
got	O
them	O
all	O
from	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
no	O
Matter	O
how	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Delaney	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
Time	O
o'Night	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Eckley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
past	O
Eight	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
Nine	O
;	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
Bell	O
rung	O
Nine	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
Delaney	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
sold	O
the	O
Things	O
?	O
Eckley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
you	O
were	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Mantelet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gold	O
Laced	O
Shoes	O
:	O
Campbell	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
ever	O
sell	O
any	O
Thing	O
before	O
to	O
this	O
Patience	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
?	O
s	O
Eckley	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
trifling	O
Things	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
some	O
Pewter	O
Gin-pots	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
-	O
Both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
sold	O
Things	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
?	O
Eckley	O
.	O
She	O
must	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
leave	O
that	O
to	O
yourself	O
to	O
consider	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
sold	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
Shop	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Manner	O
?	O
Eckley	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
sold	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Bargain	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Things	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
Use	O
:	O
She	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Laced	O
Shoes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
fit	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Mantelet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
about	O
me	O
then	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
Bargain	O
with	O
us	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
the	O
Mantelet	O
over	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Body	O
there	O
when	O
you	O
sold	O
them	O
?	O
Eckley	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
idle	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
several	O
Nights	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
be	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
Forrester	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
your	O
Wife	O
was	O
an	O
Earthen-ware	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
?	O
Eckley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Forrester	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Money	O
?	O
Eckley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
;	O
you	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mrs	O
Lenson	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
these	O
Things	O
worth	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Lenson	I-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
laid	O
at	O
about	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
above	O
50	O
s.	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
prime	O
Cost	O
.	O
Forrester	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Mantelet	O
new	O
?	O
Lenson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
second-hand	O
Things	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
Mantelets	O
were	O
new	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
worth	O
above	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mantelet	O
I	O
value	O
but	O
at	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
search	O
Mrs	O
Forrester	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
open	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
the	O
Constable	O
some	O
Shoes	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Mantelet	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Things	O
again	O
.	O
Lenson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Mantelet	O
to	O
Duke	O
William	O
's	O
Servant	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
Delaney	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Campbell	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Campbell	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
together	O
before	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
-	O
Fransham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
George	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
ever	O
since	O
he	O
suck	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
Eighteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
that	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
cloath	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Painter	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
Trade	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
a	O
Footman	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
honestly	O
and	O
justly	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
twelve	O
Months	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
:	O
He	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
500	O
l.	O
in	O
Plate	O
and	O
Jewels	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inclined	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
took	O
a	O
Pin's-worth	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Brewster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Painter	O
;	O
Campbell	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
Months	O
:	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Trade	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
a	O
Year	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Madam	O
Lumley	O
's	O
Family	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Brewster	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
when	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
our	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
Body	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
to	O
have	O
robbed	O
us	O
of	O
Things	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Abellavan	I-pers
.	O
[	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
wrote	O
his	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
so	O
properly	O
without	O
Reading	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
George	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
made	O
several	O
Errands	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
prov	O
'd	O
honest	O
:	O
The	O
last	O
Time	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Waggon	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
brought	O
some	O
Things	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
outright	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
she	O
lost	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Velvet	O
Manteel	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
Woman	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
)	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
in	O
a	O
Pawn	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
in	O
no	O
Pawns	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
odd	O
Pieces	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
some	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
yellow	O
Damask	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
about	O
Noon	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
looks	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
sold	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
an	O
Earthen-ware	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
support	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
him	O
the	O
Trouble	O
of	O
going	O
further	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
in	O
Exchange	O
for	O
Earthen-Ware	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
give	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
him	O
eleven	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
at	O
Work	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
Some	O
Part	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
black	O
Silk	O
and	O
black	O
Lace	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
an	O
Earthenware	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
drinking	O
a	O
Dram	O
when	O
Mrs	O
Forrester	O
bought	O
some	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
some	O
black	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
Mantelet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Body	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
asked	O
Mrs	O
Forrester	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
in	O
a	O
Pawn	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
Exchange	O
for	O
Earthen-Ware	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
are	O
always	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Straw-colour	O
'd	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
laced	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
old	O
dirty	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
Woman	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Dorset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs	O
Forrester	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
follows	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
formerly	O
carry	O
on	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs	O
Forrester	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
did	O
formerly	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
hear	O
she	O
sells	O
Liquors	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
deal	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
Pelham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
3	O
Years	O
:	O
Her	O
Character	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
can	O
be	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
sells	O
Liquors	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Distiller	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Shop	O
is	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
follow	O
the	O
Business	O
of	O
a	O
Seamstress	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
she	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Delaney	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
my	O
Trial	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
on	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
Delaney	O
and	O
Campbell	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Forrester	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Rim	O
and	O
Hinge	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
a	O
Penny	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
October	O
15th	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Tavistock-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
with	O
this	O
Fellow	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
standing	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
Way	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Doors	O
beyond	O
the	O
Salutation	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Touch	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Pocket	O
tore	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Knees	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
cut	O
and	O
bruised	O
with	O
the	O
Fall	O
;	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
over	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
darkish	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Salutation	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
a	O
dead	O
still	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr	O
Rock	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
Soldier	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
taken	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Sight	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Sight	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Pocket	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
Pocket	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
again	O
;	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
now	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Shilling	O
;	O
she	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
only	O
saw	O
my	O
Back	O
.	O
Squire	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Oath	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
viewed	O
his	O
Face	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
swore	O
so	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
greater	O
Regard	O
to	O
Life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
Moon	O
light	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
dark	O
Night	O
?	O
Squire	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Light	O
came	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Huggins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Constables	O
of	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Parish	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
Fire-Arms	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
might	O
endanger	O
us	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
Mrs	O
Squire	O
had	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Pocket	O
dropped	O
from	O
between	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
she	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Charles-Street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
to	O
hear	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
perceived	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Tavistock	O
Street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
Soldier	O
,	O
Thief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
