TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
1743	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIMOTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tipp	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Seller	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturgis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wolley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Wragg	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Haymond	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cosh	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fettyplace	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Millman	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
Mr	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
Foreman	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Mr	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
indisposed	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
Hawkins	O
attended	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
182	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
We	O
lost	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Shop	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr	O
Edward	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
pawned	O
to	O
Mr	O
Gimault	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Russel-Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
Mr	O
Gimault	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Piece	O
she	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Moore	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Goods	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
Ayres	O
's	O
Shop	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Piece	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willerton	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr	O
Ayres	O
;	O
I	O
measured	O
it	O
over	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Piece	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
our	O
Shop	O
before	O
she	O
brought	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Goods	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
might	O
bring	O
some	O
odd	O
trifling	O
Things	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
this	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
Thing	O
of	O
too	O
much	O
Consequence	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Person	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
Chancery-Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
A	O
Fellow-Servant	O
of	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
gave	O
her	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
unfortunately	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
Fellow-Servant	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
,	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Crushee	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
called	O
upon	O
her	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
Woman	O
brought	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
to	O
your	O
Daughter	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
at	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
come	O
Home	O
but	O
three	O
Days	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
Woman	O
has	O
brought	O
several	O
Things	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
her	O
bringing	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
to	O
your	O
Daughter	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
183.	O
James	B-pers
Guttery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
February	O
28	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
in	O
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Sidney-Alley	B-place
,	O
by	O
Leicester-Fields	B-place
Sidney-Alley	O
,	O
by	O
Leicester-Fields	O
''	O
/	O
>	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
Stockings	O
besides	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
lie	O
out	O
upon	O
a	O
Place	O
like	O
a	O
Bulk	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
Parcel	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
fourteen	O
Pair	O
;	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
Charlton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Shop	O
over-against	O
Mr	O
Carr	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lift	O
up	O
a	O
Blue	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
over	O
these	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
ragged	O
Sort	O
of	O
an	O
Apron	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Carr	O
,	O
Carr	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Fellow	O
has	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
Goods	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Body	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
.	O
-	O
Weldon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Bundle	O
that	O
he	O
dropped	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Carr	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
picked	O
the	O
Stockings	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
Time	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
take	O
Care	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
As	O
high	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
People	O
tried	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
a	O
Man	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
Stockings	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
184	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Baptist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Cripple	B-place
in	O
Walbrook	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
brought	O
the	O
Keys	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
kept	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Drawer	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Pearse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
suddled	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
one	O
Mr	O
-	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Mr	O
What	O
d	O
'ye	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Mr.	O
What	O
d	O
'ye	O
call	O
him	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
For	O
Mr	O
Matchin	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
afterwards	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
is	O
his	O
Name	O
?	O
however	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
Change	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
three	O
Guineas	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
surprized	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
paid	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Cook-Maid	O
up	O
first	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
strictly	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
Daughter	O
up	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
this	O
Girl	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
very	O
closely	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
Gold	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
cursed	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
damned	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Robinson	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Bowen	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
three	O
Guineas	O
of	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
Money	O
-	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
confess	O
this	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
unless	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Fright	O
-	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Waterman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
her	O
Uncle	O
kept	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
wrong	O
any	O
Body	O
-	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Witness	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Pearse	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
Because	O
her	O
Uncle	O
bid	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
Thing	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
nine	O
Days	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Person	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
185.	O
John	B-pers
Wynde	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calf's-Skin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Leake	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Remmington	I-pers
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Leake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
Calves-Skins	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
;	O
Mr	O
Remmington	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
Partners	O
in	O
Calves	O
all	O
the	O
whole	O
Summer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
into	O
the	O
Weight	O
of	O
my	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Fancy	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
Calf's-Skin	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
Hey	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
gone	O
the	O
same	O
Way	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
went	O
?	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Remmington	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
another	O
Skin	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
Tanners	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
my	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
one	O
Freeman	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Tanner	O
,	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
Skin	O
?	O
Leake	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
Skin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Colour	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Leake	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
White	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
call	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
only	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Spot	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Brownish	O
Colour	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mark	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Mark	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Remmington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Partner	O
with	O
Mr	O
Leake	O
in	O
this	O
Skin	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
this	O
Tanner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Skin	O
again	O
by	O
an	O
J.	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Hip	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
rob	O
Mr	O
Leake	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
Skin	O
you	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
Skin	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Tanner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
Calf's-Skin	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
that	O
Mr	O
Leake	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Yard	O
.	O
-	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Currier	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
-	O
as	O
a	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Theft	O
,	O
or	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
be	O
clear	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
again	O
To-morrow	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black	O
and	O
White-Court	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
:	O
Your	O
humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
-	O
Deval	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Currier	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
these	O
12	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Week	O
-	O
he	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
Turn-over	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Lad	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
trusted	O
him	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
over	O
then	O
?	O
Deval	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
offend	O
her	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Reason	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
my	O
parting	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Business	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Goods	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Currier	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Fact	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
22	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
last	O
January	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
17	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
Carruthers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
Victualler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Leake	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Skin	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
186.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloaths-Brush	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
Hair-Broom	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
d.	O
1	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Swine	O
's	O
Bristles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Thrum-Mop	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brush-Maker	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
Witness	O
is	O
my	O
Uncle	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloaths-Brush	O
,	O
a	O
Hair-Broom	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pound	O
of	O
Hog	O
's	O
Bristles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Brush-Maker	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
for	O
my	O
Uncle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
stole	O
those	O
Things	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
privy	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Long-Broom	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
have	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
all	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
15	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
an	O
Oath	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
swore	O
very	O
falsely	O
against	O
me	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Boy	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
lives	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
.	O
This	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
Mr	O
Read	O
's	O
had	O
lost	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
spoke	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
frightened	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
Mr	O
Read	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
lost	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
say	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
spoke	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
spoke	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
directly	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
my	O
Uncle	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
lose	O
it	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
Mr	O
Read	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Boy	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
losing	O
the	O
10	O
s.	O
-	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
frightened	O
at	O
his	O
losing	O
the	O
10	O
s.	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
about	O
18	O
Years	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Parents	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Turn-over	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
187.	O
Alice	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
China-Bason	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
,	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
China-Basons	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
Money	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
served	O
her	O
looked	O
another	O
Way	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
imagined	O
,	O
to	O
conceal	O
one	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
China-Shop	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
served	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
Things	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
China-Dish	O
.	O
My	O
Bason	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
China-Bason	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
:	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Bason	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Bason	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Casebury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
China-Bason	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bundle	O
;	O
this	O
looks	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
that	O
Bason	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Pattern	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Casebury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs	O
Ashbourner	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
China-Shop	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Mr	O
Vere	O
's	O
:	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
Dinner	O
except	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Bundle	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
her	O
Bundle	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Bason	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bundle	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Mob	O
brought	O
her	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
which	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
our	O
Man	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
Bason	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knows	O
his	O
Mark	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
locked	O
this	O
Bason	O
up	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
Casebury	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
China-Basons	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
two	O
Basons	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
Price	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
generally	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
One	O
at	O
17	O
d.	O
I	O
bid	O
14	O
d.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
14	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
served	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
China-Woman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Bason	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
15	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
Plate	O
which	O
was	O
like	O
that	O
:	O
Pray	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
sell	O
these	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
sell	O
China	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
?	O
Vere	O
.	O
Very	O
frequently	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sold	O
any	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
visiting	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
ill.	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
this	O
Alice	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
her	O
Children	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Work	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
this	O
Basket-Woman	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
some	O
China	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Enamelled	O
China	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
shewed	O
her	O
this	O
Bason	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
selling	O
Price	O
was	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
less	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Alice	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
China	O
To-day	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
little	O
disguised	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
break	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pay	O
15	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
Bason	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
this	O
Day	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
Landskip	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
Spot	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Bason	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Bason	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
Pattern	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Bason	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Pattern	O
,	O
white	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
blue	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
as	O
that	O
is	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Tower-Hill	O
with	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
(	O
Mrs	O
Mackenzie	O
)	O
and	O
met	O
Alice	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
China	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
till	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
disobliging	O
a	O
Friend	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
Bason	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
China	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
Bason	O
?	O
Tipper	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
this	O
Pattern	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
Evidence	O
did	O
hardly	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Bason	O
)	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Innys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
at	O
Quilting	O
and	O
Mantua-Making	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
from	O
six	O
to	O
six	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
valuable	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
wrong	O
any	O
Body	O
of	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
China	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
broke	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
industrious	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
gets	O
up	O
early	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mr	O
-	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
Liberty	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
and	O
honourably	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
looked	O
after	O
my	O
Wife	O
in	O
Lyings-in	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
I	O
am	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
Living	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
Undertaker	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Mr	O
Vere	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
sell	O
any	O
Basons	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Vere	O
.	O
No	O
Bason	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
was	O
sold	O
that	O
Day	O
either	O
by	O
me	O
or	O
my	O
Servants	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Bason	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
buy	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Fortman	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
Women	O
who	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Business	O
they	O
follow	O
?	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Milliner	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
facing	O
a	O
Cheese-Monger	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
ever	O
since	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Silk-Soowerer	O
lives	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Apartment	O
;	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
House	O
is	O
it	O
at	O
?	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
He	O
dresses	O
Dolls	O
for	O
the	O
Shops	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
frightened	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
speak	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Innys	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
Black-Swan-Court	O
now	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Reed	O
's	O
House	O
Guilty	O
.	O
+	O
Alice	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
China	O
Dish	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ashbourner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ashbourner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
enamelled	O
China	O
Plates	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Back	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
them	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Price	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
too	O
dear	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
less	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
cheaper	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
broke	O
three	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
said	O
they	O
cost	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
give	O
the	O
four	O
Shillings	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
she	O
stood	O
humming	O
and	O
hawing	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stir	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Good	O
Woman	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
look	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Prithee	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
espied	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
something	O
of	O
China	O
;	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
she	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
somewhere	O
else	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Steps	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
So	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
own	O
Dish	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
frightened	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Oh	O
,	O
you	O
Bold	O
Face	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Dish	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
Bold-Face	O
has	O
stole	O
my	O
Dish	O
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Dish	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Dish	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
Cloak	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
Says	O
some	O
Body	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
nothing	O
else	O
?	O
Says	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Pastry-Cook	O
's	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
of	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Bason	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Dish	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Dish	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
no	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
covering	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Short-Cloak	O
fell	O
down	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
my	O
Dish	O
?	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Ladies	O
of	O
Quality	O
that	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
188.	O
James	B-pers
Musket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Botolph-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
26	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
27th	O
or	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Botolph's-Wharf	B-place
Gate-Way	I-place
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Sugar	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
besides	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
no	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Pocket	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
Sugar	O
would	O
have	O
fell	O
through	O
between	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
far	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
or	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
rustical	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Cart	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
acknowledge	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
mastered	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Sugar	O
under	O
Botolph's-Wharf	O
Gateway	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
goes	O
about	O
the	O
Keys	O
to	O
pilfer	O
what	O
he	O
can	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Practices	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
that	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
The	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Servants	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Casks	O
for	O
Samples	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
apprehend	O
they	O
might	O
leave	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
189	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Mackay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Cambrick	O
Stocks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dairymple	I-pers
.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
six	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
Oswald	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
picking	O
up	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
searched	O
;	O
the	O
Servants	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
what	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Press	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
an	O
upper	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Oswald	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
wore	O
a	O
Livery	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
;	O
that	O
Cane	O
and	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Scrutiny	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Lowrie	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Master	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
a	O
Shirt	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
put	O
in	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Press	O
in	O
the	O
Dining-Room	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Shirts	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
Dr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Physic	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cane	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
belonging	O
to	O
Dr	O
Dalrymple	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Allen	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
Shirt	O
is	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
's	O
;	O
this	O
belongs	O
to	O
Dr	O
Dalrymple	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Shirt	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
New	B-place
Berwick-street	I-place
by	O
Soho-square	B-place
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
Dr	O
Robert	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
where	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
Body	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
but	O
himself	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Canes	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
Mr	O
Allen	O
's	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
Footman	O
's	O
;	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
with	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Shirt	O
of	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
numbered	O
and	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
D	O
the	O
Name	O
is	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
put	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Cane	O
of	O
Mr	O
Charles	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-Smith	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
where	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Hand	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
Forgiveness	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
all	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
left	O
carelessly	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
Rooms	O
where	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
shifted	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
be	O
moved	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
present	O
Master	O
is	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
appeared	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
190	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Cart-Wheels	O
,	O
with	O
Iron	O
Streaks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
December	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
N.	O
B.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
try	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
152.	O
William	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Wheelwright	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Night	O
between	O
the	O
Sixth	O
and	O
the	O
Seventh	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
Cart-Wheels	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Premises	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
called	O
Bagnell's-Marsh	O
,	O
by	O
Black-Mary's-Hole	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
my	O
Man	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Wood	O
burning	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
Wood	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Wheels	O
knocked	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
laid	O
down	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
Wheels	O
-	O
one	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
good	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
having	O
lost	O
some	O
Wheels	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
track	O
the	O
Wheels	O
;	O
we	O
tracked	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
forward	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
the	O
Spokes	O
of	O
the	O
Wheels	O
upon	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
Mr	O
Sims	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
should	O
take	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr	O
Clarke	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
you	O
be	O
a	O
Scandal	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Iron	O
Streakes	O
of	O
the	O
Wheels	O
which	O
were	O
knocked	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Marks	O
upon	O
the	O
Streakes	O
which	O
my	O
Master	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
Streakes	O
belonged	O
to	O
your	O
Master	O
?	O
Grub	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Wheels	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
my	O
Oath	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
your	O
Lordship	O
-	O
one	O
belongs	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
belongs	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
a	O
Hog-Butcher	O
,	O
(	O
calling	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
)	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
these	O
Wheels	O
were	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Grub	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Master	B-place
's	I-place
Back-Yard	I-place
,	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
it	O
lies	O
next	O
the	O
Fields	O
:	O
-	O
We	O
were	O
guided	O
by	O
the	O
Tracks	O
of	O
the	O
Wheels	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Tracks	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Wheels	O
.	O
Sims	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Tracks	O
from	O
my	O
very	O
Gate	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Gate	O
in	O
my	O
Yard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mine	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Fence	O
,	O
any	O
Body	O
might	O
bring	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Sims	O
.	O
The	O
Stable	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
opens	O
to	O
this	O
open	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
or	O
open	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
did	O
put	O
something	O
upon	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
prosecute	O
him	O
sooner	O
?	O
Sims	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
light	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Letter	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
desiring	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Wheels	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
have	O
Compassion	O
on	O
his	O
Children	O
.	O
-	O
Grub	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
mention	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
I	O
was	O
suddled	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
Thing	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
accustom	O
myself	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Maid	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hired	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
that	O
Night	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
-	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
the	O
Wheels	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Night	O
when	O
the	O
Wheels	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Maid	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
-	O
my	O
Master	O
did	O
not	O
continue	O
in	O
Bed	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
he	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
without	O
your	O
knowing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
was	O
sick	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Child	O
-	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
before	O
Mr	O
Sims	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Wheels	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Wheels	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
seven	O
small	O
Children	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
says	O
one	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
trusted	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Sims	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Wheels	O
about	O
Eight	O
or	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
Girl	O
was	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
then	O
,	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Child	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
can	O
very	O
well	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
191	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sanfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ruslip	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
++	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
Linnen	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
12	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
check	O
'd	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Short-Cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen-Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
robbing	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Day-Time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
is	O
made	O
a	O
Capital	O
Offence	O
,	O
by	O
39	O
Eli	O
.	O
t.	O
15	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
an	O
actual	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ruslip	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
my	O
House	O
open	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Twelve	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
Work	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
Farm-Yard	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
with	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
again	O
she	O
was	O
loaded	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
lodge	O
Travellers	O
,	O
at	O
Westhide	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Outhouse	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Bundle	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
Things	O
;	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Bacon	O
,	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Butter	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Hertford	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Weatherly	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Glass-Light	O
:	O
The	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
Lead	O
were	O
turned	O
up	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
These	O
two	O
Men	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Bacon	O
)	O
.	O
Mr	O
Ashley	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
,	O
is	O
my	O
Gardener	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
catched	O
her	O
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
out	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr	O
Capper	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
Confession	O
and	O
signed	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Capper	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
Masterman	O
has	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Stroler	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
192.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Copper-Sauce-pan	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Copper-Cover	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
King	B-place
Henry	I-place
the	I-place
VIII	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Andrew's-street	I-place
,	O
by	O
the	B-place
Seven-Dials	I-place
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Wife	O
take	O
the	O
Sauce-pan	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
broil	O
them	O
some	O
Steakes	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
eat	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
the	O
Sauce-pan	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Sauce-pan	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
to	O
boil	O
a	O
Scrag	O
of	O
Mutton	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
uses	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
Husband	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Woodward	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
not	O
stay	O
you	O
drunken	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
come	O
here	O
but	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
must	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
Meat	O
is	O
ready	O
:	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
the	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
Meat	O
on	O
the	O
Gridiron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Meat	O
was	O
eating	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
what	O
I	O
owed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Husband	O
owed	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
193.	O
John	B-pers
Darke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
China	O
Mugs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dame	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Codrington	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Leaf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
China	O
Mugs	O
from	O
my	O
Lady	O
Codrington	O
's	O
,	O
this	O
Boy	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
afterwards	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Mugs	O
from	O
my	O
Lady	O
Codrington	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
never	O
owned	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
something	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lady	O
's	O
Footman	O
saw	O
them	O
standing	O
upon	O
Mr	O
Allen	O
's	O
Beauset	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
with	O
what	O
Design	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
own	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
stood	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
in	O
publick	O
View	O
,	O
above	O
twelve	O
Months	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
discovered	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Age	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
my	O
Age	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
poor	O
Jack	O
!	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
194	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Case	O
for	O
Knives	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
twelve	O
Silver-handled	O
Knives	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
twelve	O
Forks	O
,	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
Another	O
Case	O
for	O
Knives	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
small	O
Silver-handled	O
Knives	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
six	O
small	O
Forks	O
,	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
small	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
February	O
28	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
Seven	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Boy	O
loitering	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
step	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Windows	O
below	O
Stairs	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Cases	O
of	O
Silver-handled	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
stand	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
two	O
Cases	O
of	O
Silver-handled	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
Lamps	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
open	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
threatened	O
to	O
beat	O
this	O
Boy	O
because	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
discover	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Somers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
of	O
so	O
tender	O
Years	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Mr	O
Hammond	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
by	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
by	O
Eight	O
.	O
Mr	O
Hammond	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
then	O
wanted	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
Seven	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
195	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
dozen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Steel	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
dozen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bath-Metal	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Feet	O
for	O
Stove-Grates	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Brass	O
Knob	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
December	O
8	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Front	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Frame	O
)	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Shutters	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
were	O
removed	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Places	O
.	O
My	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Rogues	O
being	O
disturbed	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
they	O
moved	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Shop	O
quite	O
shut	O
up	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Hatch	O
to	O
prevent	O
People	O
from	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
in	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
of	O
Mr	O
Harding	O
,	O
a	O
Brasier	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
about	O
twenty	O
Papers	O
of	O
Buckles	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
both	O
Bath-Metal	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Steel	O
Buckles	O
;	O
several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
round	O
Brass	O
Thing	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
about	O
seven	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Brass	O
Feet	O
for	O
Stove	O
Grates	O
.	O
I	O
cracked	O
the	O
Glass	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushed	O
the	O
Glass	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
?	O
Shields	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
:	O
We	O
put	O
our	O
Arms	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
Home	O
with	O
an	O
Apron	O
full	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
for	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Part	O
had	O
I	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Shields	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
but	O
five	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
us	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
one	O
Parcel	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Parcel	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
;	O
we	O
sunk	O
that	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
hard	O
working	O
Lad	O
,	O
only	O
they	O
drew	O
me	O
into	O
their	O
Company	O
.	O
-	O
Unwin	O
.	O
After	O
David	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
,	O
this	O
Fellow	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
lodged	O
at	O
Johnson	O
's	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
just	O
now	O
discharged	O
;	O
and	O
happening	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
I	O
caught	O
you	O
at	O
last	O
?	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
deserved	O
me	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
;	O
you	O
touched	O
me	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
sought	O
after	O
me	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
catch	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Way	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
his	O
constant	O
Practice	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
thieving	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Way	O
of	O
living	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
committing	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
grand	O
Thief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
gets	O
his	O
Living	O
by	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
by	O
Thief-taking	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
poor	O
Fellow	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
change	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Unwin	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
clapped	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Mr	O
Harman	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Mr	O
Unwin	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
deserved	O
me	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Failer	O
.	O
But	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
Shields	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
mentioned	O
then	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Jack	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
after	O
Mr	O
Unwin	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
poor	O
Creature	O
thinks	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swear	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Josias	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
26	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Josias	O
Taylor	O
,	O
November	O
16	O
.	O
Josias	O
Taylor	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Business	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
ordered	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
to	O
hang	O
the	O
Doors	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
ready	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Doors	O
were	O
shut	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Sash-Window	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Grates	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
120	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
stamped	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
on	O
which	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
damp	O
when	O
it	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
Office	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
lay	O
about	O
two	O
Foot	O
from	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
My	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
heading	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Barrels	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
fall	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
heading	O
of	O
the	O
Barrels	O
that	O
might	O
have	O
disturbed	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Man	O
presently	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
26	O
Pound	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Grate	O
was	O
likewise	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Coachman	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	O
Inn	O
,	O
his	O
Horses	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Grate	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Coachman	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Inn-Yard	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
seeing	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
People	O
looking	O
at	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Grate	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Inn-Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Chocolate	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
for	O
26	O
Shillings	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Nick-Name	O
of	O
Cutos	O
,	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
that	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
's	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
shoved	O
up	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
26	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Pound	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
the	O
Grate	O
down	O
?	O
Shields	O
.	O
This	O
Cutos	O
and	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
pulled	O
it	O
down	O
by	O
main	O
Strength	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
heavy	O
that	O
one	O
could	O
not	O
lift	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
six	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
a	O
Piece	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
his	O
six	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
196	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meckwold	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meckwold	I-pers
to	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meckwold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great-Russel-Street	B-place
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
from	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
indicted	O
,	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
rescued	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
taken	O
again	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
flagitious	O
Gang	O
,	O
the	O
Colonel	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
committed	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
that	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour-Window	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Meckwold	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
shut	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Blind	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Fellow-Servant	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
close	O
all	O
Day	O
long	O
,	O
was	O
pushed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Blind	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Lodger	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr	O
Meckwold	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
after	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
being	O
disposed	O
in	O
a	O
lazy	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Condition	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
(	O
the	O
Moon	O
shone	O
bright	O
on	O
that	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Day	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
and	O
another	O
consulting	O
together	O
and	O
looking	O
hard	O
at	O
Mr	O
Meckwold	O
's	O
Window	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
Sash	O
being	O
then	O
up	O
)	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
young	O
Men	O
who	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
Mr	O
Meckwold	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
set	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Shove	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
about	O
ten	O
Doors	O
farther	O
to	O
another	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
stood	O
consulting	O
again	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Hurry	O
in	O
passing	O
and	O
repassing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
Companion	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Window	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
and	O
then	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
passed	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
passing	O
or	O
repassing	O
)	O
he	O
jumps	O
on	O
the	O
Rail	O
before	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
over	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Blind	O
-	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
up	O
so	O
high	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
put	O
your	O
Hand	O
over	O
the	O
Blind	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
Hand	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
bid	O
me	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
call	O
out	O
;	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
a	O
Journyman	O
,	O
who	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
and	O
secure	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Rail	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
on	O
our	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Richard	O
,	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
our	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
upon	O
us	O
almost	O
ready	O
to	O
devour	O
us	O
,	O
Richard	O
was	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
Richard	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr	O
Meckwold	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
and	O
immediately	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
past	O
,	O
he	O
jumped	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Rail	O
,	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Blind	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Arms	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
directly	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jumped	O
off	O
the	O
Rail	O
and	O
crossed	O
to	O
our	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Arms	O
into	O
Mr	O
Meckwold	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
trimming	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Lamp	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
over	O
the	O
Rail	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
now	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
following	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
out	O
comes	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Loose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
whipp	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
Truncheon	O
to	O
defend	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
one	O
took	O
to	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
Manmouth-Street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
got	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
tumbling	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
How	O
is	O
this	O
Blind	O
fastened	O
?	O
Smart	O
.	O
The	O
Blind	O
is	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Bolt	O
which	O
shoots	O
into	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
at	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
?	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
all	O
Day	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sensible	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
Lady	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
;	O
I	O
bolted	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
had	O
unbolted	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Meckwold	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Thing	O
lost	O
or	O
moved	O
?	O
Mr	O
Meckwold	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Tea-Chest	O
moved	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
far	O
in	O
as	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
Arms	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
reach	O
the	O
Ground	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
His	O
Arms	O
and	O
Head	O
and	O
Shoulders	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
reached	O
down	O
and	O
:	O
put	O
the	O
Blind	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
was	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
Whether	O
the	O
Blind	O
was	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Sash	O
?	O
Goddard	O
.	O
The	O
Sash	O
and	O
the	O
Blind	O
are	O
different	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Blind	O
is	O
fixed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sash	O
may	O
be	O
pushed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blind	O
remain	O
fixed	O
;	O
the	O
Blind	O
is	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
Bolt	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Blind	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
Question	O
is	O
,	O
Whether	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
pushed	O
the	O
Sash	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Blind	O
must	O
not	O
fall	O
down	O
.	O
Goddard	O
.	O
It	O
can	O
not	O
fall	O
by	O
the	O
lifting	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
Sash	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
stood	O
safe	O
against	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Blind	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
?	O
Goddard	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
might	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
stood	O
very	O
safe	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
He	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Rail	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
one	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Hand	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Blind	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
too	O
k	O
the	O
Blind	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Reach	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
over	O
the	O
Window	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Blind	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
197	O
,	O
198.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland-Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Caslo	I-pers
n	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Caslon	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Sheets	O
are	O
my	O
Property	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
my	O
Washerwoman	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
out	O
Bills	O
among	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
Sheets	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
quite	O
dry	O
I	O
hung	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Day	O
we	O
sent	O
some	O
Bills	O
out	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strater	I-pers
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
brought	O
these	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
Whether	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Barnard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Mr	O
Caslon	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
Mr	O
Caslon	O
's	O
Sheets	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
out	O
a-drying	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
brought	O
this	O
Sheet	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
them	O
five	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
This	O
Sheet	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr	O
Caslon	O
.	O
-	O
Atkins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
24	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
by	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
Dishonour	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
and	O
another	O
,	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
several	O
Years	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Freeman	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
honest	O
Persons	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Daughter	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
this	O
Sheet	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
Hunt	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Paper	O
to	O
caution	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
before	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
it	O
was	O
entered	O
in	O
?	O
Coxon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
entered	O
in	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
old	O
one	O
if	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
Sarah	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
through	O
her	O
Means	O
.	O
Q.	O
Supposing	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
had	O
come	O
,	O
could	O
she	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Crown	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
Alice	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanne	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
200.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
Man	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
Flannel	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
What	O
Sort	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
low	O
Sort	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Price	O
was	O
10	O
d.	O
per	O
Yard	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
something	O
lower	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Sort	O
lower	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Groat	O
a	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
double	O
the	O
Price	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
that	O
Price	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Cloaths-Man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Monument-Alehouse	O
in	O
East-Cheap	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Women	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
Flannel	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
were	O
my	O
Goods	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs	O
Harris	O
to	O
Mr	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
White-Lion-Alehouse	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
this	O
Brown	O
:	O
Says	O
Mrs	O
Harris	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
Brown	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
Mr	O
James	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
:	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
sold	O
Flannel	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
Rate	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
flew	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Mr	O
Constable	O
,	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Door	O
a	O
little	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
were	O
4	O
Remnants	O
of	O
Flannel	O
with	O
my	O
Mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
contain	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Judgment	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
each	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
Mr	O
James	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Brown	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Mr	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
Mr	O
James	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
Brown	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
resolved	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
smoak	O
a	O
Pipe	O
till	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
was	O
at	O
Leisure	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White-Lion-Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
these	O
Flannels	O
somewhere	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
honest	O
Answer	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Pray	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
plainly	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
for	O
Answer	B-pers
,	O
D	B-pers
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
that	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Business	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Jail	O
rather	O
than	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Jail	O
;	O
for	O
these	O
Things	O
have	O
been	O
pretty	O
frequently	O
practised	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
resolved	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
from	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Flannels	O
chiefly	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
very	O
few	O
which	O
come	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
Correspondent	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
Lancashirt	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Lord	O
threatening	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
commit	O
me	O
to	O
Jail	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
Truth	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
being	O
sensible	O
of	O
his	O
Guilt	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
Tears	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
Pieces	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
this	O
Brown	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
15	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
worth	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
d.	O
per	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
about	O
Eight-pence	O
half-penny	O
per	O
Yard	O
;	O
the	O
lowest	O
priced	O
Flannel	O
we	O
have	O
is	O
Eight-pence	O
half-penny	O
per	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Goods	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
never	O
sell	O
any	O
Goods	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Staples	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
Goods	O
for	O
me	O
sometimes	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knows	O
very	O
well	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
that	O
Flannel	O
of	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
showed	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Price	O
did	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
different	O
Prices	O
,	O
sometimes	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
Seven-pence	O
or	O
Seven-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
never	O
less	O
than	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
damaged	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
a	O
Groat	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
got	O
above	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
by	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
says	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
Brown	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
mistaken	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White-Lion	O
Tavern	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
says	O
Brown	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
And	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
of	O
some	O
Body	O
that	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
my	O
Part	O
,	O
I	O
buy	O
Goods	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
comes	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
your	O
Man	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Goods	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
Goods	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Brown	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
these	O
Goods	O
from	O
Ireland	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Mention	O
made	O
of	O
any	O
particular	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Lancashire	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
Piece	O
out	O
of	O
Lancashire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
's	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
these	O
been	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
in	O
your	O
Custody	O
?	O
Mr	O
James	O
produced	O
the	O
Flannels	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
proved	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
Felony	O
upon	O
the	O
Principal	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
201.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
large	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Lyddall	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lyddall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Executor	O
to	O
one	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Rhodes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
Freehold	O
and	O
personal	O
Estate	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wishart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
Johnson	O
's	O
Custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
Distribution	O
of	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Estate	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Lyddall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
distributed	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
Property	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Lyddall	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Property	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
Executor	O
,	O
on	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Legatees	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Ring	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Ring	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
divided	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Coachman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
several	O
Publick-Houses	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
appear	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Wishart	I-pers
to	O
lock	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Bed-Chamber	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
eight	O
Nights	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
supposed	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Ring	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
unlocked	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Ring	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
now	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
this	O
Spoon	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
changed	O
at	O
the	O
Silver-Smith	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
two	O
new	O
Spoons	O
and	O
my	O
Ring	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
with	O
the	O
Silver-Smith	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
him	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
.	O
This	O
Spoon	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Spoon	O
by	O
his	O
Direction	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wishart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
that	O
Handkerchief	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
Jenny	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
(	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
Lye	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
)	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
If	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
is	O
lost	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
has	O
picked	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
to	O
use	O
;	O
the	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Drawer	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
took	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
Tea-Spoons	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
Madam	O
?	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
you	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Ring	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
these	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
or	O
better	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Three-pence	O
difference	O
,	O
between	O
his	O
old	O
Plate	O
and	O
my	O
new	O
Spoons	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
my	O
Wife	O
should	O
not	O
like	O
these	O
Spoons	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
change	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Spoons	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Wishart	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr	O
Johnson	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr	O
Birch	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
lie	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
Words	O
which	O
occasioned	O
a	O
Difference	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
As	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
Things	O
which	O
are	O
left	O
between	O
Molly	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
these	O
Spoons	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
out-right	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
out-right	O
without	O
his	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Johnson	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
any	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
gave	O
him	O
any	O
Leave	O
to	O
use	O
,	O
or	O
exchange	O
,	O
or	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
upon	O
any	O
Account	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
202	O
,	O
203	O
.	O
+	O
