TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
4th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WESTLEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Copper	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stockall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Seagrave	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Linsey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pepiat	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Warneck	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rude	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Spier	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Lott	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Periam	O
Wright	O
.	O
+	O
184.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
5	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
checker	O
'd	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
velvet	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
bible	O
,	O
common	O
prayer	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
book	O
called	O
a	O
New	O
Year	O
's	O
Gift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Euston	I-pers
,	O
then	O
spinster	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
185	O
.	O
And	O
Martha	B-pers
Page	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lascelles	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
for	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Peruke-makers	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
remained	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Martha	B-pers
Page	I-pers
's	O
lodgings	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
)	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
cambrick	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
and	O
the	O
velvet	O
hood	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
spoon	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
carried	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Spotted	O
Dog	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cambrick	O
apron	O
,	O
at	O
Daniel	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
's	O
a	O
slop-shop	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
found	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
at	O
a	O
snuff-shop	O
in	O
Ailesbury-Street	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Page	I-pers
said	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
sent	O
it	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
spotted	O
Dog	O
at	O
Islington	O
at	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Page	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
proved	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
as	O
mentioned	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
is	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Page	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
186	O
,	O
187	O
,	O
188.	O
James	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Amias	B-pers
King	I-pers
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
++	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
guns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scales	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
hand	O
saw	O
,	O
two	O
planes	O
and	O
other	O
carpenter	O
's	O
tools	O
,	O
a	O
pail	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
bars	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
kitchen	O
grate	O
,	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
++	O
Breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
a	O
dwelling	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
is	O
Death	O
.	O
Amias	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
my	O
house	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
was	O
likewise	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
guns	O
,	O
some	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
tools	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
)	O
-	O
Gregory	O
confessed	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
one	O
Dyer	O
,	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
Hayes	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
twice	O
,	O
once	O
was	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
pail	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
Gregory	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
or	O
nine	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
this	O
gun	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
4	O
s.	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Amias	O
King	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
gun	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
:	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
grates	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
penny	O
per	O
pound	O
for	O
them	O
-	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
7	O
s.	O
11	O
d.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
afterwards	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
grates	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
worked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Constable	O
)	O
.	O
Gregory	O
owned	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
twice	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
January	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
time	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
-	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
Robinson	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Gregory	O
,	O
Hayes	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Dyer	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
)	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
Hayes	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
concerned	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
pail	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Gregory	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Robinson	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Hayes	O
*	O
acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
indictment	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
Hayes	O
's	O
being	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
189.	O
Ann	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Plimpton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Plimpton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
sheet	O
and	O
blanket	O
;	O
the	O
sheet	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Nettles	O
,	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
190.	O
Sarah	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
ells	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
dowlas	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
;	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Capon	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
new	O
cloth	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
morning	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
by	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Gate	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Old	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
new	O
cloth	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
English	I-pers
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
new	O
cloth	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
new	O
cloth	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
aprons	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Capon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
child	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
new	O
cloth	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
farther	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
getting	O
a	O
spinning-wheel	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
-	O
she	O
pledged	O
them	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
191	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
pers	O
on	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
three	O
pound	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
-	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
Minton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
passage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Minton	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
-	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Minton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
three	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
cellar	O
over	O
against	O
Somerset-house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Minton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
it	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
purse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
*	O
by	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
?	O
*	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
private	O
soldier	O
.	O
Minton	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
tea	O
that	O
was	O
seized	O
in	O
a	O
barn	O
at	O
Camberwell	O
belonging	O
to	O
smugglers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
your	O
other	O
companion	O
?	O
Minton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
you	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Minton	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
-	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Wolsenden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
on	O
Easter	O
Eve	O
(	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
)	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
Minton	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
familiarly	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
robbed	O
such	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
nothing	O
we	O
can	O
have	O
nothing	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
from	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
respect	O
of	O
persons	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
farther	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
herself	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
turn	O
evidence	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
what	O
money	O
she	O
had	O
?	O
Wolsenden	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
three-pound-twelve	O
,	O
a	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
moidore	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
silver	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
herself	O
and	O
two	O
accomplices	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
left	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pawn	O
her	O
cloak	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
gone	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
accomplices	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
clothed	O
with	O
that	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
her	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
spent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
Minton	O
?	O
Wolfenden	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
in	O
particular	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
what	O
signifies	O
talking	O
,	O
the	O
truth	O
is	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
condition	O
was	O
she	O
in	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
you	O
this	O
story	O
?	O
Wolsenden	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
half	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
one	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
never	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
till	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Wolfenden	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
dogged	O
the	O
man	O
from	O
that	O
cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
into	O
broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
192.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tuffman	I-pers
;	O
two	O
frocks	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bainbridge	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bainbridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
attended	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
sickness	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
goods	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
frocks	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
frocks	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bainbridge	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
this	O
woman	O
as	O
a	O
nurse	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
petticoat	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Bugden	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bugden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
Mrs.	O
Bainbridge	O
's	O
petticoat	O
off	O
her	O
own	O
back	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
deliver	O
Mrs.	O
Bainbridge	O
's	O
petticoat	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Bugden	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bainbridge	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
petticoat	O
off	O
her	O
back	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Aswell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bainbridge	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
two	O
frocks	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
pawning	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
get	O
them	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
delivered	O
a	O
frock	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
rest	O
without	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
paid	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
lives	O
in	O
Plumbtree	O
street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
with	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bainbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
cloak	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloak	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
that	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
193.	O
David	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
checker	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
quilted	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Tennant	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Tennant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cellar	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
sell	O
linen	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
snatched	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
something	O
snatched	O
away	O
,	O
run	O
up	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Tennant	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
finding	O
himself	O
discovered	O
,	O
dropped	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
fell	O
all	O
along	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
assisted	O
me	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
before	O
he	O
fell	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
tumbled	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lying	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Simpson	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
bundle	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
bundle	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
under	O
your	O
arm	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
(	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
being	O
offered	O
the	O
book	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
swear	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
[	O
Sarah	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
in	O
Sheer-lane	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
button-shop	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
six	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ball	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
now	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
now	O
:	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
now	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
can	O
appear	O
to	O
his	O
honesty	O
;	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
his	O
dishonesty	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
has	O
had	O
her	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
194.	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hens	O
,	O
price	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cock	O
,	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Appleyard	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
fowls	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
-	O
in	O
Cary	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
with	O
the	O
fowls	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
-	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Francis	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Widham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
who	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
with	O
some	O
fowls	O
in	O
a	O
creel	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Widham	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Go	O
nearer	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
?	O
[	O
He	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
views	O
him	O
earnestly	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
.	O
]	O
Widham	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
looks	O
like	O
him	O
-	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
195.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sattin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
petticoat	O
hung	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
for	O
sale	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
by	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Justice	O
have	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
to	O
be	O
lashed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
oblige	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
196	O
.	O
+	O
Susanna	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Jefferies	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
muslin	O
hoods	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
dimitty	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Susanna	B-pers
Read	I-pers
Elius	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
her	O
Elius	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
two	O
names	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
rent	O
ten	O
pound	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
Leicester-Street	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
gone	O
:	O
before	O
she	O
could	O
come	O
to	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
front-door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
door	O
and	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
key	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
-	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
bolted	O
herself	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dorrington	O
,	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
ladder	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
barred	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
fore-door	O
drawn	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
bent	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
The	O
staple	O
was	O
forced	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
gave	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
only	O
myself	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
.	O
-	O
Smith	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
car	O
.	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny-worth	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
You	O
bitch	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
that	O
blanket	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
bundle	O
is	O
altered	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
sheet	O
then	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
You	O
bitch	O
these	O
things	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
Robinson	O
's	O
goods	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
saw	O
Robinson	O
's	O
wife	O
's	O
cloak	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
cloak	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
neighbour	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
overagainst	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Smith	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
bundle	O
opened	O
before	O
Thomas	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
it	O
was	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
bundle	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
every	O
particular	O
thing	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
bring	O
any	O
other	O
bundle	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thomas	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
cloak	O
she	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
upon	O
Robinson	O
's	O
wife	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Robinson	O
's	O
wife	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
lately	O
dead	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
bailiff	O
's	O
follower	O
and	O
a	O
thief	O
taker	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
whose	O
life	O
you	O
take	O
away	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Joiner	O
by	O
trade	O
[	O
Thomas	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
hanged	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
Robinson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
where	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
answered	O
:	O
when	O
Robinson	O
found	O
his	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
could	O
serve	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
girl	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
often	O
push	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
times	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
his	O
daughter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
in	O
Liquorpond-street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Robinson	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
pawned	O
many	O
a	O
thing	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
daughter	O
gave	O
them	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
suffer	O
for	O
all	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
daughter	O
live	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
at	O
service	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
where	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
key	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
key	O
nor	O
could	O
she	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Your	O
daughter	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
acquainted	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
not	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kicked	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
vile	O
creature	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
197.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Callen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cosby	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cosby	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
stopped	O
it	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
)	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
property	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
nurse	O
keeping	O
at	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
at	O
Tottenham-court	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
call	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
hesitate	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
brought	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
coming	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cosby	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
198.	O
Mary	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
January	O
30	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bernard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
nurse-keeping	O
,	O
and	O
nursed	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bernard	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
frock	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
again	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Granger	O
's	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
had	O
not	O
brought	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Granger	O
's	O
and	O
asked	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
3	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
words	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
200.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
March	O
20	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stepped	O
with	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Hill	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
lid	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Finding	O
it	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
by	O
force	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
some	O
questions	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
but	O
very	O
indifferent	O
answers	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
search	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
very	O
readily	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
search	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
tankard	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Clarke	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
that	O
was	O
published	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
tankard	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
's	O
the	O
tankard	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
advertisement	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
tankard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
gentleman	O
so	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
confess	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
safe	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
says	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Goal	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
201.	O
Henry	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
mittins	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
;	O
and	O
202.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
was	O
my	O
shop-boy	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
suspected	O
him	O
of	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
24th	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
carrying	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
's	O
drawers	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
childrens	O
stockings	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
legs	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
knit	O
hose	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
mittins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boys	O
worsted	O
hose	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
immediately	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
child	O
him	O
for	O
bringing	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Creed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
carried	O
these	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
she	O
checked	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
Goodman	O
's	O
drawers	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Broadhent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
her	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
What	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Broadbent	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
senses	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
girl	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hamlin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
;	O
she	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
roast	O
pork	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
her	O
husband	O
lived	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
guilty	O
;	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
Margaret	O
*	O
Goodman	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Goodman	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
very	O
heartily	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
order	O
her	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
an	O
offence	O
against	O
a	O
statute	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
it	O
Transportation	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
absolutely	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
could	O
not	O
grant	O
it	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Redman	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Redman	O
White	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Holford	B-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
in	O
for	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
quarterns	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
there	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
drunk	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
house	O
as	O
that	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
my	O
things	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
one	O
knee	O
buckle	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
servants	O
or	O
people	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
that	O
knee	O
buckle	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
-	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
stock	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
and	O
hat	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
all	O
except	O
my	O
wig	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
nothing	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
pledged	O
the	O
knee	O
buckles	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
servants	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
she	O
received	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
March	O
18	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
by	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
White	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
-	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
complaints	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
then	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
executed	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
every	O
article	O
except	O
either	O
the	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
indulge	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Constable	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
show	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
a	O
brick	O
in	O
her	O
cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
brick	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
brick	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
what	O
Sullivan	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
things	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
knee	O
buckles	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
a	O
brick	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
hers	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
Besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
girls	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
204.	O
Martha	B-pers
Lardoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Delafontaine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
Febr	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Delafontaine	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
last	O
February	O
,	O
lay	O
there	O
but	O
two	O
nights	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
sheets	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
my	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mussel	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
sheets	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
I	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
only	O
as	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
child	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
205.	O
James	B-pers
McDonald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	B-place
and	I-place
Hounds	I-place
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
pretty	O
late	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
up	O
very	O
still	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
noise	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
kick	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
John	O
in	O
Holloway-lane	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
landlord	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
yes	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
beef	O
stakes	O
and	O
was	O
eating	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
pawned	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckle	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
where	O
my	O
buckles	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
buckles	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
[	O
a	O
large	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
.	O
]	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
stuck	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
buckles	O
under	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
that	O
nobody	O
should	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Holloway	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
so	O
still	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
hear	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bundock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
John	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
paid	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
buckle	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
those	O
three	O
buckles	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
first	O
?	O
Holloway	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
first	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Holloway	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
kick	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
ways	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
lie	O
in	O
London	O
once	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
206.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
from	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
at	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Cross	O
in	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
upon	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Hinman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
two-pence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
quarterns	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
for	O
selling	O
it	O
-	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hinman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Cleavers	I-pers
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
this	O
petticoat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
fire	O
and	O
dried	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
cut	O
the	O
names	O
out	O
of	O
two	O
jack	O
towels	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
wrapped	O
the	O
petticoat	O
up	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
that	O
petticoat	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
two-pence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
quarterns	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
herself	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
knew	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
?	O
I	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
any	O
damage	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
hear	O
you	O
harmless	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
fairly	O
enough	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Crown	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
shall	O
come	O
clear	O
off	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
occassion	O
had	O
I	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Who	O
saw	O
her	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
knows	O
it	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Hinman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Bellman	O
knows	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
*	I-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
grey	O
poplin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
printed	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
calico	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
holland	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
body	O
of	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
-	O
five	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
-	O
three	O
cambrick	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
velvet	O
mantelet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
-	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rhoda	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
last	O
September	O
Sessions	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
,	O
page	O
255	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
mistake	O
discharged	O
,	O
though	O
there	O
was	O
then	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
the	O
accessary	O
,	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
bail	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proceeded	O
against	O
without	O
the	O
principal	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
lodger	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
news	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
stranger	O
that	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
through	O
your	O
occasion	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wondered	O
I	O
should	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
honesty	O
was	O
never	O
questioned	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
declared	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dogged	O
into	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
signify	O
any	O
thing	O
talking	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
pushed	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
herself	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
mantelet	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Weyburne	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Five	O
Roses	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
And	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
she	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
proved	O
the	O
finding	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Weyburne	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
208.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
India	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
thirty-four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
and	O
209.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
India	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
drawers	O
pulled	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
half-pence	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Campbell	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
terrible	O
fright	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
checkered	O
shirt	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
chest	O
(	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
great	O
haste	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
-	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
vintner	O
;	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
who	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
-	O
Campbell	O
does	O
not	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Langley	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
Campbell	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
about	O
sleeping	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
and	O
sleep	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
from	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
till	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
-	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
money	O
much	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
-	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
chamber	O
,	O
the	O
half-pence	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
where	O
the	O
India	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
fix	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
about	O
eight	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
new	O
checkered	O
shirt	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
your	O
asking	O
me	O
so	O
many	O
questions	O
;	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
missing	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
awake	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
shirt	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
watchman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
church-yard	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
charge	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
transport	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
having	O
the	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
Harry	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
him	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
pledged	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Half	O
Moon	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Beadle	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ravell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gray	O
these	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
Gray	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Parliament-house	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
that	O
a	O
night-house	O
?	O
Ravell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
met	O
Campbell	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pledge	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Campbell	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
half-pence	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Langley	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
in	O
Charles	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
sleepy	O
:	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
sleep	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Wapping	O
afterwards	O
for	O
a	O
check	O
'd	O
shirt	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
.	O
And	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
clear	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
Gray	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pawn	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Langley	O
gave	O
me	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Langley	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ravell	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Campbell	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Byne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Campbell	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Gray	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Campbell	O
guilty	O
,	O
Gray	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
210.	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brasses	O
for	O
a	O
grate	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
February	O
28	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
in	O
Bell	O
Court	O
,	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
He	O
professes	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
attorney	O
at	O
law	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
those	O
things	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
parchments	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
something	O
in	O
your	O
way	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
lawyer	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
leave	O
his	O
lodging	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
child	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
for	O
sent	O
I	O
should	O
lose	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
apprehending	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
story	O
about	O
the	O
papers	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
He	O
owed	O
me	O
money	O
for	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
down	O
one	O
evening	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
law	O
papers	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
service	O
are	O
these	O
of	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
pray	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
at	O
his	O
desiring	O
it	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
an	O
indenture	O
of	O
a	O
fine	O
belonging	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
commission	O
empowering	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
affidavits	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
as	O
a	O
security	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
papers	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
that	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
continue	O
paying	O
weekly	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
pawned	O
for	O
?	O
That	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
from	O
September	O
to	O
March	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
material	O
witness	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
have	O
proved	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
tickets	O
with	O
the	O
dates	O
and	O
the	O
sums	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
,	O
amounting	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
about	O
13	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
acknowledge	O
to	O
you	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Kitchen	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
or	O
deny	O
it	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
No	O
never	O
an	O
one	O
.	O
Jordan	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
denied	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Waters	O
present	O
when	O
Kitchen	O
was	O
asked	O
the	O
question	O
?	O
Jordan	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
under	O
misfortunes	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
steal	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
actually	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
applied	O
to	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
reputation	O
in	O
the	O
law	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
One	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
at	O
Stony	O
Stratford	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
misbehaviour	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seventeen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
at	O
Carmarthan	O
in	O
Wales	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hayward	O
an	O
Attorney	O
in	O
Salisbury-court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
these	O
circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hayward	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
211	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Lareman	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
needle	O
case	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
duffel	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
whole	O
amounting	O
to	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
wrought	O
with	O
needle	O
work	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
employed	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
compassion	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
better	O
place	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
she	O
came	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
who	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
Betty	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
Madam	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
room	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
without	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
bed	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
Most	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
arose	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
put	O
out	O
an	O
advertisement	O
with	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
by	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
My	O
petticoat	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
gown	O
,	O
cloak	O
and	O
bonnet	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
you	O
any	O
leave	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
February	O
23	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
things	O
on	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
t	O
hem	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
cleaning	O
the	O
stove	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bundle	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
washerwoman	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
my	O
mistress	O
say	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Naked	O
Boy	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
carry	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
a	O
bonnet	O
on	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grubbs	O
and	O
brought	O
six	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strainer	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
clothes	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
week	O
after	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
showed	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
-	O
these	O
are	O
they	O
.	O
-	O
Freer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
worked	O
linen	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
pattern	O
for	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baldiston	I-pers
.	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
particular	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Upon	O
seeing	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
declared	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
velvet	O
hood	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
cloak	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
gown	O
particularly	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
matched	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cowan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grubbs	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
tongs	O
and	O
strainer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Davis	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
.	O
-	O
Davis	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Heaths	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Lareman	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
plad	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Frasier	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
convicted	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
this	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
212.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Witherden	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
Holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
eight	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
cambrick	O
caps	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
two	O
suits	O
of	O
cambrick	O
pinners	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
four	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
ten	O
India	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
one	O
velvet	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
camblet	O
riding	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
diaper	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
corral	O
with	O
eight	O
silver	O
bells	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
dowlas	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Witherden	I-pers
,	O
February	O
10	O
.	O
213	O
.	O
And	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Witherden	I-pers
.	O
Joanna	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
broke	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
-	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
chamber	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
force	O
?	O
Witherden	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
water	O
tubs	O
set	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
confessed	O
that	O
her	O
sister	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
chamber	O
window	O
before	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
little	O
things	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
questioned	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
handed	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
diaper	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
some	O
aprons	O
and	O
caps	O
,	O
some	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
they	O
sold	O
and	O
some	O
they	O
pawned	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
that	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Ravens	O
's	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ravens	I-pers
.	O
February	O
11	O
,	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
brought	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
two	O
aprons	O
and	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
February	O
15	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sanders	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
daughter	O
Jewers	O
-	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
daughter	O
.	O
Sanders	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
latter	O
husband	O
.	O
Ravens	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
her	O
daughter	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
in	O
what	O
name	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jewers	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jewers	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
A	O
stranger	O
brought	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
diaper	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
deliver	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
Joanna	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Witherden	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
my	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lace	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ravens	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
Ravens	O
.	O
Sanders	O
pawned	O
this	O
lace	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
one	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dias	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Raven	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Witherden	O
found	O
some	O
things	O
there	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
my	O
mother	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
sheet	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
my	O
mother	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
;	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
sister	O
the	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
sheet	O
of	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
old	O
gentlewoman	O
(	O
Sanders	O
)	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
persuaded	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
over	O
against	O
Alderman	O
Parson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
her	O
fortune	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
sometimes	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
senses	O
,	O
partly	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
behaviour	O
of	O
these	O
children	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
has	O
so	O
far	O
turned	O
her	O
brain	O
,	O
that	O
sometimes	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
distinguish	O
between	O
good	O
and	O
evil	O
;	O
sometimes	O
she	O
acts	O
very	O
insensibly	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
imprudently	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
passion	O
.	O
Her	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
without	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
my	O
keys	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
seventeen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Mary	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sanders	O
about	O
twenty-two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
houses	O
of	O
ten	O
pound	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mc	I-pers
Neil	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
's	O
own	O
sister	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
has	O
been	O
too	O
indulgent	O
a	O
parent	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Hamilton	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
three	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
slop	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
brought	O
their	O
work	O
home	O
honestly	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
guilty	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
and	O
strainer	O
,	O
two	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
ells	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Kibball	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
February	O
17	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
214.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
books	O
unbound	O
,	O
entitled	O
the	O
Royal	O
English	O
Grammar	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
sur-master	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
school	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
edition	O
;	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nourse	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
rheam	O
of	O
demy	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Applebee	O
the	O
printer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
there	O
came	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nourse	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
a	O
thousand	O
Royal	O
English	O
Grammars	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
order	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
telling	O
them	O
over	O
I	O
found	O
300	O
short	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
number	O
was	O
short	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
absconded	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
service	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
books	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Joanes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
sell	O
the	O
gentleman	O
some	O
books	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
215.	O
Charles	B-pers
Renew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Beckles	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Beckles	O
Booth	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
on	O
the	O
southside	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
proclamation	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
twitching	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
within	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
crowd	O
.	O
Seeing	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
suspicious	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
pulled	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Exchange	O
.	O
The	O
mob	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
to	O
their	O
management	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Amsterdam	O
coffee	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
readily	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
Monday	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
war	O
proclaimed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
the	O
stones	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
-	O
I	O
follow	O
the	O
profession	O
of	O
making	O
leather	O
clogs	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leave	O
to	O
see	O
was	O
proclaimed	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
faithfully	O
,	O
justly	O
,	O
and	O
honestly	O
;	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
see	O
my	O
apprentices	O
to	O
bed	O
first	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
the	O
Alderman	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
.	O
Booth	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
desire	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
for	O
correction	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Alderman	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
proper	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
dirty	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
216	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Carberry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Flemish	B-place
church	I-place
yard	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Milward	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Milward	O
.	O
About	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
10	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Flemish	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
near	O
Tower-hill	O
(	O
I	O
lived	O
there	O
then	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
butter	O
tub	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Dick	B-pers
Carberry	I-pers
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
tore	O
my	O
apron	O
off	O
my	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
pocket	O
with	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
over	O
her	O
shop	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
pretty	O
light	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
light	O
nor	O
dark	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
dark	O
as	O
to	O
want	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamps	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
Mr.	O
Carberry	O
do	O
n't	O
meddle	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
knock	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
-	O
I	O
complained	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
sooner	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
-	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
directly	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
return	O
to	O
his	O
habitation	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
return	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
fourth	O
day	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
Justice	O
Willoughby	O
's	O
being	O
knocked	O
down	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
report	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
ship	O
after	O
that	O
-	O
I	O
complained	O
to	O
Justice	O
Dennet	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
run	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
You	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
Milward	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
rob	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
several	O
shops	O
there	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
saw	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
shut	O
their	O
doors	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
desperate	O
a	O
fellow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
another	O
midshipman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bawdy-house	O
which	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
her	O
or	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
pretty	O
freely	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
and	O
2	O
guinea	O
from	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
girl	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
guinea	O
from	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
stripped	O
us	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
our	O
reckoning	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
they	O
and	O
their	O
bullies	O
sell	O
upon	O
us	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
sixteen	O
whores	O
of	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
whores	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
she	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
robbing	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
's	O
mother-in-law	O
,	O
kept	O
a	O
vile	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
goes	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
daughter	O
and	O
throw	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
has	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
has	O
he	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
thief	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
such	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
reckoned	O
a	O
civil	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
complain	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
walked	O
home	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
