TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WESTLEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BURNET	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Feverall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Duporty	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Stonier	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
*	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Blanchett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Smoult	O
Pye	O
*	O
,	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Walling	I-pers
were	O
sworn	O
on	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
and	O
Smoult	O
Pye	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Leightenhouse	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
,	O
Charles	O
Church	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Fettyplace	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Cosh	O
+	O
,	O
+	O
And	O
Henry	O
Hayman	O
on	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cosh	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
indisposed	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
242.	O
James	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
brass	O
hinge	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
two	O
foot	O
sliding	O
rule	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
in	O
Addle	O
Street	O
,	O
this	O
hinge	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pearse	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pearse	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
in	O
Whitecross	O
Street	O
.	O
This	O
lad	O
Poole	O
brought	O
this	O
brass	O
hinge	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
six	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Weyman	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
name	O
his	O
Poole	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
two	O
foot	O
rule	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
peny	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Giles	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rugby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Weyman	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Poole	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Giles	O
the	O
founder	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
hinge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
either	O
gave	O
a	O
peny	O
for	O
the	O
rule	O
,	O
or	O
tossed	O
up	O
a	O
peny	O
against	O
it	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Giles	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
naughty	O
boy	O
to	O
serve	O
her	O
so	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
recommended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
243.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
four	O
pillowbeers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
April	O
20	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
this	O
linen	O
into	O
a	O
pan	O
ready	O
for	O
ironing	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
run	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
my	O
aunt	O
cry	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
boy	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
bundle	O
down	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
his	O
case	O
of	O
pistols	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
gang	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
but	O
himself	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
244	O
,	O
245.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
fore	O
sail	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
gib	O
sail	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
trivet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
stanchions	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
tolling	O
rope	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
bolt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
three	O
cross	O
bars	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
scuttle	O
bar	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
close	O
stool	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
246	O
.	O
And	O
Joseph	B-pers
Greswold	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
Montague	O
Yatch	O
;	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
William	O
Hall	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Yatch	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
somebody	O
had	O
drawn	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
skuttle	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
house	O
was	O
searched	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
welcome	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
it	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
tolling	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fails	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Andrew	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
own	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
(	O
Greswold	O
)	O
enticed	O
us	O
from	O
our	O
masters	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
victuals	O
,	O
or	O
clothes	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Groswold	O
sent	O
them	O
out	O
o'night	O
with	O
tools	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
vessels	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
what	O
they	O
brought	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
things	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
No	O
otherwise	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
.	O
William	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
Montague	B-pers
Yatch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
yatch	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
skuttle	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
staple	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
foresail	O
,	O
the	O
great	O
gib	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
cables	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
the	O
small	O
cable	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
them	O
both	O
cables	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
people	O
call	O
them	O
tollings	O
;	O
-	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
Greswold	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
cables	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
Greswold	O
's	O
wife	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
show	O
me	O
two	O
sails	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Greswold	O
stay	O
there	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Hall	O
No	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
cable	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pinfold	I-pers
.	O
The	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Montague	B-pers
Yatch	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
A	O
marline	O
spike	O
,	O
a	O
hammer	O
and	O
hatcher	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
the	O
first	O
night	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
Hodges	O
,	O
one	O
Williams	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
first	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
Hodges	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
second	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
Andrew	O
drew	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
skuttle	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
broke	O
the	O
yatch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
trivet	O
,	O
some	O
stanchions	O
,	O
some	O
ropes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
sails	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
gib	O
;	O
Andrew	O
handed	O
the	O
sails	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
hand	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
Greswold	O
lent	O
us	O
his	O
little	O
boat	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
another	O
to	O
suit	O
our	O
conveniency	O
:	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
large	O
boat	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ships	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
larger	O
boat	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
the	O
Saturday	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
these	O
things	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
them	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Greswold	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
sails	O
,	O
ropes	O
and	O
stanchions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
went	O
past	O
one	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yatch	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
between	O
Cole	O
Harbour	O
and	O
Stone-Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
Greswold	O
lives	O
at	O
Cole-Harbour	O
by	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ramsgate	O
Pink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
knew	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
stole	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
He	O
lent	O
us	O
a	O
boat	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
enticed	O
me	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
(	O
one	O
Griffiths	O
a	O
waterman	O
and	O
lighterman	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
living	O
open	O
yatchs	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
when	O
the	O
Montague	B-pers
Yatch	I-pers
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
Andrew	O
and	O
Hodges	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
lay	O
there	O
three	O
nights	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Andrew	O
.	O
We	O
lay	O
there	O
three	O
nights	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
any	O
other	O
vessels	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
coals	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Montague	O
yatch	O
-	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
lye	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
then	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
officer	O
promise	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
accuse	O
me	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
cleared	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
bring	O
any	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
send	O
you	O
about	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Greswold	O
lent	O
us	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
old	O
ropes	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Greswold	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
warrant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
rope	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
cable	O
,	O
he	O
walked	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Greswold	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
two	O
men	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
marsh	O
-	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Dogs	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
right	O
against	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
again	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
covered	O
over	O
in	O
a	O
copper	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
brew	O
in	O
(	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
brew	O
his	O
own	O
beer	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
water	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
copper	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
he	O
changed	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
wet	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
copper	O
?	O
Pope	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
copper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
standing	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
crouched	O
down	O
?	O
Pope	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
's	O
,	O
people	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
out-house	O
first	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Pope	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
standing	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
copper	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
to	O
Greswold	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
's	O
things	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
closet	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
His	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
some	O
old	O
ropes	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
ours	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
old	O
fails	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
show	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
for	O
Pinfold	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
talked	O
pretty	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Greswold	O
was	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
copper	O
in	O
his	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
half	O
bent	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
used	O
him	O
well	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
bring	O
cutlasses	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
properly	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
tuck	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
indeed	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
again	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Greswold	O
's	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
knew	O
these	O
lads	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
boat	O
a	O
bumboating	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leather	O
Lane	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Greswold	O
almost	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
parents	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
trouble	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
)	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
distiller	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
had	O
misfortunes	O
by	O
informations	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
publickly	O
of	O
Pinfold	O
and	O
Andrew	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
for	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
ropes	O
,	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
?	O
Pinfold	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
us	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hundred	O
of	O
iron	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
paid	O
us	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
this	O
boy	O
would	O
swear	O
so	O
roundly	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
better	O
prepared	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hall	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
these	O
things	O
worth	O
?	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
10	O
s.	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
40	O
s.	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
20	O
s.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Phillips	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
worth	O
at	O
a	O
low	O
price	O
.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
in	O
all	O
between	O
thirty	O
and	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Greswold	O
.	O
Pinfold	O
swears	O
a	O
false	O
thing	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
gave	O
but	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
iron	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
Greswold	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
Pope	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Greswold	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
People	O
used	O
to	O
talk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
coals	O
and	O
corn	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
manner	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
s	O
uspected	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
body	O
was	O
for	O
suppressing	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
kept	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
then	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
suspected	O
of	O
these	O
practices	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
people	O
have	O
found	O
their	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
Hodges	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Andrew	O
guilty	O
,	O
Greswold	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
247	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
a	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
goal	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
holden	O
at	O
Kingston	O
upon	O
Thames	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Surry	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fortesue	I-pers
Aland	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
others	O
their	O
fellow	O
Justices	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
assigned	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
said	O
goal	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ	I-place
Church	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
county	I-place
of	I-place
Surry	I-place
,	O
labourer	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
due	O
course	O
of	O
law	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
feloniously	O
and	O
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
eleven	O
holland	O
shirts	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
ten	O
table-cloths	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christian	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
by	O
a	O
certain	O
jury	O
of	O
the	O
county	O
was	O
duly	O
convicted	O
of	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christian	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christian	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
ordered	O
and	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
should	O
be	O
transported	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
plantations	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
the	O
record	O
does	O
more	O
fully	O
appear	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
17th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
large	O
within	O
the	O
realms	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
Clerkenwell	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
without	O
lawful	O
cause	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
arraigns	O
of	O
the	O
home	O
circuit	O
produced	O
the	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
conviction	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
assizes	O
held	O
at	O
Kingston	O
upon	O
Thames	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Surry	O
.	O
before	O
Sir	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
Aland	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Jurors	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Margaret	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
Jan.	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
eleven	O
holland	O
shirts	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
ten	O
table-cloths	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jurors	O
say	O
that	O
neither	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
nor	O
Margaret	O
his	O
wife	O
are	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christian	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
but	O
they	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	O
his	O
wife	O
are	O
guilty	O
of	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
goods	O
and	O
chissels	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christian	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	O
his	O
wife	O
shall	O
be	O
transported	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
plantations	O
in	O
America	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lingard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
at	O
Kingston	O
assizes	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
linen	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
transportation	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Sarnel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
at	O
Kingston	O
assizes	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
this	O
fact	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
large	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
Borough	O
Fair	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
or	O
anniseed	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
for	O
him	O
about	O
this	O
linen	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
)	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sall	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
surprized	O
at	O
my	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
goal-keeper	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Barton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
but	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
last	O
Borough	O
Fair	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
Sall	O
,	O
you	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
transported	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
see	O
I	O
am	O
returned	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
keep	O
away	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Goal	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
nobody	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
disallowing	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
of	O
returning	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
sold	O
there	O
like	O
beasts	O
,	O
like	O
sheep	O
,	O
or	O
oxen	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
buyer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Captain	O
Loney	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Frederick	B-pers
Pink	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
come	O
here	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
248	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
passage	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
the	O
Five	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
near	O
Perrot	B-place
's	I-place
illuminations	I-place
,	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	B-place
and	I-place
Groom	I-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
banks	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Saunders	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
o'night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
judge	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
immediately	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
cross	O
my	O
temples	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
blow	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
my	O
cane	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
truncheon	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
they	O
use	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
blow	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
severe	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
afterwards	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
cuts	O
upon	O
my	O
cane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
continued	O
his	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
large	O
wound	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
jumped	O
upon	O
my	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
always	O
carry	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
very	O
strong	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
to	O
tear	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
rule	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
tore	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
keys	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
never	O
go	O
home	O
again	O
(	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
pistol	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
killing	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
enough	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
already	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
certainly	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
then	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
light	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
having	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
my	O
own	O
brother	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
,	O
body	O
and	O
face	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
surprising	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
more	O
merciful	O
than	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
.	O
At	O
near	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
)	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
almost	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
into	O
the	O
Five	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
staid	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
up	O
a	O
good	O
pace	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bayonet	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
struck	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
his	O
man	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
this	O
man	O
prove	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Rowe	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
round	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
posts	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Esquire	O
Man	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
college	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Esquire	O
Chester	O
,	O
in	O
Golden	O
Square	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Esquire	O
Chester	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
eleven	O
,	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
got	O
home	O
then	O
?	O
Rowe	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
got	O
home	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
tongue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
many	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
a	O
meal	O
's	O
meat	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
met	O
him	O
?	O
Rowe	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
is	O
an	O
undertaker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
buried	O
a	O
master	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
servants	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
two	O
maids	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
guinea	O
apiece	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
ever	O
gave	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
bury	O
a	O
master	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
three	O
guineas	O
among	O
the	O
servants	O
;	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
disposed	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
meal	O
's	O
meat	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
meal	O
's	O
meat	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
gone	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
pay	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
bread	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
you	O
how	O
you	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
you	O
lived	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
reason	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
way	O
of	O
getting	O
bread	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
place	O
at	O
Esquire	O
Chester	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Esquire	O
Chester	O
's	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
said	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
Works	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
by	O
the	O
Two	O
Star	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
very	O
well	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
watch-night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
catch	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
was	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rowe	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
go	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
distance	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apprentice	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
parson	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
's	O
become	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
They	O
met	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
,	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
Perrot	O
's	O
illuminations	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
nearest	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Rowe	O
came	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rowe	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
strike	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
Rowe	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
the	O
villain	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
just	O
down	O
the	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
gun	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
my	O
apprentice	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apprentice	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
a	O
door	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
he	O
could	O
light	O
on	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
resisted	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
the	O
other	O
should	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
fired	O
the	O
gun	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
very	O
quietly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
him	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Star	O
alehouse	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
oppose	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pillars	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
*	O
hair	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hair	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
like	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
livery	O
servants	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
take	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
spare	O
my	O
life	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
law	O
is	O
on	O
your	O
side	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
right	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
the	O
law	O
is	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
take	O
what	O
it	O
will	O
allow	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
powder	O
in	O
the	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fired	O
it	O
only	O
to	O
frighten	O
me	O
.	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
from	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
till	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
used	O
some	O
artisices	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
confess	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
always	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
sent	O
a	O
Romish	O
Priest	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
any	O
damage	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
send	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
desire	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
privy	O
to	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Pray	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
business	O
:	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
meddled	O
with	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
enough	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
only	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
,	O
dined	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rothwell	O
in	O
Eagle	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
's	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
directly	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Ailesbury	O
's	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
now	O
)	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Chairmen	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
Lord	O
Ailesbury	O
's	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
parted	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
somewhat	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
then	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Graston	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
clean	O
linnen	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Mansprit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
facing	O
Beauford	O
Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
that	O
Night-between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Chairmen	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Street	O
by	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Ailesbury	O
's	O
servant	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Ailesbury	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
Buck	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
parted	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lighted	O
candles	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Paty	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Bun-House	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
walking	O
or	O
drinking	O
?	O
Paty	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
there	O
under	O
the	O
lamp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Paty	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lerose	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
watch	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
dead	O
wall	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Hide-Park	O
Corner	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
nine	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Hide-Park	O
Corner	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
spoke	O
disrespectfully	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hutchins	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
act	O
as	O
this	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Five	O
Fields	O
.	O
Paty	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Scotsman	O
lying	O
among	O
the	O
pipes	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
Hide-Park	O
Corner	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
us	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
accept	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Watkins	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
his	O
character	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
gentle	O
and	O
simple	O
always	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
-	O
Lerose	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
Paty	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
's	O
groom	O
)	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
?	O
Lerose	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
l	O
ittle	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
from	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
?	O
Lerose	O
.	O
A	O
good	O
way	O
-	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
two	O
miles	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
quite	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
look	O
cool	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
he	O
at	O
all	O
heated	O
?	O
Patey	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
heated	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
sweat	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
cool	O
in	O
his	O
countenance	O
-	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
any	O
violent	O
motion	O
.	O
Jury	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
searched	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
private	O
pockets	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
when	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
treated	O
me	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
found	O
it	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
searched	O
him	O
strictly	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
informed	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Then	O
why	O
would	O
you	O
not	O
search	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
away	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
it	O
was	O
nearer	O
eleven	O
.	O
-	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
in	O
February	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
offer	O
my	O
services	O
at	O
St.	O
Albans	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
only	O
one	O
servant	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
my	O
own	O
servant	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
more	O
than	O
negative	O
proofs	O
of	O
his	O
honesty	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
more	O
than	O
350	O
l.	O
in	O
bank	O
notes	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
specie	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
my	O
own	O
servant	O
brought	O
me	O
250	O
l	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
100	O
l.	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
some	O
circumstances	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
that	O
100	O
l.	O
My	O
own	O
servant	O
being	O
disordered	O
by	O
riding	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
intrusted	O
with	O
my	O
linnen	O
and	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
also	O
observe	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
more	O
civil	O
or	O
sober	O
servant	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
imagine	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
capable	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
-	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
his	O
character	O
and	O
behaviour	O
(	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
)	O
has	O
been	O
honest	O
and	O
just	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
gentleman	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
wanted	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
several	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hired	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
character	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
could	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
it	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
young	O
gentleman	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
and	O
soberly	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
very	O
often	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
drunk	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
from	O
you	O
upon	O
any	O
misbehaviour	O
?	O
-	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
because	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
well	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
continued	O
ill	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
wanted	O
another	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
preferable	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
I	O
knew	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
singly	O
?	O
-	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
far	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
mention	O
in	O
evidence	O
what	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
absent	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
might	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Graston	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
messengers	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
innocent	O
and	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
split	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
;	O
whether	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
said	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
249	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
back	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
who	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
customers	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
pumps	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
pumps	O
in	O
his	O
lap	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
shoes	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
250	O
.	O
+	O
Catharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
April	O
20	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Eagle	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
in	O
your	O
breeches	O
?	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
Swan	O
tavern	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
guards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
any	O
company	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
Because	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
tavern	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
then	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
odd	O
thing	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sober	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
about	O
such	O
a	O
scandalous	O
practice	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
charge	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
followed	O
no	O
other	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
your	O
watch	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
belive	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
She	O
wrenched	O
my	O
breeches	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
directly	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Eagle	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
thorough-fare	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Forrest	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
croud	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hoskins	O
holding	O
a	O
woman	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
I	O
assisted	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
tavern	O
,	O
she	O
stripped	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Hoskins	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
?	O
Forrest	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hobbins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
fishwoman	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
habitation	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
a	O
jole	O
of	O
salmon	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
(	O
that	O
last	O
witness	O
*	O
)	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
their	O
clothes	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
rogue	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
get	O
along	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
get	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
salmon	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
*	O
Hobbins	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
from	O
the	O
witness	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
unlike	O
.	O
She	O
delivered	O
her	O
evidence	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
manner	O
,	O
laughing	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
two	O
women	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
?	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
their	O
coats	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
women	O
were	O
they	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
women	O
for	O
the	O
salmon	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
my	O
mistress	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
you	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
B	O
-	O
hes	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
tavern	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
soldiers	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
afterwards	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
said	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
Do	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
service	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dutch	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
discern	O
whether	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
?	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
pursue	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
women	O
?	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
He	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
them	O
;	O
oh	O
!	O
L	O
-	O
d	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
[	O
she	O
then	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
beggar	O
woman	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
once	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Forrest	O
.	O
Were	O
Hoskins	O
and	O
you	O
acquainted	O
before	O
?	O
Forrest	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hoskins	O
before	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
.	O
Forrest	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Hobbins	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
-	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
her	O
husband	O
lives	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
serve	O
her	O
with	O
bread	O
,	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
Inn	O
in	O
Hedge	O
Lane	O
-	O
she	O
is	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
she	O
washes	O
for	O
me	O
now	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
251	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
single	O
woman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
17th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
being	O
big	O
with	O
a	O
female	O
child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
child	O
by	O
the	O
providence	O
of	O
God	O
from	O
her	O
body	O
did	O
bring	O
forth	O
alive	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
female	O
child	O
being	O
so	O
brought	O
forth	O
alive	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
this	O
land	O
is	O
a	O
bastard	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
after	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
in	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
did	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
window	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
three	O
stories	O
high	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
belonging	O
to	O
Esther	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Whetstone	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
into	O
a	O
paved	O
yard	O
,	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
down	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
casting	O
and	O
throwing	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
paved	O
yard	O
,	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
several	O
mortal	O
wounds	O
and	O
bruises	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
back	O
,	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
sides	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
wounds	O
and	O
bruises	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
back	O
,	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
sides	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jurors	O
do	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
murder	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ditcher	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
fit	O
of	O
the	O
colic	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
you	O
being	O
something	O
in	O
years	O
may	O
have	O
some	O
disorder	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Miss	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
some	O
penny-royal	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
further	O
disorder	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
birth	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
ailed	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witness	O
expressed	O
herself	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
show	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
disorder	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
aunt	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
proper	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Her	O
aunt	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ditcher	O
,	O
Nanny	O
has	O
thrown	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
has	O
she	O
thrown	O
out	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
frighten	O
me	O
to	O
death	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
oh	O
Nanny	O
!	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
as	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ditcher	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
hide	O
my	O
shame	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
fear	O
you	O
should	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
alive	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
dead	O
child	O
lye	O
upon	O
the	O
pavement	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
upon	O
it	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observation	O
upon	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
than	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
[	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
performed	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
a	O
midwife	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
barbarous	O
action	O
as	O
to	O
throw	O
her	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
shame	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
child	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
was	O
the	O
child	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Tanner	O
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
female	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
or	O
dead	O
?	O
Tanner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
judge	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kelleck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
examine	O
this	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
entirely	O
free	O
from	O
all	O
cleansing	O
,	O
but	O
naturally	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
body	O
.	O
Upon	O
examination	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
cleansed	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
contusion	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
cheek	O
by	O
the	O
Os	O
Temporum	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
confraction	O
of	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
jaw	O
bone	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Thorax	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
experiment	O
upon	O
the	O
lungs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lungs	O
would	O
swim	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
tore	O
it	O
away	O
I	O
suppose	O
from	O
her	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
lungs	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
inflated	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
swim	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
experiment	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
tearing	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
inslate	O
the	O
lungs	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
them	O
hollow	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
was	O
blackish	O
,	O
which	O
shows	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fluid	O
slate	O
while	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
mother	O
's	O
body	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
had	O
breathe	O
or	O
no	O
after	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
general	O
observation	O
in	O
cases	O
of	O
this	O
nature	O
?	O
Kelleck	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
role	O
without	O
an	O
exception	O
,	O
sometimes	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
breathe	O
before	O
they	O
come	O
really	O
into	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
that	O
experiment	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
downright	O
certain	O
and	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
an	O
infant	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
body	O
(	O
before	O
it	O
breathes	O
)	O
these	O
lungs	O
will	O
never	O
swim	O
.	O
Suppose	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
gone	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
within	O
her	O
,	O
those	O
lungs	O
will	O
never	O
swim	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
children	O
come	O
forward	O
in	O
the	O
birth	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
breathe	O
before	O
they	O
are	O
really	O
born	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
child	O
is	O
still-born	O
,	O
and	O
dies	O
before	O
the	O
delivery	O
,	O
the	O
lungs	O
will	O
never	O
swim	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
a	O
child	O
should	O
die	O
in	O
the	O
delivery	O
,	O
will	O
they	O
swim	O
?	O
Kelleck	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
possible	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
hasty	O
in	O
the	O
birth	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
apprehend	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
time	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
breathe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
any	O
respiration	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
the	O
whole	O
lungs	O
be	O
inflated	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
respiration	O
?	O
Kelleck	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
several	O
respirations	O
before	O
the	O
whole	O
lungs	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
inflated	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
contraction	O
or	O
expansion	O
of	O
the	O
lungs	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
actual	O
respiration	O
from	O
which	O
the	O
blood	O
circulates	O
is	O
performed	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
seconds	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
lungs	O
are	O
not	O
expanded	O
?	O
Kelleck	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
in	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
space	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
still-born	O
child	O
,	O
will	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lungs	O
swim	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
sink	O
?	O
Kelleck	O
.	O
There	O
have	O
been	O
experiments	O
both	O
ways	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
a	O
child	O
is	O
suffocated	O
in	O
the	O
delivery	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
does	O
it	O
occur	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
those	O
lungs	O
have	O
swam	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
have	O
sunk	O
?	O
Kelleck	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
they	O
have	O
partly	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
suffocated	O
in	O
the	O
birth	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noakes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
only	O
very	O
foolish	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
close	O
upper	O
leathers	O
for	O
shoes	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stendrup	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thirty	O
seven	O
or	O
thirty	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
reputed	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
silly	O
foolish	O
girl	O
,	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
nobody	O
can	O
say	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
sometimes	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
compos	O
mentis	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
capable	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Stendrup	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
so	O
far	O
non	O
compos	O
mentis	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
danger	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
attending	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
care	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eden	I-pers
.	O
All	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
man	O
that	O
followed	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mrs.	O
Ditcher	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
ordered	O
her	O
some	O
pe	O
royal	O
water	O
was	O
she	O
in	O
her	O
senses	O
?	O
Ditcher	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
questions	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
sense	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
so	O
?	O
Ditcher	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
said	O
when	O
she	O
flung	O
it	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
shame	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
matters	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
several	O
questions	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
delirious	O
,	O
particularly	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
her	O
delivery	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
hammered	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
her	O
brother	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lad	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
child	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
252	O
,	O
253	O
,	O
254	O
,	O
255.	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Haycraft	B-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smytheman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
hardware	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
razors	O
,	O
pen-knives	O
,	O
buckles	O
,	O
buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
shop	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
given	O
aw	O
ay	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
owned	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
full	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
:	O
the	O
women	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
stood	O
watching	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
sign	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Mcpherson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
men	O
owned	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
women	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Whiting	O
's	O
show-glass	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Griffiths	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
James	B-pers
Haycrast	I-pers
say	O
he	O
was	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Smytheman	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
with	O
the	O
women	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
hard-ware	O
,	O
the	O
women	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
hard-ware	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
together	O
;	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Griffiths	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
30	O
s.	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
more	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
Smytheman	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
chimney	O
sweeping	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
as	O
much	O
foot	O
as	O
we	O
sold	O
for	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
kicked	O
my	O
foot	O
against	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
sold	O
those	O
goods	O
to	O
Whiting	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Whiting	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
nad	O
6	O
d.	O
]	O
Griffiths	O
.	O
They	O
stole	O
the	O
trunk	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
they	O
burnt	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
(	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
's	O
clerk	O
)	O
produced	O
the	O
examinations	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Haycroft	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
,	O
1744.	O
Ann	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Haycraft	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
at	O
Town	O
Malden	O
in	O
Kent	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
about	O
three	O
years	O
since	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
last	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smytheman	I-pers
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Whiting	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
confession	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smytheman	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
April	O
12	O
,	O
1744.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smytheman	I-pers
says	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
have	O
committed	O
divers	O
burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
this	O
examinate	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
proposed	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
and	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
view	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
broke	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
hammer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
remained	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
twelve	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
this	O
examinate	O
's	O
lodging	O
at	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Holborn	O
overagainst	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Gate	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
stall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
without	O
asking	O
any	O
questions	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
asked	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
bid	O
them	O
but	O
8	O
s.	O
that	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
bought	O
them	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
The	O
confession	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
This	O
examinate	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Friday	O
last	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smytheman	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
shop	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
that	O
Smytheman	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
away	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
kept	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Francis	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
cellar	O
by	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
money	O
was	O
divided	O
between	O
them	O
share	O
and	O
share	O
alike	O
.	O
The	O
examination	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
This	O
examinate	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smytheman	I-pers
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
for	O
six	O
months	O
past	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
industrious	O
fellow	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
since	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Angel	O
Court	O
at	O
Story	O
's	O
Gate	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Whiting	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
which	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
(	O
except	O
a	O
few	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
which	O
they	O
kept	O
themselves	O
)	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
divided	O
between	O
them	O
share	O
and	O
share	O
alike	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Whiting	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
wipes	O
[	O
meaning	O
handkerchiefs	O
]	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Haycraft	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
,	O
and	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Haycraft	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smytheman	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
is	O
detained	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
those	O
goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
256.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
pork	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
pork	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
May	O
9	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
pork	O
that	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
pushed	O
the	O
hatch	O
half	O
way	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
257.	O
Francis	B-pers
Shoeler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
a	O
composition	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowles	O
,	O
that	O
fellow	O
the	O
(	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
took	O
seventeen	O
pound	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
composition	O
of	O
glass	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
ten	O
colours	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Hakewell	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
le	O
Grand	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
servants	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
seventeen	O
pound	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
composition	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
warehouse	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
Street	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
:	O
let	O
your	O
clerk	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
a	O
light	O
into	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hakewell	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
showed	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
satisfied	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
own	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
I	O
will	O
show	O
you	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
the	O
jeweller	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Levi	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Tower	O
Street	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
sorts	O
of	O
the	O
composition	O
produced	O
;	O
]	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
is	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bowles	O
's	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
number	O
and	O
colour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Morse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
our	O
warehouse	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
wine	O
glasses	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
get	O
flowered	O
round	O
the	O
edges	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
warehouse	O
keeper	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
soror	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
glasses	O
are	O
neiled	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
baskets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
composition	O
?	O
Morse	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
jewellers	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
making	O
pendants	O
for	O
the	O
lady	O
's	O
ears	O
,	O
and	O
jewels	O
for	O
the	O
kidies	O
necks	O
.	O
He	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
an	O
idle	O
story	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
avail	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
no	O
body	O
makes	O
this	O
composition	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
of	O
this	O
composition	O
?	O
Morse	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
nothing	O
but	O
drinking	O
glasses	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
his	O
house	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
of	O
Hungary	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
Prague	O
in	O
Germany	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
some	O
composition	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
glass	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
showed	O
it	O
to	O
several	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
could	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
sit	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
show	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
upon	O
commission	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
ask	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
that	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Levi	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
show	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
may	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
lowest	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
lowest	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
offered	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
seventeen	O
pound	O
three	O
ounces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
seen	O
large	O
quantities	O
of	O
this	O
glass	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
's	O
Shop	O
?	O
Levi	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
quantity	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
work	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
glass	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Levi	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
me	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
that	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
have	O
my	O
glass	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
bring	O
me	O
the	O
glass	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
getting	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
gentleman	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
thought	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
glasses	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
a	O
basket	O
about	O
streets	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
some	O
figured	O
glasses	O
,	O
a	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
this	O
glass	O
to	O
their	O
warehouse-keeper	O
to	O
exchange	O
for	O
drinking	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Morse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
so	O
,	O
our	O
warehouse-keeper	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
small	O
pieces	O
to	O
change	O
for	O
drinking	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
him	O
this	O
answer	O
;	O
our	O
business	O
is	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
glass	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
take	O
any	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
but	O
jewellers	O
?	O
Morse	O
.	O
Never	O
to	O
any	O
but	O
jewellers	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
nobody	O
that	O
makes	O
this	O
composition	O
of	O
glass	O
besides	O
Mr.	O
Bowles	O
?	O
Morse	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
Juryman	O
Sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
composition	O
of	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
with	O
this	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
sold	O
by	O
other	O
people	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Batailliard	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
apothecary	O
and	O
surgeon	O
by	O
Moorfields	O
who	O
make	O
this	O
composition	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
258	O
.	O
+	O
Lydia	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
grey	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cinnamon	O
coloured	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Coffin	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
clothes	O
April	O
19	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
before	O
night	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
clothes	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Hugh	B-pers
Osburne	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
cinnamon	O
coloured	O
coat	O
which	O
Rich	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
by	O
Johnson	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Braddock	O
.	O
This	O
coat	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Osburne	I-pers
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Osburne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sold	O
this	O
coat	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Braddock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
black	O
coat	O
and	O
the	O
grey	O
coat	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henn	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crosier	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
coats	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Henn	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
fourth	O
hand	O
.	O
-	O
Henn	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Osburne	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
clothes	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
259	O
,	O
260	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Goldburne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
six	O
pound	O
of	O
fat	O
,	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
a	O
brisket	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
a	O
chuck	O
rib	O
,	O
a	O
middle	O
rib	O
,	O
a	O
rump	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
leg	O
of	O
mutton	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
meat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Abell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
And	O
261.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Abell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
and	O
other	O
meat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
Spittlefield	B-place
's	I-place
Market	I-place
,	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flank	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
a	O
jar	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
meat	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lardent	I-pers
's	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
loose	O
persons	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
time	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lardent	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
somebody	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
meat	O
away	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
clear	O
yourself	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Isaac	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
other	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Dumb	O
Paw	O
,	O
[	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
lame	O
hand	O
]	O
and	O
Dobbs	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
meat	O
was	O
lodged	O
at	O
one	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
in	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
meat	O
here	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
welcome	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
showed	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
meat	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Leadenhall	O
Market	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
meat	O
and	O
sat	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
meat	O
was	O
vastly	O
tumbled	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
like	O
dogs	O
meat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
heart	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Carpenter	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Abell	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
over	O
night	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
about	O
lodging	O
the	O
meat	O
there	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
constables	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
several	O
disorderly	O
houses	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
men	O
for	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Stony	O
Lane	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Dobbs	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
boy	O
:	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
were	O
officers	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
power	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
unless	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
us	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
an	O
old	O
apron	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
still	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
my	O
brother	O
officer	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
hand	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Spittlefield	O
's	O
Market	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
)	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
fact	O
-	O
He	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Isaac	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
him	O
Dumb	O
Paw	O
)	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
chopper	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
moulding	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
shutter	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
meat	O
out	O
to	O
Isaac	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
two	O
turns	O
apiece	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Abell	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
chopper	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
shutter	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Dobbs	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
hopeful	O
young	O
lad	O
-	O
he	O
carries	O
meat	O
up	O
to	O
Leadenhall	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
does	O
employ	O
him	O
.	O
Abell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
employed	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Bond	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
in	O
watching	O
of	O
meat	O
.	O
Abell	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
.	O
Dobbs	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
wrong	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
it	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
guinea	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
this	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
boy	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
?	O
Pell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
sister	O
.	O
Goldburne	O
and	O
Carpenter	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Dobbs	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
262	O
.	O
+	O
Hugh	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
