TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744-5	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BURNETT	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rolfe	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Killingsworth	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Boden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Iliffe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Durno	I-pers
,	O
Conquest	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Martell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Spinnage	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
161	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tibbet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
purses	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Currey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Currey	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
as	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hid	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
bed	O
-	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
seen	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Currey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
nights	O
-	O
That	O
night	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
he	O
should	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
angry	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
bed	O
between	O
the	O
wall	O
and	O
the	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
fifty	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
for	O
?	O
Currey	O
.	O
For	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pacify	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
cold	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
till	O
I	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
had	O
her	O
hand	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
water	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nobody	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
McCardell	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
then	O
)	O
-	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
denied	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
afterwards	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bruden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
James	B-pers
Curgreys	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
supper	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
Currey	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
White	O
Cross	O
Street	O
,	O
by	O
Old	O
Street	O
Church	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pewter	O
standish	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
concerning	O
Mr.	O
Currey	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
(	O
Arthur	B-pers
McCardel	I-pers
)	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Currey	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Bruden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
landlady	O
tell	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
where	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
162	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
moidore	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Puckett	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Puckett	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crown	O
Court	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
long	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
entreated	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
in	O
Peter	B-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
foolish	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
lodging	O
)	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
shrub	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
weak	O
enough	O
to	O
consent	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
moidore	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
before	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
calling	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
chamber-pot	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missing	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Puckett	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
her	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
her	O
any	O
further	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
still	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
was	O
I	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Puckett	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
you	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Puckett	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room-door	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
all	O
my	O
clothes	O
off	O
:	O
the	O
landlady	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
too	O
.	O
Puckett	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
story	O
,	O
you	O
pulled	O
your	O
shoes	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
pulled	O
your	O
stockings	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
signify	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
Puckett	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
money	O
might	O
not	O
seatter	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
while	O
you	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Puckett	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
clothes	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
-	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
searched	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
163	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
plain	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
an	O
enamelled	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
January	O
25	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
absconded	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
wondered	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
26th	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
a	O
press	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
rings	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
absconded	O
her	O
service	O
:	O
the	O
press	O
did	O
lock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
locked	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
fifth	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
6	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
plain	O
gold	O
rings	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
Westram	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
yours	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Westram	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
my	O
mother	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
must	O
walk	O
it	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
peny	O
worth	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
coach	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
coachman	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Croydon	O
;	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
somebody	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
had	O
tea	O
for	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
beef-stakes	O
for	O
dinner	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
keeper	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
carriage	O
to	O
Westram	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
Sunday	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
Monday	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
coach	O
hire	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Wise	O
.	O
No	O
otherwise	O
than	O
as	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
for	O
pots	O
.	O
-	O
Barber	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Horsefield	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
informed	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
January	O
29	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
at	O
Westram	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
drinking-room	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
use	O
your	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
?	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
laid	O
down	O
these	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
any	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
rings	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Westram	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Horsefield	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
again	O
in	O
another	O
house	O
at	O
Westram	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
rings	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
the	O
woman	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
note	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
say	O
?	O
Horsefield	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spent	O
but	O
three	O
pence	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
these	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
's	O
rings	O
?	O
Horsefield	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Barbers	O
wife	O
's	O
wedding	O
ring	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
could	O
read	O
writing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Barber	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
rings	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
164.	O
Jane	B-pers
Linsley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
duffle	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Going	B-pers
Drayton	I-pers
,	O
February	O
18	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Drayton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
coat	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
off	O
a	O
nail	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
cross	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
Seeing	O
a	O
strang	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
either	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
or	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
impudent	O
jade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Treddell	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
?	O
Drayton	O
.	O
She	O
laid	O
the	O
coat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
Treddell	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Drayton	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
coat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
nothing	O
;	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
saucy	O
jade	O
to	O
stop	O
me	O
without	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
one	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
deserved	O
one	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
too	O
strait	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
,	O
a	O
mantua	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
shoved	O
by	O
me	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
that	O
gentlewoman	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Drayton	O
]	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
that	O
coat	O
there	O
?	O
Drayton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
came	O
the	O
coat	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
I	O
a	O
new	O
gown	O
on	O
?	O
Drayton	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
newish	O
gown	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
kept	O
me	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
165	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fitzar	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
January	O
17	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Grant	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
came	O
into	O
her	O
shop	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
wig	O
was	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
peg	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
some	O
warm	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
shaved	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
behind	O
Old	O
Street	O
Church	O
wheeling	O
of	O
bricks	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
wig	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
wig	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
shaved	O
there	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
wig	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
cheat	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
directly	O
.	O
Smith	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
note	O
[	O
receipt	O
]	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
paper	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
.	O
'	O
February	O
25	O
,	O
1744	O
.	O
Received	O
of	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
'	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
pound	O
'	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
Received	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
'	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
.	O
'	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
th	O
is	O
?	O
Whose	O
writing	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
Brown	O
's	O
writing	O
,	O
a	O
gardner	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
this	O
paper	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
any	O
service	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
informed	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
served	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
children	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
166.	O
John	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
warehouse	O
at	O
Wiggins	O
's	O
Key	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
his	O
pocket	O
hit	O
against	O
my	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
eleven	O
pound	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
and	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
hogshead	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
sugar	O
of	O
that	O
hogshead	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Eliakim	O
Palmer	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
drubbed	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
hoop	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
threatened	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
meddled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
at	O
Smart	O
's	O
Key	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
167.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tin	O
pot	O
with	O
four	O
gallons	O
of	O
lamp	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
my	O
man	O
lost	O
a	O
tin	O
pot	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
gallons	O
of	O
oil	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
pot	O
.	O
William	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Rippen	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Man	I-place
and	I-place
Still	I-place
in	O
New	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
by	O
Cloth	B-place
Fair	I-place
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopeny	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
my	O
pot	O
with	O
about	O
four	O
gallons	O
of	O
oil	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
one	O
day	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
fan-stick	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
poured	O
some	O
oil	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
tin	O
pot	O
into	O
a	O
bottle	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
pot	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
oil	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
's	O
by	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
pot	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
sent	O
his	O
man	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
pot	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Ratcliff	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
oil	O
pot	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
man	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Aris	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
pot	O
I	O
fetched	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ratcliff	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
+	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
55	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
calimanco	O
quilted	O
petcoat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
linen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
five	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
eight	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shirt	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coomer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
January	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coomer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Another	O
witness	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Coomer	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
such	O
things	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agreed	O
exactly	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
168.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
February	O
21	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
tommorrow	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
things	O
were	O
pledged	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
servant	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
169.	O
William	B-pers
Wichin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pounds	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alweston	I-pers
,	O
February	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
170.	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goods	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
,	O
February	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
171.	O
William	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Jaunon	I-pers
,	O
January	O
29	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Jaunon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
absented	O
himself	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
service	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
buckles	O
-	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Sun	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Slaymaker	I-pers
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slaymaker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Slaymaker	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
they	O
remained	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Christmas	O
week	O
he	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
[	O
Jaunon	O
]	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
brought	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
[	O
Henry	B-pers
Owden	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
]	O
Slaymaker	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
buckles	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Jaunon	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
buckles	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
[	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
]	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Barlow	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
-	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
spoon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
bring	O
a	O
spoon	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
If	O
your	O
Lordship	O
pleases	O
to	O
hear	O
me	O
.	O
First	O
of	O
all	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
spoon	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
What	O
she	O
wanted	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Five	O
shillings	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
Is	O
the	O
spoon	O
yours	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
brother	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
whether	O
he	O
fetches	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
spoon	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Harrol	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
fellow-servant	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
's	O
(	O
I	O
left	O
his	O
service	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
lady	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
172	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Stansbury	I-pers
*	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Boyers	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Saunshus	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
nighttime	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
ten	O
tin	O
canisters	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
seventy	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
eight	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
six	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
five	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
five	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
September	O
sessions	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mayoralty	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimot	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
bat	O
,	O
perriwig	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
five	O
moidores	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
his	O
[	O
Stansbury	O
's	O
]	O
dwelling-house	O
in	O
Hanging-sword-alley	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
September	O
sessions	O
in	O
that	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
number	O
VII	O
.	O
page	O
250	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
was	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
for	O
that	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
since	O
transported	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
on	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
unbarred	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
an	O
instrument	O
which	O
the	O
coopers	O
use	O
in	O
boring	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
let	O
themselves	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street-door	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
without	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
found	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
area	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
they	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
taking	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
examined	O
separately	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
glass	O
case	O
upon	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
glass	O
case	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
drawer	O
with	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
pounds	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
drawer	O
a	O
small	O
buckle	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
always	O
look	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
they	O
put	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
turned	O
a	O
screw	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
some	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
below	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
casement	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
which	O
screwed	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
unscrewed	O
;	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
half	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
pulled	O
about	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
shop	O
was	O
stripped	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
ten	O
canisters	O
with	O
tea	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
canisters	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
gardener	O
's	O
ground	O
near	O
Aylosse-street	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
shop	O
is	O
in	O
Little	O
Aylosse-street	O
,	O
Goodmans-fields	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mecum	I-pers
.	O
This	O
James	B-pers
Stansbury	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Saunshus	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Boyers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
this	O
Shop	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
tea	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
Saunshus	O
and	O
Boyers	O
are	O
both	O
Jews	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
above	O
stairs	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
ale-house	O
just	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
proper	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
full	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Spring	O
's	O
daughter	O
.	O
]	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Stansbury	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Stansbury	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
This	O
tool	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
[	O
the	O
cooper	O
's	O
tool	O
,	O
mentioned	O
before	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
Stansbury	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
:	O
Stansbury	O
took	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
our	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
a	O
boring	O
some	O
holes	O
in	O
the	O
shutter	O
with	O
the	O
iron	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
this	O
instrument	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
some	O
pewter	O
.	O
The	O
pewter	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
vast	O
great	O
noise	O
:	O
we	O
stood	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Stansbury	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
snuff	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
snuff-box	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
tinder	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
flint	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
candle	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
were	O
without	O
it	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
we	O
always	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
our	O
pockets	O
.	O
Then	O
Stansbury	O
and	O
I	O
accordingly	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
latch	O
and	O
a	O
screw	O
over	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
unscreweed	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
tea	O
canisters	O
,	O
took	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
of	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
shelves	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
thing	O
like	O
a	O
scrutore	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
ink	O
bottle	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
threw	O
down	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
white	O
canvas	O
bag	O
with	O
some	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
afterwards	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
chiefly	O
in	O
half-pence	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
drawers	O
underneath	O
the	O
scrutore	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
ruffled	O
shirts	O
,	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
shirts	O
(	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
having	O
the	O
house	O
searched	O
:	O
)	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
six	O
canisters	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
bundles	O
of	O
linen	O
(	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
bran	O
new	O
pumps	O
)	O
which	O
we	O
carried	O
home	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
we	O
locked	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
away	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
away	O
about	O
four	O
canisters	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
silver	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
brought	O
to	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
broke	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
locked	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
threw	O
the	O
key	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
them	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
find	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
To	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
White	O
Chapel	O
;	O
Boyers	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
stolen	O
goods	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
go	O
a	O
thieving	O
)	O
gave	O
us	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
clothes	O
-	O
what	O
silver	O
there	O
was	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
-	O
we	O
moved	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
Boyer	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
moved	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
room	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
:	O
we	O
emptied	O
the	O
tea	O
before	O
we	O
moved	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
different	O
parcels	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
mix	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
canisters	O
into	O
a	O
garden	O
near	O
a	O
dunghill	O
as	O
you	O
go	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Stepney	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
witnesses	O
who	O
have	O
given	O
their	O
evidence	O
may	O
be	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
questions	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
about	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
coin	O
.	O
[	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
gold	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
coin	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
pence	O
in	O
half	O
pence	O
for	O
my	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
these	O
things	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
your	O
wife	O
was	O
under	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
,	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
this	O
way	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
-	O
He	O
lay	O
there	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
will	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
do	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
been	O
tried	O
for	O
theft	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
before	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
go	O
a	O
thieving	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mecum	O
.	O
You	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stansbury	O
.	O
[	O
After	O
Mr.	O
Stansbury	O
had	O
asked	O
the	O
Evidence	O
what	O
questions	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
into	O
Court	O
again	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
mentioning	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
a	O
bureau	O
:	O
what	O
were	O
they	O
put	O
in	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
-	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
with	O
red	O
strings	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
moidore	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
twenty	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
and	O
some	O
six	O
pences	O
in	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
silver	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
key	O
when	O
you	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
door	O
fastened	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
bolt	O
and	O
a	O
latch	O
which	O
screws	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
screw	O
over	O
the	O
latch	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
screw	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aylosse	O
Street	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
our	O
house	O
is	O
almost	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
month	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Spring	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
October	O
-	O
the	O
sixth	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
?	O
Spring	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
very	O
well	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
man	O
[	O
Mecum	O
.	O
]	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
-	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
I	O
believe	O
till	O
nigh	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
-	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
-	O
they	O
had	O
only	O
three	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
such	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Spring	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
thought	O
you	O
were	O
slippery	O
rogues	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
had	O
that	O
coat	O
and	O
that	O
wig	O
you	O
have	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
sat	O
and	O
slept	O
with	O
your	O
head	O
against	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
by	O
the	O
chimney	O
corner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
there	O
been	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
now	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
persons	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Mecum	O
,	O
Stansbury	O
,	O
and	O
Saunshus	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
induced	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
warrant	O
a	O
gainst	O
these	O
persons	O
and	O
me	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
pretends	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
thieftaker	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
gentleman	O
who	O
is	O
aggrieved	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
eighth	O
or	O
ninth	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Mecum	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
sixth	O
and	O
seventh	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Mecum	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mecum	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
your	O
husband	O
and	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
last	O
October	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
We	O
lived	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
their	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
bringing	O
things	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Stansbury	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
bundle	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
husband	O
brought	O
in	O
some	O
canisters	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
there	O
besides	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
Boyers	O
and	O
Saunshus	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
bundles	O
brought	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
bring	O
them	O
at	O
once	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
at	O
twice	O
-	O
The	O
bundles	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
some	O
canisters	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
canisters	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
this	O
Mecum	O
?	O
Mecum	O
.	O
Five	O
years	O
last	O
Borough	O
Fair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
he	O
got	O
another	O
wife	O
;	O
[	O
the	O
question	O
was	O
not	O
answered	O
:	O
]	O
a	O
man	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
two	O
wives	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
that	O
Mecum	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
a	O
son	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
:	O
[	O
that	O
question	O
was	O
not	O
asked	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
only	O
his	O
whore	O
or	O
mistress	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
indicted	O
as	O
an	O
accessary	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
from	O
last	O
June	O
to	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
absent	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Sanders	O
.	O
Not	O
one	O
whole	O
day	O
,	O
nor	O
one	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
always	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
Sanders	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
a	O
whole	O
night	O
or	O
a	O
whole	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
absent	O
one	O
night	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
?	O
Sanders	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
absent	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clock-maker	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
clock-maker	O
:	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
clock-work	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
clock-maker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
his	O
tools	O
.	O
Walpole	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
young	O
lad	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
had	O
he	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
of	O
business	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
goal	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
ill	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
entrusted	O
me	O
with	O
clocks	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Walpole	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
spring-clock	O
,	O
or	O
table-clock	O
,	O
of	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
or	O
20	O
l.	O
value	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
hand	O
at	O
spring	O
work	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Sanders	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Sun	O
brew-house	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mecum	I-pers
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
lived	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
pick-pocket	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
pastrycook	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Popping's-alley	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
,	O
a	O
pastrycook	O
by	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
made	O
my	O
master	O
a	O
clock	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
frequently	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Walpole	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
when	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
work	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
at	O
Sander	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
she	O
sold	O
second-hand	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
ago	O
since	O
you	O
employed	O
him	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stansbury	I-pers
was	O
(	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
)	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Boyers	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Saunshus	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jemima	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
china	O
,	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
a	O
hood	O
,	O
scarf	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
cloth	O
cloaks	O
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
(	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
)	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
beaver	O
coating	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
-	O
Gray	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
indictments	O
.	O
173.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
goods	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
he	O
took	O
two	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
M	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
twice	O
by	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shillings	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
missing	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Queen	O
's	O
Anne	O
's	O
shillings	O
,	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
neck	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
M	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
tweezers	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Toll	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
pardon	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
174.	O
Mary	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Bagley	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
hungry	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
buckles	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
lay	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Murrow	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
quarreling	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Purpool-lane	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Give	O
Charles	O
his	O
buckles	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
[	O
Charles	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
]	O
might	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Hussey	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
buckles	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ou	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
b	O
-	O
h.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
prison	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
your	O
son	O
's	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
talked	O
very	O
san	O
iliarly	O
.	O
Murrow	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
much	O
acquainted	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
your	O
son	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
victuals	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
well	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Murrow	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
child	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	O
three	O
months	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
.	O
She	O
never	O
lived	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
bed	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
Cha	O
.	O
Murrow	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Purpool-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
tumult	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
elderly	O
woman	O
[	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
]	O
were	O
arguing	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
Old	O
b	O
-	O
h.	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
vile	O
creature	O
in	O
making	O
tumults	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
hired	O
witnesses	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
given	O
them	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
taken	O
me	O
up	O
only	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
conjurer	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
fortune-teller	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cunning	O
man	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
conjurer	O
say	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
neither	O
pawned	O
nor	O
sold	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
left	O
,	O
within	O
five	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Murrow	O
lived	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
gin	O
:	O
and	O
on	O
she	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
Mrs.	O
Murrow	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
Hannah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
about	O
this	O
fortune-teller	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
indeed	O
;	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
mother	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
Charles	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tax	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
recommended	O
to	O
a	O
fortune-teller	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
her	O
skin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
her	O
hair	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
in	O
a	O
glass	O
very	O
perfectly	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
fortune-teller	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
neither	O
told	O
nor	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
within	O
six	O
doors	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
within	O
such	O
a	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lose	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
29th	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
lived	O
with	O
Murrow	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Furrivall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
little	O
baby	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
wrong	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
.	O
Magdalen	O
Stunton	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Murrow	I-pers
's	O
wife	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
some	O
days	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
somebody	O
else	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
200	O
miles	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
has	O
moved	O
off	O
since	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
175	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Faiser	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-church	B-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
till	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
child	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
dog	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
squalled	O
out	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
batcher	O
's	O
dog	O
had	O
get	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
drawer	O
upon	O
the	O
shop	O
floor	O
(	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
fall	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hillary	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
somebody	O
behind	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
dog	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
squalled	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
drawer	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
upon	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
drawer	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
176.	O
John	B-pers
Poulton	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
county	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
+	O
him	O
,	O
December	O
8	O
,	O
1744	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
from	O
Essex	O
.	O
+	O
By	O
an	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1734	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
enacted	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
with	O
any	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
,	O
threats	O
or	O
menaces	O
,	O
violence	O
or	O
by	O
force	O
,	O
shall	O
assault	O
any	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
felony	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
felony	O
that	O
is	O
punishable	O
capitally	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
so	O
offending	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
pretty	O
near	O
Bow	B-place
Church	I-place
on	O
the	O
Essex	B-place
road	I-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Poulton	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
rode	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
he	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
offered	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
certain	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
words	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
justly	O
know	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
surprised	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
rode	O
from	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
a	O
highwayman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
meet	O
you	O
or	O
overtake	O
you	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
He	O
overtook	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
my	O
story	O
to	O
some	O
journeymen	O
carpenters	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Bow	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
riding	O
down	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
whistling	O
:	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
challenged	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
villain	O
that	O
just	O
now	O
offered	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
church	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
from	O
where	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
were	O
describing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
chesnut	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
describing	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
overheard	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
his	O
first	O
attacking	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
spurs	O
to	O
his	O
horse	O
and	O
rode	O
very	O
hard	O
down	O
towards	O
Essex	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
marshes	O
,	O
then	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
chesnut	O
horse	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Titham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
Bow	O
Bridge	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Westham	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	O
Lane	O
came	O
riding	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
highwayman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
:	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
is	O
turned	O
down	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
ways	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
marshes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
rode	O
into	O
the	O
marshes	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
on	O
osier	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
a	O
horse	O
had	O
leaped	O
over	O
.	O
I	O
tracked	O
the	O
prints	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
's	O
feet	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
into	O
the	O
osier-ground	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
highwayman	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
more	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
all	O
on	O
a-breast	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
osier	O
ground	O
;	O
another	O
person	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
fire	O
arms	O
:	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Waylep	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Samuel	B-pers
Poulton	I-pers
stop	O
the	O
gentleman	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Poulton	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Waylep	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
-	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
doing	O
of	O
?	O
Waylep	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
a	O
stage	O
waggon	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
?	O
Waylep	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
his	O
money	O
that	O
minute	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
177	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Reese	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Lestrand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
piece	O
of	O
wood	O
called	O
a	O
cooler	O
oar	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
ear	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
January	O
22	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
manslaughter	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Elers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boiling-house	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sugar	O
refiner	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Savoy	I-place
)	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
from	O
eight	O
to	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
dispute	O
between	O
them	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
misfortune	O
that	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
a	O
pan-man	O
,	O
a	O
superior	O
workman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
double	O
the	O
wages	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
this	O
happened	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
nobody	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
themselves	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
answer	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
his	O
behaviour	O
?	O
Elers	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
addicted	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
civilly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Deickman	I-pers
(	O
surgeon	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
to	O
visit	O
a	O
patient	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
dying	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
patient	O
in	O
a	O
dangerous	O
condition	O
;	O
the	O
blood	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
left	O
ear	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
mouth	O
too	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
behind	O
the	O
ear	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
contusion	O
wound	O
,	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
in	O
breadth	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
deceased	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
misfortune	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
condition	O
to	O
speak	O
?	O
Deickman	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
come	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
wound	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
him	O
this	O
dangerous	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
die	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
me	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
but	O
doubled	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hounsfoot	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
resentment	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
strength	O
he	O
would	O
still	O
have	O
sought	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
said	O
,	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
strike	O
me	O
twice	O
before	O
I	O
struck	O
you	O
?	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
that	O
question	O
neither	O
,	O
but	O
repeated	O
Hounsfoot	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
he	O
vomited	O
a	O
vast	O
quantity	O
of	O
blood	O
;	O
the	O
convulsions	O
seized	O
him	O
so	O
strong	O
,	O
that	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Elers	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
another	O
surgeon	O
;	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Pye	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
only	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
consulted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
scalped	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
trepanned	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
died	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
him	O
dog	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Swede	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
by	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
pronounced	O
the	O
word	O
Hounsfoot	O
twice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
spoke	O
more	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
pleased	O
?	O
Deickman	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
asked	O
afterwards	O
,	O
whether	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
the	O
contusion	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
blow	O
or	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
?	O
Deickman	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
blow	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
vomited	O
so	O
much	O
blood	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
internal	O
sinus	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
blow	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
fist	O
or	O
by	O
an	O
instrument	O
?	O
Deickman	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
an	O
instrument	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
hurt	O
upon	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
an	O
instrument	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Elers	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
wooden	O
oars	O
broke	O
-	O
they	O
are	O
things	O
that	O
we	O
stir	O
the	O
sugars	O
with	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
death	O
by	O
the	O
visitation	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
178	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
field	O
joining	O
to	O
Great	B-place
Marlow	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
Bisham	I-place
and	O
county	B-place
of	I-place
Bucks	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brown	O
bay	O
gelding	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
three	O
inches	O
high	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
the	O
gelding	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
into	O
the	O
market	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
toll	O
book	O
to	O
be	O
tolled	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
's	O
in	O
a	O
news-paper	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
gelding	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hrare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
town	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
when	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
sent	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Friday	O
but	O
one	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
my	O
master	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
remembered	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
remembered	O
the	O
horse	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
or	O
stop	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
further	O
till	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Collins	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
remembered	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
his	O
master	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
just	O
by	O
Long	O
Lane	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
the	O
horse	O
crossed	O
me	O
;	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
man	O
had	O
said	O
came	O
fresh	O
into	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bridle	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
-	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
horse	O
is	O
stole	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
toll	O
book	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
toll	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
seller	O
and	O
the	O
voucher	O
entered	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
met	O
the	O
seller	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
whole	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
tolled	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
voucher	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
voucher	O
said	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
vouch	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
voucher	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
without	O
sending	O
down	O
to	O
great	O
Marlow	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
published	O
an	O
advertisement	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
yesterday	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
fall	O
down	O
and	O
break	O
his	O
arm	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Dunn	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
Dunn	O
wanted	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
soul	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
About	O
fifty	O
yards	O
off	O
the	O
toll-book	O
,	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
voucher	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
toll-book	O
,	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
twenty	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
round	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
charge	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
(	O
constable	O
)	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Grays	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
a	O
farm	O
there	O
some	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
servant	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
another	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
lives	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
gentleman	O
say	O
lately	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
far	O
from	O
thinking	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
he	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
179	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Roger	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dirknell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noble	O
Charles	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
1742	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dirknel	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bolton	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
stockings	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
*	O
.	O
[	O
*	O
Henry	O
Sims	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Margerum	I-pers
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
See	O
that	O
remarkable	O
trial	O
,	O
Sessions	O
paper	O
p.	O
58.	O
trial	O
140	O
.	O
]	O
About	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
or	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
my	O
Lord	O
Duke	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
Duke	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
misfortunate	O
as	O
such	O
people	O
are	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
nothing	O
.	O
Says	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
You	O
lived	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bolton	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
get	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Duke	O
's	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
may	O
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
put	O
our	O
hands	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
a	O
helper	O
or	O
postilion	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
work	O
'd	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
We	O
intended	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
pitch-fork	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
the	O
coachman	O
lay	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
go	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
,	O
with	O
what	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
tie	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
will	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
known	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
taken	O
one	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
came	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
:	O
the	O
bar	O
not	O
being	O
quite	O
broke	O
through	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
it	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
red	O
hot	O
poker	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
how	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
in	O
Thrift-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
we	O
tossed	O
up	O
for	O
,	O
under	O
an	O
arch	O
in	O
Peter	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
won	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
were	O
together	O
?	O
Sims	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
there	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
since	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
twenty	O
people	O
into	O
his	O
information	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
from	O
being	O
a	O
soldier	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
twenty	O
people	O
into	O
his	O
information	O
before	O
the	O
woman	O
should	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
who	O
had	O
ruined	O
herself	O
upon	O
his	O
account	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
asked	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uptebake	I-pers
,	O
whether	O
putting	O
twenty	O
people	O
in	O
his	O
information	O
would	O
not	O
save	O
the	O
woman	O
from	O
ruin	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
for	O
debt	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
ruined	O
herself	O
upon	O
his	O
account	O
.	O
Sims	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
Irish	O
evidence	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
had	O
been	O
a	O
voyage	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
stab	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
-	O
(	O
next	O
April	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
*	O
two	O
years	O
)	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
ill	O
of	O
an	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
for	O
some	O
months	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
does	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
last	O
July	O
was	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
in	O
Jun	O
Walker	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sick	O
of	O
the	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
May	O
,	O
June	O
,	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
months	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
in	O
May	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
in	O
May	O
,	O
June	O
,	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
months	O
more	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Bailey	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
last	O
May	O
was	O
two	O
years	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
wound	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
of	O
an	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
for	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
in	O
May	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
undertake	O
any	O
enterprize	O
of	O
this	O
nature	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Goostry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stabbed	O
last	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
civilly	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
other	O
people	O
talk	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Raven	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
people	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
condemn	O
him	O
myself	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
stab	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
-	O
He	O
lodged	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
ill	O
of	O
an	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
consined	O
and	O
uncapable	O
of	O
working	O
?	O
Raven	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
people	O
in	O
that	O
distemper	O
are	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
so	O
all	O
the	O
six	O
months	O
?	O
Raven	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
May	O
and	O
June	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
180	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Portugal	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
19	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
thirty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
indigo	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Miles	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
I	O
put	O
5	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
money	O
(	O
about	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
)	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Bell-alley	I-place
in	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
garden	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
tenements	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
:	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
parlour	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
goods	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
presented	O
itself	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
entirely	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
cut	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
surprized	O
,	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
saw	O
that	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
papers	O
ransacked	O
and	O
turned	O
reply	O
turvy	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Harry	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
and	O
ruined	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
possible	O
you	O
can	O
lie	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
?	O
He	O
made	O
his	O
excuse	O
,	O
quivered	O
and	O
shook	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
little	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cat	O
came	O
and	O
purred	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
pistol	O
was	O
loaded	O
and	O
primed	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
.	O
The	O
thing	O
was	O
very	O
artfully	O
managed	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
marks	O
of	O
clay	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
lock	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
clay	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
foot	O
entirely	O
(	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
his	O
toe	O
there	O
)	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
untouched	O
;	O
this	O
silver	O
medal	O
and	O
this	O
copper	O
medil	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
where	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
untouched	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
individual	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Portugal	O
piece	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
wall	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
support	O
of	O
brick	O
work	O
;	O
those	O
bricks	O
were	O
loose	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
favour	O
the	O
notion	O
of	O
somebody	O
's	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
height	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
robbing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
concluded	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
creatures	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
somebody	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
