TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1745	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Whywall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tredgett	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Lathwaite	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
,	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Strangeways	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Bullmore	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fettyplace	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cosh	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
.	O
189.	O
Philip	B-pers
Launder	I-pers
,	O
*	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
17th	O
.	O
*	O
A	O
black	O
.	O
Charity	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kirby	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
the	O
spoon	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
2	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
black	O
man	O
who	O
came	O
accidentally	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
dined	O
with	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Quillet	I-pers
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Launder	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
master	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Colonel	O
Sparkes	B-pers
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
by	O
Red	O
Lion	O
Square	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
you	O
have	O
certainly	O
stole	O
this	O
spoon	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
Esq	O
;	O
Kirby	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
then	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
-	O
a	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kirby	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
from	O
Antegoa	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
thing	O
if	O
a	O
man	O
asks	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
steal	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
anger	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
plate	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
190.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rosse	I-pers
.	O
+	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4th	O
.	O
+	O
She	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
December	O
sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
No	O
1.	O
page	O
7	O
,	O
Trial	O
22.	O
Robert	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
pretended	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
understand	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ellingsworth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rigg	O
's	O
in	O
Pall	B-place
Mall	I-place
,	O
produced	O
a	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
charity	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
off	O
the	O
shopboard	O
,	O
she	O
held	O
her	O
apron	O
up	O
to	O
screen	O
her	O
from	O
being	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
swept	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
shopboard	O
.	O
She	O
spoke	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
dumb	O
[	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
seemingly	O
an	O
impediment	O
in	O
her	O
speech	O
]	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Riggs	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
wind	O
was	O
very	O
high	O
that	O
day	O
and	O
had	O
blown	O
them	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
191	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
March	O
2d	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Master	O
's	O
door	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
)	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
going	O
along	O
;	O
who	O
should	O
follow	O
them	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
they	O
walked	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
draw	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
pocket	O
is	O
picked	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Short	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
breast	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
opinion	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Blake	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
opinion	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
192.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Faulcon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
carpet	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
De	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28th	O
.	O
Lyon	O
Solomon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Costa	O
in	O
Jefferies	B-place
Square	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
beating	O
a	O
carpet	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
Leah	B-pers
Cohen	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Jacob	B-pers
Faulcon	I-pers
go	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
carpet	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
carpet	O
.	O
Leah	B-pers
Cohen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Jacob	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
beating	O
a	O
carpet	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
with	O
a	O
carpet	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulders	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Caton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
along	O
Shoreditch	O
with	O
a	O
carpet	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
something	O
over	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
this	O
carpet	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
breaking	O
up	O
house	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
193.	O
Peter	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14th	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sellon	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
of	O
Southwark	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
silver	O
in	O
exchange	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
[	O
The	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
produced	O
without	O
lid	O
or	O
bottom	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
appearing	O
so	O
very	O
suspicious	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
two	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lacey	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
goal	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
Mrs.	O
Burgess	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
tankard	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
(	O
constable	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lacey	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
fellow	O
's	O
great	O
surprise	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Burgess	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Beer	I-pers
in	O
Devonshire-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
tankard	O
there	O
wrote	O
round	O
the	O
bottom	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
cut	O
it	O
out	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Burgess	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
.	O
Justice	O
Lacey	O
's	O
clerk	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
information	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
signed	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
The	O
confession	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
feloniously	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Burgess	O
a	O
quart	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
Messrs	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Humphry	O
Sellon	O
silversmiths	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
of	O
Southwark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sellon	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
rather	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
liquor	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
194	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Udall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
*	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
offence	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
preceding	O
trial	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
capital	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
indictment	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Udall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
Crooked	B-place
Billet	I-place
by	O
the	O
Hermitage-stairs	B-place
.	O
This	O
tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
only	O
by	O
information	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lame	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Udall	I-pers
.	O
Just	O
after	O
the	O
brewers	O
had	O
done	O
starting	O
beer	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
two	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
two	O
silver	O
tankards	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
brewers	O
?	O
Udall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
the	O
brewer	O
's	O
servants	O
?	O
Udall	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
twelve	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Catliff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Udall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
brewers	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
tankards	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
brewers	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
one	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Catliff	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
such	O
a	O
ragged	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
to	O
warm	O
some	O
beer	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
brewers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
tankard	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wonnell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Ashfield	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
tankard	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Wonnell	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
bury	O
it	O
under	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
eat	O
and	O
drink	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Wonnell	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
lumper	O
of	O
ships	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
so	O
in	O
a	O
vulgar	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
unlivering	O
of	O
ships	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
his	O
landlady	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
wrong	O
in	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
fork	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
push	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
murdered	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
prevented	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
deliver	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ashfield	O
?	O
Wonnell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
a	O
lye	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ashfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lodge	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
then	O
?	O
Ashfield	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Ashfield	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
for	O
you	O
(	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
me	O
)	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
place	O
,	O
Ned	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
sell	O
a	O
trembling	O
and	O
shaking	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wonnell	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
thieving	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
concern	O
with	O
stolen	O
goods	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
Ashfield	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
again	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
your	O
not	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Ashfield	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
till	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
cried	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Farer	I-pers
(	O
a	O
waterman	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Udall	O
's	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
his	O
head	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
brewers	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
away	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
fare	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Udall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ashfield	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
collared	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
strangled	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
these	O
tormenters	O
.	O
[	O
A	O
flesh	O
fork	O
,	O
used	O
in	O
taking	O
meat	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
jobbed	O
this	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
hit	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
overpowered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
oppose	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
tankard	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
some	O
sugar	O
hogsheads	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
buried	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
dunghill	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
landlady	O
Mrs.	O
Ashfield	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
cry	O
it	O
or	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
occasion	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
cry	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dunghill	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
landlady	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
Ashfield	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
advise	O
him	O
to	O
cry	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
advise	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
cry	O
it	O
?	O
Ashfield	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
cry	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
but	O
God	O
and	O
your	O
honour	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
never	O
an	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
can	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
ill	O
word	O
.	O
Ashfield	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
195.	O
Mary	B-pers
Exton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sawkill	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
196.	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Swawbrook	I-pers
,	O
*	B-pers
otherwise	O
Beakley	B-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Pingo	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tip	O
of	O
a	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
Sep	O
.	O
Sessions	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Heathcote	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
(	O
her	O
own	O
father	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
pag	O
.	O
29.	O
trial	O
78.	O
Richard	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
ale	O
house	O
in	O
King	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
serve	O
Mr.	O
Pingo	O
,	O
an	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
pot	O
at	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
mug	O
tipped	O
with	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pingo	O
)	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
mug	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
mug	O
delivered	O
to	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
one	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
drink	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
drink	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
as	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
mug	O
was	O
tipped	O
with	O
silver	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
and	O
sold	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
son-in-law	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
transport	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
to	O
separate	O
me	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pingo	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
mug	O
tipped	O
with	O
silver	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
silver	O
off	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
melt	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
jeweller	O
.	O
She	O
afterwards	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
197	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	I-pers
otherwise	O
Graham	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
ruby	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
an	O
India	O
damask	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
calimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Sept.	O
19th	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uptebake	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uptebake	I-pers
.	O
+	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
Leekey	O
,	O
Robinson	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
+	O
He	O
was	O
evidence	O
in	O
December	O
Sessions	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Leekey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
executed	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
paper	O
,	O
No	O
1.	O
of	O
this	O
Mayorality	O
page	O
5	O
,	O
Trials	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
Only	O
in	O
selling	O
brass	O
rings	O
,	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
upon	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
house	O
(	O
just	O
by	O
Oxford	O
Chapel	O
)	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
a	O
jar	O
;	O
Leekey	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Robinson	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
Between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
Leekey	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
chin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
them	O
tumble	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Leekey	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
some	O
bitter	O
imprecations	O
;	O
and	O
made	O
Graham	O
[	O
the	O
prisoner	O
]	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
:	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
[	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
under	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
these	O
goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
]	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
news	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Graham	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
labour	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
while	O
Leekey	O
,	O
Robinson	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
divide	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
Between	O
Leekey	O
,	O
Robinson	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
and	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
that	O
Leekey	O
concealed	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Leekey	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
difference	O
about	O
them	O
(	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Leekey	O
had	O
concealed	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
advertisement	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fight	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Church	O
Lane	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
Graham	O
said	O
to	O
Leekey	O
had	O
cheated	O
him	O
in	O
pawning	O
the	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
and	O
knee	O
buckles	O
;	O
and	O
Leekey	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
Graham	O
had	O
cheated	O
him	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
in	O
selling	O
brass	O
rings	O
for	O
gold	O
ones	O
,	O
in	O
not	O
giving	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
Graham	O
off	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
twice	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
far	O
off	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
*	O
enterprise	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
upon	O
.	O
*	O
Uptebake	O
in	O
the	O
information	O
he	O
made	O
before	O
justice	O
Poulson	O
differs	O
very	O
much	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
swars	O
now	O
:	O
for	O
there	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
amounted	O
to	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
could	O
he	O
expect	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
design	O
to	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
your	O
information	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
high	O
constable	O
?	O
Uptebake	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
occasion	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
upon	O
such	O
trifling	O
affairs	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
first	O
what	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
instrument	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
information	O
-	O
He	O
never	O
committed	O
any	O
other	O
robbery	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
198	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
enamelled	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
chrystal	O
stone	O
set	O
therein	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
April	O
6th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
flushed	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
night	O
cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
Somerset-gate	B-place
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
any	O
beer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
)	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
drinking	O
,	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
dropped	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
waked	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
ragged	O
condition	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
ill	O
language	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
ring	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
will	O
hurt	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
hat	O
sell	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
closet	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
ring	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
drummer	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
in	O
soldiers	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
drummer	O
's	O
habit	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
would	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
ring	O
.	O
Finding	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Butcher	O
Row	O
by	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
there	O
(	O
she	O
was	O
here	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
)	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Catharine	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
white	O
stockings	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
dirty	O
)	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
occasion	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
impertinent	O
in	O
her	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
offer	O
you	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
fair	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
crown	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
ring	O
was	O
pawned	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
besides	O
what	O
the	O
ring	O
is	O
pawned	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
her	O
poor	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
ring	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
witnesses	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
this	O
night	O
cellar	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
ring	O
off	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
sleeping	O
with	O
his	O
head	O
upon	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
acquaint	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
bosom	O
:	O
What	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
afterwards	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
ring	O
sold	O
afterwards	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
for	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
ring	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
ring	O
off	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
drummer	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
drummer	O
stood	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
finger	O
.	O
Carter	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
ring	O
to	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
mother-in-law	O
(	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
)	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Tyler	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
199	O
,	O
200.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Buckles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
setting	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Buckles	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
sold	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
at	O
her	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
tumble	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Then	O
Booth	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
tumble	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
goods	O
.	O
She	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
:	O
then	O
Dorothy	O
Buckles	O
tore	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
a	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
(	O
a	O
bookseller	O
at	O
Gray	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
gate	I-place
,	O
in	O
Holburn	B-place
)	O
and	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Griffiths	O
cry	O
out	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
run	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
to	O
hold	O
her	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
Buckles	O
owned	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
Booth	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
201.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wilsden	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
cock	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
ducks	O
,	O
price	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Wilsden	B-place
green	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
these	O
two	O
neighbours	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
hens	O
killed	O
,	O
one	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
ducks	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
disturbed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
bag	O
while	O
the	O
fowls	O
were	O
killing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burr	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
gun	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
neighbour	O
Paulin	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
hen-house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
gun	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
at	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
One	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
snow	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
lamp	O
lighter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
trimming	O
of	O
lamps	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paulin	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Burr	I-pers
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
men	O
gone	O
by	O
with	O
empty	O
bag	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
hen-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
7	O
hens	O
,	O
4	O
ducks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cock	O
killed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
202.	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
And	O
203.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
[	O
Mrs	O
Goddard	O
being	O
a	O
French	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
her	O
evidence	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
]	O
The	O
saturday	O
before	O
Easter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
by	O
the	O
7	B-place
dials	I-place
;	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shewed	O
them	O
2	O
pieces	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
thrown	O
something	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
stooped	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
[	O
She	O
being	O
very	O
ancient	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoners	O
]	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
White	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
these	O
goods	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
[	O
Soames	O
]	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
.	O
[	O
a	O
girl	O
about	O
13	O
]	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
brought	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
in	O
a	O
round	O
about	O
apron	O
,	O
last	O
saturday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
pieces	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
from	O
an	O
hundred	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
house	O
were	O
they	O
brought	O
into	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
Into	O
Harry	B-pers
White	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
's	O
.	O
They	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
near	O
Holburn	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Soames	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
her	O
measure	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
measuring	O
them	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
White	O
wanted	O
me	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Price	I-pers
*	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Cobler	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
heart	O
misgave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
:	O
and	O
White	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
by	O
fair	O
means	O
or	O
by	O
foul	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
somebody	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
*	O
A	O
boy	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
indicted	O
this	O
Session	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
razors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
for	O
transportation	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
White	O
follow	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
Thieving	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
harbours	O
thieves	O
;	O
and	O
takes	O
children	O
away	O
from	O
their	O
friends	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
Howell	O
before	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shuckburgh	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Seawell	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Harry	B-pers
White	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Seawell	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
these	O
linens	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
Soames	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Seawell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
White	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
linens	O
in	O
Soames	O
's	O
custody	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
proprietor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Goddard	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
linens	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Goddard	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
little	O
Saffron	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
35	O
years	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
market-woman	O
,	O
I	O
sell	O
cucumbers	O
or	O
potatoes	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
season	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
mother-in-law	O
to	O
this	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
harbours	O
nothing	O
but	O
thieves	O
.	O
Hams	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
White	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
buying	O
something	O
of	O
me	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
White	O
?	O
Hams	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Carman	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
hill	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dust	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Bibby	O
?	O
Hams	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
trained	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
cradle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
she	O
been	O
trained	O
up	O
to	O
?	O
Hams	O
.	O
To	O
swearing	O
and	O
cursing	O
,	O
and	O
evil-doings	O
,	O
vile	O
doings	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
knows	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Bibby	O
bring	O
things	O
into	O
Howell	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
turned	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
White	O
never	O
lay	O
a	O
night	O
in	O
Howell	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
sometimes	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
dram	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Temple	O
.	O
Upon	O
little	O
Saffron	O
hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Hams	O
?	O
Temple	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
Yes	O
she	O
does	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
live	O
together	O
.	O
Temple	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Hams	O
?	O
Temple	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
White	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
a	O
dust	O
cart	O
in	O
Thames	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
lives	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
Howell	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Temple	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
mistake	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
204	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Keep	I-pers
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
weather	O
sheep	O
,	O
price	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
ram	O
,	O
price	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10th	O
.	O
205.	O
William	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
lost	O
thirteen	O
weather	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ram	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	I-place
;	O
we	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
skins	O
sold	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
of	O
Southwark	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
marks	O
were	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
skins	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
fifteen	O
sheep	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
was	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
suspicion	O
they	O
were	O
drove	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pickett	O
.	O
The	O
widow	O
Carter	O
lost	O
14	O
sheep	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
where	O
the	O
skins	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
which	O
we	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
in	O
Barnaby	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
skins	O
of	O
those	O
sheep	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
lost	O
?	O
Pickett	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
badly	O
marked	O
,	O
but	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
our	O
opinion	O
they	O
are	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
mark	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
blind	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
letters	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Brownscomb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
sheep	O
of	O
S	O
amuel	O
Keep	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
13	O
weathers	O
and	O
a	O
ram	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Keep	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
butcher	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
I	O
carry	O
on	O
business	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
Keep	O
when	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
that	O
killed	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
Stone	O
and	O
Scals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
buy	O
so	O
many	O
sheep	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
farmer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
skins	O
taken	O
off	O
when	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
market	O
price	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
17	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Cable	O
street	O
by	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
a	O
usual	O
place	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
in	O
?	O
Brownscomb	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
killed	O
in	O
a	O
common	O
slaughter-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brownscomb	I-pers
.	O
Stone	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
countryman	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
sheep	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
for	O
his	O
landlord	O
.	O
And	O
Scales	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
rented	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
reduced	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
the	O
sheep	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Sam	O
Keep	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
:	O
Kingsland	O
was	O
about	O
buying	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
people	O
told	O
Keep	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
flung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
dress	O
those	O
fourteen	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dressed	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
common	O
price	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
sheep	O
.	O
Keep	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Scales	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
beast	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Keep	O
and	O
Kingsland	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Star	O
in	O
Mill	O
yard	O
,	O
Goodman's-fields	O
.	O
Keep	O
said	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
Stone	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
four	O
of	O
those	O
sheep	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
killed	O
ten	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
Keep	O
?	O
Scales	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
clay	O
carter	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
farmer	O
?	O
Scales	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
married	O
the	O
widow	O
Wood	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
farm	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
Brownscomb	O
this	O
?	O
Scales	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
broke	O
or	O
breaking	O
?	O
Scales	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
goods	O
off	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
satisfy	O
his	O
landlord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
Brownscomb	O
so	O
?	O
Scales	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
stall	O
just	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Cable	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Kingsland	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
sheep	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Holland	O
.	O
My	O
opinion	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
opinion	O
Keep	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
doing	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Kingsland	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
[	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Kingsland	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Kingsland	O
a	O
butcher	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
no	O
butcher	O
;	O
he	O
suckles	O
calves	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Kingsland	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
sheep	O
skins	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
in	O
Barnaby	O
Street	O
.	O
Keep	O
delivered	O
the	O
skins	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
slaughter	O
house	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
Kingsland	O
stood	O
by	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
next	O
day	O
for	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
skins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
Kingsland	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
skins	O
?	O
East	O
.	O
Very	O
honestly	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
One	O
Robinson	O
bought	O
the	O
skins	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
14	O
skins	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
skins	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
East	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
Keep	O
's	O
skins	O
.	O
He	O
may	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
may	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
mark	O
had	O
the	O
skins	O
?	O
East	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
mark	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
Scales	O
and	O
East	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
skins	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Robinson	O
paid	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
the	O
14	O
skins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
To	O
Kingsland	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Scales	O
.	O
What	O
mark	O
had	O
these	O
sheep	O
?	O
Scales	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
red	O
oker	O
behind	O
the	O
pole	O
of	O
the	O
neck	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
mark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
's	O
mark	O
?	O
Pickett	O
.	O
Her	O
mark	O
is	O
R	O
P	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
mark	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
sheep	O
from	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
up	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
now	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Keep	O
forty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Justice	O
Bourne	O
of	O
Enfield	O
.	O
This	O
confession	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Keep	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
signed	O
it	O
freely	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
information	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
information	O
faith	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
1744	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
called	O
Fenny-Coats	O
about	O
14	O
sheep	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
widow	O
Carter	O
of	O
Enfield	O
;	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
into	O
Church	O
lane	O
,	O
near	O
White	O
Chapel	O
church	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
killed	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Scales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
carcasses	O
to	O
John	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Brownscomb	I-pers
for	O
5	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
fat	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
mulberry	O
garden	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
sold	O
the	O
skins	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Taken	O
before	O
me	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1744	O
.	O
-	O
Bourne	O
.	O
Signed	O
Sam	B-pers
Keep	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
me	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
,	O
nor	O
read	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
Keep	O
said	O
that	O
Kingsland	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
when	O
or	O
where	O
they	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
seems	O
to	O
agree	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
what	O
Holland	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believes	O
Kingsland	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
instrument	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Keep	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
sheep	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
Mr.	O
Kingsland	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
sheep	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
sheep	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
Kingsland	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lessingham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Kingsland	O
forty	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
drove	O
a	O
cart	O
as	O
a	O
scavinger	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
gentlemens	O
cellars	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
plate	O
in	O
plenty	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Keep	O
,	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Kingsland	O
acquitted	O
.	O
206.	O
John	B-pers
Sommers	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Sommerville	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
after	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
1734	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
1745	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
forcible	O
and	O
violent	O
manner	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
feloniously	O
did	O
demand	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
to	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
(	O
a	O
black	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stopped	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
James	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
trumpet	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
now	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
at	O
Pancras	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
neither	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
away	O
)	O
He	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
jumped	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
and	O
hawled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
all	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
no	O
good	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
black	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
good	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
attacked	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
gone	O
yet	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
hold	O
and	O
run	O
.	O
There	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
lady	O
in	O
the	O
church-yard	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
action	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
strike	O
at	O
you	O
with	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
an	O
empty	O
cag	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
you	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
He	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
easy	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
down	O
with	O
.	O
James	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
cag	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
himself	O
naked	O
to	O
fight	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
attack	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
-	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mustafer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Mr.	O
James	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Pancras	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
with	O
a	O
cask	O
or	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
first	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
Mustaser	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
and	O
revenge	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
gone	O
yet	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
?	O
Mustaser	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
Mustafer	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
me	O
upon	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mustafer	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
be	O
gone	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
action	O
done	O
.	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
his	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
in	O
Pancras	O
church-yard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
his	O
bag	O
and	O
strike	O
at	O
the	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
some	O
persons	O
who	O
came	O
by	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Turnell	I-pers
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
weapon	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
(	O
the	O
beadle	O
.	O
)	O
About	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
submitted	O
himself	O
and	O
asked	O
pardon	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
run	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
;	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
liquors	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
liquors	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
otherwise	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
will	O
get	O
drunk	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawksley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
buys	O
brandy	O
frequently	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
credit	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
conceive	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
tenant	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pains-taking	O
,	O
hardworking	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
vast	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsom	O
when	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsom	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
Though	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
assault	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
;	O
which	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
compromised	O
between	O
the	O
parties	O
.	O
207.	O
Jane	B-pers
Rankin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
twelve	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
dishes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
saucepans	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
coffee	O
pots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
chocolate	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28th	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
to	O
Bristol	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
father	O
last	O
January	O
was	O
twelve	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
goods	O
in	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
was	O
twelve	O
month	O
following	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
hinges	O
of	O
my	O
boxes	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
locks	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
fore	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
sister	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
back	O
garret	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
moved	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
their	O
conduct	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
at	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Cobbeau	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cobbeau	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
this	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
copper	O
chocolate	O
pot	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
linen	O
;	O
sheets	O
,	O
table	O
linen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
large	O
trunk	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
large	O
parcel	O
of	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
between	O
40	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
Helena	B-pers
Cobbeau	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
pawn	O
above	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
chocolate	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
coffee	O
pot	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Giles	O
proved	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
helped	O
Mrs.	O
Giles	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
things	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
chocolate	O
pot	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Giles	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Caveac	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
her	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
dislike	O
.	O
Five	O
or	O
six	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
English	O
,	O
Dutch	O
and	O
French	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
five	O
,	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
deal	O
in	O
lace	O
,	O
cambricks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
have	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
those	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
to	O
their	O
customers	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
might	O
have	O
wronged	O
them	O
very	O
considerably	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
208.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hallam	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16th	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
these	O
three	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
odd	O
shoe	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
cutting	O
board	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
odd	O
shoe	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
gouty	O
foot	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
209.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2d	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
210	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
these	O
goods	O
from	O
Bristol	O
fair	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Cups	I-place
in	O
Bread	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
there	O
till	O
called	O
for	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
keeps	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Bragg	O
.	O
One	O
Roberts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
clothes	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
Lady-Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Bragg	O
.	O
How	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
barber	O
's	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
-	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fraser	O
(	O
one	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
oil	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
)	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
any	O
cloth	O
(	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
cloth	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
)	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
wrong	O
season	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
for	O
such	O
cloths	O
as	O
these	O
(	O
they	O
are	O
kerseys	O
or	O
narrow	O
cloths	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
outright	O
;	O
for	O
Mr	O
Fraser	O
is	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
book-keeper	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
years	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
cloths	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
buy	O
those	O
cloths	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
them	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
.	O
This	O
made	O
some	O
words	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
divide	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
who	O
owned	O
that	O
the	O
cloths	O
were	O
his	O
?	O
Bragg	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
cloths	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
as	O
fair	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
hostler	O
at	O
an	O
inn	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Three	O
Cups	O
in	O
Bread	O
street	O
)	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
inn	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
porter	O
at	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Fraser	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
these	O
cloths	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
the	O
cloths	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
look	O
upon	O
these	O
cloths	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
good	O
judge	O
of	O
cloths	O
;	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
2	O
pieces	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
gate	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
he	O
been	O
thought	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Fraser	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
ge	O
t	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
ramble	O
into	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
nonsense	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
wandered	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Fraser	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
gone	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
with	O
his	O
words	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
notice	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
thought	O
him	O
disordered	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
cloths	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
advised	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Fraser	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
But	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
spoke	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
advised	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fraser	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
brother-in-law	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
4	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
maker	O
was	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
wanted	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
for	O
ready	O
money	O
[	O
exactly	O
half	O
the	O
price	O
they	O
are	O
laid	O
at	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
]	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pattern	O
to	O
show	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
dealer	O
in	O
cloths	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
bargain	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
spoke	O
to	O
about	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
insisting	O
upon	O
part	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
my	O
two	O
pieces	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
for	O
six	O
pence	O
a	O
yard	O
profit	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
in	O
Woodstreet	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
chamberlain	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Cups	O
in	O
Bread	O
street	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
truss	O
that	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bragg	O
,	O
the	O
maker	O
of	O
these	O
cloths	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
there	O
till	O
called	O
for	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
cloths	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jarvis	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
agent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bragg	O
,	O
and	O
puts	O
up	O
his	O
goods	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
truss	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
chamberlain	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
has	O
he	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
absent	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
time	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
George	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
truss	O
of	O
cloth	O
that	O
was	O
here	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
carter	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
quite	O
away	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
sure	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
some	O
inn	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
done	O
business	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Whaley	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
porter	O
to	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
ironmongers	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
truss	O
to	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Monmouth	O
street	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
his	O
labour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
he	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
disordered	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
absent	O
from	O
his	O
business	O
sometimes	O
?	O
Whaley	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
drunk	O
with	O
gin	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
absent	O
him	O
self	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
cholick	O
and	O
gripes	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
gallery	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
in	O
Woodstreet	O
;	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
in	O
the	O
gallery	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
gallery	O
any	O
ways	O
locked	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
cloth	O
lodged	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
in	O
the	O
gallery	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
this	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
helped	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
knott	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
truss	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
how	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
weighed	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
wrapper	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
cloth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
crested	O
plains	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
of	O
these	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
cut	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
,	O
And	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
my	O
neighbour	O
's	O
behalf	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
times	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
forced	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
absent	O
from	O
his	O
family	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
fortnight	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
Patrick	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
lunacy	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
,	O
at	O
Holborn	O
bridge	O
.	O
Some	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
brains	O
being	O
turned	O
.	O
Jury	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fraser	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
disordered	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
sometimes	O
?	O
Fraser	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
in	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
gone	O
home	O
for	O
a	O
whole	O
eight	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
opinion	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
condition	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
cloths	O
?	O
Fraser	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
spoke	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
,	O
how	O
was	O
he	O
when	O
you	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Lamb	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
appeared	O
any	O
ways	O
delirious	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
,	O
how	O
is	O
he	O
in	O
general	O
?	O
Whaley	O
.	O
Pretty	O
well	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
delirious	O
sometimes	O
?	O
Whaley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
211	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
,	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
velvet	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
ten	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
hair	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
accounts	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
ledger	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
Inn	I-place
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
town	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Woolverhampton	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
warehouse	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Whaley	O
's	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
trunk	O
with	O
my	O
clothes	O
in	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
clothes	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
street	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
sold	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
different	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
ruffles	O
off	O
these	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
intended	O
them	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Fox	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
porter	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
inn	O
.	O
And	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
turned	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
doubt	O
his	O
honesty	O
when	O
you	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
?	O
Fox	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
drinking	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
absent	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
get	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
gin	O
shops	O
at	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
Monmouth	O
street	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
accounts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee-buckles	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
business	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
in	O
Woodstreet	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
lodging	O
room	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mind	O
whether	O
his	O
trunk	O
was	O
safe	O
?	O
Elton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Elton	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
unlockt	O
,	O
which	O
surprised	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
chamberlain	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
room	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
possessession	O
of	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
such	O
a	O
slender	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
cloths	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
from	O
us	O
in	O
Chiswell	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
paper	O
of	O
accounts	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Fox	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
receipt	O
is	O
upon	O
it	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Elton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
or	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
tied	O
round	O
with	O
a	O
rope	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
the	O
father	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
cry	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
three	O
weeks	O
selling	O
cloths	O
and	O
shalloons	O
for	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
4	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
the	O
person	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
tallish	O
man	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Fish	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
+	O
Hester	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
damask	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
9	O
diaper	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
chaldron	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
8	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
ivory	O
handle	O
knives	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
7	O
ivory	O
handle	O
forks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
China	O
bason	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
glass	O
decanter	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
6	O
towels	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s	O
.	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
rubbers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
19th	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shirley	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
keeps	O
the	O
Greyhound-tavern	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
these	O
14	O
napkins	O
,	O
5	O
knives	O
,	O
6	O
forks	O
,	O
8	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
China	O
bason	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
decanter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
losing	O
things	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
7	O
dozen	O
of	O
napkins	O
within	O
in	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
nine	O
months	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
knives	O
,	O
forks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Philip	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
these	O
napkins	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
ale-house	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
towels	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sewed	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
aprons	O
,	O
5	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
forks	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
6	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
coals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
suspect	O
her	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
turned	O
of	O
fourteen	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
this	O
iron	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
's	O
coals	O
lay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
apprentice	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
A	O
good	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
the	O
coals	O
out	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
coals	O
out	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
often	O
emptied	O
the	O
cellar	O
of	O
the	O
coals	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
helped	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
knives	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
pin	O
napkins	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
her	O
bring	O
away	O
any	O
napkins	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
bring	O
any	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
away	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
some	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
bring	O
these	O
things	O
away	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
beat	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
burnt	O
the	O
coals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
napkins	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
laid	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
to	O
eat	O
her	O
victuals	O
off	O
-	O
She	O
used	O
the	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
forks	O
when	O
she	O
eat	O
her	O
victuals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
instance	O
of	O
her	O
selling	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Foley	I-pers
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
,	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
,	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
trimmed	O
the	O
coals	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Robson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
carry	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
stop	O
her	O
?	O
Robson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
because	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
coals	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
buy	O
them	O
better	O
and	O
cheaper	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
begged	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
recommend	O
her	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
213.	O
Martha	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
otherwise	O
Graham	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
On	O
Shrove-Tuesday	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
that	O
was	O
printed	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
about	O
two	O
pound	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Craft	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
sister	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
box-iron	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
(	O
fearing	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
has	O
stole	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
pattern	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
I	O
lost	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
eight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
bought	O
them	O
gave	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
5	O
s.	O
*	O
for	O
the	O
half	O
dozen	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
said	O
they	O
cost	O
him	O
twenty	O
one	O
shillings	O
a	O
dozen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fudge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
22	O
d.	O
or	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
.	O
[	O
A	O
girl	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
Stamper	O
's	O
own	O
aunt	O
]	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
day	O
's	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
make	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
day	O
's	O
work	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
come	O
very	O
well	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
this	O
?	O
Stamper	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
ale-house	O
by	O
the	O
Monument	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
(	O
the	O
basket	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
hanged	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
hurt	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
which	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blue	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cambrick	O
worth	O
10	O
s.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
my	O
aunt	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
little	O
impudent	O
jade	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sell	O
a	O
licking	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
angry	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Said	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
carrying	O
my	O
girl	O
a	O
thieving	O
.	O
Q	O
