TOKEN	NE
The	O
Black	O
Book	O
of	O
Newgate	O
OR	O
AN	O
EXACT	O
COLLECTION	O
OF	O
THE	O
Most	O
material	O
Proceedings	O
AT	O
ALL	O
The	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
baily	O
,	O
For	O
Eighteen	O
months	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
Particularly	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Tryals	O
of	O
John	O
Smith	O
George	O
Marshall	O
John	O
Darkin	O
Michael	O
Jones	O
Charles	O
Potter	O
Henry	O
Seabrooke	O
Elizabeth	O
Longman	O
Frances	O
Watson	O
,	O
alias	O
Riggs	O
.	O
Charles	O
Godfry	O
Roger	O
Withers	O
Matthew	O
Walkenden	O
John	O
Evans	O
John	O
Seabrooke	O
William	O
Minors	O
Arthur	O
Minors	O
Richard	O
Shaw	O
Thomas	O
Sadler	O
William	O
Johnson	O
Robert	O
William	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Dine	O
Nicholas	O
Throckmorten	O
William	O
Dennis	O
Mary	O
Hicks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
AS	O
ALSO	O
REFLECTIONS	O
and	O
OBSERVATIONS	O
on	O
several	O
Passages	O
.	O
Set	O
forth	O
for	O
a	O
Publick	O
warning	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
read	O
it	O
by	O
JF	O
.	O
IM	O
.	O
Gent	O
.	O
With	O
Allowance	O
.	O
Ro	O
.	O
L'Estrange	O
.	O
London	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
D.	O
M.	O
1677	O
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Sessions	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
for	O
Eighteen	O
months	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
THough	O
this	O
Collection	O
was	O
intended	O
only	O
for	O
one	O
year	O
past	O
before	O
this	O
present	O
Aug.	O
1677	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
(	O
if	O
encouraged	O
by	O
General	O
Acceptance	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
annually	O
continued	O
,	O
yet	O
we	O
shall	O
reflect	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
begin	O
with	O
.	O
An	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
sessions	O
before	O
Easter-Term	O
1676	O
,	O
beginning	O
April	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
then	O
no	O
fewer	O
than	O
Fifteen	O
men	O
and	O
One	O
woman	O
Convicted	O
(	O
per	O
Patriam	O
)	O
upon	O
fair	O
Tryals	O
for	O
their	O
respective	O
Crimes	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
;	O
of	O
whom	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
notorious	O
,	O
by	O
mercy	O
of	O
Authority	O
,	O
upon	O
consideration	O
of	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
mediation	O
of	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
solemn	O
Engagements	O
of	O
future	O
Amendment	O
,	O
obtained	O
the	O
gracious	O
favour	O
of	O
Reprieves	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
Eight	O
were	O
executed	O
April	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
their	O
Names	O
and	O
Crimes	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Michael	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Robbery	O
in	O
Dukes-place	B-place
,	O
taking	O
away	O
several	O
bags	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Jones	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
penitent	O
Speech	O
,	O
declaring	O
how	O
Idleness	O
,	O
Disobedience	O
to	O
his	O
Parents	O
,	O
Ill	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
lewd	O
Women	O
,	O
first	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
bad	O
Courses	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
to	O
this	O
untimely	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
Brick-maker	O
in	O
Frog-lane	B-place
,	O
whom	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Crew	O
barbarously	O
stript	O
naked	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
rather	O
by	O
their	O
Dogs	O
,	O
for	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
escaped	O
)	O
being	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
probable	O
,	O
going	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
like	O
Designe	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
indicted	O
and	O
acquitted	O
one	O
Sessions	O
,	O
convicted	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
condemned	O
and	O
repriev	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
,	O
though	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
to	O
contrive	O
and	O
abet	O
Rogueries	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
hang	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Longman	I-pers
,	O
an	O
old	O
and	O
impudent	O
Offender	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
above	O
Twelve	O
times	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
lately	O
transported	O
;	O
but	O
returning	O
,	O
stole	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Silks	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
employ	O
'd	O
Edward	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
to	O
engage	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
of	I-pers
Quality	I-pers
to	O
solicite	O
a	O
Reprieve	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Companions	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
they	O
observ	O
'd	O
abundance	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
Bess	O
Longman	O
cries	O
,	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
onely	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
you	O
dull	O
Fools	O
,	O
go	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
possession	O
:	O
Which	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
instigation	O
they	O
effected	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
young	O
Thieves	O
,	O
were	O
soon	O
discovered	O
;	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
suffer	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
Sessions	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
1676	O
.	O
Three	O
men	O
and	O
Two	O
women	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
onely	O
Four	O
suffered	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
After	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
being	O
Rogues	O
of	O
the	O
Foot-pad	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
pillage	O
Market-women	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hazlegrove	I-pers
for	O
having	O
Two	O
Wives	O
:	O
Upon	O
his	O
Conviction	O
he	O
prayed	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
was	O
Condemned	O
and	O
Executed	O
:	O
A	O
Case	O
that	O
seems	O
a	O
little	O
severe	O
;	O
but	O
so	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
:	O
which	O
may	O
admonish	O
Parents	O
to	O
bestow	O
,	O
and	O
Children	O
to	O
study	O
at	O
least	O
to	O
read	O
well	O
,	O
since	O
sometimes	O
a	O
man	O
loses	O
his	O
life	O
meerly	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
fourth	O
was	O
famous	O
Frances	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
Riggs	O
the	O
younger	O
.	O
Thieving	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Trade	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
;	O
her	O
Mother	O
often	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
under	O
Transportation	O
;	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Brothers	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pretended	O
Husbands	O
or	O
Gallants	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
her	O
self	O
now	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
simplicity	O
:	O
For	O
,	O
lying	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
several	O
people	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
not	O
doubting	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
safe	O
now	O
from	O
being	O
indicted	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
therein	O
her	O
Newgate-Counsel	O
fail	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
her	O
pardon	O
extended	O
onely	O
to	O
remit	O
the	O
Crime	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
convicted	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
now	O
arraigned	O
afresh	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
upon	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
followed	O
the	O
fate	O
of	O
her	O
Family	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Aug.	O
23	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
1676	O
.	O
Sixteen	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
,	O
onely	O
Eight	O
suffered	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Burglary	O
at	O
Cue	B-place
in	O
Surry	B-place
;	O
and	O
so	O
excluding	O
benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
refusing	O
to	O
plead	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
bruised	O
,	O
that	O
without	O
further	O
Execution	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
surviv	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Darkin	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Parish-Church	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Communion	O
.	O
Chalices	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
they	O
performed	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
and	O
Engine	O
of	O
Villany	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
of	O
incredible	O
force	O
for	O
forcing	O
open	O
Doors	O
,	O
Locks	O
,	O
Bolts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
this	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Darkin	O
,	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Artist	O
at	O
such	O
black	O
works	O
.	O
These	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
aver	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Vestry	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chests	O
,	O
a	O
Spectrum	O
or	O
Apparition	O
did	O
visibly	O
stand	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
so	O
resolved	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
their	O
wicked	O
Designe	O
,	O
that	O
even	O
the	O
Devil	O
himself	O
could	O
not	O
scare	O
them	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
for	O
murdering	O
her	O
Bastard-childe	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
threw	O
into	O
a	O
Pond	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Walkenden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
several	O
Burglaries	O
.	O
The	O
later	O
was	O
a	O
matchless	O
young	O
piece	O
of	O
Confidence	O
,	O
who	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
a	O
Crime	O
rarely	O
attempted	O
by	O
that	O
Sex	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
four	O
times	O
before	O
been	O
tryed	O
for	O
several	O
Offences	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
could	O
not	O
obtain	O
further	O
indulgence	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
a	O
lad	O
not	O
above	O
Fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
but	O
old	O
in	O
Roguery	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Felonies	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
both	O
whipt	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
before	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
1676	O
.	O
Sixteen	O
in	O
all	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
onely	O
Five	O
Executed	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
remarkable	O
business	O
was	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
for	O
murdering	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
a	O
Ditcher	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
(	O
not	O
then	O
taken	O
)	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
without	O
cause	O
,	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
beat	O
out	O
his	O
brains	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
stake	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
reasons	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
only	O
Manslaughter	O
:	O
but	O
Providence	O
not	O
suffering	O
Murder	O
so	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Book	O
,	O
though	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Scholar	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
tutor	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
deservedly	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Two	O
Condemned	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
above	O
Forty	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
for	O
murdering	O
her	O
Bastard-childe	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Executed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
Personating	O
another	O
man	O
as	O
Bail	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
the	O
Gallows	O
received	O
a	O
gracious	O
Reprieve	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
was	O
that	O
blasphemous	O
Impostor	O
Lodowick	B-pers
Muggleton	I-pers
tryed	O
,	O
and	O
sentenced	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
days	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
his	O
Books	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
before	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
Five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
fine	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Bail	O
(	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Party	O
or	O
Gang	O
)	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
1676/7	O
.	O
Was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
Executed	O
the	O
renounced	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
High	O
Chancellor	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Mace	O
and	O
two	O
Purses	O
.	O
Sadler	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
impudently	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
died	O
pitifully	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
little	O
generosity	O
of	O
Spirit	O
;	O
but	O
Johnson	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
becoming	O
resolution	O
and	O
staid	O
temper	O
that	O
at	O
once	O
shew	O
'd	O
his	O
sense	O
of	O
his-sins	O
,	O
and	O
faith	O
in	O
his	O
Saviour	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
repentant	O
and	O
pithy-Discourse	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Execution	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
warn	O
all	O
others	O
by	O
his	O
Example	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
suffered	O
Francis	O
Webb	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Gammond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anthony	O
Richoake	O
,	O
for	O
several	O
Burglaries	O
:	O
There	O
being	O
in	O
all	O
Fifteen	O
Condemned	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
obtained	O
Reprieves	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
1677	O
.	O
Was	O
famous	O
for	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
Condemnation	O
,	O
and	O
Execution	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dine	I-pers
,	O
two	O
own	O
brothers	O
and	O
a	O
sister	O
,	O
for	O
disfiguring	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
mangling	O
the	O
Nose	O
and	O
Face	O
of	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
that	O
behalf	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
absolutely	O
persisted	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
doing	O
this	O
cruel	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
asserted	O
their	O
innocency	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
gasp	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
very	O
much	O
pitied	O
by	O
many	O
people	O
that	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
suffered	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
for	O
murdering	O
her	O
Bastard-childe	O
:	O
As	O
also	O
David	B-pers
Hackley	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
all	O
notorious	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
formerly	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
now	O
convicted	O
of	O
several	O
Felonies	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
1677	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
then	O
Condemned	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Throckmorton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
two	O
Ministers	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
three	O
miles	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
most	O
commendable	O
courage	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ministers	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
alone	O
fought	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
for	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
moved	O
(	O
though	O
without	O
a	O
Weapon	O
)	O
by	O
his	O
servant	O
's	O
brave	O
defence	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
made	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
ride	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
suffered	O
very	O
penitently	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
At	O
which	O
time	O
was	O
likewise	O
Executed	O
William	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
for	O
murdering	O
a	O
poor	O
Tub-man	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
furious	O
passion	O
against	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
beat	O
herexceedingly	O
,	O
a	O
Croud	O
of	O
people	O
were	O
gathered	O
about	O
;	O
where	O
upon	O
taking	O
down	O
an	O
Halt-pike	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
dispatcht	O
this	O
harmless	O
man	O
,	O
sitting	O
on	O
his	O
Water-tubs	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
provocation	O
.	O
Which	O
may	O
teach	O
all	O
men	O
to	O
moderate	O
their	O
possions	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
run	O
unbridled	O
to	O
mischief	O
,	O
left	O
thereby	O
they	O
bring	O
themselves	O
to	O
some	O
such	O
shameful	O
End	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Sessions	O
in	O
July	O
1677	O
.	O
Was	O
sufficiently	O
crouded	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
that	O
Monster	O
rather	O
than	O
woman	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
who	O
suffer	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
Buggered	O
by	O
a	O
Mungril	O
.	O
This	O
detestable	O
Villany	O
was	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
by	O
Three	O
witnesses	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
vil	O
wretch	O
was	O
executed	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
Dog	O
being	O
carried	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
Tree	O
neer	O
the	O
Gallows	O
before	O
her	O
face	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
great	O
with	O
Childe	O
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Report	O
spread	O
abroad	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
this	O
woman	O
suffer	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
fall	O
in	O
Labour	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
,	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
herein	O
forsworn	O
her	O
self	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
;	O
which	O
Report	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
are	O
utterly	O
false	O
and	O
groundless	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Witness	O
continuing	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
satisfi	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
integrity	O
of	O
her	O
Testimony	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Godfry	I-pers
and	O
Rogers	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
for	O
a	O
like	O
Crime	O
committed	O
in	O
Hartfordshire	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
were	O
tryable	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
four	O
were	O
John	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Minors	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Minors	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
for	O
several	O
Burglaries	O
and	O
Felonies	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
suffered	O
John	B-pers
Gimbold	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
Russel	O
,	O
both	O
old	O
incorngible	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
Condemned	O
for	O
several	O
Felonies	O
.	O
