TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
,	O
1680.	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Fryday	O
the	O
23th	O
.	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
Treasons	O
,	O
Murders	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
Committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Condemnation	O
of	O
a	O
notorious	O
Jesuite	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Women	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proceedings	O
with	O
the	O
Apprentices	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
give	O
account	O
of	O
is	O
an	O
Irish	O
Youth	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
about	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
in	O
Goods	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
circumstances	O
thus	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
into	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
now	O
Robbed	O
,	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
over	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
the	O
Youth	O
observing	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
one	O
Morning	O
betimes	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
softly	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
his	O
Cabinet	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
took	O
thence	O
forty	O
pounds	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
twenty	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
under	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
Honour	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
shipping	O
for	O
Ireland	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
grose	O
suspicions	O
,	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
made	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
moneys	O
by	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
all	O
Circumstances	O
cosidered	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wether	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
7	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
having	O
sold	O
to	O
another	O
for	O
3	O
pounds	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
at	O
Midsummer	O
,	O
was	O
seised	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Buyer	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
makind	O
immediate	O
search	O
for	O
his	O
Chapman	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Strong-water	O
shop	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
where	O
Apprehending	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
Transportation	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
was	O
Inddicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Felloniously	O
murthering	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Shrove	O
munday	O
last	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
Westminster	I-place
(	O
for	O
now	O
of	O
late	O
that	O
Scarlet	O
Crime	O
is	O
grown	O
so	O
frequent	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
commonly	O
concludes	O
mutual	O
friendship	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Trajeck	O
Scene	O
,	O
that	O
might	O
far	O
better	O
befit	O
Pagangs	O
than	O
protestors	O
of	O
Christianity	O
)	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
this	O
fatal	O
mischief	O
was	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
had	O
several	O
fallings	O
out	O
in	O
relation	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
too	O
familliar	O
with	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
threatned	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
period	O
to	O
his	O
Life	O
or	O
loose	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
often	O
having	O
way	O
laid	O
him	O
and	O
fallen	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
unawares	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
with	O
unlawful	O
Staves	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
his	O
sword	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
surprise	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
designs	O
not	O
taking	O
their	O
wished	O
for	O
event	O
,	O
but	O
hindered	O
by	O
Providence	O
for	O
perpetrating	O
such	O
a	O
Cruel	O
in	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
this	O
Trajedy	O
was	O
compleated	O
,	O
the	O
aforementioned	O
Harrison	O
having	O
sent	O
for	O
Jacobs	O
wife	O
,	O
after	O
being	O
strictly	O
warned	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
it	O
so	O
grieved	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
vowed	O
revenge	O
,	O
and	O
waiting	O
for	O
the	O
coming	O
home	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
sooner	O
having	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
making	O
many	O
passes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
put	O
by	O
and	O
avoided	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
retreating	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
still	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
draw	O
and	O
stand	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
which	O
with	O
two	O
mortal	O
wounds	O
on	O
the	O
brest	O
about	O
four	O
inches	O
deep	O
made	O
him	O
fall	O
breathless	O
at	O
his	O
feet	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
weighing	O
all	O
circumstances	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sancy	I-pers
a	O
Frenchman	O
was	O
ttied	O
likewise	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
Brother	O
Mounsier	B-pers
of	O
twenty-eight	O
French	O
Pistols	O
,	O
6	O
Meddals	O
with	O
Coats	O
of	O
Arms	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
open	O
as	O
he	O
alleged	O
,	O
his	O
Trunks	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
,	O
the	O
party	O
robbed	O
could	O
speak	O
no	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
obliged	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
might	O
be	O
sensible	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Fellony	O
was	O
plain	O
for	O
Sancy	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
twelve	O
Pistols	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
somewhat	O
dubious	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
also	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Southy	I-pers
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
ticeing	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
Cellar	O
by	O
the	O
allurement	O
of	O
Appels	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
accomplished	O
his	O
detestable	O
Villany	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
giving	O
the	O
Child	O
the	O
foul	O
Disease	O
wherewith	O
himself	O
was	O
infested	O
,	O
but	O
likewise	O
by	O
forceable	O
penetrating	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
so	O
abused	O
her	O
secret	O
parts	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
distressed	O
wretch	O
remained	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
miserable	O
condition	O
,	O
but	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
e	O
're	O
she	O
would	O
complain	O
,	O
lest	O
her	O
Mother	O
should	O
beat	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
her	O
extream	O
torment	O
enforced	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
her	O
mother	O
no	O
sooner	O
understood	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
procured	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Chirurgions	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
if	O
possible	O
retract	O
the	O
mischance	O
;	O
who	O
did	O
conclude	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
confessed	O
at	O
large	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
ey	O
debauched	O
fellow	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
the	O
Witness	O
swore	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
Act	O
carnally	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
mother	O
,	O
threatning	O
when	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
permit	O
his	O
incestious	O
desires	O
,	O
to	O
Fire	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
her	O
Ears	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
several	O
Simptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
remain	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Rape	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rumley	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
received	O
their	O
Trials	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Baits	I-pers
near	O
Milend	B-place
green	I-place
breaking	O
through	O
the	O
shutters	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
entered	O
,	O
conveyed	O
thence	O
,	O
three	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
several	O
Brass	O
Pans	O
and	O
Kettels	O
,	O
Porringers	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
vallue	O
,	O
being	O
pursued	O
and	O
apprehended	O
they	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Digs	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Griste	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Felloniously	O
bearing	O
away	O
eighteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gardne	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
smoaka	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
the	O
maid	O
in	O
a	O
Discourse	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Purchase	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
one	O
them	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
confessed	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
bestowed	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
search	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
extenuation	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
joyned	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
Confession	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
received	O
her	O
Trial	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
in	O
Holburn	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
surprised	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
e	O
're	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
her	O
Pack	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
excuse	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
seeing	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
called	O
in	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
no	O
sooner	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
three	O
silk	O
Coats	O
,	O
Amber	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
Linnen	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
These	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
high	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
Counterfitted	O
and	O
Clipped	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
mill	O
'd	O
half-Crowns	O
,	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
shillings	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
Filed	O
and	O
washed	O
;	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Harlot	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
their	O
Discovery	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
meeting	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
Companion	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
made	O
sensible	O
of	O
her	O
new	O
imploy	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
she	O
would	O
now	O
allow	O
him	O
a	O
Guinny	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
demanded	O
how	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Trade	O
that	O
would	O
allow	O
far	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Coining	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
of	O
one	O
shilling	O
worth	O
of	O
Mettle	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
half	O
Crowns	O
telling	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
share	O
and	O
be	O
secret	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
live	O
beyond	O
his	O
expectation	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
some	O
falling	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
only	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Gallant	O
in	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dore	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
refusal	O
of	O
Admittance	O
;	O
they	O
no	O
sooner	O
enterred	O
but	O
Underwood	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
melted	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Constable	O
requesting	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
he	O
whispering	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
;	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
undone	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
discover	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
minding	O
that	O
,	O
searched	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
melting	O
Pots	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
some	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
150	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Coin	O
,	O
representing	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
shillings	O
,	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
first	O
his	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Mill	O
'd	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
pieces	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Flask	O
and	O
all	O
convenient	O
Engines	O
for	O
that	O
pernicious	O
employ	O
which	O
were	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
under	O
the	O
Hearth	O
with	O
a	O
board	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
positive	O
Evidences	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
were	O
likewise	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
Treasonable	O
practises	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
living	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
had	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
used	O
that	O
fraudulent	O
and	O
pernicious	O
Art	O
of	O
Clipping	O
his	O
Majesties	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
diminishing	O
it	O
three	O
pence	O
in	O
every	O
shilling	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
dammage	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
discovery	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
Cardmatch-wench	O
,	O
since	O
poisoned	O
)	O
whom	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
hired	O
to	O
Assist	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
intreague	O
who	O
told	O
it	O
one	O
Withers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taking	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Elizabeth	O
Richardsons	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
no	O
sooner	O
entring	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
come	O
for	O
Clippings	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
her	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
convey	O
thence	O
his	O
Tools	O
and	O
Instruments	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
fly	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stopped	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
upon	O
diligent	O
search	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
save	O
a	O
Receipt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
how	O
to	O
wash	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
his	O
Mothers	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
several	O
Rubbe	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Flask	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Mrs	O
Digbies	O
Custody	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
hid	O
beneath	O
the	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
pound	O
clipped	O
;	O
and	O
above	O
all	O
,	O
one	O
Brass	O
half-Crown	O
,	O
that	O
answered	O
to	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Clippings	O
found	O
in	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardsons	I-pers
Custody	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Dauncing	O
Suit	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardsons	I-pers
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
all	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
Edward	O
Richardson	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Treason	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Jane	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
received	O
his	O
Trial	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
For	O
that	O
he	O
unlawfully	O
Coined	O
several	O
new	O
Mill	O
'd	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
seven	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
proued	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
plate	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
betrayed	O
by	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Landlord	O
,	O
who	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Room	O
searched	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
casting	O
Mould	O
,	O
a	O
Flask	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
engraving	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
half	O
crowns	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Instruments	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
that	O
vicious	O
practice	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
in	O
Stafford-shire	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Treason	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
only	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
but	O
his	O
Landlord	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Verdict	O
as	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ralphs	I-pers
and	O
Clement	B-pers
Sells	I-pers
,	O
two	O
notorious	O
Offendors	O
,	O
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
two	O
notorious	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
upon	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bewing	I-pers
of	O
Willsdon	B-place
,	O
being	O
eight	O
in	O
Company	O
they	O
enterred	O
,	O
and	O
binding	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
except	O
the	O
Maid-Servant	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
compelled	O
to	O
light	O
them	O
from	O
Room	O
,	O
to	O
Room	O
,	O
untill	O
they	O
had	O
plundered	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Vallue	O
of	O
two	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
viz	O
,	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
two	O
Candle	O
Cups	O
,	O
twenty-nine	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
portable	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
ordering	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
up	O
some	O
Victuals	O
,	O
departed	O
with	O
their	O
Prize	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tatnam-Court	B-place
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Victualling	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
six	O
in	O
number	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
their	O
Landlord	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Hine	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
his	O
employment	O
and	O
wanted	O
Moneys	O
,	O
drawing	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
holding	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Brest	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ransack	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
sheets	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
Linnen	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
vallue	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Viz	O
.	O
Ralphs	O
confessed	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Macarty	I-pers
an	O
Irish	O
man	O
being	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
27	O
Eliz	O
.	O
for	O
having	O
taken	O
Order	O
from	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
over	O
into	O
England	O
being	O
Impeached	O
by	O
one	O
Alice	O
Turner	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
proselyte	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
Information	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Stiff	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
taking	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
entred	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
lodg	O
,	O
They	O
found	O
him	O
Confessing	O
a	O
Sick	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
no	O
sooner	O
seeing	O
them	O
begin	O
roughly	O
to	O
handle	O
her	O
Priest	O
but	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Salvation	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
They	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
a	O
Petition	O
to	O
an	O
Envoy	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
written	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
denoting	O
that	O
Daniel	B-pers
Macarte	I-pers
Priest	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
want	O
since	O
his	O
release	O
from	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
desired	O
his	O
Charity	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
a	O
Purple	O
Ribon	O
with	O
three	O
Crosses	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
all	O
Popish	O
Priests	O
do	O
usually	O
give	O
the	O
Secrameot	O
with	O
in	O
private	O
wearing	O
it	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Chrystal	O
Crucifix	O
;	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
the	O
more	O
efficacious	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
Plot	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
saying	O
Mass	O
and	O
giving	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Alice	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
not	O
only	O
at	O
the	O
Venetian	O
Embassadnrs	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
Wild	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
confessing	O
likewise	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Oats	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
High	O
Treason	O
as	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
or	O
Jesuit	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Coining	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
Convicted	O
of	O
high	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
several	O
Apprentices	O
that	O
were	O
Committed	O
to	O
the	O
GateHouse	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
,	O
being	O
turned	O
over	O
to	O
this	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
condescended	O
to	O
take	O
Bail	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
their	O
further	O
answering	O
their	O
Treasonable	O
Intentions	O
of	O
making	O
a	O
Combination	O
to	O
levy	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
all	O
24	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Dye	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Isabella	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
,	O
Clement	B-pers
Sells	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ralphs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rumley	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Wether	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maccharty	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bestin	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
:	O
14	O
burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
three	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
