TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
HOUSE	O
IN	O
The	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
8.	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Tryals	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
Murthers	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
,	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
With	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Places	O
where	O
the	O
several	O
Facts	O
were	O
Committed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Dye	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Decemb	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
1682	O
.	O
THis	O
day	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
began	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
Proclamation	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Jurys	O
were	O
called	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
24	O
Sworn	O
,	O
to	O
Try	O
the	O
issues	O
between	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Twelve	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Twelve	O
for	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Tryals	O
as	O
followth	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Trumper	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
,	O
Merchant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Bil	O
of	O
silk	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
100	O
pounds	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Marshelsea	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Cast	O
for	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
which	O
he	O
Stole	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
six	O
pound	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
Captain	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
five	O
pound	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dossey	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
s	O
Trunck	O
a	O
considerable	O
Sum	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
with	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
four	O
Trespasses	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
four	O
several	O
Bills	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Minga	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
Counterfeited	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Marmion	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Beaumont	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ditton	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wyat	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
70	O
l.	O
the	O
third	O
for	O
75	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
was	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mariot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cotten	I-pers
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Bates	O
when	O
he	O
Stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
stood	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ten	O
Apprentice	O
s	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Ryot	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
Gamaliel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tenant	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
whereof	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
also	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
as	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
was	O
peaceably	O
passing	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
but	O
Evidence	O
being	O
given	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Lungham	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Rabble	O
,	O
but	O
within	O
Doors	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Ryot	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bowen	B-pers
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lashly	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
being	O
brought	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Instant	O
from	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murthering	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
These	O
Highway-Men	O
following	O
were	O
brought	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
Instant	O
by	O
Habeas-Corpus	O
from	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Paggit	B-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Page	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
King	B-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Layfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Robbing	O
Andrew	B-pers
Meal	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
another	O
Indictment	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tibber	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Horse	O
in	O
Marlborough	B-place
Thicket	I-place
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
These	O
following	O
Foot	O
Padds	O
John	B-pers
Hutchings	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redwell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kedwell	B-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Paffet	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
allbrought	O
from	O
Chelmsford	O
Goal	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
and	O
Convict	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
of	O
a	O
Steel-Box	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
and	O
five	O
pound	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
between	O
Mile	B-place
end	I-place
and	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Rumford	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Casteel	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Convict	O
of	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morten	I-pers
Widdow	O
at	O
Newington	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
upon	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
three	O
Fellonys	O
more	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Ady	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Sitherdel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Skempton	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Aggat	O
hafted	O
Knife	O
value	O
8	O
shillings	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Pembrook	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
18	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
from	O
Vincent	B-pers
Yate	I-pers
,	O
Value	O
about	O
20	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
Fustion	O
;	O
value	O
14	O
shillings	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Amos	B-pers
Day	I-pers
was	O
Convict	O
of	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bide	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
82	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
a	O
Broker	O
was	O
Cast	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Coach-Seat	O
from	O
Elias	B-pers
Gliss	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
was	O
Convict	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
valued	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
14	O
Sheep	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Convict	O
of	O
Stealing	O
Bees-Wax	O
,	O
valued	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Coquo	O
Cup	O
from	O
Lyonel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
valued	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pardue	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Robing	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
82.	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
goods	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Macklin	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawbone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Farrower	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Ten	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
Gold	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Twenty	O
pound	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Dunny	B-pers
Will	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Apprehended	O
in	O
Court	O
one	O
in	O
Hickes-Hall	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
for	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Murther	O
committed	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Fifteen	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Alias	O
Bomen	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lashly	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Layfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redwell	I-pers
,	O
Alias	O
Kedwell	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pafet	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Casteel	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pardue	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Following	O
,	O
being	O
Convict	O
of	O
several	O
Fellonys	O
received	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fanlconer	I-pers
.	O
Arthur	O
Pembrooke	O
.	O
Edward	O
Homes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dawley	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Marklain	I-pers
.	O
James	O
Farrower	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Trumper	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Seaven	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	O
Morrice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	O
Price	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
Amos	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hummon	I-pers
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Following	O
were	O
Fin	O
'd	O
.	O
George	O
Robinson	O
Fin	O
'd	O
Forty	O
Round	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Cheap-Side	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
.	O
Gamaliel	O
Wells	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Were	O
Fined	O
each	O
twenty	O
Marks	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
