TOKEN	NE
A	O
Full	O
and	O
True	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
WHICH	O
BEGAN	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
April	O
26.	O
and	O
Ended	O
on	O
Fryday	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
,	O
1682	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
many	O
Remarkable	O
Proceedings	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
the	O
TRYAL	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
For	O
Killing	O
the	O
Bayliff	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
As	O
Also	O
,	O
In	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
Accused	O
for	O
Getting	O
his	O
Daughter	O
With-Child	O
:	O
TOGETHER	O
,	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
those	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
which	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
continued	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
:	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
EDward	B-pers
Odery	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Robbed	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
Swore	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
employed	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
(	O
after	O
receiving	O
their	O
charge	O
)	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Belther	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Butler	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
Nine	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Fifteen	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Two	O
former	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
confessing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
although	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
not	O
judged	O
to	O
be	O
above	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
the	O
accessaries	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
Griffith	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
Soaper-Lane	B-place
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
summ	O
of	O
Money	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Motley	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Fellony	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Eve	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Two	O
Farrendine	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Six	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
several	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Table-Cloath	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbonds	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Fifty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
Pawned	O
at	O
one	O
Smiths	O
a	O
Broker	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
Plea	O
was	O
their	O
Husbands	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
compelled	O
them	O
to	O
sell'um	O
;	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
having	O
been	O
Executed	O
last	O
Surray-Assizes	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
so	O
far	O
commiserated	O
them	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hundred	O
and	O
Four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
from	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Barkin-Parish	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
;	O
A	O
Person	O
comming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
opened	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
by	O
reaching	O
over	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
warning	O
being	O
given	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
upon	O
the	O
like	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
search	O
,	O
another	O
Ring	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Knife-sheath	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
alledged	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
coming	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
than	O
his	O
against	O
Hall	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Griffith	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shuter	I-pers
,	O
having	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferr	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Crape	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coat-seller	O
in	O
Great	B-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
several	O
Yards	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
;	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
,	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
alledging	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
werenever	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
Twelve	O
Pounds	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Southey	I-pers
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
would	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
Circumstantial	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
being	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
Ribbonds	O
and	O
Silks	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Uriah	B-pers
Helder	I-pers
had	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans-in-the-East	I-place
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
about	O
Fifty	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Brass-Wyre	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
some	O
parcels	O
of	O
Wyre	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rudwell	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
about	O
Five	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
and	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Broker-Woman	O
near	O
Holbourn-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
disposing	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Stilliard-makers	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
;	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
or	O
sold	O
any	O
such	O
Weights	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
layed	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Porter	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
a	O
Pot-stealer	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
near	O
a	O
Hundred	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Pewter-Pots	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
the	O
Brokers	O
Evidence	O
that	O
had	O
purchased	O
his	O
stolen	O
Ware	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smithe	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
committed	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
taking	O
about	O
Three	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Silks	O
and	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Two	O
Women	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Tape	O
,	O
Lace	O
and	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
impeached	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
otherwise	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
on	O
whom	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
conveying	O
thence	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Pillow-beers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
disposed	O
of	O
to	O
several	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
there	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
borrowed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Shift	O
availed	O
him	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
A	O
Fellow	O
that	O
was	O
Chamberlain	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
entring	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
s	O
Lodging	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
took	O
thence	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Riding	O
Furniture	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Carriers	O
,	O
directing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
Worcester	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
seized	O
in	O
the	O
Inn	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
packed	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
having	O
notice	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
owner	O
sent	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
Apprehended	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
takeing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
designed	O
to	O
ride	O
a	O
Journey	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
andso	O
to	O
restore	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
excuse	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
frivilous	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Willmore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murtherer	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
manner	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
thus	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Celler	O
under	O
the	O
Exchange	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
quarrel	O
happened	O
about	O
drinking	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
caused	O
a	O
scuffle	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
falling	O
,	O
his	O
left	O
Thigh	O
being	O
infirm	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
perishing	O
and	O
splintering	O
the	O
Bone	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
either	O
broke	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
splinters	O
of	O
the	O
Bones	O
cut	O
the	O
Arteries	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
he	O
dyed	O
within	O
7	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
former	O
malice	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
plain	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
abuse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Alderman	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Gold-watch	O
,	O
Silver-Lace	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
conveniency	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pleaded	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
many	O
slight	O
pretences	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
force	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plaid	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fitz-Patrick	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
a	O
Bayliffs	O
follower	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
;	O
several	O
Officers	O
having	O
Arrested	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
carryed	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
adjacent	O
House	O
in	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
where	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
sending	O
for	O
Bail	O
,	O
two	O
persons	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
them	O
Four	O
more	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
forcing	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
run	O
the	O
deceased	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
stabbed	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
within	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Bayliffs	O
hardly	O
escaping	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
parties	O
that	O
killed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
against	O
Elizabeth	O
Fitz-Patrick	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilfull	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dicher	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dicher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
another	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Captain	B-pers
Fosby	I-pers
;	O
of	O
which	O
Fellonies	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
John	O
Dicher	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Ann	O
Dicher	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bant	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French-man	O
,	O
and	O
late	O
Cook	O
to	O
His	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Cook	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Feversham	O
,	O
the	O
circumstances	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
being	O
these	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
and	O
sending	O
a	O
Porter	O
for	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Two	O
French	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
no	O
sooner	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drawing	O
upon	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
a	O
pass	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
swearing	O
he	O
should	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
Word	O
,	O
for	O
running	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pretended	O
the	O
deceased	O
owed	O
him	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gilbert	O
Stook-dale	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
imprisoned	O
for	O
getting	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Ursula	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
with-child	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Barr	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
70	O
Years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
inlarged	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Remarkable	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Eight	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5	O
Men	O
and	O
3	O
Women	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bants	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fitz-Patrick	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murther	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
alias	O
Ditcher	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Iane	O
Freeman	O
,	O
were	O
reprieved	O
before	O
judgement	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dicher	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rudwell	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jone	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
were	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
3	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ended	O
this	O
remarkable	O
Sessions	O
.	O
