TOKEN	NE
A	O
Full	O
and	O
True	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
WHICH	O
BEGAN	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Septemb	O
.	O
6th	O
.	O
and	O
Ended	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Septemb	O
7th	O
.	O
1682	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
Contained	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
many	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
for	O
Murders	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
,	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Misdemeanours	O
,	O
As	O
likewise	O
the	O
TRYAL	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
for	O
Killing	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
relates	O
to	O
the	O
Sister	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledge	I-pers
.	O
TOGETHER	O
,	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
those	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Septemb	O
.	O
6th	O
.	O
1682	O
.	O
THis	O
Day	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
holden	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
until	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Instant	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hurling	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
a	O
Brick-maker	O
,	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
the	O
manner	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
thus	O
;	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
for	O
Cards	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Cards	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
a	O
pack	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
several	O
Brick	O
makers	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
labouring	O
Men	O
drinking	O
,	O
enticed	O
themto	O
play	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
about	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
foul	O
play	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Farrel	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Country-men	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
then	O
returning	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Companion	O
Scuffling	O
with	O
Price	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
body	O
10	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
was	O
run	O
through	O
the	O
Arm	O
:	O
They	O
pleaded	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
expressed	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
sorrow	O
,	O
not	O
withstanding	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hester	B-pers
Wainwright	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	B-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
several	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
pounds	O
eleven	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
being	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
amongst	O
her	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
open	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
Stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
wore	O
the	O
Gowns	O
publickly	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chambden	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
of	O
Plate	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Bedding	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
Robbed	O
being	O
her	O
Sisters	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
proof	O
lay	O
upon	O
two	O
Porengers	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
alledged	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
long	O
standing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
absolutely	O
denyed	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Testimony	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
living	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
any	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
of	O
his	O
disposing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
only	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
several	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
butthe	O
Evidence	O
being	O
only	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mekins	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
was	O
these	O
;	O
She	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
now	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
door	O
to	O
beg	O
an	O
Alms	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Witness	O
swore	O
)	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
bulky	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
a	O
Warrants	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
absented	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
her	O
abode	O
for	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
alledged	O
upon	O
demand	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Loaf	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
pulling	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
perceiving	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
simple	O
Indigent	O
Woman	O
,	O
they	O
,	O
upon	O
return	O
of	O
their	O
Verdict	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
of	O
Coney-Skins	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Furrier	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
Confederate	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Shillings	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
,	O
packed	O
up	O
the	O
Skins	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
One	O
Stephen	B-pers
Aslington	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Francis	B-pers
Featherstone	I-pers
of	O
Kinsington	O
,	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
appeared	O
upon	O
tryal	O
,	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
words	O
of	O
provocation	O
having	O
passed	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Encounter	O
e	O
're	O
any	O
could	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
received	O
a	O
desperate	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
of	O
any	O
fighting	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
an	O
Ensign	O
of	O
the	O
Train'd-bands	O
,	O
and	O
Pewterer	O
in	O
Walbrook	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
who	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Benton	O
knocked	O
down	O
for	O
attemping	O
to	O
destroy	O
the	O
Bone-fire	O
made	O
before	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Chyrugeon	O
who	O
dressed	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wound	O
was	O
perfectly	O
Cured	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
return	O
confessed	O
himself	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
an	O
agreement	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
falling	O
sick	O
dyed	O
;	O
many	O
Eminent	O
Physitians	O
gave	O
their	O
Testimony	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
dyed	O
of	O
a	O
Maliguant	O
Feavor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Feavour	O
was	O
not	O
caused	O
by	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
but	O
others	O
affirming	O
that	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
blood	O
issued	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Nostrils	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
the	O
Wound	O
caused	O
the	O
Feavor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Feavor	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man's-slaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
an	O
Under-Chamberlain	O
in	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
Masters	O
House	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
32	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Gold-Smith	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
he	O
made	O
many	O
frivilous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Purkinson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Mistris	O
of	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porenger	O
,	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
she	O
confessed	O
were	O
Sold	O
and	O
Pawned	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Tutered	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
her	O
former	O
Confession	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
positive	O
by	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turners	I-pers
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
Apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
One	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
,	O
for	O
Marrying	O
with	O
one	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
alledged	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
several	O
years	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denying	O
that	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
alledgeing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Wife	O
to	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
Justice	O
Boly	O
's	O
Clerk	O
with	O
her	O
Examination	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
confessed	O
both	O
Marriages	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
her	O
other	O
Husband	O
was	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
love	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
taking	O
away	O
her	O
life	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
defective	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Taster	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
droped	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Robbing	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tann	O
of	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
of	O
Cloth	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Chaple	I-pers
two	O
Leighter-men	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Hanks	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Baile	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Towing	O
it	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Eling	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
Bedding	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Relation	O
to	O
'um	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
overtook	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
had	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
for	O
six-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Brainford	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
:	O
Samuel	B-pers
Neve	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
stole	O
in	O
Glocester-shire	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Lyon	O
Inn	O
in	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
layed	O
all	O
the	O
fault	O
upon	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
dead	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
saying	O
;	O
They	O
were	O
his	O
Horses	O
and	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
from	O
Henly	O
to	O
London	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Shillings	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
had	O
owned	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
valued	O
at	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fardinando	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mays	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Coin	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
witness	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
sufficient	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
No	O
Indictment	O
was	O
this	O
Sessions	O
preferred	O
against	O
Godwins	O
Wife	O
,	O
Sister	O
to	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledge	I-pers
lately	O
Executed	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Accusation	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
Treasonable	O
words	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
this	O
Sessions	O
9	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Wainwright	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hurling	I-pers
,	O
Peter	O
Hodges	O
,	O
Robert	O
Rogers	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Panks	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wolley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stocdale	I-pers
;	O
10	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
4	O
to	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
set	O
aside	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
