TOKEN	NE
AN	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1684	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1684	O
before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Tulse	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Holloway	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Tryed	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Judgment	O
given	O
thereon	O
,	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Ann	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Beaker	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flaxen	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
from	O
Rowland	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Queen-hithe	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
until	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
carrying	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
Apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
her	O
Master	O
stands	O
Excommunicated	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
Question	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
now	O
any	O
Right	O
to	O
his	O
Plate	O
;	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
nine	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Sawcers	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Mallow	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
;	O
which	O
Goods	O
she	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
Sell	O
them	O
outright	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
Inquiry	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
now	O
Tryed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Delphos	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French-woman	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	B-place
French	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
Shilling	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
;	O
the	O
Shilling	O
falling	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
or	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Sir	O
Job	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
they	O
were	O
Women	O
who	O
cryed	O
Strawberries	O
and	O
Cherries	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
buying	O
of	O
their	O
Strawberries	O
,	O
delivering	O
them	O
the	O
Tumbler	O
to	O
measure	O
with	O
,	O
they	O
carryed	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
only	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
cutting	O
her	O
Throat	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Vintner	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
about	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Pyecorner	O
,	O
near	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
privately	O
Marryed	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Woman	O
;	O
who	O
continued	O
also	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
House	O
in	O
Old	O
Fish-street	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
his	O
Wives	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
came	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
go	O
see	O
a	O
Cousin	O
that	O
dwelt	O
on	O
the	O
Fields-side	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wifewas	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
Cloaths	O
good	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Visiting	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
alledging	O
his	O
Cousin	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
ashamed	O
of	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
length	O
Consented	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Fellow-Servant	O
Sarah	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
:	O
't	O
is	O
also	O
observable	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
the	O
Vintner	O
Witnessed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
home	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
After-noon	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
not	O
Home	O
till	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Heat	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
a	O
discomposed	O
Person	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
also	O
proving	O
further	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
Joan	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
not	O
coming	O
Home	O
again	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
He	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
said	O
Masters	O
Door	O
in	O
Fish-street	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
was	O
a	O
Mower	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
her	O
Dead	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
Paddington	O
,	O
her	O
Throat	O
being	O
Cut	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Head	O
and	O
Face	O
beat	O
and	O
Bruised	O
:	O
also	O
the	O
Ferrel	O
of	O
a	O
Stick	O
or	O
Cain	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Dead	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
fitted	O
to	O
a	O
Cain	O
his	O
Master	O
that	O
Day	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
Home	O
without	O
a	O
Ferrel	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
it	O
some	O
Specks	O
like	O
Blood	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
Kill	O
himself	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
appeared	O
of	O
a	O
Desperate	O
Humour	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
some	O
occasion	O
,	O
Captain	O
Richardson	O
Examining	O
him	O
concerning	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
,	O
That	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Cain	O
he	O
did	O
Beat	O
and	O
Bruise	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
Knife	O
did	O
Cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
:	O
which	O
the	O
Captain	O
delivering	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
Captain	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
affirmed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
his	O
Wife	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
her	O
near	O
his	O
Masters	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
that	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
were	O
present	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
he	O
have	O
time	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
to	O
produce	O
those	O
that	O
see	O
him	O
part	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
Man	O
being	O
produced	O
that	O
could	O
say	O
the	O
least	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
exceeding	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
her	O
Grace	O
the	O
Dutch	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portsmouth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Point	O
of	O
Lorain	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
l.	O
ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Silk	O
flowered	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Silk	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
which	O
did	O
most	O
affect	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
a	O
small	O
Piece	O
of	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
of	O
flowered	O
Silk	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
so	O
stolen	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
producing	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Finisher	O
to	O
some	O
great	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
18	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
Finisher	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Cabbadge	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
since	O
Easter	O
.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
said	O
Smith	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
and	O
Morgan	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Noble	O
his	O
Grace	O
James	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ormond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
Rob	O
and	O
Steal	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Andrew	O
Hill	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Foot-man	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Ormond	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
away	O
for	O
Misdemeanour	O
;	O
which	O
Hill	O
meeting	O
and	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
Foot-man	O
that	O
now	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
assisting	O
in	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
promising	O
him	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
Reward	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
after	O
such	O
Robbery	O
:	O
To	O
effect	O
which	O
,	O
Hill	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
two	O
other	O
notorious	O
Pick-Locks	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
otherwise	O
employed	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
Morgan	O
Reading	O
for	O
his	O
Partner	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
soon	O
after	O
for	O
the	O
Highlands	O
of	O
Scotland	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
live	O
securely	O
,	O
and	O
become	O
Men	O
of	O
Substance	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
so	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Foot-man	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
by	O
leaving	O
a	O
Window	O
unshut	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
100	O
l.	O
went	O
and	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Steward	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
provided	O
armed	O
Men	O
to	O
seize	O
them	O
.	O
Hill	O
was	O
gotten	O
through	O
two	O
Rooms	O
,	O
Reading	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
both	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
Sir	O
Job	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Cartmore	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
eight	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland-Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Manta	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cotter	I-pers
:	O
He	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Burchall	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
William	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
Burchall	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
lusty	O
Youth	O
,	O
who	O
it	O
seems	O
was	O
that	O
Day	O
at	O
Play	O
,	O
having	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Water-Dog	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
likewise	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Dog	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
Pool	O
threw	O
Stones	O
,	O
or	O
Clods	O
of	O
Earth	O
,	O
at	O
Burchal	O
's	O
Dog	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
them	O
to	O
quarrel	O
;	O
and	O
Burchal	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
threw	O
any	O
more	O
Clods	O
at	O
his	O
Dog	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
one	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
conclusion	O
,	O
did	O
throw	O
a	O
hard	O
Clot	O
of	O
Earth	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
hitting	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
under	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
thereof	O
died	O
.	O
Burchall	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Intent	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
before	O
loving	O
Friends	O
,	O
Play-Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
Town-born	O
Children	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pykeman	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
,	O
Yards	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
New	B-place
Exchange	I-place
;	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
conveyed	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
though	O
greatly	O
suspected	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holtam	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Holtham	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
grey	O
Mare	O
,	O
price	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
W.	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
Holtam	O
is	O
a	O
Person	O
suspected	O
for	O
a	O
High-way	O
man	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
some	O
Country-Goal	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Removal	O
by	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
:	O
he	O
pretends	O
himself	O
to	O
have	O
lived	O
last	O
at	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Warwick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
bred	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
indeed	O
a	O
likely	O
Man	O
to	O
see	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Proof	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
both	O
Holtam	O
and	O
Bennet	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
alledged	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
him	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
whilst	O
he	O
sent	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Clark	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Drink	O
at	O
an	O
AleHouse	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
thereof	O
,	O
also	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
of	O
Fowler	O
by	O
credible	O
Persons	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Shipwash	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
a	O
Sword-Cutler	O
in	O
Chancery	B-place
lane	I-place
;	O
but	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
a	O
Booksellers	O
Shop	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Cutlers	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
snatch	O
the	O
Sword	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
made	O
such	O
quick	O
Pursuit	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
albeit	O
he	O
run	O
amongst	O
several	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
into	O
Cliffords	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
said	O
Gentlewoman	O
was	O
so	O
stout	O
as	O
to	O
overtake	O
and	O
seise	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Heldridge	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
eight	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Souldier	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Captain	O
,	O
retained	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Wars	O
,	O
receiving	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Wages	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
did	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
without	O
leave	O
of	O
his	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
feloniously	O
depart	O
the	O
said	O
Service	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
near	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
and	O
other	O
Officers	O
proved	O
the	O
same	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Colberteen	O
Lace	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fanshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Trooper	O
or	O
Granadeer	O
,	O
being	O
quarrered	O
at	O
Hellington	B-place
near	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
playing	O
at	O
Nine-pins	O
with	O
Gerrat	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Trooper	O
s	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
happening	O
to	O
quarrel	O
about	O
Payment	O
for	O
one	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
brought	O
in	O
more	O
than	O
play	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
first	O
Mead	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Dean	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
and	O
Mead	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
Dean	O
,	O
run	O
quits	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
:	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
Indicted	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Curlee	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
thereof	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Agnes	B-pers
Gandee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
;	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fran	O
Saw	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hynton	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
unadvised	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Joseph	O
Thomas	O
had	O
no	O
Intent	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
acquitted	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
without	O
paying	O
any	O
Fees	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
Pillowbeers	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
Dorrington	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
Pawned	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Bosworth	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Furnished	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Furniture	O
let	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
discharged	O
without	O
paying	O
Fees	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Merret	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
a	O
Womans	O
Band	O
,	O
a	O
Manta	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cha	B-pers
.	I-pers
Min	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dragooner	O
,	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
Tangier	O
,	O
and	O
quarter	O
'd	O
at	O
Hodsdon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Hartford	O
,	O
departing	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
without	O
License	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
several	O
hard	O
Usages	O
from	O
the	O
infe	O
iour	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
complain	O
to	O
his	O
Captain	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
some	O
other	O
like	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Leviston	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Fellow-Souldier	O
of	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
like	O
manner	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Olivant	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Angel	O
Gold	O
off	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Child	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Nag	O
coloured	O
Bay	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Allum	I-pers
,	O
living	O
at	O
Shelly	B-place
in	O
Essex	B-place
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Servants	O
of	O
Allum	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Plough	O
,	O
and	O
fixing	O
his	O
Eye	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
old	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Chippin	O
Onger	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pasture	O
;	O
riding	O
directly	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
taken	O
riding	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Market	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Page	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
thirty	O
four	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Canary	O
Wine	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
11	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
:	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
being	O
thereof	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gramant	I-pers
but	O
having	O
lain	O
two	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Beating	O
,	O
and	O
Wounding	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richeson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
some	O
Smocks	O
,	O
Aprons	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Prudence	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Twilter	I-pers
;	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
onthe	O
High-way	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
six	O
silk	O
Peticoats	O
,	O
sixty	O
four	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Copper-lace	O
,	O
thirty	O
six	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Pewter	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
most	O
malicious	O
and	O
false	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
divers	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
Indicted	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
were	O
disposed	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
In	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
as	O
Persons	O
unjustly	O
Indicted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
himself	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
three	O
Sutes	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
striped	O
Sattin	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rickets	I-pers
:	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
in	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Fire-Irons	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Durnell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
above	O
fifty	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
Bedding	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Houshold-stuff	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
stol'n	O
from	O
Durnell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Pope	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
hired	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
part	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
.	O
But	O
Pope	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
alledged	O
that	O
Durnell	O
's	O
Wife	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Porters	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
it	O
did	O
by	O
Circumstances	O
appear	O
,	O
Pope	O
was	O
too	O
great	O
with	O
Durnell	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Pope	O
;	O
also	O
that	O
Durnell	O
had	O
brought	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
Trover	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Pope	O
also	O
Arrested	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
both	O
lying	O
in	O
Prison	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Actions	O
,	O
had	O
agreed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
drawn	O
Releases	O
;	O
yet	O
after	O
Durnell	O
got	O
at	O
Liberty	O
,	O
he	O
Indicted	O
him	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
therefore	O
Pope	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Hen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Landing	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
stole	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Torton	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Landing	O
came	O
into	O
Torton	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Servant	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
Landing	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Landing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
together	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
bad	O
Circumstances	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moyle	I-pers
of	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
produced	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Calicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
Value	O
25	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Green	I-pers
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hampstead	I-pers
:	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
theroof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Nine	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	O
Hill	O
,	O
Morgan	O
Reading	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Holtham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Walden	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
Judgment	O
then	O
deferred	O
upon	O
the	O
Verdict	O
being	O
found	O
Special	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Close	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
between	O
50	O
and	O
60	O
Persons	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
and	O
Condemned	O
but	O
Reprieved	O
being	O
brought	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
severally	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
why	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
Executed	O
,	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bumstead	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
Chr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Planke	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Baal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Volour	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Gerrad	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hardin	I-pers
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
alias	O
Carus	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Den	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
Elenor	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Rob	O
.	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Wixely	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Barbadoes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Izzard	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gandee	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Enos	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
alias	O
Stone	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Axtan	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Atlee	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Russel	I-pers
alias	O
Napper	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Cha	B-pers
.	I-pers
Perrey	I-pers
alias	O
Parry	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maccarta	I-pers
,	O
the	O
four	O
last	O
having	O
some	O
Years	O
since	O
been	O
convicted	O
as	O
Seminary	O
Priests	O
.	O
Rebecea	O
Bennison	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Bennison	I-pers
,	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
being	O
included	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
General	O
Pardon	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
but	O
both	O
out	O
upon	O
Bail	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Edwards	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Pardon	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs	O
Bennison	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
when	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Two	O
Quakers	O
upon	O
Pramunire	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
also	O
included	O
therein	O
.	O
Which	O
General	O
Pardon	O
being	O
read	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Knocked	O
before	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
allowed	O
.	O
Which	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Nine	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	O
Hill	O
,	O
Morgan	O
Reading	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Holtham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Walden	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
Judgment	O
then	O
deferred	O
upon	O
the	O
Verdict	O
being	O
found	O
Special	O
.	O
Three	O
were	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Burchall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
begg	O
'd	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
granted	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cartmore	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Henry	B-pers
Curlee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Dickeson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Shipwasts	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Heldridge	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Olivant	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barnas	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
Close	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
between	O
50	O
and	O
60	O
Persons	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
and	O
Condemned	O
but	O
Reprieved	O
being	O
brought	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
severally	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
why	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
Executed	O
,	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bumstead	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
Chr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Planke	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Baal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Volour	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Gerrad	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hardin	I-pers
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
alias	O
Carus	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Den	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
Elenor	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Rob	O
.	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Wixely	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Barbadoes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Izzard	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gandee	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Enos	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
alias	O
Stone	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Axtan	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Atlee	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Russel	I-pers
alias	O
Napper	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Cha	B-pers
.	I-pers
Perrey	I-pers
alias	O
Parry	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maccarta	I-pers
,	O
the	O
four	O
last	O
having	O
some	O
Years	O
since	O
been	O
convicted	O
as	O
Seminary	O
Priests	O
.	O
Rebecea	O
Bennison	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Bennison	I-pers
,	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
being	O
included	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
General	O
Pardon	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
but	O
both	O
out	O
upon	O
Bail	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Edwards	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Pardon	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs	O
Bennison	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
when	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Two	O
Quakers	O
upon	O
Pramunire	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
also	O
included	O
therein	O
.	O
Which	O
General	O
Pardon	O
being	O
read	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Knocked	O
before	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
allowed	O
.	O
