TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Stockes	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Poe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Warfeild	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Cremer	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Gibons	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitfeild	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smallbone	I-pers
John	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pattle	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Hutchingson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hempstead	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Lin	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Edmons	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
Zacariah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
Peter	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
on	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fido	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
Fido	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
which	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Lary	O
was	O
presently	O
seized	O
:	O
The	O
proof	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Game	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Game	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
from	O
-	B-pers
Shenton	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
3	O
Hens	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Cock	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Tewerson	I-pers
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
;	O
Hickman	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Cross	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
scandalous	O
words	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
malicious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
Evidence	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
very	O
well	O
of	O
his	O
Conversation	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Loyal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Churchman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Brin	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
three	O
holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
silk	O
hoods	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
:	O
Roberts	O
's	O
Wife	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
there	O
found	O
her	O
Gown	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Gown	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Machenny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stirring	O
up	O
Sedition	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
intituled	O
,	O
A	O
seasonable	O
warning	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
persecuted	O
Church	O
of	O
Scotland	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
Book	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
very	O
much	O
Sedition	O
,	O
was	O
published	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
disturb	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
this	O
Machenny	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
fetch	O
and	O
disperse	O
scandalous	O
and	O
seditious	O
Books	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
Holland	O
:	O
The	O
Books	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
(	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
considerable	O
defence	O
)	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Grant	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
102	O
yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fitz-Zachery	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
to	O
evade	O
that	O
,	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
only	O
attested	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Crime	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
as	O
Accessary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Michaels	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
Spanish	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
l.	O
and	O
200	O
yards	O
more	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
90	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
.	O
That	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Sims	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Coat	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Th	O
:	O
Dangerfield	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bamboo	O
Cane	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
striking	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Left	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dangerfield	I-pers
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
deposing	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
coming	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Dangerfield	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
thrust	O
his	O
said	O
Cane	O
into	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
running	O
into	O
St.	O
Thavies	O
Inn	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Retinue	O
of	O
the	O
Prison	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
Dangerfield	O
would	O
dye	O
;	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Frances	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
the	O
HANGMAN	O
a	O
labour	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dangerfield	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Gaol	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
anguish	O
of	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Oh	O
my	O
Eye	O
!	O
Oh	O
my	O
Head	O
!	O
forbear	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
.	O
The	O
Physitian	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
advice	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
requisite	O
to	O
bleed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
desperately	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
vomiting	O
extremely	O
.	O
The	O
Chyrurgion	O
likewise	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
probing	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mortal	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
occasioned	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frances	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
alledged	O
;	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
Dangerfield	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
heated	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dangerfield	O
calling	O
him	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
passion	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
slight	O
Blow	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
verily	O
behaved	O
could	O
not	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
malice	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
few	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
spoke	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Deering	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
he	O
did	O
assault	O
and	O
murder	O
Henry	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Neck	O
therewith	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Goring	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
dyed	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
Scenes	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Barry	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Actresses	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
disrobe	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
become	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
present	O
whilst	O
she	O
put	O
off	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Bary	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Goring	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
,	O
cryes	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
here	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
,	O
and	O
desires	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
;	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
by	O
fair	O
means	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
by	O
foul	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
too	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
locking	O
it	O
,	O
drew	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
defending	O
himself	O
,	O
received	O
divers	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
people	O
running	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
both	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
;	O
and	O
parting	O
them	O
,	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Goring	O
presently	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
dyed	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
very	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Deering	O
himself	O
did	O
no	O
ways	O
deny	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
divers	O
who	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
how	O
Mr.	O
Goring	O
and	O
himself	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
great	O
friendship	O
together	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
apparent	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
prejudice	O
or	O
malice	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Goring	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
produced	O
many	O
persons	O
of	O
good	O
Quality	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsom	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
very	O
obliging	O
on	O
all	O
occasions	O
whatever	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
urg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
going	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
whilst	O
her	O
Husband	O
held	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
stole	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Sugar-Box	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Shop	O
;	O
whereupon	O
addressing	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
presently	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
and	O
demanding	O
why	O
they	O
served	O
her	O
so	O
?	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
Rent	O
;	O
when	O
upon	O
Examination	O
thereof	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
due	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
asserted	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
told	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
her	O
Landlady	O
no	O
Rent	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
attested	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
monies	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
some	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
to	O
buy	O
Provisions	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Davids	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quart-pot	O
,	O
on	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Pierce	O
.	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
runs	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
presently	O
missed	O
,	O
laying	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
back	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
12	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
That	O
Smith	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Criminal	O
,	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
crediting	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
diminishing	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
King	O
Edward	O
the	O
6th	O
Money	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Pieces	O
,	O
most	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
with	O
Sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
thereunto	O
belonging	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Positive	O
,	O
deposing	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Blowers	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
Enquire	O
for	O
some	O
Person	O
and	O
looking	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Clip	O
'd	O
pieces	O
,	O
with	O
Boxes	O
,	O
Sheers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
there	O
unto	O
belonging	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
make	O
but	O
very	O
cold	O
Excuses	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Lodger	O
about	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
a	O
Month	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Ignorant	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
Service	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
laid	O
the	O
Fact	O
so	O
apparent	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Jorden	I-pers
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Dowgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
ten	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Dy	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Lanton	B-pers
a	O
Silk	O
Dyer	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
very	O
sharp	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
ten	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
often	O
bring	O
Silk	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Sell	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
times	O
to	O
Weave	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
Stole	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
they	O
every	O
Day	O
Missed	O
Silk	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
produced	O
Evidence	O
for	O
his	O
Honesty	O
in	O
his	O
Livelyhood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Bought	O
the	O
Silk	O
that	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
June	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
in	O
Bell-Court	B-place
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
five	O
Scarves	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
Positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
said	O
she	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Vanderhurst	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Maries	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
June	O
26th	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
Vanderburst	O
was	O
seen	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Pursued	O
,	O
alighting	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
on	O
Foot	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Horse-keeper	O
following	O
him	O
Close	O
he	O
was	O
Taken	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
Releasment	O
,	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
Service	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
wanted	O
an	O
Horse	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
make	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Vickers	I-pers
on	O
June	O
12th	O
with	O
an	O
Handspike	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
Barnes	O
upon	O
some	O
petty	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
beat	O
the	O
said	O
Vickers	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Club	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Blow	O
the	O
said	O
Barnes	O
presently	O
Died	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Barnes	O
after	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Vickers	O
,	O
being	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
,	O
replied	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
brought	O
in	O
som	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
Vickers	O
was	O
Quarrelsome	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
begun	O
intaking	O
a	O
Bisket	O
from	O
Barnes	O
's	O
Partner	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Attwell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
May	O
30th	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
Attwell	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Branford	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Magpye	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
hired	O
for	O
one	O
Shilling	O
six	O
pence	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Horse	O
some	O
Grass	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
Branford	O
:	O
But	O
giving	O
very	O
little	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
deserting	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
recieved	O
Pay	O
from	O
his	O
Captain	O
,	O
His	O
Captain	O
attesting	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Listed	O
the	O
said	O
Anderson	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
thereupon	O
Mustered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
Quarters	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
said	O
Anderson	O
recieved	O
Pay	O
of	O
his	O
Captain	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
seen	O
by	O
his	O
Officer	O
for	O
seven	O
Days	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
said	O
Serjeant	O
accidentally	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
very	O
little	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
his	O
Captain	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
Pay	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
Listed	O
but	O
one	O
Day	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Coomes	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistoll	O
Charged	O
with	O
Bullet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
Shooting	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
he	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
attested	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
Complaint	O
made	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Coomes	O
,	O
they	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
carrying	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Coomes	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Assault	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
Examined	O
by	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
Taken	O
without	O
Pistoll	O
or	O
the	O
least	O
scent	O
of	O
Powder	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
general	O
being	O
on	O
supposition	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Battersby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
assaulted	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
on	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
attested	O
,	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
Rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
,	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
a	O
Razor	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
Upon	O
Examination	O
appearing	O
it	O
was	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Feuver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Skillet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
selling	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
apprehending	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
said	O
Pewter	O
;	O
his	O
Defence	O
only	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Owner	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
29	O
yards	O
of	O
Point-lace	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Dare	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
thus	O
:	O
That	O
Scot	O
coming	O
in	O
where	O
a	O
Maid	O
was	O
selling	O
Point	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Point	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
whereupon	O
suspecting	O
Scot	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Page	I-pers
Accessary	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lampany	I-pers
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
15	O
l.	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Weal	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Page	I-pers
his	O
Fellow-Prentice	O
was	O
sharer	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Page	O
likewise	O
confessing	O
he	O
had	O
2	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
money	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wig	I-pers
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
also	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
:	O
That	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
sollicit	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
about	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wig	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Tankard	O
by	O
Sunday	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
direct	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
:	O
A	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wigs	O
affirm	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
Martin	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
coloured	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Berkin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
a	O
Collar	O
maker	O
who	O
affirmed	O
that	O
Henry	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Hide	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
that	O
was	O
stole	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
her	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
June	O
11	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Peatly	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
Davis	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
brought	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
that	O
drew	O
it	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
throwing	O
out	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Newlan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Maries	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Littleton	I-pers
Goldsmith	O
.	O
July	O
30	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wardner	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
Argile	O
did	O
well	O
in	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
happy	O
if	O
the	O
Nation	O
would	O
Assist	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
saying	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
took	O
more	O
upon	O
him	O
than	O
was	O
Right	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
very	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
very	O
little	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	O
le	O
Fore	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
thrusting	O
the	O
said	O
Bridges	O
into	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Hoult	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
infomuch	O
that	O
she	O
dyed	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Morgan	O
committed	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
,	O
thereupon	O
White	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Filkins	B-pers
,	O
June	O
.	O
30th	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coates	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
Excuse	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Somerset	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
Pay	O
in	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
Run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
sick	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Churchouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Roderick	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
one	O
Coif	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d	O
:	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
Clipping	O
and	O
cutting	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
first	O
his	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
Shillings	O
:	O
Two	O
Goldsmiths	O
attesting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
often	O
brought	O
Clip	O
'd	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
for	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
Monies	O
they	O
recieved	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
giving	O
but	O
a	O
shallow	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Antony	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Travers	B-pers
,	O
on	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
unable	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
:	O
A	O
Woman	O
meeting	O
the	O
said	O
Becket	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dickenson	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Becket	O
pray	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
forbear	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
was	O
but	O
little	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Frisby	I-pers
on	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
12	O
glass	O
Bottles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
quarts	O
of	O
Syder	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
19	O
plum	O
Cakes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
;	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
on	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
stole	O
a	O
stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
as	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
nothing	O
but	O
Suppositions	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
a	O
Child	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
on	O
Decemb	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
from	O
Andrew	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
seizing	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
then	O
had	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
Mr.	O
White	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
one	O
Midleton	O
upon	O
an	O
Attachment	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Silke	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
from	O
Antony	O
le	O
Fountain	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
l.	O
pleads	O
Guilty	O
to	O
this	O
and	O
all	O
before	O
;	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
one	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
:	O
All	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
lost	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Pall	I-pers
had	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Linnen	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bankes	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Shooes	O
on	O
her	O
Feet	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
proved	O
that	O
Bankes	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
missing	O
;	O
All	O
her	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shooes	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Jaques	O
about	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Eye	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
strong	O
and	O
Goring	O
making	O
but	O
small	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
on	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brickwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gare	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
Eli	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
shop	O
on	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
and	O
getting	O
false	O
Keys	O
and	O
Pick	O
locks	O
into	O
their	O
Possession	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
very	O
apparent	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
coyned	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
nine	O
pence	O
,	O
on	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Emmuet	I-pers
.	O
All	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
appear	O
'd	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Henry	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Grafton	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Pallet	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Feather-bolster	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
Blankets	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Armstrong	O
's	O
custody	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Apleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
on	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Welford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
Horse	O
back	O
;	O
Apleton	O
affirmed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Joan	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
direct	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
way	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
confessing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Morday	B-pers
Cracklow	I-pers
on	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
eleven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
to	O
buy	O
Cloth	O
in	O
Cracklow	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
into	O
another	O
shop	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
enquiry	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
Cloth	O
behind	O
a	O
Counter	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golesburrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Midd	I-place
had	O
two	O
Indictments	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Towe	I-pers
;	O
another	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
Mark	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Four	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golesburrow	I-pers
.	O
Nine	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Battin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Newlan	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
.	O
Seventeen	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Allice	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Churchouse	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
Elinnor	O
Hilton	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wardner	I-pers
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
from	O
Aldgate	O
to	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
fined	O
four	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gare	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
whipt	O
from	O
Aldgate	O
to	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
fined	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Philips	O
and	O
Shaller	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Ryot	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
Prison	O
,	O
from	O
Newgate-street	O
found	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
to	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Newgate	O
again	O
.	O
Also	O
one	O
Gosmer	O
was	O
Fined	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Machenny	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
severely	O
whipt	O
,	O
for	O
dispersing	O
feditious	O
Books	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Friday	O
next	O
.	O
Thirteen	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Vanderburst	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Attwell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weal	I-pers
,	O
Nathamel	O
Page	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Somerset	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morgen	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Antony	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
;	O
after	O
Sentence	O
she	O
was	O
Reprieved	O
.	O
