TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
23th	O
.	O
24th	O
.	O
and	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
23th	O
.	O
24th	O
.	O
and	O
25th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
1687	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peaks	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Shrawley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Han	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
John	B-pers
Endarsby	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Short	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Cornwork	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Cayde	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Terrill	I-pers
John	B-pers
Revet	I-pers
George	B-pers
Westray	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Huynes	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hembrick	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Rudg	I-pers
George	B-pers
Clisby	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gaunt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Haistings	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
William	B-pers
Coodrin	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
having	O
an	O
Indictment	O
prefer	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leanords	I-place
Forster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
pleaded	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Periwig	O
,	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleives	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
valued	O
as	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Gardner	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
procured	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
Gardner	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
his	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
departed	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
yet	O
soon	O
after	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
than	O
any	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Apparel	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
presuming	O
on	O
the	O
Familliarity	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
insinuated	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
most	O
but	O
borrow	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
restore	O
them	O
and	O
it	O
moreover	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
their	O
stead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nightingall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
seven	O
Peuter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
29	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
Peuter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Nightingall	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
the	O
first	O
deposing	O
that	O
the	O
Peuter	O
(	O
to	O
his	O
knowledge	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Kitchen	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
it	O
was	O
Missing	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
Latter	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
by	O
her	O
Consent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
her	O
Masters	O
Cellar	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
securing	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Fury	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Peuter	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Street	O
being	O
likewise	O
left	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
absented	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
proof	O
but	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
attested	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Chains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bottolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Smith	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Cooper	O
,	O
came	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
things	O
specified	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
withall	O
left	O
a	O
stick	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
attested	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
hankering	O
thereabout	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Meat	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
strongest	O
stress	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Childs	O
discribing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
any	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
right	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
which	O
Felony	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
she	O
had	O
Confessed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
make	O
any	O
defence	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
confirmed	O
her	O
former	O
Confession	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Seal	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
she	O
had	O
Confessed	O
her	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Sale	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
proper	O
Plate	O
of	O
the	O
Masters	B-pers
and	O
Fellows	B-pers
of	I-pers
Baliol	I-pers
Colledge	I-pers
in	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherin	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
Testimony	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
attempting	O
to	O
Sell	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Inscription	O
and	O
Arms	O
of	O
the	O
Colledge	O
and	O
Doner	O
,	O
upon	O
Notice	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Fellows	O
of	O
the	O
Colledge	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
testified	O
as	O
much	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
near	O
that	O
Colledge	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
otherwise	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
producing	O
the	O
party	O
,	O
or	O
giving	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
accounts	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Leather	O
Chair	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
Silk	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kennet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Kennet	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
missing	O
her	O
things	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
the	O
Barr	O
of	O
Iron	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
a	O
Frying	O
Pan	O
Handle	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
she	O
lost	O
)	O
at	O
one	O
Whites	O
a	O
Brother	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
being	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
Broker	O
to	O
be	O
content	O
,	O
in	O
Gibbons	O
came	O
again	O
he	O
had	O
promised	O
which	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
with	O
Nine	O
Streaks	O
or	O
Rods	O
of	O
Iron	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Broker	O
apprehended	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
plead	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Iron	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
fortunately	O
met	O
byupon	O
Bridge	O
,	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
he	O
pretended	O
was	O
owing	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
party	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Longstaff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
about	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribond	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Alamode	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Muzling	O
Cravat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
two	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
made	O
their	O
escapes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
the	O
Cravat	O
,	O
three	O
Pinners	O
and	O
the	O
Hood	O
were	O
droped	O
;	O
against	O
this	O
his	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
out	O
cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
running	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
a	O
mistake	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
and	O
consternation	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seized	O
,	O
pretending	O
over	O
and	O
above	O
to	O
excuse	O
his	O
being	O
that	O
way	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Thief	O
,	O
though	O
but	O
a	O
Young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Torrel	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
laid	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Defacing	O
,	O
and	O
otherwise	O
Deminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
properly	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
a	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Ten	O
other	O
pieces	O
,	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
with	O
Sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Elenor	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
with	O
Torrel	O
as	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
then	O
Clip	O
,	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
Rub	O
,	O
Coined	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Custome	O
with	O
Torrel	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
two	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
of	O
little	O
Money	O
for	O
twenty	O
of	O
large	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
receiving	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
her	O
upon	O
a	O
Bible	O
to	O
Secresie	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
observed	O
Bill	O
,	O
Rub	O
clipd	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
out	O
Money	O
when	O
Clipped	O
to	O
change	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
search	O
of	O
Torrels	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
Clipped	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
hide	O
and	O
prevent	O
from	O
being	O
discovered	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
Margaret	B-pers
Torrel	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Pride	O
had	O
impeached	O
them	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Bill	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
possitive	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Clipping	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Torrel	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
White	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barly	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
likewise	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
had	O
Clipped	O
,	O
Filed	O
,	O
and	O
Deminished	O
,	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Current	O
Coin	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Three	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Sixpence	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
;	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
Rub	O
Clipped	O
Money	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
smooth	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
newly	O
done	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
custome	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
away	O
broad	O
Money	O
to	O
Clippers	O
for	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Shillings	O
advantage	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
Clip	O
one	O
sixpence	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Treason	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Ten	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
.	O
Against	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
Rub	O
Clip	O
'd	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
away	O
large	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
Clipper	O
now	O
fled	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
advantage	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
money	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
Clip	O
'd	O
,	O
besides	O
signs	O
and	O
tokens	O
of	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
Clip	O
'd	O
money	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
English	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
in	O
like	O
manner	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
seven	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Andrews	O
a	O
Victualar	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
to	O
Elenor	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Clip	O
'd	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Clip	O
'd	O
Silver	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
fly	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Clipped	O
and	O
Suspitious	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
pleading	O
Ignorance	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
excusing	O
his	O
flight	O
with	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
fearing	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
in	O
consideration	O
he	O
was	O
ingaged	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
for	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
for	O
Hogs	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nuthall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High-Misdemeanour	O
,	O
to	O
uttering	O
Clip	O
'd	O
money	O
and	O
bringing	O
broad	O
Money	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barly	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
of	O
Clip	O
'd	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
23	O
s.	O
Clip	O
'd	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
Broad	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
utterly	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
possitive	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
as	O
that	O
foregoing	O
Couple	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
changing	O
Broad	O
money	O
for	O
Clipped	O
,	O
for	O
gain	O
sake	O
,	O
receiving	O
in	O
that	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
advantage	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
Elenor	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
had	O
changed	O
money	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
especially	O
Esther	O
Mathews	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
had	O
changed	O
money	O
with	O
herself	O
by	O
small	O
parcels	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
allowance	O
proportionably	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
utterly	O
denying	O
what	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
her	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
changed	O
but	O
one	O
Half	O
Crown	O
with	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
had	O
eighteen	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
,	O
no	O
considerable	O
Sums	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
to	O
that	O
intent	O
or	O
purpose	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Upter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
Upter	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
;	O
who	O
deposing	O
that	O
they	O
surprising	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
leaped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Casement	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
for	O
his	O
enterance	O
by	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Quarry	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Maid	O
seized	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
secured	O
.	O
His	O
Plea	O
against	O
this	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
catching	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
business	O
by	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
matter	O
by	O
reason	O
nothing	O
was	O
taken	O
or	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
layed	O
,	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Small	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
laid	O
for	O
Felony	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
Fifty	O
Marble	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
Marble	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
properly	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
Townsend	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
;	O
but	O
Small	O
and	O
Clark	O
puting	O
themselves	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
for	O
their	O
Tryal	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
only	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
laid	O
down	O
with	O
Mortar	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
adjudging	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Felony	O
;	O
they	O
extended	O
their	O
favour	O
so	O
far	O
to	O
Townsend	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
retract	O
his	O
Plea	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
putting	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
a	O
fresh	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
Carrier	O
of	O
C.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
false	O
mony	O
knowingly	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
Mill	O
'd	O
money	O
that	O
had	O
passed	O
through	O
divers	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Credit	O
and	O
Honest	O
Reputation	O
being	O
attested	O
by	O
divers	O
persons	O
of	O
Eminent	O
Quality	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
giving	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Stains	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Brian	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
flowered	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Petty-coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
Stains	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
her	O
committing	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Stains	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Wilks	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pen	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Fredrick	B-pers
Cassibon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
dozen	O
of	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Pillows	O
,	O
Lace	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Brook	O
's	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Carpenter	O
putting	O
himself	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
in	O
Mere	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
other	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Giles	B-pers
Deny	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Wearing	O
Apparrel	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
which	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Brooks	O
having	O
before	O
confessed	O
the	O
Indictments	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Turbith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
&	O
a	O
Jacobus	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
Moss	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Felony	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
during	O
her	O
living	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
again	O
put	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
there	O
made	O
a	O
repetition	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Colechurch	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
upon	O
whose	O
testimony	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Wilson	O
had	O
confessed	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
whilst	O
Clinton	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
instrument	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chest	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
promising	O
him	O
a	O
proportionable	O
share	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
ring	O
against	O
Clinton	O
but	O
Wilson	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Wilson	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Deminishing	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
6	O
K.	O
Charles	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
8	O
Charles	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Sixpences	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Coin	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
her	O
rub	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Mony	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
smooth	O
and	O
passable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
Broad	O
Mony	O
for	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Mony	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Allowance	O
of	O
24	O
s.	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
these	O
amounting	O
to	O
Clipping	O
,	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
as	O
Accessary	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
stands	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
an	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
,	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
broad	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
than	O
what	O
Fletcher	O
had	O
confessed	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
proving	O
insufficient	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Deminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Seven	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Coin	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
with	O
Margaret	O
Torrel	O
lately	O
Convicted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
large	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Clipped	O
money	O
with	O
the	O
advantage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
bring	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
likewise	O
seen	O
her	O
rub	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
look	O
Old	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
bringing	O
Testimony	O
of	O
her	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
by	O
her	O
Labour	O
and	O
Industry	O
for	O
a	O
Lively	O
hood	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
exchanging	O
large	O
money	O
for	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
Clipped	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
Elenor	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
gave	O
Testimony	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
bring	O
broad	O
mony	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
her	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
usual	O
advantage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
rub	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
pass	O
Currant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
sometimes	O
she	O
changed	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
sometimes	O
more	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
her	O
innocency	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
many	O
protestations	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Willloghby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
changing	O
broad	O
money	O
for	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
Clipped	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Ashlock	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
changing	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
broad	O
money	O
for	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
Clipped	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Elenor	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
bring	O
money	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
;	O
but	O
she	O
bringing	O
persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Labouring	O
Woman	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
living	O
by	O
Washing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frail	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
melting	O
Clippings	O
to	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
melted	O
Clippings	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
quantities	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
in	O
Coveton	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
as	O
Well-Close	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
trust	O
by	O
one	O
Fryer	O
,	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
for	O
Clipping	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Line	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryon	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Harrington	O
,	O
Hicks	O
,	O
and	O
H	O
-	O
had	O
dragged	O
the	O
deceased	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Milford-Lane	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
a	O
General	O
Warrant	O
to	O
seize	O
upon	O
Suspicious	O
persons	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
delay	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
since	O
fled	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prison-house	O
of	O
Gilbert	O
Thomas	O
in	O
Lukeners	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
he	O
was	O
received	O
by	O
Line	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
beaten	O
by	O
Harrington	O
and	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
then	O
continuing	O
several	O
days	O
chained	O
to	O
the	O
Flour	O
without	O
sustenance	O
,	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Proof	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
sought	O
by	O
many	O
Excuses	O
to	O
evade	O
it	O
:	O
Harrington	O
,	O
H	O
-	O
and	O
Hicks	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
and	O
consent	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Twine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
her	O
free	O
consent	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
Seventeen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Blew	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
Uxbridge	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
for	O
8	O
d.	O
at	O
an	O
Neighbouring	O
Ale-house	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
double	O
Flaxen	O
Clout	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
Lewin	O
's	O
Daughter	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Line	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
alledging	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
a	O
Thorow-Fare	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
value	O
being	O
very	O
small	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butter	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Parker	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
De	O
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
with	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Vallains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
his	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Beton	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
44	O
Cocks	O
and	O
Hens	O
,	O
and	O
Ten	O
Geese	O
and	O
Ganders	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trunk	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trunk	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
.	O
Also	O
upon	O
a	O
third	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
;	O
with	O
which	O
Gelding	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Clarkenwell	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pedworth	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bays	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Cloath	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloath	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Pettycoats	O
of	O
Crape	O
and	O
Silk	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
which	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
produced	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
of	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
the	O
party	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denying	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
produced	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Selwin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
one	O
Smock	O
,	O
one	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
two	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
25	O
s.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
Selwin	O
that	O
she	O
seized	O
on	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
were	O
removed	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
pretending	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Womans	O
Labour	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
affright	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
been	O
her	O
Landlady	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
nothing	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
her	O
self	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Caracter	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
First	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Coat	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
from	O
Brian	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
Secondly	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Winsor	I-pers
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Brooks	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Hill	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
step	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
upper	O
Rooms	O
,	O
and	O
braking	O
open	O
divers	O
Trunks	O
,	O
took	O
thence	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seized	O
in	O
attempting	O
another	O
Robery	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
alledged	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Obeham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gillham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
but	O
puting	O
himself	O
for	O
his	O
Tryal	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leanords	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Stepwell	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
She	O
and	O
her	O
Family	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
12	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
2	O
Laced	O
Coifs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cap	O
with	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallance	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
Goods	O
,	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
pilfring	O
Fellow	O
,	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bellenger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Monys	O
,	O
from	O
Samuell	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
by	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
remarkable	O
piece	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolphs	I-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Feather	O
Beds	O
,	O
2	O
Bolsters	O
a	O
Chopping	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
and	O
a	O
Iron	O
Beats	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
half	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
a	O
Skreen	O
and	O
Rug	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waight	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
removed	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
Waight	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ordered	O
to	O
prefer	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
Hicks-Hall	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Millinor	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
were	O
Tryedfor	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Beaker	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Edwards	O
and	O
Cary	O
coming	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
her	O
to	O
Seower	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Spoons	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Millinor	O
Gary	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
confessed	O
they	O
delivered	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
Savage	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
Dudley	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
were	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Quant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Sarsnet	O
Hoods	O
,	O
2	O
other	O
Hoods	O
,	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Point	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petty-coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
being	O
discovered	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
leaped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
dropped	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
alledging	O
,	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
had	O
fled	O
had	O
white	O
Stockings	O
,	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Minchin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Boyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Duel	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
nothing	O
being	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Party	O
that	O
lodged	O
there	O
abouts	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Donn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparrel	O
,	O
as	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Pettycoates	O
,	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
by	O
forcing	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
opening	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
:	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Spaniard	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
received	O
their	O
Dividend	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
D	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
in	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
,	O
of	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Desk	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Study	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
by	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Desk	O
with	O
the	O
Mony	O
taken	O
thence	O
the	O
Desk	O
being	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
found	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
i'th	O
new	O
Buildings	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
Writings	O
of	O
concernment	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Mony	O
gone	O
,	O
yet	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
D	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
being	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
how	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Confederate	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
,	O
committed	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
defence	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
,	O
against	O
Davis	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
D	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Davis	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Mackfenne	I-pers
,	O
being	O
brought	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Small	O
value	O
,	O
was	O
upon	O
plain	O
proof	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
grand	O
Jury	O
returned	O
ignorance	O
on	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
of	O
Death	O
upon	O
9	O
viz	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
D	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
Roger	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	O
Hicks	O
,	O
T	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
Margaret	B-pers
Torrel	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
English	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
Reprieved	O
before	O
Judgement	O
,	O
4	O
viz	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Millinor	O
Cary	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
12.	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bellinger	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Phillip	O
Stains	O
,	O
Mary	O
Turbith	O
,	O
William	O
Banister	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Donne	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
Ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
4.	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Nath	O
.	O
Brooks	O
and	O
Edw	O
.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
4.	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Longstaff	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	O
Mackfenne	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
who	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty	O
Larcenary	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Punishment	O
changed	O
into	O
a	O
Weeks	O
imprisonment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frail	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
continue	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
it	O
be	O
payed	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Torrel	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
White	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellys	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
latter	O
was	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
