TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
6th	O
.	O
7th	O
.	O
and	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
7th	O
.	O
and	O
8th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Kimbal	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peckman	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Roll	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Minchal	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hugehut	I-pers
James	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Oakly	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Goodhand	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whit	I-pers
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Brettridge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Tatlock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pattle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
Henry	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
alias	O
Bell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Pountny	I-place
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
sixteen	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Musling	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
Henly	O
being	O
sometime	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
Committed	O
,	O
Apprehended	O
for	O
cheating	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
by	O
asking	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
wrong	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
taxed	O
with	O
this	O
Robbery	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Apron	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
Goswel	O
street	O
for	O
sixpence	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
accordingly	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
Court	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Doble	I-pers
being	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
:	O
The	O
First	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Peuter-Plates	O
,	O
one	O
Peuter-Dish	O
,	O
six	O
Quart-Pots	O
and	O
one	O
Brass-Pan	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
five	O
Peuter-Plates	O
from	O
Gregory	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Agnes	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallins	O
,	O
one	O
Counterpain	O
,	O
one	O
Rug	O
,	O
two	O
Mantles	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
one	O
Pillowbare	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
from	O
Mathew	B-pers
Howlet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
one	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
Upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
unless	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
might	O
be	O
first	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
granting	O
him	O
the	O
Favour	O
to	O
consider	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
danger	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
incurr	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
Refusal	O
;	O
he	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bengaul	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Leonard	B-pers
Tippet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
her	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
their	O
Masters	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
thrust	O
the	O
Silk	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
questioned	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
further	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
one	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Harvy	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
their	O
Chamber	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
found	O
a	O
remarkable	O
piece	O
of	O
Money	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
defrauded	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
likewise	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
upon	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
thence	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
her	O
former	O
Confession	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
nor	O
capable	O
of	O
offering	O
any	O
thing	O
material	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
;	O
yet	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
reduced	O
their	O
Verdict	O
within	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
Pettilarcinary	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Lace	O
'd	O
Pinner	O
,	O
lay	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Simkin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
Pinner	O
mentioned	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Possession	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Willmot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Cornelian	O
Ring	O
,	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
one	O
Embrodered	O
Purse	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
Boxes	O
,	O
one	O
small	O
Jewel	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
being	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Willmot	I-pers
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Flowered	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
through	O
the	O
defect	O
and	O
insufficiancie	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burgin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
having	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
preferred	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Deminishingthe	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Twenty	O
half	O
Crowns	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
Sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catharine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
Defacing	O
and	O
Deminishing	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
&	O
c.	O
Viz	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
the	O
First	O
,	O
his	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Coin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Powr	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
Catharine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
on	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
seen	O
her	O
Clip	O
divers	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
but	O
had	O
her	O
self	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
purchased	O
Guineas	O
by	O
her	O
order	O
,	O
with	O
Clipped	O
Money	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Elizabeth	O
Creed	O
File	O
divers	O
parcels	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
further	O
appearing	O
by	O
other	O
Testimony	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
searching	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
File-dust	O
,	O
but	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Clipped	O
Money	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
unfinished	O
,	O
being	O
with	O
other	O
Instruments	O
useful	O
on	O
that	O
occasion	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
Confessing	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Shambrook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Trusses	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wilcock	I-pers
's	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
Wilcocks	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Hey	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Hovel	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
but	O
producing	O
Evidence	O
to	O
testifie	O
his	O
long	O
inhabiting	O
that	O
Parish	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Deans	I-place
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
valu	O
'd	O
at	O
6	O
l.	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
valu	O
'd	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
valu	O
'd	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
living	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
missing	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
17	O
s.	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
,	O
she	O
after	O
some	O
difficulty	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
imployed	O
it	O
in	O
buying	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Fruit	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
also	O
upon	O
search	O
a	O
New	O
Shilling	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
by	O
her	O
Mistris	O
in	O
a	O
Closset	O
to	O
try	O
her	O
fidelitie	O
,	O
and	O
moreover	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
delivering	O
it	O
to	O
Andrew	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
her	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
but	O
only	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
report	O
he	O
was	O
aquitted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Imbrodered	O
Holster-caps	O
valu	O
'd	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Furnis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
Evidence	O
was	O
given	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
Imbroderry	O
to	O
a	O
Companion	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
follows	O
the	O
Profession	O
of	O
Craft	O
of	O
a	O
Taylor	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
London	O
for	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Taylor	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Sadler	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
peice	O
not	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
positive	O
proof	O
being	O
made	O
out	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Grove	O
sold	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
valu	O
'd	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Perry	O
,	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cup	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Hounds	O
ditch	O
for	O
Twelve	O
Shillings	O
;	O
where	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
Perry	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
restor	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessing	O
as	O
much	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
consideration	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Rowland	B-pers
Litton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
valu	O
'd	O
28	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
valu	O
'd	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleives	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Frienged	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Brush	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Top	O
;	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Litton	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
March	O
was	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Litton	O
meeting	O
with	O
Cooly	O
for	O
some	O
considerations	O
carried	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
drinking	O
pretty	O
freely	O
,	O
he	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
staying	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Litton	O
was	O
a	O
Sleep	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
his	O
Trunk	O
and	O
Closet	O
,	O
possessed	O
himself	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
;	O
with	O
which	O
unlocking	O
the	O
outward	O
Dore	O
he	O
fled	O
for	O
Ireland	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
returning	O
to	O
London	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
evade	O
it	O
and	O
justifie	O
his	O
Innocence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humphry	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frise	O
Coat	O
valu	O
'd	O
at	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hatt	O
valu	O
'd	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waight	I-pers
Junior	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Blackfryers	I-place
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Waight	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Challenged	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
Coat	O
was	O
likewise	O
produced	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
them	O
in	O
Court	O
but	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
pleading	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
Green	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
Testifie	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Husbands	O
Coat	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Chuttle	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Wordal	I-pers
and	O
others	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
forcible	O
Entry	O
upon	O
the	O
Cellar	O
or	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lecount	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Merchant	O
in	O
Mincing-Lane	B-place
London	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
about	O
Forty	O
two	O
Hogsheads	O
of	O
French	O
Wine	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
they	O
pleading	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
puting	O
themselves	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
their	O
Tryals	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Wordal	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
great	O
Ability	O
and	O
undertaking	O
,	O
had	O
bargained	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
Lecount	O
for	O
twenty	O
Tuns	O
of	O
French-Wine	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
Writings	O
were	O
drawn	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Moneys	O
for	O
the	O
Wines	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
within	O
a	O
week	O
following	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Payment	O
Wordal	O
with	O
a	O
considerable	O
strength	O
of	O
men	O
forcing	O
the	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
set	O
Porters	O
on	O
work	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Lecount	O
,	O
to	O
pull	O
up	O
the	O
Wine	O
and	O
convey	O
it	O
thence	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
and	O
behoof	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
afterward	O
Replevined	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
sundry	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
partys	O
who	O
now	O
took	O
their	O
Tryals	O
were	O
Aiding	O
,	O
and	O
Abetting	O
to	O
Wordal	O
in	O
his	O
resolute	O
and	O
unlawful	O
undertaking	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
hired	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
that	O
intent	O
and	O
purpose	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Riot	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Nelson	O
and	O
Chuttle	O
:	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Congreen	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
alias	O
Levinston	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Richard	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Preston	I-pers
Scituate	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Hair	O
Chamblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Steel	O
and	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Walnut	O
Tree	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Sash	O
Window	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
drawn-up	O
in	O
a	O
Ground-Parlour	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
then	O
somewhat	O
within	O
Night	O
Hide	O
crep	O
'd	O
in	O
and	O
delivered	O
out	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
to	O
Levistone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Congreen	O
and	O
Savage	O
stood	O
a	O
Loff	O
,	O
but	O
afterward	O
they	O
met	O
and	O
sheared	O
the	O
Booty	O
,	O
throwing	O
the	O
Box	O
behind	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
taken	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Moneys	O
,	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
Riping-Chizles	O
and	O
Pick-Lock	O
Keys	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Potly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Coif	O
,	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
,	O
Nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribon	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
;	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bigland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
Gloves	O
,	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Loads	O
of	O
Wood	O
or	O
Timber	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Girl	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
nothing	O
,	O
unless	O
a	O
few	O
sticks	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Thackery	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Aprons	O
,	O
one	O
Musling	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
one	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Bigland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Hood	O
valued	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Compassionating	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
Crime	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fauster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
being	O
Circumvented	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
only	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
32	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Dorwille	I-pers
of	O
St.Giles	B-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Wiggans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dyed	O
Linnen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
his	I-pers
Partner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Bengaul	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
Dyed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
which	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
for	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Cliffords-Inn	O
:	O
Her	O
Plea	O
was	O
she	O
was	O
ignorant	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
alledging	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
unknowingly	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
(	O
and	O
Agnes	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
not	O
)	O
being	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
one	O
Rug	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Bret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
guilty	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Indictments	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
alias	O
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
enter	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
,	O
by	O
was	O
interupted	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
accomplish	O
his	O
design	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Hugh	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Bayly	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
two	O
persons	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
shewing	O
some	O
dislike	O
of	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Publick-Room	O
,	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
staying	O
for	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
Butler	O
that	O
lived	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
throw	O
out	O
part	O
of	O
their	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
their	O
Escape	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
Thomson	O
utterly	O
denying	O
ever	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Bayly	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
severale	O
persons	O
to	O
give	O
Testimony	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
honest	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
supposing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Deserting	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Parsons	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Grafton	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
Received	O
his	O
Shilling	O
Enterance	O
or	O
Retaining	O
Mony	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
further	O
Received	O
the	O
Kings	O
Pay	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
was	O
Mustered	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Claud	B-pers
Durain	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Keneday	I-pers
,	O
were	O
put	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Deserting	O
their	O
Colours	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
had	O
Reconciled	O
themselves	O
to	O
their	O
Officer	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
purpose	O
and	O
intent	O
to	O
returne	O
to	O
their	O
Duty	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cartmal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Deserting	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Sr.	O
Martin	B-pers
Beckman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Retaining	O
Mony	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blackway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
Bermonsy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Deserting	O
his	O
Colours	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Retaining	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
further	O
advantages	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Pay	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
Listed	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
procedent	O
August	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Southwark	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Deserting	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Listing	O
or	O
Retaining	O
Shilling	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Deserting	O
got	O
a	O
Ship-Board	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
Holland	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
no	O
better	O
things	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
valu	O
'd	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Swanly	I-pers
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
Pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
one	O
Atkins	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
cut	O
the	O
strinsg	O
and	O
taken	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Line	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
discovery	O
thereof	O
they	O
fled	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
valu	O
'd	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Leadon	O
Cestorn	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Grates	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Box	O
,	O
three	O
Turkey-work	O
Cushons	O
and	O
24	O
peices	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
Souces	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
mentioned	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
the	O
Lookin	O
glass	O
to	O
sail	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
Pleading	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Paty	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Six	O
pence	O
for	O
her	O
trouble	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
no	O
otherwise	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
Married	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
34th	O
,	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Lile	I-pers
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
a	O
Live	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
second	O
Wife	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Lile	I-pers
,	O
though	O
she	O
had	O
Sworn	O
her	O
Marriage	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
denying	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
Marryed	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
only	O
as	O
his	O
Companion	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
contrary	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
And	O
she	O
by	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Goloon	O
Lace	O
valu	O
'd	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Baradel	I-pers
his	O
Master	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
usual	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Ends	O
and	O
Slips	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
performed	O
with	O
the	O
Lace	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Finisher	O
those	O
things	O
for	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
allowed	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
the	O
Galoon	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
many	O
peices	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
Cabage	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Boul	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Taster	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Holland	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
coming	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
for	O
him	O
thither	O
,	O
they	O
there	O
sat	O
drinking	O
till	O
Ann	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
pretending	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Company	O
and	O
returned	O
not	O
till	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Coxons	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
possitive	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dille	I-pers
in	O
Hatton-Garden	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sidebottom	I-pers
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
against	O
his	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
have	O
discovered	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
Sidebottom	O
overaw	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
threatning	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Testimony	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Trabern	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
thus	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
in	O
Service	O
,	O
complained	O
one	O
Morning	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
very	O
bad	O
with	O
a	O
Cold	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
former	O
Suspition	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
survey	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
Room	O
,	O
as	O
some	O
thing	O
suspecting	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
by	O
many	O
Symtoms	O
that	O
something	O
extraordinary	O
had	O
befell	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
understood	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
cast	O
in	O
the	O
Bog-house	O
,	O
where	O
upon	O
search	O
it	O
was	O
accordingly	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
full	O
grown	O
Child	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Draydon	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
160	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
C	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Grocer	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before-mentioned	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
he	O
had	O
proved	O
unfaithful	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
discharged	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
when	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
broak	O
through	O
a	O
Window	O
on	O
the	O
back-side	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
a	O
Chest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
wherein	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
lay	O
'd	O
them	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
departed	O
;	O
whichupon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
he	O
Confessed	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
Wastband	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
his	O
Truss	O
,	O
Glove	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
150	O
Guineas	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
pieces	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
Confessed	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
for	O
,	O
or	O
purchased	O
with	O
his	O
Masters	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
debate	O
arising	O
,	O
whether	O
by	O
(	O
reason	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
altered	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
never	O
being	O
effectually	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
or	O
not	O
)	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
10	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
a	O
forcible	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
Result	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
be	O
determined	O
upon	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Prosecution	O
arising	O
from	O
a	O
Drinking-hour	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Moneys	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
Confessed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
Forty	O
pounds	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
said	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
otherwise	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Clasp	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
one	O
Cravat	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Calebo	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
the	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Door	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
opened	O
by	O
picking	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
upon	O
Arnolds	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
for	O
another	O
Robery	O
,	O
the	O
Clasp	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
won	O
them	O
at	O
play	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sharland	I-pers
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Player	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Felonys	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Couzens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Dudly	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
one	O
Hat	O
,	O
one	O
Cain	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Fringe-Gloves	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
removed	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tuisden	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
further	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Confessed	O
one	O
Clark	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
removed	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bamford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
Alice	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
to	O
Dine	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
their	O
Gang	O
,	O
took	O
opportunity	O
in	O
her	O
Absence	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
her	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
moneys	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
soon	O
after	O
their	O
departure	O
suspecting	O
some	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Ring	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
with	O
Gurney	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
refuse	O
to	O
Confess	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
her	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Bow	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Seuks	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Felonys	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
being	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Cheating	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norrice	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
valu	O
'd	O
20	O
s.	O
under	O
presence	O
of	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
coming	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
wrong	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
converting	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
confessed	O
the	O
defraud	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Parret	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankerd	O
valu	O
'd	O
9	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Boul	O
valu	O
'd	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
Six	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
Curral	O
,	O
Three	O
silver	O
Bodkins	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
Six	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
valu	O
'd	O
12	O
l.	O
together	O
with	O
605l	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
is	O
appeared	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
aforesaid	O
Edwards	O
waken	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sleep	O
by	O
the	O
noise	O
he	O
heard	O
;	O
soon	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Theives	O
breaking	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
entred	O
below	O
by	O
breaking	O
two	O
Bars	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
his	O
man	O
lay	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
bound	O
,	O
whereupon	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
in	O
vain	O
attemped	O
to	O
enter	O
his	O
Chamber	O
at	O
the	O
Trap-door	O
,	O
they	O
attempted	O
the	O
stairs	O
which	O
he	O
guarded	O
with	O
a	O
Pitch-Fork	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
being	O
debar	O
'd	O
of	O
entrance	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
broak	O
in	O
upon	O
him	O
through	O
a	O
Mudd	O
or	O
Lome	O
Wall	O
near	O
to	O
a	O
Chimny	O
,	O
with	O
Swords	O
and	O
Pistols	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
being	O
over	O
power	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
fall	O
on	O
their	O
Knees	O
and	O
beg	O
for	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
cuting	O
a	O
Cord	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
bound	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Ransaked	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
only	O
four	O
entering	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
rest	O
supposed	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
Eleaven	O
surrounded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
whose	O
hands	O
the	O
mony	O
fell	O
,	O
which	O
Edward	O
's	O
Wife	O
threw	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Brewer	O
,	O
Edward	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
man	O
that	O
Entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lighted	O
,	O
and	O
Edwards	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Parret	O
was	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
less	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
hold	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Head	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Casement	O
:	O
swearing	O
that	O
unless	O
she	O
drew	O
it	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Casement	O
he	O
would	O
Pistol	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
were	O
the	O
Sword	O
and	O
Hanger	O
afterward	O
taken	O
disagreable	O
to	O
those	O
they	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Robery	O
committed	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
Parret	O
,	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
Sawyer	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Noble	O
,	O
than	O
what	O
himself	O
had	O
confessed	O
of	O
Sawyers	O
lending	O
him	O
mony	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wapell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
9.	O
and	O
10.	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
day	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Locks	O
being	O
broken	O
and	O
picked	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
Removed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Land	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Adjudging	O
it	O
no	O
Burglary	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
of	O
Death	O
upon	O
a	O
Eleven	O
Persons	O
viz	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sharland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Trabern	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Parret	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Hangd	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Reprived	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Pleading	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Negative	O
.	O
Nine	O
Person	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	O
,	O
Hide	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Congreen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bamford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Doble	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
Three	O
viz	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grifith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Cozens	O
.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
Nine	O
viz	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Potly	I-pers
,	O
Jone	O
Thackery	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Wiggans	I-pers
who	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petelercenary	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
penalty	O
changed	O
into	O
a	O
days	O
Imprisonment	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
who	O
had	O
incur	O
'd	O
the	O
like	O
penalty	O
was	O
set	O
a	O
side	O
before	O
sentance	O
.	O
Fin	O
'd	O
Six	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Chuttle	I-pers
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
before	O
the	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
York	I-pers
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
peice	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
1	O
s.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooly	I-pers
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
beg	O
'd	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
consideration	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Exhibition	O
thereof	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
alow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
