TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
alias	O
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Aldershaw	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Asheley	I-pers
alias	O
Browne	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
Church	I-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
Sacriligiously	O
did	O
take	O
away	O
2	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloaths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Velvet	O
Pawl	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Velvet	O
Pulpit	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
one	O
Velvet	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
Velvet	O
Cushion	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Plush	O
Cushion	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Plush	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Holland	O
Surplices	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Flagon-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
l.	O
one	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
another	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
Gilt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
one	O
Gilt	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
chief	O
was	O
Stephen	B-pers
Fawson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Crossfeild	I-pers
,	O
Church-wardens	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
lost	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Benneson	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Collet	O
had	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Vestry	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
both	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
did	O
not	O
Charge	O
Aldershaw	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
actually	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Collet	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Sacriledge	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bridger	I-pers
of	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
three	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bridger	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
of	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
four	O
Shifts	O
,	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
some	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
small	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
one	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
Williams	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Webb	O
as	O
Accessary	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
Pillows	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
committed	O
in	O
trust	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Williams	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
left	O
to	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
Webb	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Davis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mattocks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
singly	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Feilds	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Sable	O
Tippet	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
odd	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
with	O
great	O
Asseverations	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ranshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Glass	O
Bottel	O
gilded	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Circumstantial	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Prescilla	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
seven	O
Napkins	O
,	O
two	O
Towels	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Stayrs	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
Insignificant	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Willcox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
and	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Fawset	I-pers
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Velvet	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
some	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
particularly	O
a	O
Coat	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Fullers	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
D	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
one	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
possitively	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Marrow	B-pers
Pynes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
Lace	O
of	O
Partridge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Hart	I-place
in	O
Aldersgate-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
slipt	O
the	O
Lace	O
into	O
her	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodhall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
charged	O
2	O
Inches	O
deep	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
gainsay	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Killpatrick	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
two	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
alias	O
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Fustian	O
from	O
one	O
Parkinson	B-pers
and	O
one	O
Drinkhill	B-pers
;	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stuff	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Symon	B-pers
Fanshaw	I-pers
of	O
two	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Natural	O
Child	O
,	O
a	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Melancholy	O
Woman	O
Naturally	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
a	O
Cork	O
about	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
put	O
there	O
by	O
violence	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
was	O
doubtful	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
Melancholy	O
Woman	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
rub	O
Mony	O
round	O
the	O
edges	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Corroborating	O
Depositions	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
clear	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rosseter	I-pers
alias	O
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
Clipping	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
Scales	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
one	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Clip	O
one	O
Shilling	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Strutton	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
Gray	O
through	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
denyed	O
it	O
very	O
impudently	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
one	O
Peacock	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
not	O
fully	O
possitive	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwel	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Babbington	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
only	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stretch	I-pers
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Seymor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
changed	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
their	O
Lodging	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
of	O
2	O
Gold	O
Ear	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Enticed	O
the	O
Child	O
abroad	O
from	O
her	O
Fathers	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Eares	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Ear	O
Rings	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictiment	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
for	O
taking	O
an	O
Ear	O
Ring	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ear	O
of	O
one	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
likewise	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
aboutYears	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
denyed	O
it	O
very	O
stifly	O
at	O
their	O
Tryal	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Mansfeild	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
one	O
Willison	B-pers
s	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
which	O
she	O
denyed	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Rings	O
again	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rainsford	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
Robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Locket	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
getting	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
seized	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Window	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pybus	I-pers
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
five	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lashly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Interrupted	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
Walter	O
Strickland	O
Wounded	O
the	O
Constable	O
in	O
his	O
Thigh	O
and	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
a	O
further	O
Scuffle	O
arose	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
which	O
Lashly	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Blow	O
given	O
him	O
near	O
his	O
Left	O
Eye	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
within	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
by	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Fewd	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Chyrurgeon	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Scull	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Walter	O
Strickland	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Post-Master	O
gave	O
account	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
being	O
his	O
Friends	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
,	O
very	O
late	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
they	O
abused	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
pass	O
quietly	O
;	O
and	O
although	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
particularly	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
killed	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Judges	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
That	O
where-ever	O
any	O
Officer	O
(	O
as	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
immediate	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
those	O
Persons	O
were	O
by	O
the	O
Constitution	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
as	O
the	O
Jury	O
Returned	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
severe	O
Repremand	O
given	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Danbey	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Feilds	I-place
,	O
taking	O
away	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
Danbey	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Proof	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
Doyle	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Danbey	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Lanson	I-pers
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Lansons	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
the	O
Room	O
ready	O
Furnished	O
,	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
stole	O
the	O
Sheets	O
:	O
The	O
Matter	O
was	O
found	O
Special	O
,	O
till	O
further	O
Consideration	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
denyed	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lucy	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
who	I-pers
was	I-pers
before	I-pers
Tryed	I-pers
by	I-pers
the	I-pers
Name	I-pers
of	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	O
Mattock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
again	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Bancroft	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
being	O
doubtful	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
a	O
Special	O
Verdict	O
.	O
Millicent	B-pers
Hummerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Twyger	I-pers
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Meriddee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Scarves	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
Laces	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
met	O
upon	O
the	O
Stayrs	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
denyed	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Emme	B-pers
Bevis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Coyn	O
,	O
2	O
broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Coyn	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
Franklin	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Gold	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
in	O
her	O
and	O
no	O
Felony	O
;	O
because	O
not	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Henry	O
VIII	O
.	O
for	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Trumbal	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lashly	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
alias	O
Grange	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Gwin	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Thornycroft	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
six	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
eight	O
Gold	O
Seals	O
set	O
with	O
Cornelion	O
Heads	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Ruby	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
another	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
Emmerauld	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ship	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Beza	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Lock	O
being	O
pickt	O
;	O
and	O
Trumbal	O
confest	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
besides	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
the	O
rest	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
private	O
,	O
otherwise	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
blown	O
up	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Woman	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
being	O
Adderton	O
's	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Pick-Locks	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Tom	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
was	O
Lashly	O
,	O
because	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
Robert	O
Trumbal	O
and	O
Robert	O
Adderton	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Francis	B-pers
Jakeman	I-pers
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Hawter	I-pers
of	O
several	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Huybert	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Croule	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
out	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Play	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
his	O
Corporal	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shot	O
Croule	O
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
Bullet	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Notorious	O
High-way	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hosey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bristol	O
Carrier	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
2	O
Mares	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
Hosey	O
the	O
Carrier	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
more	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
Hounslow-heath	B-place
,	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Mares	O
and	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rigbey	I-pers
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
for	O
Publishing	O
two	O
Libels	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Intituled	O
,	O
The	O
Trimming	O
Court	O
Divine	O
:	O
The	O
second	O
about	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Russell	O
's	O
Ghost	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
Misdemeanour	O
he	O
was	O
Fined	O
one	O
hundred	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
7	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Woodhall	O
,	O
Marrow	O
Pynes	O
,	O
Mary	O
Hutchins	O
,	O
John	O
Huybert	O
,	O
Mary	O
Wade	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	O
Mansfeild	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Kill-patrick	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
William	O
Gray	O
,	O
John	O
Strutton	O
,	O
James	O
Barrow	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Jones	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
11	O
.	O
John	O
Gwin	O
,	O
John	O
Collet	O
,	O
Jane	O
Williams	O
,	O
John	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Martha	O
Walters	O
,	O
Mary	O
Streth	O
,	O
Katherine	O
Seymor	O
,	O
Mary	O
Danby	O
,	O
Robert	O
Trumball	O
,	O
Robert	O
Adderton	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Walters	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
5	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Knight	O
,	O
Millicent	O
Hummerson	O
,	O
Prescilla	O
Long	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Butler	O
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	O
Wright	O
.	O
Martha	O
Walters	O
pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Walter	O
Piggot	O
,	O
for	O
Pulling	O
in	O
Guild-Hall	O
as	O
a	O
Free-man	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Find	O
20	O
Nobles	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
for	O
Publishing	O
two	O
Libels	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Intituled	O
,	O
The	O
Trimming	O
Court	O
Divine	O
:	O
The	O
second	O
about	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Russell	O
's	O
Ghost	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
Misdemeanour	O
he	O
was	O
Fined	O
one	O
hundred	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Walter	O
Strickland	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
for	O
killing	O
Thomas	O
Lashly	O
,	O
all	O
prayed	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
their	O
Clergy	O
;	O
but	O
an	O
Appeal	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
Murther	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Spitting	O
Drops	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
take	O
safely	O
and	O
go	O
abroad	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
powerfully	O
discharge	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Stomach	O
of	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
frees	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Gout	O
,	O
Dropsie	O
,	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
all	O
Infection	O
Venerial	O
,	O
or	O
Mercurial	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Cures	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Pallat	O
,	O
Nose	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
ulcers	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
prevents	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
also	O
those	O
approved	O
Drops	O
for	O
Cure	O
of	O
Fistula	O
's	O
,	O
Piles	O
,	O
or	O
Hemorrhoides	O
,	O
several	O
having	O
been	O
cured	O
by	O
once	O
Applying	O
.	O
By	O
Doctor	O
Archer	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Book	O
called	O
Every	O
Man	O
his	O
own	O
Doctor	O
:	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
spoke	O
with	O
at	O
his	O
chamber	O
at	O
the	O
Sadlers	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Muse	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
from	O
Noon	O
till	O
5	O
.	O
Evening	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Knight's-Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
sells	O
not	O
his	O
Drops	O
,	O
but	O
administers	O
them	O
as	O
needful	O
.	O
He	O
freely	O
gives	O
his	O
Advice	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Is	O
Plow-Yard	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	O
Kirlens	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
to	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
until	O
his	O
death	O
:	O
Who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
(	O
hindering	O
no	O
Business	O
)	O
undertakes	O
to	O
Cure	O
any	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Swellings	O
in	O
the	O
Nese	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
parts	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
,	O
and	O
Venerial	O
Disease	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
until	O
the	O
Cure	O
be	O
finished	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
both	O
cured	O
many	O
hundreds	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
carries	O
the	O
evil	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
distroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
Box	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
a	O
better	O
purger	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
ever	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
clense	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
causes	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gouts	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Payns	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
;	O
with	O
another	O
Drink	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Quart	O
,	O
he	O
Cures	O
all	O
Fevers	O
and	O
hot	O
Distempers	O
without	O
Bleeding	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
few	O
Bodys	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
writes	O
or	O
comes	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
