TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Kings	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Tear	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jenny	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
John	B-pers
Grosvenor	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bathoe	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Pellington	I-pers
William	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
Gilbert	B-pers
Hawton	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
John	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
Ambrose	B-pers
Hemborrow	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Taylour	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Collwell	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Jerrot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Binlose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Longford	I-pers
Gent	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
evidenced	O
thus	O
Mr.	O
Longford	O
being	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
certain	O
Sum	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
namely	O
5	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
his	O
Master	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Father	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
wont	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
eldest	O
Clark	O
,	O
but	O
happening	O
to	O
imbezle	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
strait	O
how	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
his	O
said	O
Masters	O
for	O
the	O
encompassing	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
first	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Study	O
;	O
but	O
failing	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
murther	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
getting	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
feeling	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Penknife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
it	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Longford	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
deep	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Longford	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
his	O
Sword	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
prick	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
left-side	O
:	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Longford	O
crying	O
out	O
Theeves	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
surrendred	O
himself	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
falling	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Man	O
Binlose	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
ingeniously	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
fact	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
also	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
having	O
great	O
Remorse	O
of	O
Conscience	O
for	O
his	O
so	O
notorious	O
a	O
Crime	O
,	O
being	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
himself	O
said	O
)	O
under	O
strong	O
Temptations	O
by	O
the	O
Common	O
Enemy	O
of	O
Mankind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
stupendiously	O
presumptous	O
that	O
would	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
abuse	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
without	O
Remorse	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
grievously	O
ashamed	O
to	O
express	O
his	O
Confession	O
of	O
so	O
horrid	O
a	O
Crime	O
,	O
seeming	O
very	O
Pensive	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
both	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
F	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
30	O
Swords	O
with	O
Silver	O
Hilts	O
,	O
value	O
80	O
l.	O
and	O
14	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Richard	B-pers
Savadge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
in	O
Exchange-Alley	B-place
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
Swords	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
3	O
Guineas	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rose-Diamond	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
400	O
l.	O
from	O
Moses	B-pers
Mokatoa	I-pers
Jew	O
:	O
who	O
,	O
after	O
being	O
sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Nurse	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
having	O
lived	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
her	O
Mrs	O
and	O
her	O
having	O
some	O
small	O
falling	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missed	O
his	O
Diamond	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
but	O
Presumptous	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rate	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk-Pettycoat	O
quitted	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
twilight	O
10	O
s.	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alathea	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Garrat	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
two	O
Boxes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
broke	O
upon	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
L	O
-	O
,	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
:	O
who	O
said	O
That	O
Trant	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
an	O
Amendment	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
:	O
And	O
they	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
Trant	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jesson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
6000	O
.	O
Bricks	O
,	O
vlaue	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Peryll	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
lost	O
his	O
Bricks	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
but	O
to	O
10.	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
favourable	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Bickery	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21.	O
of	O
December	O
Bickery	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Closet	O
where	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
mist	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
stifly	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Court	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Malice	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
lived	O
honest	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
her	O
livelihood	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
from	O
one	O
Matthew	B-pers
Rymer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
Girle	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
confess	O
(	O
being	O
taxed	O
by	O
her	O
Master	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Mony	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
called	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
tall	O
lusty	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Evidence	O
that	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
Education	O
,	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Felony	O
being	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Rantzau	I-pers
a	O
Frenchman	O
and	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
F	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
Party	O
Jury	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Harder	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Switzer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
are	O
these	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Volley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
David	B-pers
Colliver	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Burrowes	I-pers
James	B-pers
Garryor	I-pers
Ambrose	B-pers
Hemborrow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shavaleer	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Grymmot	I-pers
.	O
After	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
those	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
,	O
from	O
Holland	O
in	O
the	O
Packet	O
Boat	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
Acquaintance	O
before	O
,	O
yet	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
wanting	O
Mony	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Harder	O
had	O
plenty	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
wait	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Assassinated	O
him	O
,	O
near	O
Chelsy	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
Inhumane	O
manner	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
Seven	O
Wounds	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
besides	O
Rifleing	O
of	O
him	O
of	O
about	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tabaco	O
Box	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Murtherers	O
,	O
F	O
-	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
without	O
being	O
taxed	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
great	O
suspition	O
,	O
but	O
Rantzau	O
was	O
taken	O
amongst	O
the	O
Dutch	O
Guards	O
at	O
Dartford	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
freely	O
confess	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
Oh	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
England	O
to	O
Murther	O
so	O
Innocent	O
a	O
Man	O
!	O
And	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
Bloody	O
;	O
F	O
-	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
cleaned	O
his	O
Sword	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Fight	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
near	O
Fleury	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
double	O
Story	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
Chelsey	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Swords	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Testimony	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
matter	O
appeared	O
very	O
Strenuous	O
and	O
Pregnant	O
before	O
,	O
even	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Rantzau	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
F	O
-	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
Out	O
landish	O
Men	O
that	O
assisted	O
him	O
:	O
F	O
-	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
at	O
Chelsey	O
.	O
The	O
Box	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Maker	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
by	O
Collonel	O
Willet	O
,	O
his	O
endeared	O
and	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
Rantzau	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
positive	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Circumstances	O
against	O
F	O
-	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Felix	B-pers
Don	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pattrick	I-pers
and	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
Bond	O
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	O
Falconer	O
for	O
Threescore	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lawful	O
English	O
Mony	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
one	O
John	O
Swayne	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
pretended	O
was	O
gone	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
Pattrick	O
acknowledged	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
Swayne	O
before	O
Sir	O
Miles	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
B	O
-	O
justified	O
his	O
name	O
to	O
be	O
Swayne	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
publish	O
and	O
produce	O
the	O
said	O
false	O
Bond	O
to	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Executor	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	O
Falkner	O
;	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Sum	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
doubting	O
of	O
a	O
Cheat	O
:	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
false	O
Bond	O
were	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Whately	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
into	O
the	O
business	O
by	O
the	O
urgent	O
Sollicitations	O
,	O
and	O
cunning	O
Devices	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
which	O
he	O
readily	O
confest	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Bond	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
ingenuously	O
Forged	O
Falknor	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
abundance	O
of	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
attended	O
the	O
Cheat	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
Papers	O
of	O
Pattricks	O
own	O
Hand	O
writing	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
true	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
B	O
-	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
Personate	O
one	O
Swayne	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Falconer	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
the	O
Bond	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
Swayne	O
lent	O
the	O
Mony	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Falconer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lewis	O
was	O
also	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Series	O
of	O
the	O
Trick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
filled	O
up	O
the	O
Bond	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
;	O
but	O
Lewis	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
firstly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
Peremptory	O
in	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
did	O
strive	O
to	O
Extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
but	O
Patrick	O
ingenously	O
confest	O
The	O
whole	O
Matter	O
:	O
So	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
and	O
distinct	O
hearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Forgery	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Harryes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
happened	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
were	O
Fighting	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
by	O
he	O
intermedied	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
Fight	O
fairer	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
surly	O
manner	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
Fight	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
Ears	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Hanger	O
and	O
made	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Rapier	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
happened	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saltmarsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
16	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
absented	O
herself	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Service	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
a	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
4	O
Guineas	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
alias	O
Vane	B-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Arreigned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
Forging	O
,	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Making	O
three	O
score	O
Pieces	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mixed	O
Metals	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
It	O
was	O
declared	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
heard	O
to	O
Clip	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Porter	O
,	O
since	O
fled	O
-and	O
there	O
were	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Room	O
.	O
Much	O
Evidence	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Porter	O
and	O
Michael	O
Wright	O
actually	O
Clip	O
several	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
Wright	O
was	O
an	O
Artist	O
at	O
Clipping	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
Yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
being	O
render	O
of	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Crucibles	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Work	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
heard	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
by	O
stamping	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
particularly	O
one	O
Sunday-Night	O
from	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
But	O
none	O
saw	O
them	O
actually	O
forge	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Gold-Watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
5	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
with	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
all	O
amounting	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Thieves	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Garret	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
wherein	O
was	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
at	O
Windsor	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Locket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
murthering	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
brought	O
forth	O
the	O
Child	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
conveyed	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
:	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Jawbone	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
scissers	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Mouth	O
2	O
Inches	O
deep	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
length	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Kneaves	I-pers
of	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Kneaves	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-Market	B-place
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
feeling	O
her	O
tampering	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
immediately	O
dropt	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
pleaded	O
Poverty	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Savidge	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Richey	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Jackeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
laced	O
Night	O
Royle	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Suit	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Silk-Gowns	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	O
Jakeman	O
aforesaid	O
and	O
one	O
Judith	B-pers
Hawton	I-pers
.	O
Jakeman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	O
Savadge	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
her	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Richey	O
came	O
to	O
invite	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Funeral	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
stories	O
when	O
first	O
asked	O
about	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
charge	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ives	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
4	O
China	O
Plates	O
and	O
4	O
China	O
Sawcers	O
,	O
and	O
Serge	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Ives	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
imbezled	O
and	O
conveyed	O
away	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chests	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
all	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
a	O
Pillowbeer	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
.	O
2	O
Deal-Boards	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Goodlopp	I-pers
some	O
of	O
the	O
Wheat	O
and	O
one	O
Board	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Cook	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Wheat	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Boards	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Wheat	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Ancient	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
being	O
Married	O
to	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
at	O
Westchester	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
our	O
Late	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
was	O
Marryed	O
to	O
one	O
Christian	B-pers
Artichel	I-pers
at	O
Dukes	B-place
Place	I-place
,	O
the	O
former	O
Wife	O
Jones	O
,	O
being	O
alive	O
,	O
which	O
Woman	O
came	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
Married	O
to	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Marriage	O
was	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
be	O
proved	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
short	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
he	O
deny	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
do	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Charles	B-pers
Pledwell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Gold	O
sealed	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hatband	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
former	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
or	O
old	O
Grudge	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Pledwell	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Pearse	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
claimed	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
)	O
about	O
Pledwells	O
Marrying	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
lived	O
formerly	O
with	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Pearse	O
assalted	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Pleadwell	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
sitting	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
pulled	O
her	O
Ear	O
Rings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Ears	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
a	O
Byonet	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
hand	O
off	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
any	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
Pleadwell	O
had	O
Robed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Trymmer	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
he	O
asserted	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hatband	O
sell	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
matter	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Trespass	O
than	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
since	O
Executed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
thus	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
met	O
one	O
Bowcher	B-pers
in	O
Honslow-Hearth	B-place
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Mare	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
price	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
;	O
which	O
Mare	O
(	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Gazette	O
)	O
was	O
found	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Stable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
at	O
an	O
Execution	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
constantly	O
affirming	O
their	O
former	O
Depositions	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Giles	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Pick-pocket	O
Boys	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
off	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Brumleystreet	B-place
,	O
near	O
Short	I-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
Carter	O
,	O
besides	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denyed	O
it	O
stifly	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
Carter	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
Webb	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charnell	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
off	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
Two	O
Salvers	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Poringer	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
discovered	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Setter	O
for	O
High	O
way-men	O
and	O
Robbers	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Brooks	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
watcht	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
whilest	O
another	O
Man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
away	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Mony	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Rings	O
;	O
which	O
Plate	O
they	O
sold	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
after	O
shared	O
the	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
a	O
fair	O
Story	O
,	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
his	O
innocency	O
,	O
complaining	O
of	O
Malice	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
only	O
stood	O
as	O
a	O
Spy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
hearing	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Hannah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Meeres	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
Collar	O
Bone	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Chizel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languishing	O
lived	O
till	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
:	O
Hannah	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
as	O
Principle	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
strook	O
the	O
Deceased	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Maryone	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
several	O
Silks	O
and	O
Damask	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broaken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
End	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
good	O
Evidence	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Innocent	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitcher	I-pers
alias	O
Healing	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
twenty	O
Pieces	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tynn	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Metals	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
Forge	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Smith	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
following	O
his	O
Calling	O
had	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
accomplish	O
his	O
Projects	O
in	O
this	O
Nature	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
Clip	O
'd	O
seen	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
not	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Validity	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
robing	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Charles	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Westmorland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
Pound	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Westmorland	O
,	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plates	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Bake-house	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
Baker	O
)	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
forgot	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
and	O
melted	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
Fryday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
and	O
Edmund	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Arrained	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
was	O
Tryed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
The	O
Indictments	O
against	O
them	O
consisted	O
of	O
Two	O
Parts	O
,	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Treasonable	O
Design	O
carrying	O
on	O
to	O
Depose	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Subvert	O
and	O
Alter	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
raise	O
War	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
which	O
said	O
Traiterous	O
and	O
Wicked	O
Designs	O
and	O
Purposes	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
pass	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Meet	O
and	O
Conspire	O
together	O
,	O
withseveral	O
other	O
Traitors	O
not	O
yet	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
Compose	O
several	O
Treasonable	O
Letters	O
,	O
Notes	O
and	O
Memorandums	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
the	O
most	O
effectual	O
way	O
and	O
means	O
how	O
they	O
might	O
Dethrone	O
and	O
Depose	O
our	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
describing	O
therein	O
how	O
the	O
Affairs	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
what	O
Strength	O
and	O
Force	O
our	O
Shipping	O
was	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Fortifications	O
of	O
several	O
Sea-Port-Towns	O
within	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Part	O
was	O
their	O
adhering	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
's	O
Enemies	O
:	O
And	O
to	O
that	O
end	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
Acquaint	O
Lewis	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
hire	O
a	O
Boat	O
and	O
Embarque	O
themselves	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Transport	O
themselves	O
and	O
Pacquet	O
of	O
Treasonable	O
Letters	O
into	O
France	O
,	O
agreeing	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
their	O
said	O
Passages	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
One	O
hundred	O
Pound	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
their	O
Treasonable	O
Voyage	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
their	O
Passage	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
below	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
then	O
Taken	O
by	O
Captain	O
Billop	O
,	O
who	O
Cruised	O
abroad	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
particularly	O
from	O
Step	O
to	O
Step	O
,	O
how	O
cunningly	O
and	O
subtilly	O
they	O
managed	O
this	O
horrid	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
by	O
hiring	O
the	O
Smack	O
called	O
the	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
to	O
convey	O
them	O
secretly	O
into	O
France	O
;	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
Water	O
in	O
a	O
Skuller	O
at	O
Surrey-Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Vessel	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Tower	O
:	O
From	O
thence	O
they	O
set	O
Sail	O
down	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
till	O
coming	O
within	O
the	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
Frigate	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
Long-reach	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Smack	O
to	O
hide	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Quarter-Hatches	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
some	O
Fear	O
of	O
being	O
discovered	O
:	O
There	O
they	O
remained	O
till	O
past	O
that	O
Danger	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
within	O
Sight	O
of	O
Gravesend	O
they	O
hid	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
it	O
Captain	O
Billop	O
came	O
aboard	O
them	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
Pressing	O
the	O
Masters	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
assistants	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
indeed	O
his	O
Design	O
and	O
real	O
Intention	O
was	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
those	O
Traytors	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
lying	O
along	O
under	O
the	O
Hatches	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
their	O
being	O
haled	O
up	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pacquet	O
of	O
Treasonable	O
Papers	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
's	O
Bosom	O
:	O
which	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Nottingham	O
;	O
who	O
examined	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
being	O
examined	O
by	O
the	O
Cabinet	O
Council	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
and	O
purport	O
:	O
The	O
Letters	O
being	O
also	O
Read	O
against	O
them	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
were	O
adjudged	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
less	O
Import	O
than	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
hearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
Edmond	O
Elliot	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
further	O
order	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
thus	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3	O
.	O
William	O
Harris	O
Charles	O
Hodson	O
Richard	O
Kelly	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
14	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Graham	O
and	O
John	O
Ashton	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Drawn	O
,	O
Hanged	O
and	O
Quartered	O
,	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
John	O
Benlose	O
H	O
-	O
F	O
-	O
Anne	O
Stephens	O
Jane	O
Carr	O
Joseph	O
Trant	O
Francis	O
Leitchfeild	O
,	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Read	O
Lewis	O
Rantzau	O
Margaret	O
Roberts	O
Samuel	O
Porter	O
Christopher	O
Pearse	O
and	O
,	O
Nicholas	O
Carter	O
.	O
Robert	O
Cook	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
and	O
2	O
Deal-Boards	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipped	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holbourn-Bars	O
.	O
Felix	O
Don	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Pattrick	O
and	O
S	O
-	O
who	O
were	O
convicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
their	O
Ears	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
continue	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
twelve	O
Months	O
after	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Intent	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
England	O
's	O
Alarm	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
French-King	O
's	O
Cruelties	O
Exposed	O
.	O
Containg	O
a	O
True	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
Usage	O
these	O
Three	O
Nations	O
may	O
expect	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
unhappy	O
as	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
Prey	O
to	O
that	O
most	O
Cruel	O
and	O
Bloody	O
Tyrant	O
.	O
Humbly	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
serious	O
Consideration	O
of	O
all	O
such	O
Protestants	O
as	O
endeavour	O
to	O
promote	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
Enslave	O
these	O
Protestant	O
Kingdoms	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
L.	O
C.	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
If	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
or	O
Gentlewoman	O
have	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
to	O
speak	O
Latin	O
or	O
French	O
Truly	O
and	O
Properly	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Explain	O
any	O
Author	O
according	O
to	O
Grammer	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
but	O
spare	O
two	O
hours	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
Charles	O
Switerda	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Prosesteth	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
and	O
easie	O
Method	O
to	O
teach	O
them	O
the	O
said	O
Language	O
in	O
one	O
Tear	O
.	O
Those	O
who	O
have	O
learned	O
formerly	O
may	O
recover	O
it	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
,	O
He	O
Teachesh	O
alsouther	O
Languages	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
desires	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Grammer	O
in	O
2	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Grammatical	O
and	O
Historical	O
Cards	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
where	O
he	O
Teacheth	O
in	O
Clements	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Canon	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Feather	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Grayes-Inn	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Whereas	O
a	O
Mistake	O
was	O
commited	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Printed	O
Papers	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
Johnson	O
,	O
last	O
Dying	O
Speech	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
mean	O
the	O
Apocherary	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
did	O
cause	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
therefore	O
infested	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Order	O
,	O
it	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
(	O
who	O
printed	O
he	O
said	O
speech	O
)	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
said	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
former	O
Landlord	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
E	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
know	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Hall	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
seever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargrism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
indent	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
causeth	O
a	O
sticking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
He	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
serves	O
.	O
