TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
the	O
31th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
2d	O
days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
31th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
and	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1692	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sarjeant	O
Lovewell	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Sherly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ruddyer	I-pers
,	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milbourn	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	O
E	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Postb	I-pers
Archibald	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Applebury	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Keates	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
Giles	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chiser	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hopper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
John	B-pers
Milgate	I-pers
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
from	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Tower-Ward	B-place
,	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
that	O
two	O
Genteel	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
pewter	O
Pot	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
idle	O
Fellows	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Parnel	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
staid	O
a	O
small	O
time	O
there	O
he	O
Run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Cloth	O
being	O
Unloading	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dixy	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
s	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
cart	O
with	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Dixy	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
watches	O
their	O
demeanor	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
catches	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Bryant	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
Stealing	O
Twenty	O
two	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
Three	O
Razors	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Turner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
make	O
visits	O
often	O
times	O
to	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sold	O
a	O
Lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hair	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
one	O
Eldridge	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Turners	O
leave	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pledwell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Nich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
one	O
Shell-box	O
,	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
one	O
little	O
Bag	O
with	O
40l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entertained	O
as	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
and	O
when	O
Opportunity	O
served	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
silver	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Newgate	O
committed	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
:	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
the	O
said	O
Osborne	O
Bond	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Gold	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
besides	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
proved	O
the	O
Fact	O
plainly	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Pynes	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
high-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Shallcross	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
Mr	O
Shallcross	O
being	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
High-way	O
about	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Kings	O
gates	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Grays-Inn-lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Persons	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
holding	O
Pistols	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
gag	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
'd	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
24s	O
.	O
one	O
Walking	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
inced	O
Metal	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
11s	O
.	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
30s	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Shallcross	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
positively	O
to	O
be	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
knowledge	O
he	O
had	O
was	O
from	O
Johnson	O
,	O
alias	O
Gee	O
,	O
Condemned	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
Law	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
Guilty	O
James	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
against	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Cart	O
near	O
the	O
Conduit	O
in	O
Tyburn	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
appeared	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
meeting	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
about	O
giving	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
force	O
the	O
Pole	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
which	O
thrust	O
him	O
down	O
before	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
which	O
run	O
over	O
him	O
and	O
brusied	O
him	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
Died	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Boys	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
,	O
driving	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
so	O
stumbling	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
off	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
Cart-Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
no	O
ways	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
August	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
Steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
Broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
was	O
shut	O
before	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Chisel	O
and	O
other	O
Implements	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Shoes	O
were	O
put	O
off	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Taken	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
not	O
Appearing	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ironmonger	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ear	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
2l	O
.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
150	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
That	O
on	O
Whit-Sunday	O
whilest	O
Mr.	O
Reynold	O
's	O
Servant	O
was	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
Broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
were	O
said	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
that	O
could	O
charge	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
only	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Repute	O
before	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Old	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
Davis	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
Fled	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
was	O
Taken	O
for	O
another	O
fact	O
in	O
South	O
Wark	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
walking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Ironmonger-Lane	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Indicted	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Law	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Perfidious	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
;	O
yet	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Deaves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	B-place
Ward	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
20s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
a	O
Drinking	O
,	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Deaves	O
Swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
for	O
two	O
Pieces	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pledwell	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hare	O
's	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mrs.	O
Hare	O
was	O
drawing	O
some	O
Drink	O
for	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
slipt	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
called	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
very	O
fine	O
Apparel	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hare	O
's	O
much	O
like	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Cheat	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Husbands	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Named	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
she	O
Married	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
Dukes	O
Place	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
several	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
person	O
she	O
Marryed	O
was	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
she	O
Married	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
lady	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Married	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
her	O
Name	O
of	O
Adams	O
and	O
Carter	O
,	O
into	O
that	O
of	O
Elliot	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Estate	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
Look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cheat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
direct	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
the	O
Proof	O
was	O
very	O
strenuous	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
besides	O
both	O
the	O
Husbands	O
were	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
F	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
priviliy	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Patey	I-pers
the	O
sum	O
of	O
40s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
Mist	O
.	O
Patey	O
's	O
stall	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall	B-place
Market	I-place
to	O
Cheapen	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Lamb	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
immediately	O
missing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
stopped	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
Evil	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Rolphe	I-pers
alias	O
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Baggs	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
and	O
163	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
Wiliam	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Flemming	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
one	O
silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Newmans	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Rob	B-pers
Crigg	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
of	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gray	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
Gaws	O
Hood	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
Examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Basdell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
Swore	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Filings	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clippings	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Tiles	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martyn	O
,	O
and	O
Susannah	O
hid	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
her	O
Mouth	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Clipping	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
forc	O
'd	O
she	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Files	O
and	O
Rubbing	O
Leathers	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
besides	O
they	O
denied	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
desired	O
Entrance	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Clipping	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Basdell	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
equally	O
concerned	O
for	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Melting	O
pot	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
by	O
Susanna	O
full	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
found	O
here	O
towards	O
Westminster	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
better	O
Colour	O
upon	O
the	O
Roguery	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
Guinea	O
's	O
changed	O
for	O
Broad-Money	O
,	O
adding	O
withal	O
that	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Relation	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
that	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
legacies	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
out	O
in	O
Goodmans	O
Fields	O
in	O
one	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Coventry	O
Fields	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
Sheers	O
was	O
heard	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
;	O
Thomas	O
Martyn	O
denied	O
all	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
John	O
Basdell	O
,	O
urging	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lame	O
Man	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
able	O
to	O
Execute	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
denied	O
all	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
extenuate	O
her	O
Crime	O
,	O
urging	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Publick-house	O
before	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
it	O
and	O
for	O
ought	O
she	O
knew	O
,	O
the	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
left	O
there	O
100	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
several	O
Persons	O
had	O
been	O
Hang	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
to	O
her	O
Advantage	O
nor	O
nothing	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
offer	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
Tryal	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Susanna	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
not	O
Taken	O
,	O
Did	O
Falsly	O
,	O
Feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
Traitorously	O
Counterfeit	O
60	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mint	O
Metals	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
Gravel	B-place
Lane	I-place
in	O
Ratcliff	I-place
high-way	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
Thumping	O
was	O
heard	O
,	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
beating	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Stamps	O
found	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
besides	O
some	O
Clippings	O
that	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Half-Crowns	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
was	O
so	O
plain	O
and	O
pregnant	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rathea	B-pers
Desborrow	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Dimishing	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
Together	O
with	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
For	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
did	O
Combine	O
to	O
deceive	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
people	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
in	O
Clipping	O
40	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
200	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
Shears	O
,	O
Melting	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Conveniences	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Persons	O
besides	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
Mrs	O
Palmer	O
being	O
fled	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
fixed	O
upon	O
four	O
little	O
Tables	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
Wood	O
under	O
them	O
,	O
formally	O
fixed	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
Warner	O
's	O
Fingers	O
were	O
all	O
black	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
several	O
other	O
Aggravating	O
circumstances	O
were	O
offered	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
all	O
denied	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
what	O
hath	O
been	O
sworn	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
favourable	O
Accounts	O
of	O
their	O
past	O
Lives	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
positively	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
actors	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Crime	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Palmer	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Actoress	O
;	O
Moreover	O
,	O
Desborrow	O
and	O
Warner	O
had	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
Industrious	O
to	O
Live	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
a	O
Mantua-Maker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
a	O
Nurse-Keeper	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
satisfied	O
the	O
Court	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
V	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
likewise	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
James	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petty-Coat	O
from	O
one	O
Dobbs	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Likewise	O
Joanna	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
parcels	O
of	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Broad-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Coining	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
several	O
half-Crowns	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
for	O
broad	O
Money	O
in	O
exchange	O
of	O
Clipt	O
;	O
The	O
false	O
Money	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
coin	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
Malice	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
from	O
Cha	B-pers
.	I-pers
Allinson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
Pistols	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Brokers	O
to	O
borrow	O
Money	O
upon	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welcher	I-pers
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
him	O
no	O
good	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
when	O
first	O
Taken	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
calico	O
Frocks	O
,	O
Taffety	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
some	O
Gloves	O
and	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Ralph	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
twelve	O
Plates	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Night	O
finding	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
)	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
in	O
Newgate	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Warrington	I-pers
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Don	O
Diego	B-pers
Capillar	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
as	O
is	O
before	O
a	O
specified	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Thomas	O
Noon	O
's	O
Tryal	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
from	O
John	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
Positively	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
stood	O
there	O
selling	O
Cattle	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Confest	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Deane	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Othorn	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Drink	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Collin	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
between	O
them	O
slipt	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
particular	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Halstead	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
Broke	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
One	O
Bed	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
two	O
Blankets	O
and	O
one	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
a	O
Sute	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
Taken	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
Aug.	O
carrying	O
away	O
72	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
12s	O
.	O
Twelve	O
Yards	O
more	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
Eleven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
27s	O
.	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
besides	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
Broke	O
open	O
about	O
twelve	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
Stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
Taken	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phenix	B-pers
Wannerton	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
44s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
four	O
Pillow-bears	O
2s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chare-woman	O
,	O
to	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
abroad	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
days	O
Work	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
For	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
Susan	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Knight	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Steal	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
)	O
Twelve	O
dozen	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
Four	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
others	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
these	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
God	O
Dam	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
Clip	O
off	O
his	O
Ears	O
for	O
a	O
Groat	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Skinner	O
Swore	O
it	O
flat	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Varience	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Grudge	O
was	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
Skinner	O
was	O
Jealous	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Delamot	I-pers
alias	O
Delabowre	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Leepman	I-pers
,	O
not	O
Taken	O
,	O
did	O
Deceive	O
and	O
Defraud	O
one	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
of	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
four	O
Gold-Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
one	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Crociate	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
Lend	O
them	O
60	O
l.	O
upon	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Diamomds	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
right	O
in	O
their	O
kind	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
putting	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Fast-day	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
another	O
Box	O
wherein	O
were	O
Two	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
stuft	O
with	O
Paper	O
.	O
And	O
before	O
he	O
paid	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Box	O
Sealed	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
Trick	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
one	O
Box	O
of	O
Rings	O
,	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearls	O
,	O
and	O
Crociate	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Committed	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ruffians	O
that	O
committed	O
that	O
Horrid	O
,	O
Barbarous	O
and	O
most	O
Hellish	O
Murder	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
Famous	O
Doctor	O
Andrew	B-pers
Clench	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
was	O
Executed	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Miller	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
Miller	O
lately	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
who	O
Declared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
Miller	O
told	O
her	O
upon	O
his	O
Death	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
Departed	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
himself	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
and	O
Murthered	O
him	O
by	O
Strangling	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
tyed	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
hard	O
Sea-Cole	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
placed	O
upon	O
his	O
Wind-pipe	O
,	O
as	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
when	O
the	O
Doctor	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-Street	B-place
;	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
attest	O
in	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
any	O
Jury	O
whatsoever	O
find	O
any	O
Person	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
such	O
a	O
slender	O
Testimony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
a	O
Dying	O
Man	O
's	O
words	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Witnesses	O
Sworn	O
and	O
Examined	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Miller	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Boar	O
's	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
on	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Harper	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
Acquaintance	O
he	O
had	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Miller	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
departed	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
almost	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
withal	O
the	O
Witness	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Miller	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
almost	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Heat	O
,	O
and	O
lookt	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
some	O
Extraordinary	O
Business	O
that	O
might	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Fermentation	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
two	O
Persons	O
in	O
Red	O
Coats	O
like	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
Harrison	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
said	O
Miller	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
look	O
into	O
all	O
Gazettes	O
and	O
News	O
Papers	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
not	O
inquired	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
concluded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Miller	O
was	O
certainly	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Assassinates	O
and	O
Harrison	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
not	O
withstanding	O
his	O
indiscreet	O
denial	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
not	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Murderers	O
would	O
surely	O
be	O
detected	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
after	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinions	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
returned	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
was	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
28s	O
.	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moseley	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Shift	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
although	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Kath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Worden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
Aug.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldergate	I-place
,	O
of	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Monks	I-pers
House	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
one	O
Scarf	O
5s	O
.	O
Seven	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
l.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
Monk	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
and	O
Bound	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
he	O
cut	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pynes	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Shop	O
lifting	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Beres	I-pers
Shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
of	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Kalamanca	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
using	O
their	O
Art	O
of	O
Legerdemane	O
,	O
they	O
slipt	O
away	O
the	O
stuff	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
persued	O
and	O
stopt	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Holmes	O
confest	O
it	O
when	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
justifie	O
their	O
Credit	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
two	O
Petty	O
coats	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leaver	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
catcht	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pick-lock	O
Key	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Balconey	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
in	O
their	O
Enterprize	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
off	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Intent	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Richard	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
2s	O
.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
and	O
57	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Leaver	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
alone	O
a	O
Considerable	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
presently	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Leaver	O
missed	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
besides	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
since	O
he	O
hath	O
been	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
offered	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
Unlock	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
were	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Closet	O
that	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Turner	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
preceeding	O
Tryal	O
is	O
made	O
appear	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peirce	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Gowen	B-pers
Burket	I-pers
,	O
one	O
padlock	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burket	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
Broke	O
open	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
Four	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
seen	O
(	O
by	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
who	O
followed	O
them	O
)	O
go	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Burket	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
a	O
Betty	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Matches	O
and	O
a	O
Tinder	O
box	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
Surprised	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
were	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
accidentally	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
alias	O
Wharton	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Robbery	O
,	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Don	O
Diego	B-pers
Capyllar	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
Gold	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
One	O
Box	O
inlaid	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Standish	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
two	O
Snuff	O
boxes	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
one	O
little	O
Box	O
Chafed	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Diamond	O
,	O
value	O
25l	O
.	O
one	O
other	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Table	O
Diamond	O
,	O
value	O
30l	O
.	O
one	O
other	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
one	O
other	O
Gold	O
Chain-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
17s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
one	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
with	O
a	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
four	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
silver	O
Shirt-boxes	O
inlaid	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
four	O
Latin	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
one	O
Indian	O
stone	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
two	O
small	O
Indian	O
Pen-boxes	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
twelve	O
pieces	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
with	O
several	O
Dressing-boxes	O
,	O
Laced	O
Ruffles	O
and	O
other	O
good	O
Linnen	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
57l	O
.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
Numbered	O
,	O
all	O
Spanish	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
My	O
Lord	O
Head	O
;	O
keeps	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
where	O
Noon	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
used	O
to	O
Resort	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Dressing	O
boxes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Noon	O
was	O
seen	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
owned	O
before	O
to	O
have	O
lodged	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
Head	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doctor	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
although	O
not	O
yet	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
has	O
ordered	O
an	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
up	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Will	O
.	O
Warrington	O
as	O
his	O
right	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
as	O
a	O
Nick-name	O
:	O
Noon	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Delabasset	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
one	O
rateen	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
way	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Double	O
Refin	O
'd	O
Sugar	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
three	O
Pound	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
eight	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Sugar	O
Candy	O
,	O
value	O
5d	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Jo	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Mr	O
Bagnall	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Lodging	O
being	O
Search	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Sugars	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Foreman	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goldsmiths	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
mist	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
shop	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
buying	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
disown	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
present	O
time	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
Essayer	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Goldsmiths	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
buying	O
some	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
by	O
Mistake	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
being	O
Accessaries	O
with	O
one	O
Judith	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
who	O
before	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
three	O
Linnen	O
Bags	O
with	O
103	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
that	O
Judith	O
Rolph	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Flemming	O
when	O
she	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
sharers	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
positively	O
Sworn	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blundervill	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
seven	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
thus	O
committed	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
together	O
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Quarreling	O
,	O
calling	O
each	O
other	O
Rogues	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Fighting	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
Farmer	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
wounded	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
Friends	O
and	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
sudden	O
heat	O
of	O
passion	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hanwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Whitby	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
at	O
Brandford	I-place
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
about	O
their	O
Pedegrees	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
height	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
first	O
to	O
Boxing	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
drew	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Blagrave	O
gave	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wait	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
former	O
Malice	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Beating	O
,	O
Kicking	O
,	O
and	O
Bruising	O
one	O
Will	B-pers
Vernish	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Belly	O
and	O
Stomach	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
upon	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Bruises	O
and	O
beating	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Bruises	O
appear	O
'd	O
outwardly	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
Discolouration	O
of	O
the	O
Flesh	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
upon	O
Safforn-Hill	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
found	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
happily	O
parted	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
who	O
lived	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
Francis	O
uppermost	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
three	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
weakly	O
infirm	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
complain	O
particularly	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
were	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Coifs	O
,	O
value	O
2s.	O
,	O
an	O
A-La-Mode	O
Hood	O
,	O
one	O
scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
Aug.	O
from	O
Fran	B-pers
.	I-pers
Frobisher	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hood	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phenix	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Petty	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
one	O
A-La-Mode	O
Hood	O
,	O
one	O
Tammy	O
Petty	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
with	O
5s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Petty-coat	O
and	O
a	O
Scarf	O
and	O
two	O
Hoods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
wicked	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
leant	O
her	O
the	O
Cloths	O
to	O
wear	O
in	O
her	O
Service	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
of	O
19	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Barret	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
three	O
Boards	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Boards	O
of	O
Barret	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
G	B-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Flint	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Puddle-Dock	B-place
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
'll	O
make	O
me	O
spill	O
the	O
Drink	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Page	O
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Material	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Tryal	O
was	O
respited	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
Plead	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
allowed	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
presented	O
Gloves	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
being	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
his	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
Gloves	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
for	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
France	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
was	O
Discharged	O
by	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Doatey	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Clipper	O
;	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
WHEREAS	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
in	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
several	O
Orders	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
upon	O
several	O
Court-days	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
Victualler	O
,	O
or	O
Ale-House-keeper	O
,	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
or	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
shall	O
Sell	O
Drink	O
in	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
Obeyed	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
several	O
Persons	O
found	O
Guilty	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
strictly	O
Ordered	O
and	O
Commanded	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
Person	O
keeping	O
any	O
Publick	O
House	O
will	O
sell	O
Drink	O
in	O
any	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
or	O
Tankards	O
,	O
upon	O
Peril	O
of	O
their	O
Licenses	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	O
Ferguson	O
,	O
Philip	O
William	O
,	O
Mich.	O
Hall	O
,	O
John	O
Noble	O
,	O
James	O
Browne	O
,	O
Judith	O
Rolph	O
,	O
Mary	O
Stoakes	O
,	O
alias	O
Adams	O
,	O
Anne	O
White	O
,	O
Kath	O
Worden	O
,	O
Martha	O
Knight	O
,	O
mary	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Anne	O
Halsted	O
,	O
Anne	O
Herring	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
John	O
Lewis	O
,	O
John	O
Turner	O
,	O
Rich	O
Blundervill	O
,	O
Henry	O
Blagrave	O
,	O
Joanna	O
Harris	O
,	O
V	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Anne	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Phenix	O
Wannerton	O
,	O
Kath	O
.	O
Morris	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Ray	O
,	O
Mary	O
Clark	O
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Thomas	O
Noon	O
,	O
Francis	O
Turner	O
,	O
F	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Abraham	O
Turner	O
,	O
William	O
Carter	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
Thomas	O
Martin	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Martin	O
,	O
John	O
Basdell	O
,	O
John	O
Harris	O
,	O
Jonathan	O
Sheldon	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Drury	O
,	O
George	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Smith	O
,	O
alias	O
Pledwell	O
,	O
was	O
Respited	O
after	O
Judgment	O
;	O
and	O
William	O
Warrington	O
,	O
was	O
Respited	O
before	O
Judgement	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
4	O
Jane	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Pynes	O
,	O
Mary	O
Holmes	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
Steward	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Martin	O
pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
John	O
Delamot	O
alias	O
Delabowre	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
Four	O
Nobles	O
as	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
Committed	O
till	O
it	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
A	O
Mourning	O
Ring	O
in	O
Memory	O
of	O
your	O
Departed	O
friend	O
:	O
Containing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Weeping	O
.	O
The	O
Sick	O
Man	O
's	O
Passing	O
Bell	O
.	O
The	O
Pilgrim	O
's	O
Guide	O
.	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
died	O
suddenly	O
.	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Bills	O
of	O
Mortality	O
.	O
The	O
Author	O
's	O
Meditations	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
Sickness	O
and	O
Death	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Walk	O
among	O
the	O
Tombs	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Funeral	O
Monuments	O
;	O
Of	O
the	O
several	O
Customs	O
of	O
Burial	O
from	O
Adam	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
:	O
Of	O
Epitaphs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Funeral	O
Honours	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
recoomended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
Funerals	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Dunton	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
,	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Sovereign	O
Head-Pill	O
,	O
which	O
infallibly	O
Cures	O
all	O
pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
whether	O
old	O
or	O
newly	O
Contracted	O
;	O
speedily	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
Swimmings	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
,	O
preventing	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
of	O
Apoplectical	O
Fits	O
,	O
preserves	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Accidents	O
offending	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Strengthens	O
the	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
disburdens	O
the	O
Brain	O
of	O
all	O
offensive	O
Humours	O
,	O
thereby	O
rendring	O
the	O
Understanding	O
more	O
clear	O
and	O
Vigorous	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
an	O
expeditious	O
way	O
in	O
Curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
