TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
and	O
15th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
and	O
15th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1692.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sarjeant	O
Lovewell	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dighton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Florent	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stanchiffe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Essington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Turvill	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Reynoldson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Symcock	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hynder	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bromfeild	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
EDward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
Gagg	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
they	O
saluted	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
's	O
Man	O
with	O
several	O
Blows	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
abused	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
all	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
,	O
being	O
dark	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askue	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
26	O
Ells	O
of	O
A-la-mode	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
to	O
cheapon	O
some	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
sleight	O
of	O
Hand	O
she	O
pincht	O
away	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Mony	O
about	O
her	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
any	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
Suspicious	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Welted	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Welted	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Bothaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Lutestring	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Shop-Lifter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
the	O
Silk	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
only	O
she	O
declared	O
freely	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Ill	O
Woman	O
in	O
times	O
past	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
she	O
was	O
become	O
a	O
new	O
Convert	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
that	O
owned	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
only	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
:	O
So	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Stiddiard	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Knowles	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Rob	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
besides	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
before	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	O
Turner	O
to	O
have	O
shewed	O
Knowles	O
the	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Tanner	O
's	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Elis	B-pers
.	I-pers
Toogood	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coral	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
last	O
Sessions	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
plain	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Car-man	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Cramp	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
Cart	O
against	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Thigh	O
-of	O
which	O
she	O
dyed	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
unloading	O
some	O
Coals	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
the	O
Hamlet	O
Drums	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
Beating	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
affrighted	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
trampled	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
her	O
Thigh	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Cured	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
deposed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Hurt	O
did	O
any	O
ways	O
contribute	O
towards	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
Child	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Florett	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
South	I-place
Mimms	I-place
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
for	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
Florett	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
fear	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
48	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
but	O
Florett	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
two	O
Men	O
met	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Barnet	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Riding	O
home	O
from	O
London	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mony	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Kath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Arnett	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Lowder	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Pillows	O
,	O
two	O
Pillow-beers	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Dow-lace	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
one	O
Steward	B-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaval	I-pers
a	O
French	O
man	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pound	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
weight	O
of	O
Sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Heynes	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
Galloon	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
yet	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Charge	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
May	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
(	O
Wife	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
May	I-pers
)	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Whitrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
away	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Carpet	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
but	O
little	O
worth	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Petty	O
Lacenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Royley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Serge	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Head-dressing	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
Confest	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Nourse	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Page	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
together	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
side	O
of	O
Southampton	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Page	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
conveyed	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
Died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
Write	O
down	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Nourse	O
before	O
he	O
departed	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
she	O
said	O
Page	O
was	O
Kill	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rain	O
bow	O
Coffee	O
house	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
hot	O
Words	O
together	O
about	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
70	O
l.	O
odd	O
Mony	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Nourse	O
owed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
and	O
there	O
Fought	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
perswade	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
was	O
Wounded	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
be	O
Drest	O
at	O
another	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
said	O
Page	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
ill	O
of	O
his	O
Wound	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Ridley	O
's	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
precedent	O
Malice	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
a	O
sudden	O
heat	O
of	O
Passion	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
well	O
weighed	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fawkner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
,	O
one	O
Common	O
Prayer-Book	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
Whipcord	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Dunghil	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
thing	O
off	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
that	O
place	O
for	O
shelter	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pistol	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
,	O
and	O
Leather-bag	O
with	O
Bullets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
bundle	O
of	O
Whipcord	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
Suspicions	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
say	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rantzey	I-pers
,	O
Partners	O
in	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Linen	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
70	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
made	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
came	O
about	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
the	O
Brewer	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Stoak-hole	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Counting-House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
feared	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
make	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
flowered	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Tabbey	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
another	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
immediately	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gurley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Fettyplaces	O
in	O
Wine-Office	B-place
Court	I-place
in	O
Fleet	I-place
street	I-place
(	O
where	O
upon	O
Search	O
)	O
was	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
and	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
;	O
the	O
strength	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
mostly	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
seen	O
oftentimes	O
very	O
private	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cloth	O
hang	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
to	O
conceal	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Have	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
abroad	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Danby	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Awde	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entertainedby	O
Mrs.	O
Awde	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
mist	O
her	O
Gown	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
after	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
in	O
Sohoe	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	O
Turner	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
Yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Tankard	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
Try	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictm	O
.	O
one	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tankard	O
went	O
into	O
King-street	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Talked	O
privately	O
together	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tankard	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
long	O
Field	O
behind	O
Southampton	B-place
House	I-place
they	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
Fight	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
Died	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tankard	O
made	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tankard	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
his	O
Son	O
or	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
Dead	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
concuring	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
relation	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
lying	O
under	O
him	O
not	O
Drawn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
:	O
The	O
Swords	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tankard	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Unlawful	O
one	O
to	O
fight	O
a	O
Duel	O
withal	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
longer	O
than	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Tankard	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
of	O
Fighting	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
only	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
towards	O
Tatnam	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
affronted	O
him	O
about	O
drinking	O
Healths	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
did	O
begin	O
any	O
Health	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
always	O
oppose	O
him	O
or	O
contradict	O
him	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
did	O
immediately	O
demand	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
to	O
fighting	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
ever	O
since	O
been	O
under	O
great	O
trouble	O
of	O
Mind	O
for	O
so	O
sad	O
an	O
Accident	O
;	O
besides	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
Wounded	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
lead	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
Dead	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
led	O
him	O
far	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
then	O
,	O
only	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Healths	O
drank	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
distaste	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
arise	O
there	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
lasted	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
particularly	O
Summed	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
desired	O
carefully	O
to	O
weigh	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
according	O
to	O
their	O
Consciences	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tankard	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Putnam	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Putnam	I-pers
,	O
Labourers	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Charles	O
Putnam	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
near	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Melting-pot	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
full	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clippings	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
higher	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
and	O
Melting-pots	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
other	O
Necessaries	O
for	O
the	O
Clipping	O
Trade	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Charles	O
Putnam	O
was	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
some	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Clipt	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	O
Putnam	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
presently	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
wont	O
often	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
Charles	O
Putnam	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
said	O
Putnam	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Charles	O
Putnam	O
's	O
Man	O
and	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
were	O
both	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
Clip	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Men	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Stairs	O
often	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Shears	O
found	O
in	O
Thomas	O
Putnam	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Canon	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
gave	O
him	O
Two-pence	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Melting-pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
that	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
two	O
Brothers	O
were	O
equally	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
and	O
Rubbing-stones	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Charles	O
Putnam	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
surprized	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
first	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
had	O
an	O
extravagant	O
Hanging	O
Sword	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
him	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
hang	O
'd	O
him	O
presently	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
honestly	O
and	O
fairly	O
heretofore	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
always	O
received	O
good	O
Mony	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
latter	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
likewise	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
hurt	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
particularly	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Clerk	O
sometime	O
ago	O
in	O
the	O
Ballance-Office	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
justly	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
distinctly	O
directed	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
,	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Putnam	O
's	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Moore	O
:	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burrowes	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
Church	I-place
at	O
the	O
Bridge-foot	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sword	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
Fellows	O
that	O
were	O
about	O
him	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
again	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
Mony	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Murray	B-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Stealing	O
Seventeen	O
Pistols	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
Lodging	O
was	O
found	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Pistols	O
with	O
Silver	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Silk	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
Pawn	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stollen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
disowned	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
Ellis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
Ellis	O
particularly	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Murray	B-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
in	O
Bishopgate	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
120	O
A	O
la	O
mode	O
Hoods	O
,	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
White	O
Sarsnet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
Fourteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lute-string	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
18	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Tippets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
16	O
Black	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value10	O
l.	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
200	O
Yards	O
of	O
gray	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
66	O
Womens	O
Girdles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
120	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
Silk	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Hair-Fringe	O
,	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
Copper-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
120	O
Yards	O
of	O
other	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
96	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Ellis	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
in	O
Half-Moon-Court	O
in	O
Bishopgate-street	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
was	O
hid	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
and	O
the	O
Rafters	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	O
used	O
to	O
Lodge	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Confederates	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
Ellis	O
had	O
another	O
Lodging	O
near	O
the	O
Artillery-Ground	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
several	O
other	O
parcels	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Ellis	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Painter	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Living	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
speak	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
House	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Painted	O
it	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
:	O
Nicholas	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Demmy	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wigg	I-pers
s	O
Hat	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
Ironmonger	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
Instant	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wigg	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Demmy	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
run	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
persuit	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
who	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Abel	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
doing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
to	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
for	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
consider	O
further	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hodston	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Named	O
Frances	B-pers
Bredey	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1686.	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Dublin	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Named	O
Mary	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
at	O
Stepny	B-place
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Minister	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
Married	O
him	O
to	O
Bredy	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Dublin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
Co-habited	O
together	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Deacons	O
Orders	O
when	O
he	O
Married	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
inconsiderately	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
satisfied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
his	O
Orders	O
were	O
sufficient	O
enough	O
to	O
Marry	O
them	O
:	O
Another	O
Witness	O
corroborated	O
the	O
Ministers	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
some	O
indifferent	O
Questions	O
not	O
Pertinent	O
,	O
to	O
Invalidate	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
material	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Evidence	O
who	O
Swore	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
said	O
Bredy	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
Co	O
habited	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
one	O
Child	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
readily	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Married	O
the	O
second	O
Wife	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	O
Dyer	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
any	O
further	O
trouble	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Ireland	O
,	O
about	O
Michaelmas	O
1686.	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
supposed	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
Marry	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
Bredy	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
strived	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Court	O
withal	O
by	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
he	O
called	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
not	O
Sworn	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Marriage	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Marriage	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Hearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stable	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
deph	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
Indicted	O
likewise	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
;	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
forced	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Stable	O
standing	O
by	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
interposed	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Womans	O
part	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
a	O
Caning	O
the	O
said	O
Stable	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-man	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
Johnson	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Stabs	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
Sworn	O
only	O
by	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Distracted	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Lady	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
said	O
Lady	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
Charged	O
her	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
Kill	O
'd	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
Charge	O
Johnson	O
sooner	O
,	O
was	O
because	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
declared	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coroner	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Black	O
did	O
Cane	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
Stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
not	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
contradict	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
believe	O
her	O
Evidence	O
,	O
being	O
doubtful	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Red	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Black	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Finch	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Joan	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Cows	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Field	O
at	O
Kentish-Town	B-place
in	O
Pancras	O
Parish	O
but	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
could	O
swear	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witness	O
who	O
proved	O
that	O
Collins	O
owed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
considerable	O
Sum	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Collins	O
made	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
over	O
to	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Collins	O
,	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
Sequestred	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Cows	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Debt	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
made	O
out	O
by	O
very	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jane	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Locket	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
chained	O
Coral	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
Judith	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
;	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
from	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mony-Box	O
value	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
29	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
Spencer	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
Lodged	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Steel	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
make	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
first	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
in	O
Course	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lenon	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
Committed	O
upon	O
one	O
Joshua	B-pers
Droaning	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancras	I-place
near	O
the	I-place
Pinder	I-place
of	I-place
Wakefield	I-place
,	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
the	I-place
Court	I-place
of	I-place
Guard	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
who	O
is	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
his	O
Peruke	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lead	O
him	O
aside	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
bound	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
good	O
Evidence	O
who	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Chamber	O
from	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
till	O
Ten	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Richard	B-pers
Colket	I-pers
in	O
Pancras	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Colket	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
Crab-tree	B-place
Fields	I-place
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sword	O
lying	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
small	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Colket	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Ball	O
in	O
White-Friars	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
Friends	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
;	O
however	O
they	O
changed	O
Gloves	O
at	O
last	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
morrow	O
Morning	O
they	O
Fought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kill	O
'd	O
Colket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
sometime	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalseys	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Colket	O
abused	O
him	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Black-Guard-Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
Serve	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
urging	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
ill	O
will	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Colket	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Houssing	O
adorned	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Connyers	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joan	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
three	O
other	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
six	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
another	O
that	O
is	O
Absconded	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Rose	O
's	O
House	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
looking	O
for	O
Prohibited	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Keys	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
Connyers	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
Search	O
for	O
some	O
Prohibited	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Rose	O
a	O
Clipping	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
a	O
Filing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
an	O
Evidence	O
to	O
contradict	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
Rose	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
since	O
Price	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
as	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
Officer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
below	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
produce	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
justifie	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Clever	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Laced	O
Tippet	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
near	O
London-Wall	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hickman	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Honeywood	I-pers
her	O
Master	O
,	O
three	O
Laced	O
Coronets	O
,	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Table	O
cloth	O
,	O
some	O
Holland	O
Coifs	O
and	O
Aprons	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Taken	O
three	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
directed	O
her	O
Master	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hardwicke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Coronet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
Coifs	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Hardwick	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Door	O
Locked	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Hooper	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
unlock	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Hardwick	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Paw1ned	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Barbican	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
farther	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
Hardwick	O
Lodged	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
Confest	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
absconded	O
themselves	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Hooper	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
;	O
but	O
Deale	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Hooper	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Deale	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Josias	B-pers
Whitbey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Patrick	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
gave	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Whitbey	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Vesey	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Words	O
hapned	O
betwixt	O
Mr.	O
Whitbey	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Vesey	O
,	O
concerning	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Gee	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
whispered	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
meant	O
the	O
Capital	O
Letter	O
G	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Name	O
Gee	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Whitbey	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
paid	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Vesey	O
's	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Mediator	O
,	O
and	O
perswaded	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Friends	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
they	O
whispered	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
kept	O
Mr.	O
Whitbey	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Vesey	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Vesey	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Whitbey	O
promised	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pursue	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
Word	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
between	O
a	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Whitbey	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Vesey	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Whitbey	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Witness	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
)	O
did	O
give	O
a	O
Thrust	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
own	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
near	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Vesey	O
way-laid	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
qualifie	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
followed	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Angel-Inn	B-place
on	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
as	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
Mortal	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Vesey	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
before	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felon	O
and	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Loggins	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Filing	O
and	O
Defacing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
of	O
Clippings	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Copper	O
pieces	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
at	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
Child	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Clippings	O
in	O
Lester-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
brough	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
the	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
Lester-Fields	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
The	O
Girl	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
upon	O
Oath	O
being	O
under	O
Age	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
colour	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
Coin	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
10	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
of	O
K.	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
K.	O
James	O
II	O
's	O
Groats	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Stamps	O
and	O
Shears	O
for	O
Clippings	O
and	O
other	O
Necessaries	O
fit	O
for	O
Coining	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
searcht	O
;	O
The	O
false	O
Coin	O
and	O
the	O
Metal	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
Browne	O
was	O
and	O
in	O
Sarah	O
Brownes	O
Hand	O
was	O
found	O
two	O
Counterfeit	O
Half	O
pence	O
and	O
two	O
false	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Groats	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
if	O
a	O
Drawer	O
which	O
Fisher	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
hard	O
Pains	O
takers	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
Stich	O
Bodice	O
for	O
their	O
Livelihood	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
was	O
strong	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Fisher	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
John	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Sarah	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
Sheep	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
;	O
The	O
Sheep	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
Payne	O
confest	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
Payne	O
had	O
the	O
Sheep	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
at	O
Knights-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Arthur	O
Bunn	O
bought	O
the	O
Sheep	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
Payne	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Sheep	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Poverty	O
,	O
and	O
ow	O
'd	O
Mony	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
and	O
Bunn	O
paid	O
honestly	O
for	O
the	O
Sheep	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Payne	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Robling	I-pers
in	O
Exeter-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robling	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Maid	O
that	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
theirs	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
might	O
be	O
drawn	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Rosseter	I-pers
;	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
Sold	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
May	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Forbus	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
4	O
Childrens	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Bell	O
metal	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Blankets	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
paid	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
Was	O
found	O
Guilt	O
of	O
Petty	O
Larcenary	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Brownet	I-pers
's	O
House	O
about	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Sarsnet	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Tippet	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Captain	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Child	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
French	O
Pistols	O
,	O
35	O
s.	O
four	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Burnet	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
presently	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Child	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Welsh	O
and	O
Burnet	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Radcliff	B-place
High-way	I-place
and	O
called	O
for	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
missed	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
himself	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Burnet	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Welsh	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbara	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
alias	O
Rolph	B-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
l.	O
three	O
Spoons	O
,	O
three	O
Muslin	O
Cornets	O
;	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Confest	O
when	O
Taken	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
F	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Baker	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
besides	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
in	O
Butler	B-place
's	I-place
Ally	I-place
in	O
Grub-street	I-place
;	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Fellows	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Fingers	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
round	O
his	O
Middle	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
him	O
intoCellar	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
Taken	O
at	O
his	O
ife	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Tanner	O
did	O
entice	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Purser	O
,	O
Landlord	O
Mr.	O
Jervis	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
,	O
t	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stood	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Jervis	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
quiet	O
,	O
whilst	O
Purser	O
and	O
Tanner	O
were	O
above	O
Stairs	O
Rifling	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Tanner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
confest	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Knappyer	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
in	O
offering	O
21	O
Shillings	O
and	O
3	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Matthias	I-pers
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
Shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
changed	O
27	O
Guinea	O
's	O
h	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Rate	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Silver	O
he	O
gave	O
in	O
Exchange	O
was	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
ly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Clasey	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clasey	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
Arraigned	O
in	O
one	O
Indictment	O
;	O
For	O
that	O
Mary	O
Tisdal	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
did	O
Steal	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Mary	O
Tisdal	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Accessories	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Treley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Cutting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
where	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
with	O
Clipt	O
Mony	O
and	O
Melting	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
Shears	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
a	O
Clipping	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Bosom	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
Mrs.	O
Treley	O
seem	O
'd	O
much	O
concerned	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
that	O
could	O
charge	O
her	O
home	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Gardner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Fulk	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Mony	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sheldon	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
Mary	O
Browne	O
was	O
found	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
and	O
some	O
Clipt	O
Mony	O
and	O
Clippings	O
lying	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
broad	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
Sheldon	O
was	O
found	O
standing	O
without	O
the	O
Chamber-Door	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sheldon	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Clippings	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
Red-Lyon-Inn	O
Passage	O
in	O
Great	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
she	O
paid	O
those	O
that	O
the	O
dealt	O
with	O
in	O
as	O
good	O
Mony	O
as	O
is	O
wont	O
to	O
pass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Browne	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
hired	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sheldon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Whiteing	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiteing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petty-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petty-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Tippet	O
,	O
a	O
Laced	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
;	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Billidge	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
against	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
which	O
Indictment	O
consisted	O
of	O
Three	O
Parts	O
;	O
The	O
First	O
set	O
forth	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
procure	O
a	O
certain	O
small	O
Vessel	O
,	O
(	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
making	O
her	O
a	O
Cruising	O
Privateer	O
)	O
to	O
convey	O
and	O
carry	O
over	O
several	O
Persons	O
into	O
France	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
profest	O
Enemies	O
to	O
our	O
present	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
part	O
was	O
for	O
Drinking	O
a	O
Health	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
K.	O
the	O
late	O
K.	O
James	O
,	O
his	O
Queen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Hans	O
in	O
Kelder	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Prosperity	O
and	O
good	O
Success	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
Designs	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
part	O
was	O
for	O
Drinking	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
the	O
Confusion	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
Hunch	O
'd	O
Nose	O
William	O
's	O
Forces	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
K.	O
and	O
hoped	O
withal	O
that	O
King	O
James	O
would	O
be	O
here	O
within	O
this	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
abovementioned	O
Health	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Agreement	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
several	O
persons	O
into	O
France	O
,	O
particularly	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Penn	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
his	O
Incouragement	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
20	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Man	O
for	O
every	O
person	O
he	O
should	O
carry	O
;	O
Nay	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
French	O
Commission	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Passenger	O
the	O
prisoner	O
should	O
send	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Tartar	O
(	O
meaning	O
thereby	O
the	O
French	O
Privateers	O
)	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
fear	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
find	O
out	O
away	O
speedily	O
to	O
clear	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
several	O
Letters	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
strived	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Reproach	O
and	O
Scandal	O
upon	O
the	O
King	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
avail	O
'd	O
him	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
frivelous	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
force	O
on	O
the	O
prisoners	O
side	O
,	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
sum	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
very	O
distinctly	O
to	O
the	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
Consequence	O
such	O
Presidents	O
are	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
tended	O
only	O
to	O
foment	O
and	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
heats	O
and	O
divisions	O
amongst	O
the	O
Kings	O
Subject	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
great	O
favour	O
shewed	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
such	O
Persons	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
exemplarily	O
punished	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
well	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
20	O
.	O
John	O
Connyers	O
,	O
John	O
Price	O
,	O
Elis	O
.	O
Askue	O
,	O
Elis	O
.	O
Stiddiard	O
,	O
Anne	O
,	O
Danbey	O
,	O
William	O
Shavall	O
,	O
Charles	O
Nourse	O
,	O
William	O
Noble	O
,	O
James	O
Whitbey	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Payne	O
,	O
John	O
Burnet	O
,	O
Kath	O
.	O
Arnett	O
,	O
Elenor	O
Lowder	O
,	O
Jane	O
Warner	O
,	O
Alice	O
Webb	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bowman	O
,	O
Mary	O
Tisdale	O
,	O
Elis	O
.	O
Whiteing	O
,	O
Elis	O
.	O
Hooper	O
,	O
Anne	O
Mills	O
.	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
16	O
.	O
Charles	O
Putnam	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Putnam	O
,	O
John	O
Burrowes	O
,	O
Rich	O
.	O
Elis	O
Mary	O
Nicholas	O
,	O
M	O
-	O
F	O
-	O
,	O
Henry	O
Tankard	O
Elis	O
.	O
Deale	O
,	O
Elis	O
.	O
Gardner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Browne	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Sheldon	O
,	O
John	O
Browne	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Browne	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Welch	O
;	O
Richard	O
Blackford	O
and	O
Ruth	O
Phillips	O
who	O
were	O
Convicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
that	O
were	O
Condemned	O
this	O
Sessions	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
5	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Harding	O
,	O
Elis	O
.	O
Hicks	O
,	O
alias	O
Hickman	O
,	O
Elis	O
.	O
May	O
,	O
Hester	O
Hodges	O
,	O
Mary	O
Clever	O
.	O
Elisabeth	O
Gardner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Browne	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Sheldon	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Browne	O
,	O
pleading	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
Billidge	O
Clayton	O
,	O
Fined	O
500	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
George	O
Knapier	O
for	O
uttering	O
false	O
Mony	O
,	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
Committed	O
till	O
he	O
Perform	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	O
Nourse	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
being	O
Respited	O
now	O
by	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
Pardon	O
from	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
Edward	O
Jones	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	O
Fowler	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
Guild	O
Hall	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
there	O
to	O
Answer	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	O
Hodston	O
,	O
for	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
was	O
Bailed	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Branding	O
being	O
remitted	O
by	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Order	O
&	O
c.	O
Francis	O
Moore	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Putnan	O
's	O
;	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
A	O
True	O
and	O
perfect	O
Relation	O
of	O
that	O
most	O
Sad	O
and	O
Terrible	O
Earth	O
quake	O
at	O
Port-Royal	O
in	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
which	O
happened	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
two	O
Minutes	O
time	O
the	O
Town	O
was	O
Sunk	O
under	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Two	O
Thousand	O
Souls	O
Perished	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Large	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Crocket	O
:	O
As	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
Earthquake	O
which	O
happen	O
'd	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Holland	O
Flanders	O
,	O
France	O
,	O
Germany	O
,	O
Zealand	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
in	O
most	O
parts	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
being	O
a	O
Dreadful	O
Warning	O
to	O
the	O
Sleepy	O
World	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
God	O
's	O
heavy	O
judgments	O
shewed	O
on	O
a	O
tinful	O
People	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Forerunner	O
of	O
the	O
Terr	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
.	O
Printed	O
on	O
a	O
Broad	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Curious	O
Cut	O
,	O
Lively	O
representing	O
the	O
Desolation	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
Miller	O
at	O
the	O
Gilded	O
Acorn	O
in	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
G.	O
Croom	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
near	O
Baynards-Castle	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
EVangelital	O
Repentance	O
unto	O
Salvation	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
Repented	O
of	O
upon	O
2	O
Cor	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
most	O
Seasonable	O
,	O
short	O
Considerations	O
on	O
that	O
great	O
Context	O
Heb	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Yet	O
once	O
more	O
I	O
shake	O
not	O
only	O
Earth	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Solemn	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Dreadful	O
Earthquake	O
in	O
Jamaica	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
later	O
Monitory	O
Motion	O
of	O
the	O
Earth	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
,	O
and	O
beyond	O
the	O
Sea	O
.	O
Whereunto	O
is	O
Adjoined	O
a	O
Discourse	O
on	O
Death-Bed	O
Repentance	O
,	O
On	O
Luke	O
22	O
.	O
39	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Beverley	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
Miller	O
at	O
the	O
Gilded	O
Acorn	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
,	O
Reign	O
,	O
Supports	O
,	O
and	O
sudden	O
Foil	O
of	O
Popery	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Three	O
Years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
James	O
the	O
II	O
.	O
late	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Six	O
Popish	O
Pillars	O
,	O
The	O
Anabaptists	O
,	O
Presbyocrians	O
,	O
Quakers	O
,	O
Independents	O
,	O
Roman-Catholicks	O
and	O
Popish	O
Church-men	O
.	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Croom	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
near	O
Baynards-Castle	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
THese	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
that	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew-Ball	O
in	O
Whale-bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
by	O
inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
it	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Sovereign	O
Head-Pill	O
,	O
which	O
Infalliby	O
Cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
whether	O
old	O
or	O
newly	O
Contracted	O
speedily	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
Swimmings	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
,	O
preventing	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
of	O
Apoplectical	O
Fits	O
,	O
preserves	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Accidents	O
offending	O
the	O
Eyes	O
;	O
Strengthens	O
the	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
disburthens	O
the	O
Brain	O
of	O
all	O
offensive	O
Humours	O
,	O
thereby	O
rendring	O
the	O
Understanding	O
more	O
clear	O
and	O
Vigorous	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
with	O
Directors	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
an	O
expeditious	O
way	O
,	O
in	O
Curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
without	O
Drawing	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
Excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
