TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
KING	O
and	O
QUEEN	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
For	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
third	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
an	O
Adjournment	O
again	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
1693	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
third	O
of	O
June	O
and	O
by	O
an	O
Adjournment	O
again	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
,	O
1693.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trevill	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Trinley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Foard	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bardy	I-pers
.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Saywell	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
John	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Matthias	B-pers
Cupper	I-pers
.	O
Crisp	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hynde	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hynde	I-pers
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Winkle	I-pers
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cripps	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
Emanuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tippet	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Martha	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
alias	O
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
and	O
arraigned	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
one	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stitch	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
a	O
Coral	O
30s	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
three	O
broad	O
plates	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
15l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
from	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Hawksworth	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Wayte	I-pers
in	O
Great	B-place
Fish-street	I-place
in	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
three	O
Sugar	O
Castors	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
one	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-cloths	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
6	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Challis	B-pers
Searl	I-pers
a	O
little	O
Youth	O
Aged	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
of	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Constantine	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Crond	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
the	O
day	O
Captain	O
Winter	O
was	O
Executed	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
pick	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
neighbours	O
who	O
appeared	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
any	O
ill	O
disposition	O
,	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
pilfering	O
nor	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
constantly	O
to	O
School	O
as	O
was	O
Attested	O
by	O
the	O
School-master	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Scholar	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
in	O
London	O
;	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapened	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
a	O
Brass	O
one	O
the	O
stead	O
thereof	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
found	O
the	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
upon	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
ill	O
design	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
probably	O
fancying	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Proverb	O
,	O
that	O
Exchange	O
is	O
no	O
Robbery	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
at	O
the	B-place
Cock	I-place
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
made	O
appear	O
that	O
one	O
Hyllary	B-pers
Basley	I-pers
was	O
most	O
likely	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
)	O
for	O
5l.3s	O
.	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Hyllary	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Workman	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Theft	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
London	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
one	O
Flanders	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cravat	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
who	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
met	O
Mrs	O
Collins	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
and	O
jostled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
contained	O
17	O
l.	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
immediately	O
missing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
Bag	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
two	O
,	O
sufficient	O
Citizens	O
that	O
were	O
accidentally	O
standing	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
defence	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
do	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
alias	O
Pierce	I-pers
two	O
Brethren	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
tankard	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
Knight-Riders-street	B-place
value	O
5l	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
both	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
three	O
Tankards	O
they	O
escaped	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
but	O
were	O
soon	O
taken	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
better	O
Colour	O
on	O
their	O
design	O
,	O
was	O
drest	O
up	O
in	O
Womens	O
Apparel	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Thomas	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
but	O
John	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	O
so	O
Aparell	O
'd	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
John	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
make	O
haste	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
first	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
offer	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
material	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Thomas	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sarner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
value	O
each	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Waldor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
of	O
Harrow	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mare	O
price	O
25s	O
.	O
from	O
Moses	B-pers
Edling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
;	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
Sarner	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
driving	O
the	O
Sheep	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
towards	O
London	O
;	O
Sarner	O
declared	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
the	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
of	O
Pynner	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
heretofore	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
said	O
that	O
Sarner	O
hired	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
turned	O
the	O
Matter	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
material	O
evidence	O
to	O
disprove	O
or	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
that	O
Sarner	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Mare	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
Merrick	O
both	O
of	O
Sheep	O
and	O
Mare	O
.	O
[	O
Merrick	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Sarner	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
;	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
one	O
Gober	B-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
Gober	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
resisted	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Gober	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
having	O
struggled	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
Gober	O
was	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
although	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Corroborating	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
them	O
fight	O
;	O
So	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
impudence	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Prudence	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
Eleven	O
Flaxen	O
napkins	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
three	O
Smocks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Arthur	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
of	O
Heston	B-place
;	O
near	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
;	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stole	O
off	O
the	O
Hedge	O
;	O
which	O
Linnen	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
old	O
House	O
uninhabited	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
upon	O
a	O
Wad	O
of	O
Straw	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Poverty	O
pinching	O
them	O
,	O
caused	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Linnen	O
off	O
the	O
Hedge	O
;	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brathwayte	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Steel-hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Cane	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
running	O
down	O
Old	O
So-ho	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
he	O
alleged	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Boatey	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boatey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
)	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
some	O
Pillow-bears	O
and	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Dowtey	I-pers
of	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
let	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
pleaded	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
given	O
them	O
ten	O
times	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
could	O
disprove	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
that	O
had	O
so	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mabel	B-pers
Symmonds	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
and	O
41s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Postern	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Postern	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
Postern	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
entertained	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
she	O
mist	O
her	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
leaving	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
church	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
no	O
Person	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
when	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
one	O
Witness	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
weighing	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
by	O
the	O
Posey	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
thus	O
(	O
Christ	O
and	O
thee	O
my	O
Comfort	O
be	O
)	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
seemed	O
to	O
arise	O
somewhat	O
from	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
none	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
False	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
one	O
bad	O
Half-Crown	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
between	O
Michaelmas	O
and	O
Christmas	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Brazier	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
bad	O
Half-Crowns	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
divers	O
Half-Crowns	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
more	O
Brass	O
in	O
them	O
than	O
true	O
Mettal	O
,	O
so	O
more	O
properly	O
to	O
be	O
applied	O
to	O
a	O
Brazier	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
very	O
good	O
Money	O
to	O
those	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
dealing	O
withal	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
chose	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
Money	O
rather	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
favoured	O
of	O
Malice	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pead	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
in	O
Holborn	B-place
(	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
)	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
one	O
Sable	O
Tipper	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
she	O
stole	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
of	O
Gold	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
another	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jollen	I-pers
a	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Morris	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
entrusted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
near	O
Bedford	O
Wall	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Pead	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
of	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
Persons	O
abovementioned	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Persons	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Morris	O
she	O
could	O
never	O
get	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
Gold	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Gentlewomens	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Goates	O
's	O
the	O
pawn-brokers	O
in	O
Shooe-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Allen	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
Pead	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
,	O
Morris	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Cloathes	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
feigned	O
Story	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Maudlin	B-pers
Bevell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Groydon	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Tippet	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
Laced	O
with	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
value	O
3l.a	O
Silver	O
Girdle	O
,	O
a	O
Muff	O
,	O
a	O
Gawle	O
Hood	O
,	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Groydon	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Pasteboard	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Herb-shop	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Groydon	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
particularly	O
a	O
Fan	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
remarkable	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
hands	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
would	O
not	O
serve	O
her	O
turn	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
honestly	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
particularly	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
in	O
Monmouth-shire	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
according	O
to	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
nothing	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
her	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
small	O
things	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lambeth	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kneves	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Flitch	O
of	O
Bacon	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
about	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
for	O
7s	O
.	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
it	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
besides	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
Bacon	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Tabby	O
value	O
35s	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
alias	O
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
likewise	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Calico	O
Window-Curtains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
and	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
of	O
Thistleworth	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Morris	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
a	O
young	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
800	O
Half-pence	O
and	O
Farthings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Locker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
Locker	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	B-place
,	O
being	O
wont	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
Errands	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mistrust	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
London	O
he	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
were	O
to	O
divide	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
D	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
short	O
Ribs	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
upon	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
1689.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
D	O
-	O
absconded	O
until	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
hearing	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Cave	O
was	O
Barbarously	O
Murdered	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
first	O
Mr.	O
White	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
sate	O
upon	O
the	O
dead	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
dead	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Witness	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Examination	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
that	O
was	O
Kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
D	O
-	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
Chocolate-house	O
in	O
Bridges-street	B-place
in	O
Covent-Garden	I-place
on	O
the	O
day	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
D	O
-	O
presently	O
charged	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
with	O
taking	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
question	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
did	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Mr	O
D	O
-	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
fury	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
D	O
-	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
was	O
allowed	O
as	O
good	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Law	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Name	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
he	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
presumed	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
him	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
when	O
Mr.	O
cave	O
was	O
Kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
submit	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Judgment	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
giving	O
this	O
Reason	O
for	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
because	O
Cave	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
to	O
Mr.	O
D	O
-	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
so	O
affront	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
therefore	O
was	O
a	O
fresh	O
provocation	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Not	O
burnt	O
,	O
being	O
remitted	O
by	O
the	O
Act	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
Diamond	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
came	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Yeom	O
.	O
Were	O
both	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Philemon	B-pers
Quoyne	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
for	O
stabbing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
this	O
Account	O
;	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green	I-place
Dragon	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
Nichols	O
sat	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
way	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refused	O
,	O
damning	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
great	O
Oaths	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Quoyne	O
interposing	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
two	O
passes	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
running	O
from	O
them	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stampt	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
him	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Dog	O
dead	O
yet	O
?	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
pursued	O
the	O
said	O
Quoyne	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
down	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
gushed	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Mouth	O
by	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
Carter	O
's	O
trampling	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
demanded	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
;	O
Carter	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
about	O
Nichols	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
which	O
blow	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
wound	O
from	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
retreated	O
to	O
some	O
adjacent	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
arrest	O
;	O
Nichols	O
alledged	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
the	O
Soldier	O
Casey	O
challenged	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
knocked	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Horse	O
stood	O
cross	O
the	O
Gate-way	O
,	O
which	O
hindered	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
passage	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
Witness	O
to	O
attest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
almost	O
20	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
upon	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Fray	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
opposition	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
killed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
doubt	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Quoyne	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
Murther	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
acquitted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
and	O
Esther	B-pers
King	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Cornhill	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
mind	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Nags-head	B-place
,	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
100	O
Guineas	O
lately	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
them	O
presently	O
at	O
work	O
to	O
examine	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
;	O
says	O
Ann	O
Harris	O
,	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
sit	O
nearer	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guineas	O
dropt	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
found	O
upon	O
King	O
in	O
her	O
Stockings	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
her	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
upon	O
Harris	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
were	O
squeezed	O
out	O
of	O
Harris	O
's	O
Throat	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
swallow	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
presumed	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Powder	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
take	O
for	O
Fits	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
troubled	O
withal	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Guineas	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
being	O
frankly	O
given	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
that	O
King	O
pickt	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
the	O
Guineas	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
Ann	O
Harris	O
;	O
King	O
had	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
appeared	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
fair	O
heretofore	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
late	O
behaviour	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
;	O
Harris	O
had	O
no	O
Friend	O
for	O
her	O
Credit	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
swearing	O
,	O
debauched	O
Woman	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Morris	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
who	O
was	O
nominated	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Presley	I-pers
,	O
since	O
Executed	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
now	O
arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
persons	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Sir	O
John	O
Friend	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
two	O
Silver	O
Monteths	O
value	O
50l	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Basons	O
value	O
40l	O
.	O
three	O
Salvers	O
15l	O
.	O
a	O
Beaker	O
10l	O
.	O
two	O
Jarrrs	O
20l	O
.	O
8	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
18l	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
more	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
two	O
Chafingdishes	O
3l	O
.	O
two	O
Tumblers	O
4l	O
.	O
seven	O
Salts	O
7l	O
.	O
a	O
Mug	O
3l	O
.	O
two	O
Cups	O
3l	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
two	O
Chamber-pots	O
8l	O
.	O
two	O
Head-pieces	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Snuff-dishes	O
12l	O
.	O
four	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
20l	O
.	O
six	O
Porringers	O
12l	O
.	O
thirteen	O
Spoons	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
twelve	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
more	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
six	O
Silver	O
Combs	O
25s	O
.	O
two	O
Plates	O
6l	O
.	O
one	O
Sugar-box	O
50s	O
.	O
a	O
Mustard-pot	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Funnel	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Spoon	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
another	O
Spoon	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Skillet	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
Watches	O
12l	O
.	O
eleven	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-box	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Diamond	O
value	O
20l	O
.	O
100	O
Broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
107l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
Friend	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
whether	O
guilty	O
of	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beacon	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
threescore	O
and	O
nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
another	O
piece	O
value	O
11s	O
.	O
9d	O
.	O
and	O
180l	O
.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
Whitworth	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.Beacon	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Beacon	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
leaving	O
his	O
Son	O
and	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Servants	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Whitworth	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
long	O
a	O
contriving	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Clements	O
and	O
one	O
Belcher	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
that	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
,	O
one	O
English	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Beacon	O
declared	O
further	O
upon	O
Oath	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
pieces	O
found	O
about	O
Whitworth	O
,	O
and	O
29	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Beds-Tester	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Whitworth	O
Lodged	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
6s	O
6d	O
.	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
Nixon	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
Shillings	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
remark	O
by	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Beacon	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
10l	O
.	O
more	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Nixon	O
's	O
Bed-Tester	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Beacon	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
with	O
their	O
own	O
Seal	O
,	O
which	O
Nixon	O
said	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
Belcher	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
Clement	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
26l	O
.	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Beacon	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Whitworth	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
Nixon	O
denied	O
all	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
too	O
;	O
Clement	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
marked	O
F.E	O
.	O
was	O
lent	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Lease	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
farther	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
before	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
one	O
Aswater	O
at	O
Reading	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Summer	O
Assizes	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
whom	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
neither	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
but	O
as	O
vain	O
excuses	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
Charged	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
considered	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Devereux	B-pers
Beasant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
8	O
Silver-handled	O
Sword	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
another	O
Sword	O
3l	O
.	O
6	O
other	O
Swords	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tempest	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
whom	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dozen	O
new	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
hiding	O
a	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Mantle-Tree	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Kent	O
flatly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
;	O
Barker	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Kent	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Swords	O
;	O
Beasant	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Kent	O
,	O
Barker	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Beasant	O
:	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Marble	O
Image	O
of	O
a	O
Dog	O
value	O
49s	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Ragoone	I-pers
the	O
fifth	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
lost	O
a	O
Horse	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
use	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
driving	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Housekeeper	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
May	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mantua	O
gown	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dighton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
Cox	O
confessed	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
May	O
pleaded	O
Not-guilty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
only	O
Mr.	O
Dighton	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
some	O
water	O
was	O
fetching	O
to	O
cast	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
better	O
considering	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
positive	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
at	O
the	O
Griffen	B-place
upon	O
Windmill-Hill	I-place
;	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
rub	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Money	O
upon	O
a	O
Tyle	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
Crevas	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
Tyle	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissers	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sixpences	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
Woman	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
for	O
Drink	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
half-Crown	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
Drink	O
besides	O
the	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
suspicious	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
a	O
Printer	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Composing	O
and	O
Printing	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
thereby	O
to	O
disturb	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
the	O
Present	O
Government	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
false	O
and	O
pernicious	O
Libel	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Virulent	O
and	O
Malicious	O
Expressions	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Libel	O
under	O
a	O
Bolster	O
of	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
Two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Milbourne	O
by	O
his	O
Counsel	O
called	O
several	O
good	O
Men	O
for	O
to	O
vindicate	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Parish	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Milbourne	O
lived	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
apprehended	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
discreet	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
well-affected	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
frequented	O
the	O
Church	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
Corroborated	O
by	O
some	O
Booksellers	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
dealings	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
being	O
considered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
values	O
4s	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Satin	O
Cap	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
20s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
buying	O
,	O
getting	O
,	O
obtaining	O
,	O
and	O
acquiring	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Clippings	O
about	O
20	O
Ounces	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
's	O
Compting-house	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abbot	O
being	O
searcht	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
Lady	O
Dartmouth	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
of	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
by	O
their	O
Counsel	O
called	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
first	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
secondly	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
when	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Partner	O
one	O
Goring	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
absconded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
others	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Credit	O
and	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fair	O
Dealer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Reputable	O
man	O
amongst	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
buy	O
Clippings	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
;	O
one	O
Witness	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
Money	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
for	O
Clippings	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
Scarf	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
Hood	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
which	O
Felony	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
O	I-pers
Neale	I-pers
in	O
Pepper-street	B-place
in	O
Southwark	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lifted	O
the	O
Door	O
off	O
the	O
Hinges	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
Law	O
was	O
a	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Womans	O
Sleeve	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Coopers	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
good	O
Witness	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
getting	O
,	O
keeping	O
and	O
concealing	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
several	O
Clippings	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
law	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
about	O
70	O
Ounces	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Hurt	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
in	O
the	O
le	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
below	O
Stairs	O
were	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
more	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Clippings	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
entertaining	O
Evil-disposed	O
Persons	O
therein	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
one	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
brisk	O
young	O
Girl	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
had	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
pull	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Belly	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
that	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
good	O
,	O
a	O
Commodity	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
enough	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
good	O
daubs	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
called	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elye	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
evil	O
Repute	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
that	O
oftentimes	O
there	O
was	O
Swearing	O
,	O
Roaring	O
and	O
Damning	O
all	O
the	O
Night	O
long	O
,	O
drinking	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
pitch	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
fall	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
Her	O
House	O
is	O
in	O
Flower-de-luce	B-place
Court	I-place
in	O
Fetter-Lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
there	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
Lewd	O
Women	O
seen	O
to	O
resort	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
great	O
damage	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Youth	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
their	O
Masters	O
also	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Witness	O
Swore	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mercer	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Lewd	O
and	O
Wicked	O
Women	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Leonard	B-pers
Po-Jenner	I-pers
and	O
Attbut	B-pers
Remmington	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Publishing	O
a	O
most	O
base	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Entitled	O
,	O
The	O
Kings	O
Speech	O
to	O
his	O
Parliament	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Clench	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-house	I-place
in	O
Mitre-Court	I-place
,	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Parliament	O
first	O
sate	O
,	O
comes	O
Mr.	O
Jenner	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Libel	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Speech	O
to	O
his	O
Parliament	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
right	O
Speech	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
Mr.	O
Jenner	O
how	O
he	O
durst	O
carry	O
such	O
papers	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Remmington	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
Paper	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Closet-goods	O
,	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
argued	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jenner	O
found	O
the	O
paper	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Credible	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jenner	O
was	O
well-affected	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
often	O
drank	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
heretofore	O
,	O
but	O
lately	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
without	O
naming	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Remmington	O
because	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
him	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
John	O
Press	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Callion	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
a	O
Thread	O
Lace	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stitch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Brooks	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Beaver	O
hat	O
40s	O
.	O
36	O
Napkins	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
5l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
better	O
opportunity	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
one	O
Peter	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Surname	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Benn	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
assistant	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
who	O
are	O
fled	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
confess	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witness	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
only	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Boreman	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
a	O
Cup	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
and	O
32s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Francis	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
a	O
Rose-Tree	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Francis	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
Pawn	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Colour	O
of	O
Evidence	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
guilty	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Parish	O
Boys	O
abovesaid	O
in	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Boys	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Procession	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
o	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
knock	O
the	O
said	O
Prosser	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
both	O
Hands	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Skull	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Feavor	O
and	O
Convulsion	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Youths	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
Fact	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
great	O
extremity	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
danger	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Laytus	I-pers
a	O
Mantua-maker	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Composing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
2	O
false	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Libels	O
,	O
one	O
called	O
,	O
A	O
Song	O
made	O
upon	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
another	O
,	O
A	O
Song	O
made	O
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
the	O
Burden	O
of	O
which	O
Songs	O
were	O
,	O
A	O
dainty	O
fine	O
King	O
,	O
A	O
dainty	O
fine	O
Queen	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
indeed	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
Swore	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
write	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
sing	O
the	O
Songs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
when	O
first	O
taxed	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
to	O
sing	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
her	O
Counsel	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
account	O
she	O
workt	O
hard	O
for	O
a	O
living	O
at	O
her	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
speak	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
any	O
ways	O
disaffected	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
serve	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
in	O
the	O
third	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
were	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Broad	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Pistole	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
and	O
16s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Corbet	O
Swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
aboard	O
at	O
the	O
Temple	O
being	O
a	O
Laundress	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
pickt	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Gold	O
and	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
home	O
;	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
said	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
Five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
enticed	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
Swear	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Gold	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
11	O
l.	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
part	O
Silver	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
committed	O
upon	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Mot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Mot	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
were	O
walking	O
one	O
Evening	O
in	O
Southampton	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
Rogues	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
Mot	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
besides	O
20s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Mot	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
set	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Women	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
their	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
Credited	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
entrap	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
damask	O
Table-cloth	O
5s	O
.	O
three	O
Smocks	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
two	O
Wastecoats	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
silent	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Ring	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
Fulham	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
fled	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
trifling	O
matter	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shakemaple	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
Two	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Holborne	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
information	O
,	O
they	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Horn	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
a	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
searching	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Filings	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
near	O
80	O
Ounces	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
coming	O
from	O
Tatnam	O
Court	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
too	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
late	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
dealt	O
in	O
Second-hand	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
employed	O
himself	O
besides	O
in	O
getting	O
in	O
all	O
Debts	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
did	O
employ	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
Families	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
good	O
Repute	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10000	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
which	O
gave	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Nailer	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
File	O
and	O
Shears	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
there	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
owed	O
him	O
a	O
spight	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
Money	O
they	O
owed	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
and	O
a	O
Gun	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
very	O
well	O
loaded	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Loyalty	O
to	O
his	O
King	O
and	O
Countrey	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
integrity	O
upon	O
all	O
Accounts	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
Printer	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
was	O
read	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Compose	O
,	O
Print	O
and	O
publish	O
Two	O
Malicious	O
,	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Traiterous	O
Libels	O
,	O
The	O
first	O
Entitled	O
,	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
the	O
present	O
Confederacy	O
,	O
and	O
late	O
Revolution	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Entitled	O
,	O
A	O
French	O
Conquest	O
neither	O
desirable	O
,	O
nor	O
practicable	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
upon	O
his	O
Request	O
ordered	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Pannel	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
time	O
till	O
Saturday	O
to	O
prepare	O
for	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
was	O
again	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
were	O
summoned	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Issue	O
were	O
called	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Appearances	O
recorded	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liberty	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Exceptions	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prescription	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
35	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
full	O
number	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
sworn	O
were	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
whose	O
names	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Crisp	B-pers
Grainge	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blissett	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hynde	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hinde	I-pers
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rumidge	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freebody	I-pers
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
opened	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Offence	O
that	O
was	O
contained	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
the	O
highest	O
degree	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
compassing	O
and	O
designing	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
Overt	O
Act	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Intention	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
Overt	O
Act	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Composing	O
,	O
Printing	O
,	O
Publishing	O
and	O
dispersing	O
of	O
two	O
Treasonable	O
Libels	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
contained	O
,	O
the	O
Rankest	O
,	O
Vilest	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
malicious	O
Treasons	O
that	O
ever	O
could	O
be	O
imagined	O
by	O
any	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
Paper	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
name	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
design	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
merely	O
to	O
incite	O
all	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Subjects	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
raise	O
War	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
called	O
and	O
sworn	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Messenger	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
above	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
in	O
printing	O
Seditious	O
Libels	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
could	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
till	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
spying	O
two	O
Journey-men	O
Printers	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
missed	O
from	O
the	O
publick	O
Printing-houses	O
this	O
half	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
exactly	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Skudamore	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
)	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
suspected	O
they	O
worked	O
privately	O
:	O
So	O
having	O
got	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
avoid	O
any	O
suspicion	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
first	O
asked	O
what	O
Lodgers	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
then	O
turning	O
his	O
head	O
aside	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
well	O
knowing	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
,	O
she	O
immediately	O
cry	O
d	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
)	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
hair	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
Murther	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
uncivil	O
manner	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
scorned	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Subject	O
to	O
Hook-Nose	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Beadle	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
made	O
a	O
particular	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Landlady	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lapidary	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
.	O
There	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
shoving	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
run	O
upon	O
Wheels	O
,	O
close	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
suspicion	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
to	O
remove	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
done	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Door	O
which	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
entring	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Printing	O
press	O
,	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Materials	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
farther	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Trunk	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Libels	O
,	O
and	O
Libellous	O
Pamphlets	O
;	O
one	O
Entitled	O
,	O
A	O
Caution	O
to	O
the	O
Navy	O
;	O
another	O
,	O
Historical	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
the	O
Wars	O
;	O
another	O
,	O
A	O
Second	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Salisbury	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Errata	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
&	O
c.	O
found	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Book	O
called	O
,	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
the	O
Confederacy	O
:	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Desk	O
(	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
knew	O
well	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
seized	O
it	O
before	O
)	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Desk	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Libels	O
(	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Trial	O
)	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
,	O
which	O
Desk	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
these	O
they	O
seized	O
and	O
secured	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
put	O
their	O
private	O
Marks	O
upon	O
the	O
Libels	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
's	O
Chamber	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
alighted	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
through	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
overtaken	O
by	O
the	O
Porter	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
This	O
was	O
fully	O
and	O
clearly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Libels	O
were	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
abundance	O
of	O
Base	O
,	O
Vile	O
,	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Traiterous	O
Expressions	O
,	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
honest	O
Englishman	O
to	O
hate	O
and	O
abominate	O
all	O
such	O
Traiterous	O
and	O
disaffected	O
Principles	O
.	O
That	O
Libel	O
called	O
,	O
A	O
Caution	O
to	O
the	O
Navy	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Printing-room	O
,	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
corrected	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
those	O
Letters	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Form	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Caution	O
to	O
the	O
Navy	O
was	O
printed	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
with	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
Character	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
the	O
Libels	O
he	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
matter	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
an	O
Overt-Act	O
,	O
therefore	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
adjudged	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
praying	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
Counsel	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
plead	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
Law	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
answered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
question	O
was	O
Whether	O
he	O
printed	O
those	O
Treasonable	O
Books	O
,	O
which	O
plainly	O
answered	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
Press	O
also	O
)	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
so	O
printing	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
an	O
Overt-Act	O
in	O
the	O
Judgment	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
;	O
therefore	O
the	O
Person	O
so	O
offending	O
must	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cook	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Matter	O
of	O
Law	O
in	O
his	O
Case	O
;	O
who	O
says	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Intention	O
of	O
the	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
injury	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
person	O
,	O
by	O
buying	O
a	O
Gun	O
or	O
Gunpowder	O
,	O
or	O
Poyson	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
accounted	O
an	O
Overt-Act	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
Primitive	O
Times	O
,	O
before	O
Printing	O
was	O
Invented	O
,	O
writing	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Overt-Act	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
therefore	O
Printing	O
was	O
more	O
manifestly	O
an	O
Overt-Act	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
room	O
for	O
any	O
Counsel	O
to	O
be	O
assigned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
of	O
Law	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
plead	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
any	O
unnecessary	O
trouble	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
grounds	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
Plea	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
offer	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
any	O
way	O
advantageous	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
very	O
patiently	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Treby	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
Telling	O
them	O
what	O
dangerous	O
Consequences	O
such	O
Treasonable	O
Libels	O
were	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
great	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
malicious	O
a	O
Treason	O
as	O
ever	O
could	O
be	O
imagined	O
;	O
but	O
especially	O
when	O
considered	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
against	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Prince	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
this	O
Nation	O
,	O
with	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
intent	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
done	O
only	O
to	O
exasperate	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
Sedition	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
amongst	O
us	O
;	O
therefore	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
what	O
the	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
sworn	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
printed	O
the	O
Libels	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
must	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
otherwise	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
withdrawn	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
William	O
Anderton	O
,	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
why	O
Sentence	O
should	O
not	O
pass	O
upon	O
him	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
:	O
He	O
read	O
a	O
Petition	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
please	O
to	O
allow	O
him	O
Counsel	O
,	O
to	O
plead	O
to	O
a	O
point	O
of	O
Law	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
of	O
Law	O
did	O
arise	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
longer	O
time	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Angell	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
was	O
Read	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
one	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
Convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
the	O
fifth	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
stole	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
for	O
a	O
Cravat	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Angell	O
Rolph	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Grace	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
receive	O
from	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Dempsey	O
and	O
Edward	O
Boyce	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
harbour	O
,	O
comfort	O
and	O
maintain	O
her	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
answer	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Whereas	O
in	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Spadings	I-pers
alias	O
Parker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Abigail	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
she	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
make	O
manifest	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
was	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Husband	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Born	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Presentment	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
at	O
the	O
Session	O
.	O
Against	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
.	O
Against	O
Mary	B-pers
Lowes	I-pers
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Ax	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
.	O
Against	O
the	O
Butchers	O
in	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
their	O
small	O
meat	O
there	O
.	O
Against	O
the	O
Singers	O
and	O
Sellers	O
of	O
Ballads	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Liberties	O
hereof	O
Against	O
all	O
Lotteries	O
and	O
Unlawful	O
Gaming	O
houses	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
.	O
Against	O
all	O
Taverns	O
and	O
Alehouses	O
that	O
entertain	O
Persons	O
on	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
keep	O
their	O
Doors	O
open	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
16	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Granger	O
,	O
Isabella	O
Clark	O
,	O
Ann	O
Harris	O
,	O
Esther	O
King	O
,	O
John	O
Webb	O
,	O
Richard	O
Merrick	O
,	O
Morris	O
Moor	O
,	O
Richard	O
Whitworth	O
,	O
William	O
Clement	O
,	O
William	O
Nixon	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Kent	O
,	O
John	O
Barker	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Stitch	O
,	O
John	O
Randall	O
,	O
John	O
Dudley	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Anderton	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Clark	O
,	O
Ann	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
Esther	O
King	O
,	O
Respited	O
after	O
Judgement	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
Ann	O
Forster	O
,	O
Mary	O
Stephens	O
,	O
Mary	O
Underwood	O
,	O
J	O
-	O
B	O
-	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Starr	O
alias	O
Osborn	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Sarner	O
,	O
John	O
earl	O
,	O
Mary	O
Allen	O
,	O
Mary	O
Pead	O
,	O
Mary	O
Harris	O
,	O
Ann	O
Bayley	O
,	O
Mary	O
May	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cox	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Adams	O
,	O
Susanna	O
Phillips	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
C-	O
,	O
John	O
Jennings	O
,	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
Morris	O
Morris	O
,	O
Maudlin	O
Bevell	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Miller	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Whitworth	O
,	O
and	O
Prudence	O
Sanders	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
John	O
Hudson	O
,	O
William	O
Brathwait	O
,	O
Ambrose	O
Whaley	O
,	O
John	O
Evans	O
,	O
Andrew	O
Evans	O
,	O
John	O
Bowman	O
,	O
Deveraux	O
Beasant	O
,	O
Bryant	O
Lamb	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Paddison	O
,	O
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
1	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hudson	O
Thomas	O
Carter	O
and	O
Ralph	O
Nichols	O
Respited	O
from	O
Burning	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesties	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Fined	O
John	O
Abbot	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Richard	O
Hurt	O
Fined	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
they	O
perform	O
it	O
.	O
Alice	O
Randall	O
Fined	O
20l	O
.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Ely	O
20l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
they	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Bridget	O
Laytus	O
Fined	O
200l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
of	O
William	O
Canning	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
for	O
publishing	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Declaration	O
are	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Ensuing	O
Sessions	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
begin	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
next	O
,	O
by	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
