TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Kings	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HUMPHRY	B-pers
EDWIN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rome	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Whester	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
John	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Warpool	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Worell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shellie	I-pers
Caleb	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Houting	I-pers
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
Brion	B-pers
Turberville	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Lobb	I-pers
James	B-pers
Carkwick	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
John	B-pers
Maird	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
of	O
London	O
Gent	O
.	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
that	O
Trade	O
in	O
Wilson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Species	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
That	O
Wilson	O
owned	O
that	O
Hill	O
had	O
wrought	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
That	O
Wilson	O
had	O
borrowed	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
27	O
s.	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
him	O
more	O
on	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
more	O
good	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
them	O
make	O
false	O
Money	O
.	O
At	O
another	O
time	O
Hill	O
borrowed	O
30	O
s.	O
of	O
good	O
Money	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
engage	O
to	O
furnish	O
them	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
get	O
above	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shortly	O
inrich	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
their	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
rather	O
Coin	O
Dutch	O
Money	O
than	O
English	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
less	O
dangerous	O
and	O
more	O
profitable	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
and	O
one	O
Davis	O
were	O
so	O
ingenious	O
in	O
Making	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
scarcely	O
be	O
perceived	O
from	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
contradict	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
pretending	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
not	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
the	O
Crime	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
feloniously	O
Choaking	O
and	O
Strangling	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
,	O
being	O
her	O
Landlord	O
and	O
Landlady	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
entred	O
her	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
enquiring	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
Still-born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
:	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
foot	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
imputed	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
death	O
to	O
a	O
fright	O
she	O
had	O
by	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
provision	O
for	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
heard	O
below	O
stairs	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
Noise	O
there	O
,	O
her	O
Landlord	O
keeping	O
a	O
Tin-Shop	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
days	O
before	O
bespoke	O
a	O
Midwife	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
declared	O
she	O
had	O
engaged	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
really	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
ill	O
design	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
expose	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
the	O
Scandal	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Chany	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burdet	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Doulas	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Linen	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
drop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bevin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hobs	I-pers
Widow	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Hobs	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
Visit	O
a	O
sick	O
Relation	O
,	O
and	O
entrusting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
discoverd	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Houndsman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
with	O
the	O
Barrel	O
of	O
a	O
Musket	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Blow	O
given	O
,	O
which	O
struck	O
down	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
several	O
other	O
blows	O
;	O
That	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
none	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
wore	O
a	O
Souldier	O
s	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Musket-barrel	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Stock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
broken	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
lace	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
perceive	O
his	O
face	O
:	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
who	O
first	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisonerin	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
excessive	O
Drinking	O
upon	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
coming	O
home	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
which	O
seem	O
'd	O
no	O
ways	O
to	O
extenuate	O
his	O
Crime	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Evan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
13	O
Holland	O
Hankerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Night-Rail	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entered	O
Evans	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
hold	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherly	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
about	O
Michaelmas-day	O
Last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Ship-yard	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
,	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Pholix	B-pers
Tayte	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Baldwin	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
diaper	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
perceived	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
jump	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pepperin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
Butter	O
and	O
Waters	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Marybone	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
coloured	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Bundle	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
about	O
26	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
Marsh	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
between	O
the	O
Lord	B-place
Mayor	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Banqueting-House	I-place
and	O
Tyburn	B-place
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
meeting	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
riding	O
on	O
Marsh	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
escaped	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
towards	O
Bow	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
calling	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
hotly	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
discharged	O
a	O
Pistol	O
or	O
Musquetoon	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
quitting	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watermen	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
were	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
borrowed	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
one	O
Price	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hardin	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Shopkeeper	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
suffering	O
of	O
Squibs	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
submitted	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
fined	O
40	O
Shillings	O
:	O
As	O
was	O
also	O
Henry	B-pers
Emet	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
and	O
Buckley	B-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
likewise	O
submitted	O
,	O
were	O
fined	O
40	O
Shillings	O
each	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bren	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
throwing	O
of	O
Squibs	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
thrown	O
from	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
into	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
submitting	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
fined	O
a	O
Noble	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
alias	O
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
;	O
The	O
first	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
at	O
Lamb's-Chappel	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Priestgrove	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
two	O
Testificates	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
were	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Rogers	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
lying	O
in	O
Childbed	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
Rogers	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
some	O
Clouts	O
to	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
value	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cockrell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bailly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
non	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bailly	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bonn	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Quilt	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
two	O
Pillows	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Brokers	O
Shops	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
discovered	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
her	O
Commitment	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bon	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Plush	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
63	O
yards	O
of	O
Prunell	O
,	O
and	O
34	O
pounds	O
of	O
Grogram	O
Yarn	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
two	O
Pawnbrokers	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Good	I-pers
pawn	O
'd	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
William	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
occasion	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
Abroad	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
Chamber	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
at	O
her	O
being	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
what	O
Goldsmith	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Cup	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
exchange	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
's	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
but	O
Williams	O
declared	O
that	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
were	O
very	O
Honest	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
Copper	O
Furnace	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Hempen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Sheets	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
but	O
dropt	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Cheating	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
More	I-pers
of	O
3	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
Counterfeit	O
Letters	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
alias	O
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
Bar	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Coach	O
seat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mosly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
More	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
4	O
slit	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
whole	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Fortiscue	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
8	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
20	O
Shillings	O
in	O
the	O
Species	O
of	O
Sixpences	O
of	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Aderly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
offering	O
5	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Fearne	I-pers
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Aderly	O
uttered	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Russel	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
Aderly	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
Russel	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
and	O
Aderly	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Kenedy	I-pers
Widow	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Trunk	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Maid	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Absence	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rot	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ockey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hanwel	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
a	O
Cart	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cart	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Custody	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
discovered	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Katharine	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Sable	O
Tippet	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Muff	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blackway	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
and	O
carry	O
off	O
his	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
:	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
taken	O
within	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
having	O
broke	O
a	O
Glass	O
Window	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
entred	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
stript	O
her	O
self	O
naked	O
;	O
and	O
Lambeth	O
was	O
seized	O
without	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
Smith	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
Lambeth	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
45	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shortditch	I-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rebeka	B-pers
Knox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Copper	O
Kettle	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
on	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Wicket	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
between	O
London	O
and	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Kensington	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rid	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
threatned	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perceiving	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
rid	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
falling	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
on	O
foot	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
being	O
known	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
there	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
was	O
under	O
Cure	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterward	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Strutt	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
Two	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
two	O
blew	O
Shifts	O
and	O
some	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dirikson	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Freemly	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doddy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Clench	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clench	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Doddy	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
seize	O
the	O
first	O
Booty	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
they	O
met	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
from	O
whom	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Sheet	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
altogether	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
only	O
seemed	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Crimes	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
jointly	O
with	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
:	O
one	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Wey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
8	O
Pistols	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
44	O
Guineas	O
Value	O
22	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
56	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
said	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
3	O
Pound	O
18	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Moneys	O
Numbered	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Chamberlain	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Lodged	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
bed	O
as	O
usually	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
aways	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Rooms	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
,	O
who	O
next	O
Morning	O
miss	O
'd	O
their	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Breeches	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
staircase	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Felonies	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Panker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
of	O
one	O
Linen	O
Bag	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
15	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
's	O
Numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
at	O
Guild-hall	B-place
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
not	O
pickt	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
search	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
offered	O
12	O
Guineas	O
to	O
Stifle	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hockwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
3	O
Coloured	O
Aprons	O
,	O
6	O
Muslin	O
Pinners	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Linen	O
Curtains	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
one	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
creep	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
them	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
seized	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sibel	B-pers
Bursman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
falsly	O
counterfeited	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
Last	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
a	O
Seaman	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
Cheat	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
,	O
Subjects	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jean	B-pers
Carrel	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carrel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Siffton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Buffy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Margret	B-pers
Crafton	I-pers
Widow	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodie	O
's	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murrall	I-pers
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wooten	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Finn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
of	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
five	O
Exchequer-bills	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
;	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
of	O
a	O
Pocket-handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pulling	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
drop	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
owned	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Night-tail	O
value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
16	O
l.	O
in	O
MoneyNumbred	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Spurrier	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Watkison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Genting	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Callico	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Segar	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
Spinster	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Sable	O
Tippet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Mohair	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
Abroad	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
joyntly	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
Ann	B-pers
Whitle	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
referring	O
and	O
abetting	O
Segar	O
and	O
Potter	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
for	O
Robbers	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
positively	O
Sworn	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
Segar	O
and	O
Potter	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Whitle	O
of	O
Fellony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Segar	O
,	O
Potter	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whitle	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Witty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
Bengal	O
Bag	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Bason	O
value	O
:	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Box	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
disposed	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
returning	O
from	O
Church	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
their	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
upon	O
their	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
offered	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
it	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
of	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barncluff	I-pers
alias	O
Rives	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Norcoat	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Rives	I-pers
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
dozen	O
of	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
five	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
eight	O
other	O
Rings	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
fifteen	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
twenty	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooebuckles	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
Consultations	O
,	O
several	O
Consultations	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
and	O
at	O
London	O
among	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
perpetrate	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
concluded	O
to	O
be	O
performed	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Peace	O
was	O
proclaim	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
facilitating	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Rives	O
inticed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
abroad	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Solemnity	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
Elizabeth	O
Barncluf	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber-door	O
and	O
Trunk	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
both	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
parted	O
among	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
Bundles	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
their	O
Laps	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	O
Barncluf	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Norcoat	O
and	O
John	O
Rives	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
as	O
Accessories	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Barncluff	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Norcoat	O
,	O
Rives	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Tailer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Allen	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
5	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
commanded	O
him	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alighting	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
followed	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knowing	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
Lett	O
the	O
same	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
2	O
Razors	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Razor-case	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
Hone	O
tipt	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
alias	O
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ludington	I-pers
Widow	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
another	O
Ring	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Midleton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sirat	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Aderton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
one	O
floured	O
Lutestring	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
one	O
Sarsenet	O
Hood	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
was	O
fined	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
for	O
making	O
and	O
selling	O
of	O
Squibs	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
fined	O
40	O
s.	O
for	O
suffering	O
Squibs	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
fined	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
fined	O
10	O
Groats	O
on	O
the	O
like	O
Account	O
.	O
Robert	O
Clark	O
was	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Aderly	O
was	O
fined	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
,	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
18	O
.	O
William	O
Wilson	O
John	O
Hill	O
Charles	O
Harding	O
Mary	O
Segar	O
Mary	O
Potter	O
Richard	O
Dounes	O
William	O
Holiday	O
Thomas	O
Shelly	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
Edward	O
Weeks	O
James	O
Freemly	O
Thomas	O
Dody	O
John	O
Shorter	O
Elizabeth	O
Barncluf	O
John	O
Norcoat	O
John	O
Rives	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
and	O
William	O
Johnson	O
.	O
The	O
four	O
Women	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
:	O
Mary	O
Segar	O
,	O
Mary	O
Potter	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Rives	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
Henry	O
Gordon	O
Grace	O
Chinay	O
Mary	O
Cope	O
Rebecca	O
Hatch	O
Margaret	O
Adams	O
Mary	O
Spurrier	O
--	O
-	O
Betty	O
John	O
Mosly	O
John	O
Williams	O
Margaret	O
Bevin	O
Elizabeth	O
More	O
Prudence	O
Brooks	O
Ann	O
Holland	O
Susan	O
Windham	O
Ann	O
Witty	O
Margaret	O
Midleton	O
Susan	O
Wiseman	O
Isabella	O
Dickens	O
Ann	O
Whitle	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
William	O
Perry	O
Jane	O
Vaughan	O
Mary	O
Bailly	O
Thomas	O
Huggins	O
William	O
Ockey	O
Elizabeth	O
Murray	O
And	O
Elizabeth	O
Pepperin	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Robert	O
Mitchell	O
William	O
Hudson	O
Phelix	O
Tait	O
Thomas	O
Nichols	O
Thomas	O
Morgan	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
by	O
J.	O
D.	O
for	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
R.	O
Baldwin	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
England	O
both	O
Ecclesiastical	O
and	O
Civil	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
earliest	O
Accounts	O
of	O
Time	O
to	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
majesty	O
King	O
William	O
III	O
.	O
Taken	O
from	O
the	O
most	O
Antient	O
Records	O
,	O
Manuscripts	O
and	O
Historians	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
,	O
and	O
Memorials	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
both	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Foundations	O
of	O
the	O
Noted	O
Monasteries	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Universities	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
By	O
James	O
Tyrcel	O
Esq	O
;	O
Fol	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
l.	O
A	O
New	O
History	O
of	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Writers	O
:	O
Containing	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Authors	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Testament	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Lives	O
and	O
Writings	O
of	O
the	O
Primitive	O
Fathers	O
;	O
An	O
Abridgment	O
and	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
Works	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
compenditious	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Councils	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Written	O
in	O
French	O
by	O
Lewis	O
Ellies	O
du	O
Pin	O
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
the	O
Sorbon	O
.	O
In	O
7	O
Vol	O
.	O
Fol	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
A	O
Detection	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
during	O
the	O
4	O
last	O
Reigns	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Interregnum	O
;	O
consisting	O
of	O
private	O
Memoirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
With	O
Observations	O
and	O
Reflections	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Appendix	O
discovering	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
many	O
Secrets	O
never	O
before	O
made	O
publick	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
more	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Civil	O
Wars	O
in	O
England	O
than	O
has	O
yet	O
been	O
given	O
.	O
By	O
Rog	O
.	O
Coke	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
very	O
much	O
corrected	O
with	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
.	O
Printed	O
on	O
a	O
New	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
better	O
Paper	O
than	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
.	O
Price	O
7	O
s.	O
An	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
Sir	O
Walter	O
Raleigh	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
in	O
5	O
books	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Creation	O
to	O
Abraham	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
From	O
Abraham	O
to	O
the	O
Destruction	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
of	O
Solomon	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Destruction	O
of	O
Jerusalem	O
to	O
Philip	O
of	O
Macedon	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
From	O
Philip	O
of	O
Macedon	O
to	O
the	O
Race	O
of	O
Antigonus	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
establishment	O
of	O
Alexander	O
until	O
the	O
Conquest	O
of	O
Asia	O
and	O
Macedon	O
by	O
the	O
Romans	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
particular	O
Chapters	O
are	O
succinctly	O
abridg	O
'd	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Method	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
larger	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
his	O
Premonition	O
to	O
Princes	O
.	O
Price	O
5s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
An	O
essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Mankind	O
in	O
Matters	O
of	O
Religion	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Reasons	O
in	O
particular	O
for	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
not	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Test	O
but	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Churches	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
General	O
Naturalization	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
Postscript	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Convocation	O
man	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Joannis	O
Clerici	O
Ars	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
in	O
qua	O
ad	O
Studia	O
Linguarum	O
Latiniae	O
,	O
Graecae	O
,	O
&	O
Hebraicae	O
via	O
munitur	O
;	O
Veterumque	O
emendandorum	O
,	O
&	O
Spuriorum	O
Scriptorum	O
a	O
Genuinis	O
dignoscendorum	O
ratio	O
traditur	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
Vol	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Speedy	O
Method	O
of	O
attaining	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
containing	O
such	O
Precepts	O
as	O
are	O
common	O
to	O
all	O
Languages	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
,	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
Leanest	O
Capacites	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
those	O
of	O
riper	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
Child	O
that	O
can	O
read	O
English	O
,	O
may	O
by	O
this	O
Method	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
arrive	O
at	O
a	O
greater	O
degree	O
of	O
Knowledg	O
than	O
is	O
usually	O
attain	O
'd	O
after	O
several	O
years	O
Drudgery	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
Road	O
.	O
Most	O
Logical	O
Terms	O
being	O
in	O
this	O
Treatise	O
also	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Reasoning	O
may	O
be	O
perfectly	O
learn	O
'd	O
without	O
too	O
much	O
further	O
trouble	O
.	O
By	O
A	O
.	O
Lane	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
:	O
A	O
Treatise	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
publick	O
.	O
By	O
Marius	O
D'Assigny	O
B.	O
D.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Scotland	O
's	O
Sovereignty	O
affected	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Dispute	O
concerning	O
Homage	O
,	O
against	O
those	O
who	O
maintain	O
that	O
Scotland	O
is	O
a	O
Fee	O
Liege	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Scots	O
owes	O
Homage	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Tho	O
.	O
Craig	O
.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
Latin	O
Manuscript	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preface	O
containing	O
a	O
Confutation	O
of	O
that	O
Homage	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
performed	O
by	O
Malcolm	O
III	O
.	O
to	O
Edward	O
the	O
Confessor	O
,	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Present	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
as	O
to	O
Coin	O
and	O
publick	O
Charges	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
Parts	O
.	O
Treating	O
of	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Ways	O
and	O
Means	O
to	O
procure	O
it	O
;	O
of	O
Raising	O
its	O
Value	O
,	O
against	O
which	O
the	O
opposite	O
Prejudices	O
,	O
as	O
injurious	O
to	O
King	O
,	O
Parliament	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
,	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lock	O
's	O
chief	O
Positions	O
,	O
are	O
refuted	O
by	O
demonstrable	O
Reason	O
and	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Hodges	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Supplement	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
Short-hand	O
yet	O
shorter	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-writing	O
advanced	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
swift	O
,	O
easy	O
,	O
regular	O
,	O
and	O
natural	O
Method	O
than	O
hitherto	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Ridpath	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Funds	O
of	O
the	O
Million-Act	O
,	O
Lottery-Act	O
,	O
and	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Briscoe	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Advice	O
to	O
the	O
Young	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Reasonableness	O
and	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Conversion	O
,	O
in	O
several	O
Sermons	O
on	O
Eccles	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Price	O
2.	O
s.	O
--	O
--	O
The	O
Groans	O
of	O
a	O
Saint	O
under	O
the	O
Burden	O
of	O
a	O
mortal	O
Body	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Belcher	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
,	O
from	O
Cor	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
--	O
-	O
Hymns	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
the	O
Sufferings	O
of	O
our	O
Blessed	O
Saviour	O
Jesus	O
Christ	O
,	O
compos	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Celebration	O
of	O
his	O
holy	O
Supper	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
--	O
-	O
A	O
Poem	O
to	O
the	O
memory	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Timothy	O
Cruso	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
These	O
4	O
by	O
Joseph	O
Stennet	O
.	O
Emblems	O
by	O
Fra	O
.	O
Quarles	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Hieroglyphicks	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
Cuts	O
being	O
newly	O
illuminated	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
,	O
illustrated	O
with	O
40	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Price	O
1.	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Artamenes	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Grand	O
Cyrus	O
,	O
that	O
famous	O
Romance	O
.	O
In	O
10	O
Books	O
.	O
By	O
Mons	O
.	O
De	O
Saudary	O
.	O
English	O
'd	O
by	O
F.	O
G.	O
Adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
various	O
Sculptures	O
,	O
Price	O
25	O
s.	O
Chamberlen	O
's	O
Midwifery	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Rutherford	O
's	O
Letters	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Fulfilling	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
for	O
confirming	O
Believers	O
,	O
and	O
convincing	O
Atheists	O
,	O
with	O
rare	O
Histories	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
.	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
An	O
Exposition	O
with	O
practical	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Job	O
:	O
By	O
Alexander	O
Nisbet	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Directory	O
of	O
Prayer	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Commentary	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
Psalm	O
.	O
By	O
R.	O
Campel	O
.	O
A	O
Help	O
to	O
Prayer	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Direction	O
how	O
to	O
perform	O
that	O
holy	O
Duty	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
well	O
pleasing	O
to	O
God	O
.	O
With	O
Prayers	O
for	O
Morning	O
and	O
Evening	O
.	O
--	O
-	O
An	O
Assize	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
at	O
St.	O
Edmunsbury	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Packe	O
Esq	O
;	O
High	O
Sheriff	O
of	O
the	O
County	O
,	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
--	O
-	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
H.	O
Edwin	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
1697	O
.	O
These	O
3	O
by	O
Tho	O
.	O
Knaggs	O
M.	O
A.	O
Chaplain	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Ford	O
,	O
Earl	O
of	O
Tankerville	O
.	O
Gaging	O
made	O
easy	O
.	O
The	O
Providences	O
of	O
God	O
towards	O
this	O
Nation	O
in	O
Introducing	O
the	O
True	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
defence	O
of	O
that	O
preserving	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
their	O
Rights	O
and	O
liberties	O
,	O
while	O
other	O
Nations	O
were	O
ravish	O
'd	O
of	O
theirs	O
,	O
as	O
our	O
Counsellors	O
desig	O
'd	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Slingsby	O
Bethel	O
Esq	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
speedily	O
pulish	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
complete	O
History	O
of	O
Europe	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
thereof	O
,	O
Civil	O
and	O
Military	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Treaty	O
of	O
Nimeguen	O
,	O
1678	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
at	O
Riswick	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
included	O
the	O
Preliminaries	O
and	O
Articles	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
the	O
Infringements	O
thereof	O
,	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Confederacy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Revolution	O
of	O
England	O
&	O
c	O
With	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Actions	O
by	O
Sea	O
and	O
Land	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Steps	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
this	O
General	O
Peace	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
Offers	O
thereof	O
after	O
the	O
Battel	O
of	O
La	O
Hague	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
happy	O
Conclusion	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
divers	O
Original	O
Papers	O
and	O
Memoirs	O
never	O
before	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
concern	O
'd	O
therein	O
;	O
and	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
exact	O
Journal	O
of	O
Affairs	O
for	O
above	O
these	O
20	O
Years	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Introduction	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
before	O
the	O
Treaty	O
of	O
Nimeguen	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Advances	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
obtaining	O
an	O
Universal	O
Monarchy	O
.	O
In	O
8o	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Harris	O
and	O
John	O
Nicholson	O
in	O
Little-Britain	O
;	O
and	O
Andr	O
.	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
Whereas	O
Ann	O
Laurence	O
(	O
of	O
middle	O
Stature	O
,	O
about	O
24	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
fresh	O
Colour	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
Evil-mark	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
Arm	O
below	O
her	O
elbow	O
,	O
is	O
near	O
Kinswoman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alder	O
at	O
the	O
blew	O
Boar-Inn	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
last	O
Bartholomew	O
and	O
Southwark	O
Fairs	O
with	O
Toys	O
)	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Machel	O
's	O
in	O
Salmon	O
Court	O
on	O
Bread-street	O
Hill	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
3d	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
with	O
her	O
five	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
whosoever	O
secures	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
gives	O
Notice	O
to	O
M.	O
Machel	O
at	O
the	O
Post-boy	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
gate	O
of	O
the	O
General	O
Post-Office	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
shall	O
have	O
ten	O
shillings	O
Reward	O
.	O
