TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
1697	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HUMPHRY	B-pers
EDWIN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smartfort	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burd	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thurrogood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
Cave	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gunson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Bennet	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wyld	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
William	B-pers
Silcoks	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
Marmaduke	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pedly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Tomlen	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Indian	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Tomlen	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Hoskins	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
suddenly	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
dropt	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
saw	O
Hoskins	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hutcheson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
laced	O
Head-dress	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Head-dress	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Seamstresses	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Peter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Wilmot	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Jelly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
laced	O
Headdress	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
another	O
Head-dress	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wey	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Band-box	O
through	O
Little	B-place
Lombard	I-place
street	I-place
about	O
six	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
standing	O
up	O
against	O
her	O
whilst	O
some	O
others	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Band-box	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
escaped	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lay	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
returned	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Country	O
by	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Inn	O
on	O
Holborn-bridge	O
,	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
and	O
suddenly	O
after	O
mis	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
several	O
Shops	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Goods	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
stop	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
10	O
dozen	O
of	O
the	O
Gloves	O
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
Young-man	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
fully	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
180	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Laplow	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Swithens	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Patrick	B-pers
Oliphant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pattens	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Laplow	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Wilson	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Wilson	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Laplow	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Wilson	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Laplow	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Wilson	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
when	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Laplow	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
lodged	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
took	O
occassion	O
to	O
rifle	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wilson	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
part	O
discoveredelsewhere	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elenor	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Trout	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
lookt	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
declared	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
touch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
at	O
High-gate	O
;	O
and	O
withal	O
,	O
abundance	O
of	O
substantial	O
People	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Brenant	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Peppet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
when	O
she	O
nor	O
none	O
else	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
carryd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
perceived	O
by	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Milman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
nigh	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
one	O
Inch	O
in	O
breadth	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
being	O
Drinking	O
together	O
,	O
some	O
Difference	O
hapned	O
about	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
provocation	O
than	O
a	O
Lye	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
other	O
provocation	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Will-church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Willen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
280	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shaksby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hampshire	I-pers
,	O
one	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
Notice	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
seized	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Horse	O
stole	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
lane	O
in	O
his	O
Passage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
his	O
Head	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
his	O
Tail	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
kickt	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
step	O
over	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
unexpectedly	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
:	O
Which	O
Defence	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
make	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
Proof	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Bridle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Helens	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
and	O
[	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
]	I-pers
Hornby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-church	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Honner	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Honner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Thread-Stocking	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Duburgy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
as	O
Aiding	O
,	O
Abetting	O
,	O
and	O
Assisting	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mallony	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Duburgy	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Coller-bone	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
deep	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
altogether	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Wine	O
and	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
hapned	O
between	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Duburgy	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
have	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
another	O
naked	O
Sword	O
betwixt	O
his	O
Legs	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
at	O
Table	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
and	O
Duburgy	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
suddenly	O
after	O
taken	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Understanding	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
between	O
Duburgy	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Provocation	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
:	O
and	O
there	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Duburgy	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cheader	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
,	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Gayat	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
Muslen	O
Head-dress	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
another	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
when	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
leaving	O
Fire	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
where	O
the	O
Children	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
escaped	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
crying	O
out	O
Fire	O
,	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
it	O
was	O
extinguished	O
without	O
doing	O
any	O
damage	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
searcht	O
after	O
,	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Foule	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spelman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Landress	O
;	O
had	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
occasion	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
missed	O
several	O
Sums	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
procured	O
two	O
Persons	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
wait	O
in	O
private	O
Places	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
her	O
open	O
the	O
Closet-door	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
seized	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
with	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
re-delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
seeming	O
Trust	O
reposed	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
unlocking	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
door	O
in	O
an	O
upper	O
Chamber	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisius	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Halibrand	B-pers
Hording	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
deep	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
and	O
as	O
coming	O
away	O
,	O
stopt	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Palm	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
having	O
occasion	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
stiff	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
defect	O
in	O
the	O
Hinges	O
or	O
Latch	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
unknown	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
supposed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Company	O
had	O
kept	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
some	O
Words	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
Companies	O
,	O
and	O
terminated	O
at	O
last	O
in	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
several	O
Passes	O
were	O
made	O
,	O
one	O
Party	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
be	O
standing	O
opposite	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
were	O
engaged	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Wound	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
Accident	O
having	O
happen	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
sudden	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Burges	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Innocency	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Young	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Croger	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Gloves	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
liking	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
desired	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
search	O
for	O
,	O
another	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
presently	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Apron	O
as	O
a	O
Pledg	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
known	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Mees	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Frontyn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cellar	O
at	O
Whitehall	B-place
,	O
10	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Claret	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
10	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Cherry	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Pint-pots	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
the	O
Pewter	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
some	O
Quantities	O
of	O
the	O
Wines	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
confessed	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
at	O
their	O
Trial	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Grahams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Jane	B-pers
Shudbrook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
two	O
Past-board	O
Boxes	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
some	O
Head-dresses	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Shudbrook	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
the	O
Maid	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
suddenly	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
Boxes	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
closely	O
pursued	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Dancy	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hobbard	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
murder	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
long	O
and	O
8	O
deep	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
corner	O
of	O
Exeter-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
where	O
calling	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
having	O
notice	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dancy	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Followers	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dancy	O
have	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
re-entring	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Dancy	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
Follower	O
immediately	O
disarmed	O
Mr.	O
Dancy	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
some	O
time	O
strugling	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
taking	O
the	O
Alarm	O
,	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
amongst	O
them	O
Harding	O
;	O
and	O
pushing	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
slashing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
their	O
Escapes	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
against	O
Harding	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
Hobbard	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Harding	O
Swore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
heard	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
at	O
Chatham	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
many	O
Broils	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
worst	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Course	O
of	O
Evidence	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
Harding	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
affect	O
Mr.	O
Dancy	O
either	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
opposing	O
of	O
the	O
putting	O
the	O
Writ	O
in	O
execution	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
killing	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Harding	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dunval	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Mantua-Gown	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Christ-church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Collason	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
9	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Ely	O
;	O
some	O
Stockins	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Climpson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Grant	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Ely	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
Webster	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
an	O
opportunity	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Rooms	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
Grant	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
Webster	O
's	O
Name	O
:	O
upon	O
rifling	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Grant	O
deserted	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
Webster	O
owned	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plainly	O
against	O
Grant	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Webster	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Grant	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Webster	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Great	I-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Staines	I-place
,	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Billingsly	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Princes	O
Mettle	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
two	O
Keys	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	O
Edmonds	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Bridgwater	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
Sorrel	O
Gelding	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
Gelding	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Horses	O
being	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Grounds	O
,	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
off	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
further	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
Information	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
on	O
the	O
Sorrel	O
Gelding	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
last	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
fellow	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
:	O
It	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
not	O
in	O
any	O
danger	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
pieces	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
and	O
having	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Sorrel	O
Horse	O
on	O
a	O
Swap	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Little-Elfort	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	I-place
of	I-place
Essex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
Elbow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchers	I-place
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
Travelling	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
crossing	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
rode	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Bruise	O
:	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
complained	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Bruise	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
vomited	O
above	O
a	O
Gallon	O
of	O
blood	O
:	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
opened	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bruise	O
had	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Blood	O
to	O
congeal	O
at	O
his	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
its	O
due	O
Circulation	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
which	O
might	O
probably	O
sooner	O
have	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
his	O
Vomiting	O
and	O
Purging	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
giving	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Bruise	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
withal	O
one	O
who	O
rid	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
the	O
Bruise	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
,	O
declared	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
giving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Truelove	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Kettle	O
into	O
a	O
Sack	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Skillington	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edgworth	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
swapt	O
him	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Possession	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Midlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Red	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
next	O
Pay-day	O
:	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
then	O
have	O
it	O
or	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
very	O
threatning	O
Words	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
obliged	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Provocation	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
as	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Abetting	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Male	O
infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
by	O
placing	O
the	O
Child	O
under	O
two	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
smothered	O
,	O
and	O
languished	O
by	O
the	O
Bruise	O
to	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
when	O
it	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Churchwardens	O
and	O
Overseers	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Thompson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Lying-in	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
Griffeth	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
Lying	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
Thompson	O
down	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
pushing	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
met	O
Thompson	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
after	O
her	O
big	O
Belly	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
had	O
none	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
satisfying	O
,	O
they	O
entered	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
observed	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
being	O
newly	O
Delivered	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
all	O
the	O
Room	O
over	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
last	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
two	O
Bolsters	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
its	O
Back	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
someprovision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
hid	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
conceal	O
her	O
Shame	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
lived	O
above	O
24	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Baptized	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
Delivered	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
upon	O
these	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hannoway	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Margret	B-pers
Pour	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Burrous	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wooton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Henn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
Pocket-book	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
5	O
Exchequer-Bills	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
there	O
but	O
them	O
two	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
deserted	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
having	O
the	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sacksford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Slaymaker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
Farriers	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Arnaut	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
entred	O
the	O
Cabin	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
and	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
secretly	O
taking	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hatchet	I-pers
two	O
Exchequer-Bills	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
just	O
received	O
his	O
Pay	O
as	O
a	O
Mariner	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bills	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
Holmes	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
Hitchcock	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Gang	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Hitchcock	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
H	O
G	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
her	O
Husband	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
offered	O
false	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
;	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
having	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
accordingly	O
at	O
their	O
next	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
him	O
9	O
false	O
Shillings	O
for	O
6	O
good	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
5	O
or	O
10	O
l.	O
more	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
care	O
how	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Counterfeit	O
money	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
undone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Necessity	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
a	O
false	O
Shilling	O
,	O
some	O
Mettle	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
that	O
hellish	O
Trade	O
were	O
found	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
false	O
Money	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Persons	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Instruments	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Black-friers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
6	O
s.	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
for	O
5	O
of	O
good	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
greater	O
Quantities	O
proportionably	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
false	O
Money	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Mettle	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Charcoal-fire	O
just	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Tools	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seized	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
actually	O
coin	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
fled	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
impeach	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Backhurst	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
50	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
lesser	O
Quantities	O
of	O
good	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
false	O
Money	O
from	O
one	O
Underwood	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
she	O
got	O
nothing	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
therefore	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Underwoods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
divers	O
Parcels	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
good	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
question	O
'd	O
on	O
such	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
:	O
and	O
Malice	O
seeming	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hanna	B-pers
Hutt	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
20	O
false	O
Shillings	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
rather	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Malice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Bucknall	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Hinkly	I-pers
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Chamberlain	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodged	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Trunk	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
lighted	O
him	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
under	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Trunk	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
his	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
Trunk	O
was	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Gallery	O
fronting	O
his	O
Chamber	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
strew	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
some	O
other	O
Rooms	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
when	O
upon	O
occasion	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Symons	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
:	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Jelly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
laced	O
Headdress	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wey	I-pers
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
of	O
Harlington	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
Sheep	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Sheep	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
cut	O
in	O
Quarters	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
hollow	O
Tree	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
got	O
some	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
such	O
as	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
Father	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
10	O
Ducks	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cow-house	O
with	O
the	O
Ducks	O
put	O
up	O
into	O
two	O
Bags	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
an	O
open	O
Out-house	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Necessity	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Scales	I-pers
,	O
Israel	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Niblet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Dandy	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Arundel	B-pers
Walding	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
6	O
Flaxen	O
Shirts	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
first	O
Three	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
Dandy	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Possession	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
for	O
more	O
Wine	O
,	O
forwhich	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
did	O
known	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
prosecuted	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
familiar	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rome	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Monky	I-pers
Davy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
Covering	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
having	O
entred	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
open	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
being	O
above	O
it	O
but	O
those	O
below	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
Monky	O
,	O
Davy	O
was	O
seized	O
:	O
and	O
some	O
going	O
up	O
afterwards	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
also	O
seized	O
;	O
yet	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
Women	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
over-powering	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
escaped	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
condemned	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
was	O
detained	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bartram	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
one	O
Trunk	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
24	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Constance	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Worell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
6	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
off	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
given	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
discovered	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
2	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Meal	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Sacks	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
Orford	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hanmore	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
of	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haycock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Alice	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Sutes	O
of	O
Head-cloths	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hurford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pure	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
none	O
having	O
been	O
above	O
but	O
them	O
two	O
between	O
the	O
Moneys	O
being	O
seen	O
and	O
its	O
missing	O
:	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Shacksford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elia	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stowell	I-pers
of	O
Finchley	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bramly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Back-door	O
,	O
let	O
in	O
a	O
fellow	O
who	O
assisted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Migly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag-Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
defective	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Plant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
49	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Diss	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin-Breeches	O
,	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
absent	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Courtis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Glass	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
by	O
Huggins	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
her	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
no	O
way	O
affecting	O
Mason	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Huggins	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
steal	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Wooliston	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Wooliston	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
Mrs.	O
Wooliston	O
having	O
business	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
in	O
Westminster	O
was	O
shuffed	O
up	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
pickt	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
Mrs.	O
Woolision	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
Swear	O
to	O
her	O
Pockets	O
being	O
pickt	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealling	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
dollers	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
4	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
at	O
Mile-end	B-place
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
from	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
drink	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
came	O
in	O
without	O
Breeches	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
breeches	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
one	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
tied	O
to	O
a	O
Tree	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Blick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Nov.	O
100	O
pieces	O
of	O
carved	O
Wood	O
for	O
Frames	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
discovered	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
places	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
William	O
Marslin	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Shackshy	O
,	O
Ann	O
Webster	O
,	O
John	O
Edmonds	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Nichols	O
,	O
John	O
Chambers	O
,	O
George	O
Grames	O
,	O
Henry	O
Harding	O
,	O
William	O
Skillington	O
,	O
David	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Robert	O
Mannin	O
,	O
Mary	O
Huggins	O
,	O
Ann	O
Stowell	O
,	O
William	O
Riggs	O
,	O
John	O
Arnant	O
,	O
Israel	O
Bridges	O
,	O
William	O
Scales	O
,	O
John	O
Sacresford	O
,	O
William	O
Dobson	O
,	O
William	O
Hitchcock	O
,	O
James	O
Niblet	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
15	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Palnier	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Laplaw	O
,	O
Jane	O
Tomlens	O
,	O
Mary	O
Russell	O
,	O
Ann	O
Burrous	O
,	O
Grane	O
Hornby	O
,	O
Jane	O
Grant	O
,	O
kathren	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Simon	O
Dubury	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Foule	O
,	O
H	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
William	O
Skillington	O
,	O
George	O
Maxfield	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Wooten	O
,	O
David	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Alice	O
Bates	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Brenant	O
,	O
Mary	O
Cheader	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Young	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Young	O
,	O
Henry	O
Burton	O
,	O
William	O
Mees	O
,	O
John	O
Truclove	O
Francis	O
Pye	O
;	O
Joseph	O
Warner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Gregory	O
,	O
Constance	O
Green	O
,	O
Francis	O
Oxford	O
,	O
Francis	O
Cooper	O
.	O
M	O
-	O
N	O
-	O
was	O
Fined	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
opening	O
Letters	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
Exchequer-Bills	O
,	O
to	O
he	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
it	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
Fined	O
120	O
l.	O
for	O
Forging	O
3	O
Seamens	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Navy	O
Office	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Pay	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
3d	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
England	O
both	O
Ecclesiastical	O
and	O
Civil	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
earliest	O
Accounts	O
of	O
Time	O
to	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
King	O
William	O
III	O
.	O
Taken	O
from	O
the	O
most	O
Ancient	O
Records	O
,	O
Manscripts	O
and	O
Historians	O
Containing	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
,	O
and	O
Memorials	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
both	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
By	O
James	O
Tyrrel	O
Esq	O
;	O
Fol	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
l.	O
A	O
Detection	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
during	O
the	O
4	O
last	O
Reigns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Interregnum	O
;	O
consisting	O
of	O
private	O
Memoirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
many	O
Secrets	O
never	O
before	O
made	O
publick	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
more	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Civil	O
Wars	O
in	O
England	O
than	O
has	O
yet	O
been	O
given	O
.	O
By	O
Rog	O
.	O
Coke	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
7	O
s.	O
An	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
Sir	O
Walter	O
Raleigh	O
's	O
history	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
in	O
5	O
Books	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Creation	O
to	O
Abraham	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
From	O
Abraham	O
to	O
the	O
Destruction	O
the	O
Temple	O
of	O
Solomon	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Destruction	O
of	O
Jerusalem	O
to	O
Philip	O
of	O
Macedon	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
From	O
Philip	O
of	O
Macedon	O
to	O
the	O
Race	O
of	O
Antigonus	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
establishment	O
of	O
Alexander	O
until	O
the	O
Conquest	O
of	O
Asta	O
and	O
Macedon	O
by	O
the	O
Romans	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
his	O
Premonition	O
to	O
Princes	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
A	O
compleat	O
History	O
of	O
Europe	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
thereof	O
,	O
Civil	O
and	O
Military	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Treaty	O
of	O
Nimeguen	O
,	O
1675	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
at	O
Reswick	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Including	O
the	O
Articles	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Infringements	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
The	O
Turkish	O
Wars	O
;	O
The	O
forming	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
of	O
confederacy	O
;	O
The	O
Revolution	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
With	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Actions	O
by	O
Sea	O
and	O
Land	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Secret	O
Steps	O
towards	O
a	O
Peace	O
,	O
both	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
during	O
the	O
last	O
Negotiation	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
Original	O
Letters	O
,	O
Papers	O
and	O
Memoirs	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
Among	O
others	O
are	O
several	O
Letters	O
between	O
the	O
Emperor	O
,	O
Duke	O
of	O
Lorain	O
,	O
K.	O
of	O
Poland	O
,	O
Count	O
Staremburg	O
,	O
Grand	O
Vizier	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Turkish	O
Wars	O
:	O
The	O
Speeches	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Russel	O
,	O
Col.	O
Sidney	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Monmouth	O
's	O
and	O
Argile	O
's	O
Declarations	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exclusion	O
:	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
's	O
Declarations	O
:	O
The	O
Claim	O
of	O
Rights	O
for	O
England	O
and	O
Scotland	O
.	O
The	O
Negotiations	O
at	O
Reswick	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Articles	O
of	O
Peace	O
at	O
large	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
Exact	O
Journal	O
of	O
all	O
Transactions	O
for	O
above	O
these	O
20	O
Years	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Mankind	O
in	O
Matters	O
of	O
Religion	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Reasons	O
in	O
particular	O
for	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
not	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Test	O
but	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Churches	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
General	O
Naturalization	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
Postscript	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Convocation-man	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Joannis	O
Clerici	O
Ars	O
Critica	O
,	O
in	O
qua	O
ad	O
Studia	O
Linguarum	O
Latina	O
,	O
Graecae	O
,	O
&	O
Hebraicae	O
via	O
munitur	O
;	O
Veterumque	O
emendandorum	O
,	O
&	O
Spuriorum	O
Scriptorum	O
a	O
Genuinis	O
dignoscendorum	O
ratio	O
traditur	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
Vol	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Speedy	O
Method	O
of	O
attaining	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
containing	O
such	O
Precepts	O
as	O
are	O
common	O
to	O
all	O
Languages	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
what	O
is	O
more	O
peculiar	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
sitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
those	O
of	O
riper	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
Child	O
that	O
can	O
read	O
English	O
,	O
may	O
by	O
this	O
Method	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
arrive	O
at	O
a	O
greater	O
degree	O
of	O
Knowledge	O
than	O
is	O
usually	O
attain	O
'd	O
after	O
several	O
years	O
Drudgery	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
Road	O
.	O
Most	O
Logical	O
Terms	O
being	O
in	O
this	O
Treatise	O
also	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Reasoning	O
may	O
be	O
perfectly	O
learn	O
'd	O
without	O
much	O
farther	O
trouble	O
.	O
By	O
A	O
.	O
Lane	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
:	O
A	O
Treatise	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
publick	O
.	O
By	O
Marius	O
D'Assigny	O
B.	O
D.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Scotland	O
's	O
Sovereignty	O
asserted	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Dispute	O
concerning	O
Homage	O
,	O
against	O
those	O
who	O
maintain	O
the	O
Scotland	O
is	O
a	O
Fee	O
Liege	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Scots	O
owes	O
Homage	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Tho	O
.	O
Craig	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Short-hand	O
yet	O
shorter	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-writing	O
advanced	O
in	O
a	O
ore	O
,	O
easy	O
,	O
regular	O
,	O
and	O
natural	O
Method	O
than	O
hitherto	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Ridpath	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Artamenes	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Grand	O
Cyrus	O
,	O
that	O
famous	O
Romance	O
.	O
In	O
10	O
Books	O
.	O
By	O
Mons	O
.	O
de	O
Scudery	O
.	O
English	O
'd	O
by	O
F.	O
G.	O
Adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
various	O
Sculptures	O
.	O
Price	O
25	O
s.	O
Chamberlen	O
's	O
Midwisery	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Rutherford	O
Letters	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Fulfilling	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
for	O
confirming	O
Believers	O
,	O
and	O
convincing	O
Atheists	O
,	O
with	O
rare	O
Histories	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
An	O
Exposition	O
,	O
with	O
practical	O
Observations	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Job	O
:	O
By	O
Alexander	O
Nisbet	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Present	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
as	O
to	O
Coin	O
and	O
publick	O
Charges	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
parts	O
.	O
Treating	O
of	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Ways	O
and	O
Means	O
to	O
procure	O
it	O
;	O
of	O
Raising	O
its	O
Value	O
,	O
against	O
which	O
the	O
opposite	O
Prejudices	O
,	O
as	O
injurious	O
to	O
King	O
,	O
Parliament	O
and	O
People	O
,	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lock	O
's	O
Chief	O
Positions	O
,	O
are	O
refused	O
by	O
demonstable	O
Reason	O
and	O
Master	O
of	O
Fact	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Hodges	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Help	O
to	O
Prayer	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Direction	O
that	O
holy	O
Duty	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
well	O
pleasing	O
to	O
God	O
.	O
With	O
Prayers	O
for	O
Morning	O
and	O
Evening	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
By	O
T.	O
Knaggs	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
Providences	O
of	O
God	O
towards	O
this	O
Nation	O
in	O
introducing	O
the	O
True	O
Religion	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Slingsby	O
Bethel	O
Esq	O
;	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
a	O
Vacuum	O
;	O
wherein	O
is	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
be	O
demonstrated	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Vacuum	O
runs	O
though	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
in	O
all	O
Bodies	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
lover	O
of	O
the	O
Corpuscular	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Gauging	O
and	O
Measuring	O
made	O
a	O
brief	O
Con	O
of	O
Measuring	O
of	O
Surfaces	O
and	O
Solids	O
after	O
a	O
more	O
concise	O
and	O
inelligible	O
Manner	O
than	O
commonly	O
practised	O
.	O
Containing	O
,	O
First	O
,	O
The	O
most	O
Material	O
Propositions	O
of	O
Geometry	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
Mensuration	O
.	O
2dly	O
.	O
The	O
way	O
of	O
Measuring	O
Surfaces	O
.	O
3dly	O
.	O
The	O
way	O
of	O
Measuring	O
Solids	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
be	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
or	O
Liquid	O
after	O
a	O
most	O
exact	O
Method	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
Lovers	O
of	O
Art	O
;	O
such	O
as	O
Gaugers	O
,	O
Measurers	O
,	O
Painters	O
,	O
Carpenters	O
,	O
Joyners	O
,	O
Masons	O
Bricklayers	O
and	O
Glaziers	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
At	O
a	O
Compendium	O
of	O
the	O
Theory	O
and	O
Practice	O
of	O
Chirurgery	O
.	O
In	O
Seven	O
Books	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Salmon	O
M.	O
D.	O
In	O
2	O
Vol	O
.	O
Price	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Militia	O
Reform	O
'd	O
;	O
or	O
an	O
Easy	O
Scheme	O
of	O
Furnishing	O
England	O
with	O
a	O
constant	O
Land	O
force	O
,	O
capable	O
to	O
prevent	O
or	O
to	O
subdue	O
any	O
Foreign	O
Power	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
maintain	O
perpetual	O
Quiet	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
without	O
endangering	O
the	O
Publick	O
Liberty	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
There	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
2	O
,	O
A	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
shewing	O
that	O
a	O
Restraint	O
on	O
the	O
Press	O
is	O
absolutely	O
inconsistent	O
with	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
dangerous	O
to	O
the	O
Liberties	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
The	O
Grounds	O
and	O
Occasions	O
of	O
the	O
Controversy	O
touching	O
the	O
Unity	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Methods	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
manag	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Means	O
to	O
compose	O
it	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Divine	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Whitlook	O
near	O
Stationers-hall	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
THomas	O
Darby	O
,	O
Cabinet-Maker	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
leaving	O
off	O
Trade	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
will	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
forthwith	O
at	O
very	O
reasonable	O
Rates	O
;	O
where	O
all	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
Ladies	O
.	O
or	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Scrutores	O
,	O
Cabinets	O
,	O
Tables	O
,	O
Stands	O
,	O
or	O
Looking	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
sorts	O
of	O
Cabinet	O
work	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
Prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
mention	O
hundreds	O
of	O
Patients	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
cured	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
omitted	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
this	O
Famous	O
City	O
is	O
sufficiently	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Ability	O
and	O
Care	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
way	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
infallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head	O
Ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
:	O
Takes	O
away	O
sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Govt	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Fevers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
He	O
bath	O
also	O
an	O
Expeditious	O
way	O
in	O
curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainty	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
