TOKEN	NE
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24	O
,	O
25	O
,	O
26	O
and	O
27th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1699	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1699	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
William	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
Poole	B-pers
Berrisford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saywell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Awsiter	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Allibone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sheward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lee	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Locket	O
with	O
Pearls	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
66	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Pounds	O
of	O
old	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sheward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hannah	I-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
7	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloath	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Night-rail	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phillip	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dionys	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Cloath	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
watch	O
'd	O
their	O
opportunity	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
when	O
searched	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
confidently	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
hurt	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
by	O
hastily	O
cutting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
they	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
and	O
Conversations	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humphry	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
value	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
about	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Celler	O
Window	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
stumbled	O
at	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
above	O
Two	O
hundred	O
Thieves	O
that	O
harboured	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dennis	B-pers
Bonsellers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Eighteen	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
Dead	O
Nails	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Ware-house	O
was	O
Broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
find	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
accordingly	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
same	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Rivellow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Eighteen	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
Brandy	O
and	O
fine	O
Spirits	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
once	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
handed	O
out	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
with	O
him	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
a	O
Smith	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
fearing	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
might	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
wronged	O
by	O
such	O
Evil	O
Practices	O
,	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
accordingly	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidencenot	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Woollard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murdey	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Sell	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
Person	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
to	O
Sell	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
thereupon	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Flower	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Meal	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Sacks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
their	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
times	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
two	O
Sacks	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Sacks	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
fetch	O
Bran	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
usually	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Trapps	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfeild	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Four	O
Ducks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Mackerness	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	O
alias	O
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Muslin	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
Callico	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
Nightrails	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Hoods	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wash-house	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
meeting	O
with	O
Loe	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Butchers	O
Arms	O
by	O
White	O
Chapel	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wood	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stole	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
rescued	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Comrades	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Cooleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hillendon	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Tamareene	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
several	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
Acton	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pen-knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
:	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
Twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Iron	O
half	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Seven	O
pound	O
Weights	O
,	O
value	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
several	O
Weights	O
out	O
of	O
Spittle-fields	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Weights	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Rape-oyl	O
,	O
value	O
Eight	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
rolled	O
off	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
Bosse-Alley	O
by	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
roll	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Brandy	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
rolling	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
Officers	O
came	O
and	O
seized	O
it	O
,	O
supposing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Uncustomed	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Oyl	O
was	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
get	O
some	O
Body	O
else	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
good	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Abchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
new	O
Act	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Fifty	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
fourth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Counting	O
house	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Publickly	O
Stealing	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Apron	O
Four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sixteenth	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
therewas	O
another	O
Boy	O
that	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
when	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
Steal	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Plow-Irons	O
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Plow	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
was	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
other	O
Plow-Irons	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
said	O
they	O
lost	O
their	O
Irons	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Plows	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Foot-path	O
by	O
the	O
way-side	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
several	O
Parcels	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Everson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Dukes	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Two	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
Kersey	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
Twenty	O
four	O
Pounds	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Eighth	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Black-fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrowson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
ninth	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruse	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
Twelve	O
Pence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Languished	O
to	O
the	O
Fifth	O
of	O
April	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
washing	O
of	O
Vessels	O
at	O
a	O
Derby	O
Ale	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
Pints	O
of	O
Derby	O
Ale	O
he	O
drew	O
for	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
replied	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Cheating	O
Rogue	O
and	O
Rascal	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
drawn	O
Three	O
:	O
With	O
that	O
words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
the	O
Eyes	O
with	O
a	O
Whisk	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
struck	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
thrown	O
his	O
Whisk	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
to	O
reach	O
something	O
else	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
Bleeding	O
,	O
and	O
Bled	O
for	O
Four	O
hours	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
friendly	O
and	O
kind	O
to	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
particularly	O
he	O
had	O
shewed	O
great	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
offended	O
,	O
thinking	O
by	O
fair	O
means	O
to	O
work	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Obedience	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Court	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hanwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
one	O
Penny	O
Farthing	O
in	O
Monies	O
Numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Magdalane	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribbs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Marshals-Court-Officer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
imployed	O
to	O
Arrest	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
about	O
Red-Lyon-Square	B-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Drinking-Box	O
:	O
The	O
Plaintiff	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Officers	O
Follower	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Action	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
should	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Officers	O
Follower	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
so	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Demsdale	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Cumbey	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
seventh	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
Cumbey	O
come	O
to	O
Dobson	O
with	O
some	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
Feague	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
replied	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Stuff	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
;	O
sometime	O
after	O
Cumbey	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
Dobson	O
Feague	O
some	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
and	O
Cumbey	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hired	O
a	O
Room	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
Shandois	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
which	O
being	O
afterwards	O
Search	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
Flasks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
fitting	O
for	O
that	O
wicked	O
Trade	O
:	O
Dobson	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
pardoned	O
for	O
such	O
Offences	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
Cumbey	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Coarts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Four	O
Carcases	O
of	O
Veal	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Seventeenth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	B-pers
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Calves	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
also	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
Men	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
stealing	O
the	O
Calves	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
escaped	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
likewise	O
run	O
away	O
for	O
fear	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
a-him	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
New	O
Act	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Thirty	O
six	O
Silk	O
Tippets	O
,	O
value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
;	O
Eighty	O
four	O
Silk	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
second	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Womans	O
Custody	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
hid	O
under	O
some	O
Logs	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
Boys	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
watched	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
publickly	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lyddall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
an	O
Indian	O
Callico-Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Eighth	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
Pawned	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ezra	B-pers
Batte	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Eight	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Ballandine	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
Eight	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
Two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Hardass	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Selwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
eight	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Selwood	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
Bobbin	O
of	O
Silk	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Foreman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
about	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Fob-Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
his	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
wronged	O
him	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
of	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
Silk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hinchman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
fourth	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Musquet	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
Pence	O
,	O
laden	O
with	O
Gun-Powder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leaden	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
shooting	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
Drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Kings-head	B-place
at	O
Kensington	I-place
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happening	O
that	O
a	O
Cake	O
was	O
broken	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hinchman	O
told	O
the	O
Maid	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
seemed	O
contented	O
.	O
But	O
another	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
occasion	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Cake	O
that	O
is	O
broke	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cock	O
'd	O
the	O
Musquet	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
sure	O
your	O
Gun	O
is	O
not	O
Charged	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
drew	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
Discharged	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Belly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Friend	O
would	O
have	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
fetcht	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Charged	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Uriah	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hugh	I-pers
Remington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Laced	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
Bible	O
2	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Fighting	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
Felonious	O
Act	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tawdrell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Clift	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
all	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bernard	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Vessel	O
of	O
Punch	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
heard	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Tawdrell	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Dung-hill	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
Dung	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stuck	O
a	O
Pitch-fork	O
upon	O
the	O
Cask	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
removing	O
the	O
Dung	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Laced	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Cornet	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Corke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
his	O
Maid	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
back	O
was	O
turned	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cranaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
seven	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Caudell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecuter	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Little	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Iron	O
Locks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Sison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Sison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Trinity-Minories	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Toleson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
328	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Stale	O
Beer	O
,	O
32	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Black	O
Cherry-Beer	O
,	O
40	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Double	O
Beer	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
divers	O
considerable	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Tub	O
full	O
of	O
Drink	O
in	O
his	O
Seller	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Philip	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
Guilty	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Ten	O
Pence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Pontlkin	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
Cross	O
barr	O
Shot	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bromwell	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shot	O
was	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
procure	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Orrel	I-pers
to	O
swear	O
High	O
Treason	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hibbs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Solomon	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
sold	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
Coyn	O
in	O
Surry	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
by	O
Bunhill-Fields	B-place
,	O
they	O
found	O
all	O
sorts-of	O
things	O
sitting	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
in	O
this	O
Kind	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
formerly	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chatburn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
numbred	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
taking	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomazin	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
the	O
Indictments	O
were	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
Sutton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
being	O
accessaries	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Sutton	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
for	O
the	O
High-Way	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
at	O
Eling	B-place
on	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
on	O
Roger	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Woollard	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moodey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fulmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
writing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
most	O
wicked	O
,	O
Prophane	O
,	O
Seditious	O
and	O
Devilish	O
Libel	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
Aurea	O
Clavis	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
contained	O
many	O
Devilish	O
and	O
Wicked	O
Sentences	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
likewise	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Sect	O
of	O
the	O
Origenists	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Boles	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
after	O
a	O
Fact	O
committed	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Dicket	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Coffee	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Godin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Plump	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Petty-coat	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Night-rayle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wosterne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
plead	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Caswell	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Harrow	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
:	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dewy	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Claridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Catherine	I-pers
Glew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
Holmes	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
on	O
Cooper	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Swallow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
John	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Truelove	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Bullock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Moone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Gibson	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Leger	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
divers	O
dangerous	O
and	O
seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
King	O
William	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Offence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
took	O
the	O
Oaths	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
Fidelity	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
divers	O
dangerous	O
and	O
seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Arch	O
bishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Presentment	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
Sworn	O
to	O
Enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
do	O
present	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
IMprimis	O
,	O
We	O
Present	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
Henry	O
VII	O
.	O
all	O
Persons	O
selling	O
in	O
any	O
Unsealed	O
Measures	O
,	O
the	O
Party	O
so	O
offending	O
shall	O
Forfeit	O
for	O
the	O
First	O
Offence	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
Offence	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
third	O
Offence	O
to	O
forfeit	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
by	O
another	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
16th	O
year	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
I.	O
all	O
and	O
every	O
Person	O
,	O
selling	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
Unsealed	O
Measure	O
,	O
shall	O
for	O
every	O
Offence	O
Forfeit	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
And	O
that	O
by	O
another	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Tear	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
every	O
Person	O
selling	O
in	O
any	O
Unsealed	O
Measure	O
shall	O
for	O
every	O
Offence	O
forfeit	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
50	O
s.	O
which	O
said	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
due	O
Encouragement	O
,	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
have	O
been	O
totally	O
neglected	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
Prejudicial	O
to	O
all	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
resorting	O
and	O
inhabiting	O
within	O
this	O
City	O
and	O
Liberties	O
,	O
especially	O
the	O
Poor	O
resorting	O
to	O
Brew-houses	O
and	O
other	O
Publick	O
Places	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
we	O
earnestly	O
recommend	O
to	O
this	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
imaginable	O
care	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Laws	O
may	O
be	O
speedily	O
Executed	O
for	O
redressing	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Offences	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Barton	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Demsdale	O
alias	O
Dobson	O
,	O
Solomon	O
Hewit	O
,	O
John	O
Holmes	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Walter	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Demsdale	O
pleaded	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanelled	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
visible	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Left	O
Cheek	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
)	O
2	O
.	O
James	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
Dennis	O
Bonsellers	O
,	O
Philip	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Humphry	O
Chapman	O
,	O
Francis	O
Coleman	O
,	O
William	O
Coarts	O
,	O
William	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
Godfrey	O
Caswell	O
,	O
Robert	O
Dale	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
Simon	O
Gerrard	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Gray	O
,	O
John	O
Harris	O
,	O
John	O
How	O
,	O
Mary	O
Lyddal	O
,	O
John	O
Miller	O
,	O
Edward	O
Pontkin	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Sheward	O
alias	O
Smith	O
,	O
Eleana	O
Sutton	O
,	O
Andrew	O
Trapps	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	O
Willis	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whippp	O
'd	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
Ezra	O
Battee	O
,	O
Ann	O
Cook	O
,	O
John	O
Drury	O
,	O
Alice	O
Flood	O
,	O
alias	O
Moone	O
,	O
Richard	O
Loe	O
,	O
Mary	O
Sison	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
Martha	O
Williams	O
.	O
Susan	O
Broadhurst	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
May	O
pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
and	O
Westminster	O
hall	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Moore	O
Fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
William	O
Buttler	O
,	O
Fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
Sureties	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
A	O
New	O
way	O
of	O
Glass-cupping	O
,	O
performed	O
without	O
Fire	O
,	O
Lamp	O
,	O
or	O
Mouth-Suction	O
,	O
Invented	O
by	O
F.	O
Hawksbee	O
only	O
,	O
in	O
Queens-head	O
Court	O
in	O
Guiltspur-street	O
,	O
just	O
without	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
now	O
for	O
the	O
publick	O
good	O
selleth	O
the	O
Engine	O
,	O
Glasses	O
,	O
Scarrifying	O
Flems	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
appurtenances	O
that	O
compleats	O
its	O
Practice	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
so	O
easie	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Operation	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
is	O
capable	O
of	O
performing	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Glasses	O
that	O
will	O
Cup	O
a	O
whole	O
Finger	O
or	O
Toe	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
besides	O
others	O
larger	O
and	O
smaller	O
than	O
can	O
be	O
useful	O
any	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
several	O
Glasses	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
applied	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
one	O
small	O
Engine	O
required	O
in	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
suction	O
to	O
be	O
continued	O
to	O
any	O
degree	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Operator	O
shall	O
find	O
necessary	O
.	O
Attendance	O
is	O
daily	O
given	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
to	O
show	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Operation	O
to	O
any	O
Physician	O
or	O
Surgeon	O
that	O
shall	O
desire	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
now	O
practised	O
by	O
several	O
Eminent	O
Surgeons	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
.	O
WHereas	O
of	O
late	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
last	O
Execution	O
,	O
have	O
published	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
Criminals	O
:	O
The	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
now	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
thinks	O
fit	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
imposed	O
upon	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
utterly	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Condemned	O
Prisoners	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
Confessions	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
,	O
can	O
be	O
given	O
till	O
next	O
day	O
Eleven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Attested	O
under	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
constantly	O
printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Mellet	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
if	O
cureable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Paslages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Cureable	O
,	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
in	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
mention	O
Hundred	O
of	O
Patients	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
Cured	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
this	O
famous	O
City	O
is	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Ability	O
and	O
Care	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
way	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
PILL	O
which	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
Infallibly	O
Curing	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
It	O
Cures	O
the	O
Head-ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
:	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
,	O
takes	O
away	O
sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Govt	O
.	O
It	O
Cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Fevers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
make	O
no	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
Sign	O
is	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
.	O
The	O
above-said	O
Pills	O
and	O
Gargarism	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
of	O
J	O
.	O
Mayor	O
,	O
Printer	O
and	O
Stationer	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
