TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1707	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Bedingfeld	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Queens	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Selathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Umphreys	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hasel	I-pers
Leonard	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
Hugh	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fawkes	I-pers
Austin	B-pers
Oldisworth	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hymore	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Litchbourn	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mist	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Capper	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
William	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wyburd	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Worsden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Finchly	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bed-Tick	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
Cloth	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Augustine	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
and	O
Hired	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Night	O
they	O
Stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
broken	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Finchly-Common	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Slippers	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
and	I-place
Agnes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Apprehended	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
they	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
calling	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ursula	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Eyliff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mainford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Fifteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Garters	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
.	O
A	O
Silver	O
Cross	O
Gilt	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
with	O
Green	O
Stones	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
is	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
apprehendedher	O
upon	O
Suspicition	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
so	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catharine	B-pers
Grint	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvas	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
Cheapn	O
'd	O
some	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
Watching	O
their	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
Turner	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servants	O
and	O
Grint	O
,	O
while	O
Grint	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Slipt	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
off	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Charg	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Offering	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Cristal	O
,	O
and	O
Cypher	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
Confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
exchang	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
plain	O
Ring	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
;	O
others	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sundley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Holland	O
,	O
Shirts	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
20	O
s.	O
18	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
18	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Noah	B-pers
Overy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Family	O
were	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
Bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jane	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
with	O
23	O
Stones	O
set	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
18	O
l	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Pan	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
Tea	O
spoons	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jane	O
Davis	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
Lived	O
with	O
Sir	O
David	B-pers
Nurl	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
she	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Family	O
for	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
there	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
given	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
who	O
had	O
Lived	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
that	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
true	O
Jane	O
Davis	O
,	O
Hired	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Family	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
That	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
following	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
arose	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Dressing	O
Room	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Buckle	O
was	O
laid	O
)	O
to	O
Scour	O
the	O
Irons	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Footman	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
an	O
Out-House	O
,	O
Knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
privacy	O
to	O
impart	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
safe	O
,	O
late	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
missing	O
the	O
Moment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Buckle	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Plat	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
show	O
it	O
the	O
Person	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
described	O
it	O
by	O
its	O
having	O
8	O
Great	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
Little	O
ones	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Jeweller	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
Buckle	O
,	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
the	O
Model	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Buckle	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
exactly	O
with	O
that	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sell	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Plat	O
did	O
not	O
employ	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Sell	O
any	O
Buckle	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
denyed	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
else	O
where	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
Committed	O
.	O
To	O
Invalidate	O
which	O
Evidence	O
,	O
8	O
Persons	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Family	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
ProsecutorsHouse	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jane	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
little	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Demon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
She	O
Ass	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Barnet	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Saffron	B-place
Walden	I-place
,	O
in	B-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Essex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
Wife	O
Hannah	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
His	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Surrige	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
1693	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
First	O
Marriage	O
was	O
the	O
Parson	O
of	O
Walden	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
Granted	O
a	O
Licence	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Marry	O
Elizabeth	O
Surrige	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
actually	O
Married	O
them	O
in	O
Walden	O
Church	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Surrige	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Married	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Second	O
Marriage	O
was	O
the	O
Parson	O
of	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Simpson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
brought	O
a	O
Licence	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Marriage	O
from	O
the	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
Licence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Married	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
Married	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Dead	O
above	O
7	O
Years	O
:	O
But	O
produc	O
'd	O
no	O
Proof	O
to	O
Induce	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
believe	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
Artful	O
ways	O
to	O
gain	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Simpson	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
feign	O
'd	O
himself	O
Sick	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
shew	O
of	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
time	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Practice	O
of	O
Piety	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
Book	O
to	O
teach	O
them	O
how	O
to	O
Dye	O
well	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
he	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
great	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
keep	O
his	O
Coach	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Stich	O
'd	O
Night	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Night	O
Gown	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Compting	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Cap	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
one	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Cap	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
But	O
producing	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
Saint	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winlow	I-pers
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marlton	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
made	O
Answer	O
that	O
the	O
Devil	O
bewitch	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
opened	O
a	O
Desk	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trepass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Queens-high-way	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bread-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Mildreds	I-place
Parish	I-place
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Baggs	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
25	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Edwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
1704	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
Riding	O
by	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Horses	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Cut	O
the	O
Straps	O
of	O
his	O
Port-Manteau	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
apprehended	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
at	O
Bread	O
Street	O
they	O
came	O
all	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Force	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Baggs	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
contain	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
perfect	O
view	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Smiths	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
was	O
sent	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
not	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Ann	B-pers
Byass	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Balford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tividal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Pipes	O
,	O
and	O
Watching	O
her	O
opportunity	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Lodging	O
and	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
divers	O
false	O
Keys	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
and	O
Paul	B-pers
Debroslus	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
Cheapn	O
'd	O
some	O
Muslen	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
for	O
Scotch	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
dealing	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
Bennet	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Muslen	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
Bennet	O
let	O
it	O
Drop	O
from	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Thomson	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Satten	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Coat	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslen	O
Nightrail	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Callicoe	O
Gowns	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
consisted	O
of	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
hearing	O
a	O
strange	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
where	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lambourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
Buy	O
Callicoe	O
for	O
a	O
Childs	O
Dust	O
Gown	O
that	O
while	O
Brewer	O
was	O
treating	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
Lambourn	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
Dropt	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Lambourn	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Brewer	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
she	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Chesterfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
Buy	O
Rags	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servants	O
back	O
being	O
turned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
N.	O
B.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Under	O
Turnkey	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
was	O
openly	O
censur	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
(	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
)	O
been	O
rude	O
to	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
John	O
Hermon	O
Brian	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
hard	O
Labour	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Bennet	O
,	O
Ann	O
Davis	O
,	O
Catharine	O
Grint	O
,	O
Mary	O
Lambourn	O
,	O
Ann	O
Munday	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Mainford	O
Sarah	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
John	O
Turner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Turner	O
,	O
John	O
Timms	O
,	O
Magaret	O
Underhill	O
.	O
Pettit	O
Larcenies	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Jane	O
Evans	O
,	O
Ann	O
Young	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Chesterfield	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Nash	O
,	O
Ann	O
Cook	O
.	O
John	O
Winlow	O
Fined	O
10	O
Groats	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Bell	O
,	O
Fined	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
for	O
her	O
Trespass	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
SHORT-HAND	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
most	O
approved	O
Method	O
extant	O
,	O
is	O
taught	O
to	O
Perfection	O
,	O
by	O
William	O
Robinson	O
,	O
at	O
Habitations	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
taketh	O
Tryals	O
and	O
Sermons	O
or	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
Oration	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
Exactness	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
spoken	O
with	O
at	O
the	O
Rainbow-Coffee-House	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
on	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
and	O
Fridays	O
,	O
from	O
9	O
till	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
at	O
Jones	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Finchlvne	O
near	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
daily	O
,	O
from	O
two	O
to	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Three	O
Black-birds	O
in	O
the	O
Great-Minories	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
Is	O
sold	O
,	O
a	O
never	O
failing	O
Ointment	O
that	O
Cures	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduced	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
time	O
,	O
having	O
often	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
pains	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
