TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1707	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powel	O
,	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Forewood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wormlayton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Comfort	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
James	B-pers
Rochester	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Anstey	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Adshed	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hazzard	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Fan	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Vizzard	O
Mask	O
12	O
d.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
place	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
search	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
her	O
Sisters	O
,	O
and	O
proof	O
made	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
thither	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Juel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
28	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gadd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
till	O
her	O
return	O
;	O
that	O
returning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
upon	O
Examination	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Band-box	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
riding	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	O
Moor-gate	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
snatch	O
a	O
Band-box	O
from	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
be	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pattens	O
16	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Ruffles	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Montisano	I-pers
alias	O
Joseph	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Tavis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
striking	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
set	O
with	O
Agat	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Hook	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-dresses	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Bed-Quilt	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
Martin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
understood	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gang	O
that	O
haunted	O
that	O
quarter	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
four	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
of	O
Low	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
Jones	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Angel	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
observing	O
a	O
Sash	O
Window	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
close	O
,	O
Montisano	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
accordingly	O
,	O
while	O
Martin	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
Scout	O
;	O
that	O
Montisano	O
threw	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
Linnen	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Mony	O
among	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
was	O
likewise	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	B-place
,	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
espy	O
'd	O
a	O
Tankard	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
they	O
observing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Montisano	O
leap	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
cut	O
out	O
four	O
Quarries	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
reach	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
out	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
one	O
half	O
Crown	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
alias	O
Wilkinson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
26	O
Guinea-pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gasts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishop's-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
5	O
Guinea-pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
13s	O
.	O
5d	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
14	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
47	O
Tin	O
Meddals	O
,	O
2	O
Broad-pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
38	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Garret	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
fix	O
nothing	O
upon	O
Saunders	O
and	O
Mercer	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Garret	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wetherly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Baggs	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
green	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crofton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
her	O
Examination	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stoln	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sloane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
16	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dina	B-pers
Rupel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
7l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bathourn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
6	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
19l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodyere	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
P-	B-pers
E-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Edmunds	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
and	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boteler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
)	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Nine	O
Baggs	O
of	O
Hopps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Villanous	O
and	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
Mr.	O
Boteler	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
said	O
Carter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
thereof	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Biggleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bagg	O
,	O
with	O
19s	O
.	O
and	O
3d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Haynes	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
Male	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
large	O
penetration	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
cross	O
a	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
gain	O
'd	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
direction	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
had	O
injured	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
nor	O
calling	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nest	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sanchy	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burton	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Henry	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1704.	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
one	O
Sanchy	B-pers
,	O
whom	O
she	O
marry	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1695.	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evers	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Evers	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
4	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
15s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
some	O
Child-bed-Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Suttle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Piercy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Mothers	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
of	O
hers	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
others	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
prov	O
'd	O
true	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
10s	O
.	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
Pickles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
accordingly	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
Hannah	O
Evers	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Evers	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Low	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bunch	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Captain	O
John	B-pers
Guyon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
blue	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
yellow	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
green	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Guyon	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
was	O
Madam	O
Guyon	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
three	O
Men	O
rush	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Mony	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
repl	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Mony	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
;	O
upon	O
their	O
going	O
to	O
which	O
Room	O
she	O
lockd	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
struck	O
her	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
,	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Stature	O
of	O
Low	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
;	O
she	O
viewing	O
them	O
by	O
no	O
light	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
this	O
particular	O
,	O
That	O
Hall	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
perfect	O
knowledge	O
of	O
his	O
Countenance	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
swore	O
positively	O
against	O
Hall	O
.	O
Another	O
considerable	O
piece	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
one	O
Briggs	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
eleven	O
Years	O
Old	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
near	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
six	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
near	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
and	O
hear	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
(	O
Viz	O
.	O
)	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Wast-coat	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver-Thread	O
,	O
and	O
Buttons	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
Head-dresses	O
,	O
with	O
Knotts	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
exactly	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Bunch	O
say	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Hand	O
o	O
n't	O
too	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
Hall	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
they	O
should	O
make	O
a	O
better	O
Hand	O
o	O
n't	O
to	O
Morrow	O
Night	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
distinguish	O
one	O
from	O
another	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
spoke	O
aloud	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
another	O
Brother	O
Stitch	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
spoke	O
softly	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
another	O
by	O
their	O
proper	O
Names	O
.	O
That	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
an	O
Appointment	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Fighting-Cocks	O
in	O
Bun-hill	O
Fields	O
,	O
between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
acquainting	O
his	O
Father	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
Persons	O
,	O
acquainting	O
some	O
stout	O
Men	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
engag	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
away	O
they	O
met	O
them	O
going	O
thither	O
;	O
in	O
their	O
pursuit	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
fir	O
'd	O
several	O
Pistols	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
apprehended	O
them	O
.	O
Low	O
took	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
himself	O
,	O
to	O
excuse	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyl	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Young	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
1st	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
That	O
Hopley	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Boyl	O
below	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
above	O
,	O
Boyl	O
unlock	O
'd	O
a	O
Closet	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Hopley	O
came	O
down	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Boyl	O
,	O
was	O
again	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mantua	O
,	O
Silk	O
hood	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bethia	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
,	O
to	O
treat	O
for	O
some	O
Heads	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christianus	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
46	O
l.	O
from	O
Alexander	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
80	O
l.	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Montisano	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Callico	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Curtis	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
That	O
Low	O
lifted	O
up	O
a	O
Sash	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
below	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Mony	O
amongst	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Montisano	I-pers
,	O
were	O
again	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gately	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Shagrene-Box	O
studded	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
likewise	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Montisano	I-pers
,	O
was	O
again	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Perruke	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Dutton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
that	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Sash	O
being	O
lifted	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
his	O
Family	O
then	O
being	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Willis	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
pick-Lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chamber-Door	O
,	O
and	O
Cabbinet	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Mony	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
O	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Duglas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
1	O
Tun	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Duglas	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Warehouse	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lying	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
privately	O
took	O
the	O
Brandy	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
alledging	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Flannel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
adjoyning	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
alarm	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Cry	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stol'n	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
value	O
7	O
pound	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
rid	O
to	O
Hampsted	B-place
Market	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
up	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
half	B-place
Moon	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
for	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
there	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
Wetherly	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
actually	O
Steal	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Moon	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Horse	O
Stealer	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bran	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
the	O
Jury	O
accquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Christianus	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
104	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
,	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
64	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
of	O
24	O
Horn	O
Combs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Redbourn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Muslen	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
George	B-pers
Botkin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Muslen	O
Neckcloth	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Stooks	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Goose	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Bason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goose	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Waldram	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wyles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Boobuck	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hollit	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shay	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
6	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Ravish	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
7	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
9	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
Richard	O
Low	O
,	O
Stephen	O
Bunch	O
,	O
William	O
Davis	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Montisano	O
,	O
William	O
Kite	O
,	O
O	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
Thomas	O
Earl	O
,	O
John	O
Read	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
hard	O
Labour	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
Robert	O
Windsor	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Juel	O
,	O
Deborah	O
Garret	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Evers	O
,	O
Mary	O
Thomson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Hoply	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Royl	O
,	O
Alice	O
Jones	O
,	O
Christianus	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Norman	O
,	O
John	O
Waters	O
.	O
Petit	O
Larcenies	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
Mary	O
Morrice	O
,	O
John	O
Timms	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Howel	O
,	O
Mary	O
Palmer	O
,	O
Elianor	O
Steward	O
,	O
John	O
Waldram	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Boyl	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
THere	O
is	O
Printed	O
at	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Printing-Office	O
in	O
Black-Fryers	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Common-Prayer	O
,	O
in	O
410	O
,	O
upon	O
very	O
good	O
Paper	O
and	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
Parish-Clarks	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
Families	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
;	O
also	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
All	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common-Prayers	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
un-Rul	O
'd	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Volumes	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
speedily	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
THE	O
History	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Cathedral	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
from	O
its	O
first	O
Foundation	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
time	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
Sir	O
.	O
William	O
Dugdale	O
a	O
History	O
.	O
Extracted	O
out	O
of	O
Original	O
Charters	O
,	O
Records	O
,	O
Leigor	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Manuscripts	O
:	O
With	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Deans	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
its	O
first	O
Foundation	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
time	O
.	O
Adorned	O
with	O
several	O
Prospects	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Church	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
Christopher	O
Wren	O
's	O
own	O
Plates	O
.	O
Continued	O
from	O
where	O
Sir	O
William	O
Dugdale	O
leaves	O
off	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Divine	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Whereunto	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
St.	O
Peters	O
Church	O
at	O
York	O
:	O
Containing	O
its	O
Ancquities	O
,	O
Ancient	O
Monuments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
all	O
its	O
Archbishops	O
and	O
Deans	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
time	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
several	O
Prospects	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
remarkable	O
Tombs	O
.	O
This	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
by	O
their	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
found	O
the	O
useful	O
for	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
at	O
the	O
among	O
many	O
others	O
tho	O
I	O
know	O
Mr	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Atkins	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
.	O
1702	O
.	O
Newly	O
Published	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
and	O
Enlarged	O
to	O
more	O
than	O
Double	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Sheets	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Impression	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Vencreal	O
Diseases	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
seves	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
infecting	O
;	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
infection	O
;	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
infected	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Infallible	O
way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
;	O
Easiness	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
Infected	O
;	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
missed	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
Skillful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venceral	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mountebanks	O
,	O
Impostors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Vencreal	O
and	O
other	O
Gleets	O
,	O
Introductory	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
their	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
,	O
are	O
briefly	O
describ	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procuration	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculine	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
published	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Martin	O
.	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
remov	O
'd	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Preface	O
in	O
the	O
Book	O
)	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
W.	O
Howes	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Seneca	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Isted	O
against	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
Dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
Sudden	O
Surprizes	O
,	O
and	O
sinking	O
of	O
Spirts	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
and	O
inveterate	O
Giddinesses	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Paintings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
succesfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
daplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
)	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
:	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Black-Birds	O
in	O
the	O
Great-Minories	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Is	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
a	O
never-sailing	O
Ointment	O
that	O
Cures	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
time	O
having	O
often	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Base	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
,	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
late	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
William	O
Kellitt	O
,	O
for	O
Curing	O
of	O
Agues	O
,	O
who	O
left	O
the	O
only	O
Secret	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
still	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
their	O
long	O
Experience	O
,	O
and	O
Practice	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
26	O
Years	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
)	O
never	O
failed	O
to	O
Cure	O
that	O
Distemper	O
perfectly	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
Patient	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
,	O
Quality	O
,	O
Constitution	O
or	O
habit	O
of	O
Body	O
soever	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
.	O
(	O
No	O
Cure	O
no	O
Mony	O
.	O
)	O
MRs.	O
Frances	O
Shastoe	O
's	O
Narrative	O
.	O
Containing	O
;	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
in	O
Sir	O
Theophilus	O
Oglethorp	O
's	O
Family	O
;	O
where	O
,	O
hearing	O
many	O
Treasonable	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
others	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Pretended	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
was	O
Sir	O
.	O
Theophilus	O
's	O
Son	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
trick	O
'd	O
into	O
France	O
by	O
Sir	O
Theophilu	O
's	O
Daughters	O
,	O
and	O
barbarously	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Papist	O
and	O
Nun	O
.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
to	O
Swisserland	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
arriv	O
'd	O
in	O
England	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
1705	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Just	O
Published	O
,	O
Bumography	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Touth	O
at	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Tuils	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Lampeon	O
privately	O
dispers	O
'd	O
at	O
Tunbridge	O
Wells	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
1707.	O
by	O
a	O
Water-Drinker	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Characters	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noted	O
Water-Drinkers	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
merry	O
Elegy	O
upon	O
Mother	O
Jefferies	O
;	O
the	O
ancient	O
Water-Dipper	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
The	O
Prophetical	O
Warnings	O
of	O
John	O
Lucy	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
pronounc	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Operation	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
,	O
and	O
faithfully	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
spoken	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
Parts	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Author	O
.	O
In	O
few	O
Days	O
will	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
.	O
A	O
Book	O
Entitiled	O
,	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Enthusiastick	O
Impostors	O
,	O
on	O
Divinely	O
Inspir	O
'd	O
Prophets	O
.	O
