TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queens	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
and	O
15th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Bisby	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bodicoat	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Swinhow	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gavin	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Bossel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bowton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dowel	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Winkfield	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pannet	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fullwood	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Taper	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Channel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Stall	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
produce	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dirty	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Pawly	I-pers
,	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pawly	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Shop-Lifters	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
apprehended	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
Stealing	O
Callico	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Dirty	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
drop	O
a	O
piece	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
piece	O
was	O
convey	O
'd	O
by	O
Jones	O
behind	O
a	O
close	O
Stool	O
,	O
which	O
likewise	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clear	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
9	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hool	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Maries	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
Piece	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
at	O
their	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
unlock	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
then	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
taking	O
out	O
Mony	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
on	O
Good-Fryday	O
she	O
took	O
fromthence	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
20	O
s.	O
to	O
one	O
Pugh	O
,	O
and	O
reserv	O
'd	O
the	O
Guinea	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
Mark	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Silvester	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1706.	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
marry	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1698.	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
Sylvester	B-pers
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
about	O
9	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
Marriage	O
was	O
likewise	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Forgery	O
,	O
in	O
Personating	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Hattervile	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Swearing	O
to	O
a	O
Debenture	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Defraud	O
her	O
Majesty	O
of	O
101	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Mansion	O
House	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
none	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Susannah	O
Griffin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
8	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
broken	O
several	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Strainer	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
upon	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Breast	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
prov	O
'd	O
clearly	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Ilness	O
was	O
much	O
beaten	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
barbarously	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
those	O
Bruises	O
were	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Revelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
35	O
Pictures	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
7	O
Napkins	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvas	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
cross	O
Stitch	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bonythan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Yeamans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crutcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walk	O
'd	O
divers	O
times	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
broke	O
the	O
Show	O
Glass	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
buried	O
the	O
Rings	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
which	O
were	O
accordingly	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
Lumbard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Elatch	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Servants	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
reach	O
some	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wickstead	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Potten	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
27	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Poringer	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Scizars	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Satten	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mackarty	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
1st	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
upon	O
a	O
Pole	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Foul	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
Foul	O
,	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Basket	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Stones	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
treat	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leaving	O
behind	O
him	O
the	O
Stones	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
his	O
Basket	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
likewise	O
being	O
very	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
Bayley	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
Bayley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
teazing	O
him	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
advis	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
admit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
Strangled	O
;	O
then	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
Stab	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Stab	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
2	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
Another	O
Person	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
she	O
run	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
Stab	O
given	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Intestines	O
hanging	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
another	O
Stab	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Opinion	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
'em	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
no	O
Weapon	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
any	O
Provocation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
commit	O
so	O
horrid	O
a	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
turn	O
it	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Anderson	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
other	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
with	O
that	O
given	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stint	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bateman	B-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pinknis	I-pers
;	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Stint	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Bateman	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
she	O
personated	O
)	O
to	O
James	O
Pinkins	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
2d	O
Day	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
wash	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
several	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
making	O
search	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
upon	O
examination	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
Elizabeth	O
Bateman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Stent	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
and	O
Britton	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Stolen	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Mordant	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Locket	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Horseman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Childs	O
Basket	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Queen	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
prepare	O
himself	O
for	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
William	O
Gregg	O
,	O
David	O
Bayley	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Mark	O
Bryan	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Dirty	O
,	O
Edward	O
Silvester	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Gwin	O
,	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
,	O
Mary	O
Stent	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
Martha	O
Walker	O
,	O
Richard	O
Yeamans	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
Petit	O
Larcenies	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Kelly	O
and	O
Jane	O
Jenkinson	O
.	O
T	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
Fin	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
from	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
Street	O
,	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
A	O
Ministers	O
Cloth-Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
Bands	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Octaro	O
Manuscript	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
If	O
any	O
shall	O
bring	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
at	O
College	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
printer	O
near	O
Blacksmiths	O
Hall	O
,	O
on	O
Lambeth-Hill	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
well	O
rewarded	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
will	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
.	O
THE	O
charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
true	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
(	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
seweral	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
Charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinement	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nearest	O
Relation	O
,	O
Cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Methods	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
of	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
hazardous	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
sobpoin	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
seat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
peculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
curing	O
their	O
Gleets	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
Seminal	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
pertinent	O
Observations	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
,	O
Likewise	O
the	O
certain	O
easy	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
Infection	O
,	O
tho	O
never	O
so	O
often	O
accompanying	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
polluted	O
Companion	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
C.	O
surgeon	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
,	O
Edmund	O
Curle	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
attach	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
THE	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Robert	O
Feilding	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Marrying	O
her	O
Grace	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Cleeav-land	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	O
Wadsworth	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1806.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Beddingfess	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
Ovel	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Sir	O
Powys	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Queen	O
's	O
Bench	O
Sir	O
John	O
Bkncow	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
,	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
With	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
letters	O
between	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
and	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mrs.	O
Wadlworth	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Anne	O
Countess	O
of	O
Fielding	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
all	O
the	O
Learned	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Council	O
Perused	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Spiritual	O
Court	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sentence	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Morphew	O
near	O
Stationers-Hall	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
There	O
is	O
printed	O
a	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Printing	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Common-Prayer	O
,	O
in	O
410.	O
upon	O
very	O
good	O
Paper	O
and	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clarks	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
Families	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
also	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
All	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bible	O
and	O
Common-Prayers	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
un-Rul	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
volumes	O
.	O
Newly	O
Published	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
and	O
Enlarged	O
to	O
more	O
than	O
Double	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Sheets	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Impression	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
Kinds	O
,	O
earnous	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
;	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
;	O
Certainly	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
Infected	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
,	O
hasiness	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
infected	O
,	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
Skilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
venereal	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Roin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mounted	O
Impostors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
whole	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Venereal	O
and	O
other	O
Gleets	O
,	O
Introductory	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Gental	O
Parts	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
their	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
,	O
are	O
briefly	O
describ	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
why	O
Cleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
.	O
Seen	O
,	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inferred	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
Publishd	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marten	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
remov	O
'd	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Preface	O
to	O
the	O
Book	O
)	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
W.	O
Hawes	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Senecars	O
Heat	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Isted	O
against	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Black-Birds	O
in	O
the	O
Great-Minories	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Is	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
,	O
a	O
never-failing	O
Oyntment	O
that	O
Cures	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
all	O
bought	O
the	O
Partics	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
time	O
having	O
often	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
safe	O
and	O
comfort	O
of	O
many	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
efectually	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fitten	O
,	O
often	O
,	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
,	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
ual	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
Sudden	O
Surprizes	O
,	O
and	O
Sinking	O
of	O
Spirits	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
and	O
inveterate	O
Giddinesses	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Faintings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experience	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
)	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
.	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
The	O
fam	O
'd	O
Canker-Water	O
,	O
WHich	O
so	O
perfectly	O
and	O
immediately	O
cures	O
all	O
Cankess	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heats	O
and	O
Inflammations	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
far	O
gone	O
;	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
Tongue	O
,	O
Checks	O
,	O
of	O
Lips	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
saved	O
he	O
lives	O
of	O
several	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
only	O
to	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
Robins	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Exchange-alley	O
,	O
as	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Its	O
Virtue	O
decays	O
no	O
in	O
keeping	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
useful	O
and	O
much	O
esteemed	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
Incomparable	O
Cordial	O
Stomach	O
Pills	O
,	O
WHich	O
without	O
Purging	O
,	O
Confinement	O
,	O
or	O
Trouble	O
,	O
absolutely	O
Cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
,	O
Indigestions	O
,	O
Stoppage	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
disorders	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
Inveterate	O
or	O
Enstream	O
,	O
proceeding	O
from	O
what	O
Cause	O
soever	O
;	O
also	O
wonderfully	O
Comforts	O
and	O
Strengthens	O
a	O
Cold	O
,	O
Raw	O
,	O
Weakly	O
and	O
Sickly	O
Stomach	O
,	O
discharging	O
thenced	O
,	O
natural	O
caution	O
only	O
,	O
all	O
impure	O
of	O
offending	O
Matter	O
:	O
Procures	O
a	O
good	O
Appetite	O
,	O
and	O
admirably	O
Wind	O
.	O
These	O
Excellent	O
Fists	O
being	O
very	O
small	O
and	O
safe	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
may	O
readily	O
be	O
taken	O
at	O
all	O
seasons	O
;	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Dificulty	O
or	O
Danger	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
per	O
Box	O
(	O
containing	O
9	O
Doses	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
usually	O
enough	O
for	O
Cure	O
.	O
)	O
Sold	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Stationer	O
upon	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Marshal	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Grace	O
Church	O
street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
at	O
Purcels	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mayos	O
,	O
Stationer	O
,	O
against	O
Water	O
Lane	O
end	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Christian	O
,	O
Drugster	O
,	O
against	O
Somerset	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
A	O
safe	O
and	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
WHither	O
it	O
proceeds	O
from	O
Rheume	O
,	O
Rottenness	O
of	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Worms	O
in	O
'em	O
,	O
or	O
Stumps	O
,	O
&	O
c.'Tis	O
a	O
Liquid	O
,	O
prepar	O
'd	O
without	O
any	O
Mercury	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
pernicious	O
Ingredients	O
too	O
often	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
commonly	O
attended	O
with	O
unhappy	O
Effects	O
;	O
this	O
incomparable	O
Remedy	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
safely	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
certainly	O
Cures	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
Invetterate	O
,	O
Violent	O
and	O
Raging	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
effectually	O
preserves	O
both	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
from	O
Putrefaction	O
and	O
Decay	O
,	O
and	O
absolutely	O
clears	O
'em	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Sold	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
Stationer	O
,	O
upon	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Milner	O
at	O
the	O
red	O
M	O
,	O
in	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jenning	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Milk	O
Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Parson	O
a	O
Cane	O
Shop	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Horn	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Perrey	O
Perfumer	O
next	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Howel	O
Perfumer	O
,	O
next	O
Leisester	O
house	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
Da	O
.	O
Perronet	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Dyot	O
Street	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
AN	O
Answer	O
to	O
several	O
Treatises	O
lately	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
of	O
the	O
Prophets	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
part	O
,	O
by	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Bulkley	O
,	O
Bar	O
,	O
Price	O
8	O
d.	O
where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
Cry	O
from	O
the	O
Defatt	O
,	O
with	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lacy	O
's	O
Preface	O
price	O
8	O
d.	O
Mr	O
Marion	O
's	O
Prophetical	O
Warnnings	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Lacy	O
's	O
Warnings	O
,	O
1st	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Tracts	O
relating	O
thereunto	O
.	O
THE	O
Sot-weed	O
Factor	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
Voyage	O
to	O
Maryland	O
,	O
a	O
Satyr	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
is	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Laws	O
,	O
Governments	O
,	O
Courts	O
and	O
Constitutions	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Buildings	O
,	O
Feasts	O
,	O
Frolicks	O
,	O
Entertainments	O
and	O
Drunken	O
Humours	O
of	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
America	O
.	O
In	O
Burle	O
que	O
Verse	O
.	O
By	O
Eben	O
.	O
Cook	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
THE	O
Wooden	O
World	O
dissected	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
1st	O
a	O
Ship	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
2d	O
a	O
Sea	O
Captain	O
,	O
3d	O
.	O
a	O
Sea	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
4th	O
a	O
Sea	O
Chaplain	O
,	O
5th	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
6th	O
the	O
Purser	O
,	O
7th	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
8th	O
the	O
Gunder	O
,	O
9th	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
10th	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
,	O
11th	O
a	O
Sea	O
Cook	O
,	O
12th	O
a	O
Mioshipman	O
,	O
13th	O
the	O
Captains	O
Steward	O
,	O
14th	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
a	O
lover	O
or	O
the	O
Mathematicks	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
Edition	O
corrected	O
and	O
amended	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
SEcret	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Clodesly	O
Shouvel	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Admiral	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
containing	O
his	O
Birth	O
,	O
Education	O
and	O
Rife	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Naval	O
Battles	O
since	O
the	O
Revolution	O
and	O
other	O
honourable	O
Exploits	O
performed	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
more	O
exact	O
relation	O
of	O
the	O
Enterprize	O
upon	O
Toolon	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
yet	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
served	O
in	O
that	O
Expedition	O
and	O
was	O
several	O
Years	O
under	O
Command	O
of	O
that	O
Admiral	O
;	O
with	O
his	O
Effigies	O
curiously	O
engraven	O
on	O
a	O
Copper	O
Plate	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
MEmoris	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Villanous	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
late	O
famous	O
and	O
Notorious	O
Robber	O
,	O
Pen	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Mouth	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
exact	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Thief	O
in	O
General	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
lively	O
Representation	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
Inhabitants	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Manners	O
and	O
Customs	O
observed	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Nature	O
and	O
Means	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
commit	O
their	O
several	O
Thefts	O
and	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Distinctions	O
observed	O
in	O
their	O
respective	O
Functions	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
generally	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
those	O
sort	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
conceal	O
their	O
Villanies	O
;	O
and	O
Rules	O
to	O
avoid	O
being	O
Robb	O
'd	O
or	O
Cheated	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Usefully	O
set	O
forth	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Instance	O
of	O
many	O
honest	O
People	O
.	O
THe	O
3d	O
Volume	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Poems	O
on	O
divers	O
Subjects	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
charitable	O
Citizen	O
.	O
Fortunes	O
bounty	O
.	O
A	O
Satyr	O
against	O
the	O
corrupt	O
use	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
A	O
Dialogue	O
between	O
Britannia	O
and	O
prudence	O
.	O
A	O
Protestant	O
Scourge	O
.	O
A	O
Musical	O
Entertainment	O
.	O
The	O
Libertine	O
's	O
Choice	O
.	O
All	O
Men	O
mad	O
.	O
Helter	O
Skelter	O
.	O
Honesty	O
in	O
Distress	O
.	O
The	O
1st	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Journey	O
to	O
H	O
-	O
.	O
A	O
Satyr	O
against	O
Wine	O
.	O
A	O
Poem	O
in	O
praise	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
.	O
A	O
Poem	O
on	O
the	O
Success	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Poems	O
never	O
before	O
printed	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
author	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
B	O
Bravge	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Friendly	O
Correspondences	O
,	O
or	O
Epistolary	O
Satyrs	O
upon	O
Virture	O
and	O
Vice	O
,	O
in	O
several	O
Letters	O
under	O
the	O
following	O
Heads	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
Tom	O
Brown	O
's	O
last	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
witt	O
Friends	O
and	O
Companions	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
A	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
London	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
concerning	O
the	O
Publick	O
Affairs	O
of	O
this	O
Town	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
pleasant	O
,	O
comical	O
,	O
and	O
delightful	O
Prdictions	O
and	O
Observations	O
upon	O
every	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
remarkable	O
Day	O
throughout	O
the	O
whole	O
Year	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
;	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Writings	O
hitherto	O
exta	O
t.	O
All	O
Sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
