TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Ward	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Gould	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Domvile	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Mayling	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Kittle	I-pers
George	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
William	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Tredway	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
William	B-pers
Strode	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Arlidge	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bavand	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Kilgore	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Tuckwell	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hownsby	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Dowlace	O
Smocks	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
from	O
Home	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
upon	O
her	O
Body	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
bundled	O
upin	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
Jennet	B-pers
Mekclan	I-pers
at	O
Edenborough	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Scotland	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1686.	O
Jane	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
in	O
1682	O
,	O
at	O
Lisbon	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pattrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
Committed	O
by	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Gody	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
11	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
Lawson	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
with	O
his	O
Carr	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
at	O
High	B-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
for	O
Toll	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
unwilling	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
whipt	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
sudden	O
Run	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
having	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Body-Horse	O
was	O
by	O
it	O
beat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Cartway	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
which	O
running	O
over	O
broke	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
Peaceable	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
towards	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Lamb	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
a	O
Lamb	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Flock	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Butcher	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ear	O
Ring	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Cypher	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Poringers	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Whitsonday	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Family	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
Ware	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Kemp	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
by	O
violently	O
throwing	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Stone	O
Hearth	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Evidenceit	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
warm	O
Words	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Dish-clout	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
against	O
the	O
Hearth	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Injury	O
she	O
received	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Wife	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cantwell	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1704	O
.	O
His	O
1st	O
Wife	O
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
at	O
St.	O
Germains	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
France	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1688.	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
giving	O
no	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
Searl	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
,	O
North	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Callico	O
Petticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
5	O
Suits	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Headcloaths	O
4	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lebar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Searl	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	O
North	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Sarah	O
North	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
their	O
Work-Shop	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Searl	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Eckington	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hester	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jenken	B-pers
Curtsenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Witham	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
Wait	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
That	O
going	O
off	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
Wait	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Williams	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joannah	B-pers
Dollison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barwel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
Window	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Lindsay	O
;	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
2	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
new-wash	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
rescuing	O
2	O
Men	O
from	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Queens	O
Service	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
from	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
his	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entered	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Strainer	O
,	O
Goods	O
Stolen	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
Stol'n	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Philis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
2	O
Stones	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Breadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Coopers	O
Howel	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
Languished	O
till	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Parker	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Parker	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
's	O
Door	O
:	O
That	O
high	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bidding	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
beat	O
his	O
Wife	O
as	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Swore	O
by	O
his	O
Maker	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
step	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
punch	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Elbows	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retreated	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
desist	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Howel	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
still	O
persisting	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
strike	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
with	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Weapon	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
large	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
brought	O
divers	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Quarrelsome	O
Disposition	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
divers	O
substantial	O
Persons	O
,	O
Men	O
of	O
Quality	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
peaceable	O
quiet	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
whole	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bore	O
any	O
Premeditated	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
;	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bignel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Leatherfetch	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Hesikias	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shurley	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
Persons	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Bag	O
,	O
a	O
Gores	O
Stone	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Shurley	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
called	O
a	O
Louis	O
d'Or	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
from	O
home	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
and	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
fast	O
:	O
That	O
returning	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Locks	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
and	O
Scrutore	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
frequent	O
his	O
House	O
)	O
caus	O
'd	O
his	O
Lodging	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
a	O
Portmantua	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Goods	O
:	O
That	O
upon	O
Examination	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
restor	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
15	O
of	O
his	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Hart	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	O
Aldersgatestreet	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
producing	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Worsdel	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Worsdel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Rut	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munk	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
11	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
4	O
Raysors	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
Holland	O
Triming	O
Cloaths	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Munk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
value	O
37	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Marshal	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
1	O
Dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Childrens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	O
Thomson	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Crafts	O
a	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Ann	O
Worsdel	O
,	O
directed	O
himself	O
and	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
breaking	O
;	O
that	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
and	O
himself	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
but	O
Rut	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
A	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
when	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
3d	O
Crafts	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Ann	O
Worsdel	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
them	O
with	O
Thompson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
as	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
)	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
,	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
Ann	O
Worsdel	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
afterwards	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
by	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
last	O
Indictments	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Franklon	I-pers
Condrio	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
Goldsmith	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
Forg	O
'd	O
and	O
Publish	O
'd	O
at	O
Worcester	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
confin	O
'd	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
down	O
and	O
try	O
'd	O
at	O
Worcester	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Uttering	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
a	O
110	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
Payment	O
for	O
Watches	O
,	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Note	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
fully	O
to	O
be	O
Forg	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Forgery	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Stolen	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
Stolen	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bunting	O
Cloth	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Thread	O
Lace	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
alias	O
Jones	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
66	O
Ells	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Chaunce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stoke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
alias	O
Sary	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
June	O
the	O
3d	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Medal	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Broad	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
18	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
his	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
alias	O
Boult	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
leaving	O
her	O
alone	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Murfy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Steal	O
Files	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Maupas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
plainly	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Richard	B-pers
Northcoat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Ewes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
50	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Evan	O
Ewes	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Felony	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Buglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Claudius	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tilly	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Tilly	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
1	O
Pound	O
15	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lynes	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prison	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
while	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elianor	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
M	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
Roger	O
Worsdel	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
13	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Allen	O
,	O
Jane	O
Holt	O
,	O
Ann	O
Hutchins	O
,	O
David	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Jane	O
Cole	O
,	O
Jane	O
Jenkinson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Mary	O
North	O
,	O
Richard	O
Northcoat	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Needham	O
,	O
R	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Ann	O
Price	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Ware	O
.	O
Petit	O
Larcenies	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
Amy	O
Wait	O
,	O
Joannah	O
Dolison	O
,	O
Henry	O
Atkins	O
,	O
Ann	O
Pickering	O
,	O
Ann	O
Rawlinson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Green	O
,	O
Mary	O
Deal	O
,	O
Amy	O
Chaunce	O
,	O
Ann	O
Murfy	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bingnel	O
,	O
Susan	O
nah	O
Thomson	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Child	O
Fined	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
Just	O
Published	O
the	O
sixth	O
Edition	O
with	O
great	O
Additions	O
,	O
of	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
;	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
;	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
Infected	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
;	O
Easiness	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
infected	O
;	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
Skilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mountebanks	O
,	O
Impostors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Venereal	O
and	O
other	O
Gleets	O
,	O
Introductory	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
their	O
Life	O
and	O
Abuse	O
,	O
are	O
briefly	O
describ	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
Publishd	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marton	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
remov	O
'd	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Preface	O
in	O
the	O
Book	O
)	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
and	O
M.	O
Atkins	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenoe	O
at	O
Seneca	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Isted	O
against	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
THE	O
Charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
true	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
(	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
several	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
Charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinement	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nearest	O
Relation	O
,	O
Cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Methods	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
or	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
hazardous	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoin	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Seat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
seculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
curing	O
their	O
Gleets	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
Seminal	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
pertinent	O
Observations	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
certain	O
easy	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
Infection	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
often	O
accompanying	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
polluted	O
Companion	O
.	O
By	O
T.C	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
,	O
Edward	O
Curle	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
fetch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
THere	O
is	O
Printed	O
at	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Printing-Office	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Common-Prayer	O
,	O
in	O
410.	O
upon	O
very	O
good	O
Paper	O
and	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
Parish-Clarks	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
Families	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Avy	O
Mary-Lane	O
,	O
also	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
All	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common-Prayers	O
Ruld	O
or	O
un-Rul	O
'd	O
,	O
also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
to	O
3	O
Volumes	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
.	O
Dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
great	O
Oppressions	O
and	O
sinking	O
of	O
Spirits	O
(	O
title	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
Common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
Giddinesses	O
,	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Faintings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
)	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
:	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remove	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
The	O
fam	O
'd	O
Canker-Water	O
,	O
WHich	O
so	O
perfectly	O
and	O
immediately	O
cures	O
all	O
Cankers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heats	O
and	O
Inflammations	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
far	O
goes	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
Tongue	O
,	O
Cheeks	O
,	O
or	O
Lips	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
saved	O
he	O
Lives	O
of	O
severel	O
both	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
only	O
to	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
Robins	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Exchange-alley	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Its	O
Vertue	O
decays	O
not	O
in	O
keeping	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
useful	O
and	O
much	O
esteemed	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
Incomparable	O
Cordial	O
Stomach	O
Pills	O
,	O
WHich	O
without	O
Purging	O
,	O
Confinement	O
,	O
or	O
Trouble	O
,	O
absolutely	O
Cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
,	O
Indigestions	O
,	O
Stoppage	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
disorders	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
Inveterate	O
or	O
Extream	O
,	O
proceeding	O
from	O
what	O
Cause	O
soever	O
;	O
also	O
wonderfully	O
Comforts	O
and	O
Strengthens	O
a	O
Cold	O
,	O
Raw	O
,	O
Weakly	O
and	O
Sickly	O
Stomach	O
,	O
discharging	O
thence	O
by	O
natural	O
by	O
tuation	O
only	O
,	O
all	O
impure	O
or	O
offending	O
Matter	O
:	O
Procures	O
a	O
good	O
appetite	O
,	O
and	O
admirably	O
expels	O
Wind	O
.	O
These	O
Excellent	O
Pills	O
being	O
very	O
small	O
and	O
safe	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
may	O
readily	O
be	O
taken	O
at	O
all	O
Seasons	O
;	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Difficulty	O
or	O
Danger	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s	O
per	O
Box	O
(	O
containing	O
9	O
Doses	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
usually	O
enough	O
for	O
Cure	O
.	O
)	O
Sold	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
Stationer	O
upon	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
mr	O
.	O
Marshal	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Grace	O
Church	O
street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
at	O
Purcels	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mayos	O
,	O
Stationer	O
,	O
against	O
Water	O
Lane	O
end	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Christian	O
,	O
Drugster	O
,	O
against	O
Somerset	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
A	O
safe	O
and	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
WHither	O
it	O
proceeds	O
from	O
Rheume	O
,	O
Rottenness	O
of	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Worms	O
in	O
'em	O
,	O
or	O
Stumps	O
,	O
&	O
c.'Tis	O
a	O
Liquid	O
,	O
prepar	O
'd	O
without	O
any	O
Mercury	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
pernicious	O
Ingredients	O
too	O
often	O
used	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
commonly	O
attend	O
'd	O
with	O
unhappy	O
Effects	O
;	O
this	O
incomparable	O
Remedy	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
safely	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
certainly	O
Curos	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
Invertterate	O
,	O
Violent	O
and	O
Raging	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
effectually	O
preserves	O
both	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
from	O
Putrefaction	O
and	O
Decay	O
,	O
and	O
absolutely	O
clears	O
'em	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Sold	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
Stationer	O
,	O
upon	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Milner	O
at	O
the	O
red	O
M	O
,	O
in	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jenning	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Milk	O
Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Parson	O
a	O
Cane	O
Shop	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Horn	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Perrcy	O
Perfumer	O
next	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Howel	O
Perfumer	O
,	O
next	O
Leicester	O
House	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
Da	O
.	O
Perronct	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
Arms	O
in	O
Dyot	O
Street	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
NOw	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
few	O
Days	O
will	O
be	O
Published	O
all	O
the	O
Work	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Edmund	O
Hickeringil	O
Rector	O
of	O
All	O
Saints	O
in	O
Colchester	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
Volumes	O
in	O
80	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
his	O
Picture	O
curiously	O
engraven	O
on	O
a	O
Copper	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
his	O
Mescellaneous	O
Tracts	O
bound	O
or	O
single	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
SEcret	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Cloudesly	O
Shovel	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Admiral	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Wooden	O
World	O
diffected	O
,	O
in	O
14	O
Characters	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
Edition	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Seditious	O
Insects	O
or	O
the	O
Levellers	O
assembled	O
in	O
Convocation	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
's	O
Tale	O
from	O
the	O
28th	O
Book	O
of	O
Orlando	O
Furiosa	O
,	O
P.	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Don	O
Politico	O
Piscatoria	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Political	O
Fisherman	O
,	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Court	O
Favourite	O
,	O
p	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Sotweed	O
Factor	O
or	O
a	O
Voyage	O
to	O
Maryland	O
,	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
An	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
the	O
Prohibition	O
of	O
Commerce	O
with	O
France	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
present	O
War	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
fraudulent	O
Methods	O
usually	O
taken	O
to	O
cheat	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
of	O
her	O
Customs	O
,	O
and	O
Proposals	O
for	O
preventing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
Sentences	O
of	O
the	O
Diffenters	O
with	O
timely	O
Remarks	O
,	O
p.	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Fence	O
for	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
,	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
Mrs.	O
Francis	O
Shaftoes	O
Narrative	O
containing	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
in	O
it	O
Theophilus	O
Oglethorps	O
Family	O
,	O
where	O
hearing	O
many	O
treasonable	O
things	O
and	O
among	O
others	O
that	O
the	O
pretended	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
,	O
Sir	O
Theophilus	O
's	O
son	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
All	O
sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
A	O
Physician	O
of	O
Eminence	O
and	O
great	O
Practice	O
in	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
in	O
compassion	O
to	O
such	O
who	O
are	O
distemper	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
thro	O
'	O
Ignorance	O
or	O
Indigence	O
,	O
neglect	O
timely	O
Care	O
,	O
or	O
fall	O
into	O
unskilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
,	O
has	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
offer	O
some	O
gentle	O
purging	O
Pills	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
purchas	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
Price	O
,	O
which	O
alone	O
(	O
without	O
hinderance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Inconveniency	O
,	O
and	O
usually	O
in	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Day	O
time	O
)	O
safely	O
and	O
compleatly	O
cure	O
any	O
Conorrhaea	O
,	O
or	O
Robbing	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
with	O
Heat	O
and	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urin	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
ill	O
cur	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
clear	O
of	O
any	O
Relicks	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Disease	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Water-man	O
's	O
Arms	O
behind	O
old	O
Round	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
containing	O
six	O
Doses	O
,	O
seal	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
printed	O
Directions	O
for	O
their	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
delivered	O
to	O
any	O
Messenger	O
.	O
Convulsions	O
having	O
of	O
Late	O
been	O
extremely	O
Rife	O
and	O
Mortal	O
amounting	O
to	O
one	O
fourth	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Weekly	O
Bills	O
of	O
Mortality	O
,	O
not	O
withstanding	O
the	O
many	O
Infallible	O
Remedies	O
publickly	O
pretended	O
to	O
&	O
c.	O
Therefore	O
supposing	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
found	O
of	O
that	O
Certainty	O
in	O
Cure	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Inducement	O
to	O
what	O
is	O
here	O
offer	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Remedy	O
of	O
a	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
physician	O
,	O
which	O
't	O
is	O
hoped	O
will	O
better	O
answer	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
made	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
dangerous	O
Cases	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
known	O
it	O
to	O
fail	O
of	O
Success	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
other	O
Means	O
used	O
,	O
has	O
had	O
no	O
effect	O
:	O
Being	O
also	O
of	O
that	O
gentleness	O
and	O
safety	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Sucking	O
Child	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
hazard	O
.	O
It	O
gives	O
present	O
help	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
amazing	O
Disorders	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Fits	O
be	O
almost	O
continuel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
parts	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
Convulsed	O
and	O
Distorted	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
very	O
ready	O
and	O
effectual	O
help	O
for	O
all	O
Risings	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Sick	O
be	O
almost	O
Strangled	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
apparent	O
danger	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
had	O
of	O
a	O
Physician	O
at	O
the	O
Smyrna	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Finch	O
Lane	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
spoken	O
with	O
from	O
8	O
to	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
.	O
