TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
Days	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1708/9	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DUNCOMBE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Brownwel	I-pers
David	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bodicoat	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
More	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
Brian	B-pers
Turbervil	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cliffe	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltby	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Litchburn	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dymond	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wyburd	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Pryor	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
16	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tilden	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Main	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Porter	O
being	O
at	O
their	O
Warehouse	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
Hogsheads	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
stepping	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
his	O
Apron	O
and	O
Pockets	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Middleditch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
producing	O
divers	O
substantial	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Warman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
King	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
together	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
themselves	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
retire	O
a	O
little	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
presently	O
return	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
:	O
That	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
Circumstances	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sufficient	O
reason	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
who	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
loose	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Wife	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
June	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
1705.	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
gave	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Marriage	O
with	O
Stroud	O
being	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Byren	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Singleton	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Ham	O
of	O
Bacon	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
22	O
Sheeps	O
Tongues	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
shut	O
the	O
Hatch	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
down	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Williard	I-pers
alias	O
Gladman	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Satten	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapened	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
buying	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Sheet	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Skelthorp	I-pers
alias	O
Skulthorp	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Hills	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
new-Buildings	O
from	O
the	O
Strand	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Kings-street	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
direct	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Horse-pond	O
dried	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
by	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
demanding	O
of	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Bionet	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
That	O
hethen	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
great	O
Coat	O
from	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Rings	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
People	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
beg	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Mony	O
and	O
Coat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pretended	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
committed	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
him	O
was	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Affront	O
,	O
in	O
tempting	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
so	O
foul	O
a	O
Crime	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
these	O
Assertions	O
,	O
nor	O
producing	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
again	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Booker	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assaulted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
William	O
Hills	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steevenson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Firing	O
the	O
Mansion	O
House	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Palfreman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
49	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Ring	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Mitre	O
Tavern	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Mony	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
thereupon	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constables	O
came	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	B-place
as	O
disorderly	O
Persons	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
convey	O
'd	O
herself	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Appartment	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Mony	O
and	O
Ring	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
'till	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Manslaughter	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
More	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
depos	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
2	O
Brothers	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Charles	O
,	O
Colonel	B-pers
Lillystone	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
at	O
Daniel	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Gerrard-street	O
,	O
and	O
continu	O
'd	O
Drinking	O
'till	O
2	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
Charles	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
took	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
's	O
Neice	O
by	O
the	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
his	O
Niece	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Words	O
arose	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Brothers	O
part	O
,	O
Colonel	O
Lillystone	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
's	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
by	O
the	O
Colonel	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
safe	O
Home	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Blows	O
exchang	O
'd	O
between	O
Charles	O
Walker	O
and	O
the	O
Colonel	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Walkers	O
were	O
thrust	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
whispered	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Ear	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
heard	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
stretch	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Arm	O
and	O
said	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Walkers	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
Colonel	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
,	O
being	O
accompanied	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
's	O
Boy	O
with	O
a	O
link	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Colonel	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
returning	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
,	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
Saluted	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
and	O
parried	O
a	O
while	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
then	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
received	O
very	O
abusive	O
Language	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
peaceably	O
Home	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Home	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Colonel	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
likewise	O
Home	O
,	O
bringing	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stood	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Rascal	O
and	O
cowardly	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Damn	O
him	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
Reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
over-hearing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
bear	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
Coward	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
slipt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
after	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
mutually	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
Fought	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
few	O
passes	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
his	O
Deaths	O
Wound	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
dear	O
More	O
,	O
and	O
lead	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watchouse	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
dress	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
attempt	O
to	O
work	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Death	O
Bed	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
be	O
discharged	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
seeking	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
abundance	O
of	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Malt	O
Ticket	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
77588	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Farthing	O
a	O
Day	O
Interest	O
,	O
bearing	O
Date	O
July	O
27th	O
1697	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
Guenetta	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
a	O
Malt	O
Ticket	O
to	O
the	O
Malt	O
Office	O
at	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
to	O
be	O
Check	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Ticket	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
much	O
difficulty	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
closely	O
examin	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
full	O
Discovery	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Ticket	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
good	O
and	O
some	O
bad	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Guenetta	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
gave	O
up	O
a	O
Box	O
wherein	O
was	O
contain	O
'd	O
divers	O
Plates	O
of	O
Tickets	O
,	O
Graving	O
Tools	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
ofMaterials	O
that	O
are	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
of	O
Tickets	O
.	O
The	O
Ticket	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
nicest	O
Observation	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeited	O
from	O
a	O
Plate	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Box	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
write	O
in	O
3	O
Tickets	O
R.	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Name	O
that	O
is	O
Written	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
each	O
true	O
Ticket	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
exactly	O
done	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
scarcely	O
discernable	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
True	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
ones	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hibbard	I-pers
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
lately	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
nameless	O
Person	O
and	O
bring	O
him	O
the	O
Tickets	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hibbard	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
nameless	O
Person	O
brought	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Materials	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
fit	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Tickets	O
without	O
passing	O
the	O
Check	O
.	O
But	O
producing	O
no	O
Proof	O
to	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carriton	I-pers
alias	O
Gallow	B-pers
alias	O
Thomson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Scarves	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Girdle	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
finding	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
proving	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Redmond	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Chimney	O
Glass	O
,	O
11	O
Pictures	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
desire	O
,	O
was	O
granted	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blansfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
parsel	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smythy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
by	O
an	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
from	O
Bedford	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Blakaby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brerecliff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
visit	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Rodericks	I-pers
alias	O
Waller	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wappen	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
17	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
alias	O
Jockey	B-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Bessick	O
a	O
Horse	O
Stealer	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
Minor	O
near	O
Plimouth	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Possession	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
Minor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
according	O
to	O
Bessicks	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Rone	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
who	O
according	O
to	O
Bessicks	O
Information	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
upon	O
Richard	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smythy	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
having	O
lost	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
were	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
William	O
Jackson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lost	O
his	O
Gelding	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
a	O
frivolous	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
1	O
Cock	O
and	O
7	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Furbelow	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dan	B-pers
.	I-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
Northen	I-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
200	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
35	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Rowley	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walder	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Walden	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davenant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
;	O
2	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
A	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Copley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Dish	O
5	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Copley	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
others	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Garden	O
Wall	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chamber	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
so	O
full	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
Swear	O
possitively	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Hour	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Polfreeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Prudam	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
his	O
Cart	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Prudam	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
other	O
Child	O
ren	O
were	O
playing	O
in	O
the	O
Queens	O
High-way	O
with	O
Straw	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
seeing	O
him	O
drove	O
his	O
Cart	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
's	O
Case	O
,	O
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
by	O
Certiorary	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Bench	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brerewood	I-pers
,	O
that	O
was	O
formerly	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Defrauding	O
Mr.	O
Pitkins	O
Creditors	O
,	O
and	O
Absconded	O
contrary	O
to	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliment	O
made	O
on	O
his	O
Account	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Imprisoned	O
during	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
3	O
times	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
first	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
Easter	O
Term	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
Michaelmas	O
Term	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
Hillary	O
Term	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
11	O
and	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Days	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
7	O
.	O
Martha	O
Elliot	O
,	O
Martha	O
Warman	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
A	O
-	O
,	O
George	O
Skeltborp	O
,	O
Edward	O
Cox	O
,	O
John	O
Berry	O
,	O
John	O
Cook	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
;	O
Ann	O
Blakaby	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Trott	O
.	O
Petit	O
Larcenies	O
7	O
.	O
John	O
Beaumnont	O
,	O
John	O
Polfreeman	O
,	O
M	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Byrin	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Thompson	O
,	O
David	O
Richards	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Williard	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
THE	O
Office	O
of	O
the	O
Taylors	O
Friendly	O
Society	O
,	O
for	O
Insurance	O
upon	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
,	O
is	O
kept	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Witch-street	O
,	O
3	O
days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Tuesdays	O
and	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
from	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
1	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
to	O
7	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
,	O
every	O
second	O
and	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
every	O
Month	O
,	O
the	O
Trustees	O
constantly	O
meet	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
:	O
And	O
on	O
Thursday	O
at	O
the	O
crooked	O
Billet	O
in	O
Billeter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Spotted-Dog	O
in	O
Shoemaker-row	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryars	O
,	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Hours	O
.	O
Here	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
assuring	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
and	O
by	O
Wifes	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
when	O
1500	O
have	O
Subscrib	O
'd	O
,	O
200	O
l.	O
at	O
their	O
Deaths	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
which	O
Subscribes	O
upon	O
their	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
shall	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
be	O
reduced	O
to	O
Poverty	O
and	O
want	O
Relief	O
,	O
all	O
such	O
shall	O
be	O
relieved	O
and	O
assisted	O
with	O
all	O
things	O
necessary	O
at	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Society	O
,	O
till	O
their	O
Claims	O
come	O
due	O
.	O
The	O
charge	O
which	O
each	O
Subscriber	O
pays	O
,	O
for	O
Policies	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
Entrance	O
and	O
first	O
Claim	O
being	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
second	O
Insurance	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Number	O
,	O
kept	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Amicable	O
Society	O
,	O
whereby	O
any	O
Subscriber	O
to	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
whether	O
Male	O
or	O
Female	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
may	O
it	O
they	O
please	O
become	O
Subscribers	O
here	O
also	O
by	O
paying	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
Policy	O
,	O
Stamps	O
and	O
Entrance	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
Quarter	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
will	O
120	O
l.	O
be	O
divided	O
Quarterly	O
among	O
the	O
Executors	O
,	O
Administrators	O
or	O
Nominees	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
overtaken	O
with	O
Poverty	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
relieved	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Society	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
other	O
Benefits	O
which	O
are	O
too	O
large	O
here	O
to	O
mention	O
,	O
shall	O
therefore	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Abstract	O
of	O
the	O
Settlement	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
Print	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Gratis	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Places	O
where	O
the	O
Office	O
is	O
kept	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
before	O
directed	O
.	O
THis	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
That	O
any	O
Person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Minister	O
's	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Cassocks	O
,	O
Silk	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Sashes	O
Lawyers	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Livery	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Gowns	O
for	O
Mayors	O
and	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
any	O
Corporation	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Anthony	O
Ingram	O
,	O
Robe-maker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Livery	O
Hood	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
North-Gare	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
who	O
bath	O
of	O
them	O
ready	O
made	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
at	O
reasonable	O
Pieces	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
and	O
Prknclla	O
sold	O
for	O
Ministers	O
wear	O
.	O
THE	O
Charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Rememedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
true	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
(	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
several	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
in	O
both	O
exes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanell	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
Charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinement	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nearest	O
Relation	O
,	O
cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
a	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Methods	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
or	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
hazardous	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoin	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Seat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
received	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
peculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
during	O
their	O
Gleets	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
Seminal	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
pertinent	O
Observations	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
certain	O
easie	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
Infection	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
often	O
accompanying	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
polluted	O
Companion	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
C.	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	O
Chorle	O
at	O
the	O
seacock	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
1708	O
price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
THE	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Robert	O
Feilding	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Marrying	O
her	O
Crac	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Cleeaveland	O
;	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mary	O
Wadsworth	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
with	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Letters	O
between	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mr.	O
Wadsworth	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Anne	O
Countess	O
of	O
Fielding	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
all	O
the	O
Learned	O
Arguments	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
Perused	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
spiritual	O
Court	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sentences	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Morphew	O
near	O
Stationers-Hall	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
MArten	O
's	O
Treatise	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
,	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
infected	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Insallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
.	O
Business	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
infected	O
;	O
Reasons	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
Skilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
liver	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taints	O
and	O
Mercury	O
.	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mountebanks	O
Impoltors	O
&	O
c.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
or	O
Seminal	O
,	O
briefly	O
describing	O
the	O
use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
their	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
Publishd	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marten	O
.	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
and	O
M.	O
Atkins	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
A	O
Collins	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Seneca	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westmin-ster-Hall	O
;	O
Book	O
sellers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
further	O
and	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
beyond	O
the	O
Chappel	O
,	O
John	O
Marten	O
Surgeon	O
writ	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
.	O
MArten	O
's	O
Appendix	O
to	O
the	O
sixth	O
Edition	O
of	O
his	O
Book	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
new	O
System	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Secret	O
Infirmities	O
and	O
Diseases	O
,	O
Natural	O
,	O
Accidental	O
and	O
Venereal	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
that	O
defile	O
and	O
ruin	O
the	O
Healths	O
of	O
themselves	O
and	O
their	O
Posterity	O
,	O
obstruct	O
Conjugal	O
Delectancy	O
and	O
Pregnancy	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
various	O
Methods	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
Something	O
particular	O
concerning	O
Generation	O
and	O
Conception	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
Miscarriages	O
in	O
Women	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Causes	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
done	O
before	O
.	O
Useful	O
for	O
Physicians	O
,	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
Apothecaries	O
,	O
and	O
Midwives	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
Have	O
,	O
or	O
Are	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
sassing	O
under	O
any	O
such	O
Impure	O
or	O
Defective	O
Indispositions	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
further	O
warning	O
against	O
Quacks	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
some	O
less	O
notorious	O
Abuses	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
that	O
People	O
may	O
avoid	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Marten	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
Printed	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Letter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Paper	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
his	O
Book	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
who	O
please	O
may	O
bind	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Sold	O
in	O
Octavo	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Places	O
above	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
THE	O
Truth	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Murders	O
,	O
Robberies	O
and	O
Burnings	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
Bradsorton	O
and	O
Upton-Snodsbury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Worcetter	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
Examination	O
,	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
,	O
of	O
John	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
Tho	O
.	O
Symonds	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	O
Hobbins	O
and	O
John	O
Allen	O
,	O
Labourars	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Crimes	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Bp	O
.	O
of	O
Oxford	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
after	O
their	O
Condemnation	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
whole	O
Transaction	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Likewise	O
,	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
remarks	O
on	O
their	O
dying	O
Speeches	O
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
on	O
Occasion	O
of	O
a	O
late	O
inperfect	O
,	O
false	O
and	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Entituled	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
John	O
Palmer	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Symonds	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
who	O
were	O
executed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
R.	O
W.	O
-	O
Printed	O
for	O
Jonah	O
Bowyer	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
ALL	O
,	O
Melancholly	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
great	O
Oppressions	O
and	O
Sinking	O
of	O
Spirt	O
's	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
Giddinesses	O
,	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Paintings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
,	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convolsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
:	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
RObert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed	O
Lane	O
,	O
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Aye-Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
Booksellers	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rull	O
'd	O
or	O
unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
or	O
plain	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrand	O
,	O
also	O
other	O
fine	O
Cuts	O
and	O
fitted	O
for	O
all	O
Sizes	O
of	O
Common-Prayer	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
Works	O
of	O
all	O
Sizes	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
in	O
Latin	O
.	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
Common-Prayers	O
,	O
Tast	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Psalms	O
,	O
with-the	O
new	O
Supplement	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
The	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
In	O
3	O
Washington	O
and	O
Wingate	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
,	O
Clarendor	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
in	O
Folio	O
and	O
Octave	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
new	O
Transactions	O
Esops	O
Fables	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Cuts	O
are	O
likewise	O
sold	O
by	O
Y.	O
Baker	O
in	O
Mercet	O
chappel	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Also	O
Bp	O
.	O
Beveradges	O
Writes	O
ins	O
Vol	O
.	O
Dean	O
Stamphan	O
in	O
the	O
Epistles	O
and	O
Gospels	O
,	O
in	O
4	O
Vol	O
.	O
The	O
Witch	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
.	O
RElief	O
and	O
a	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
stubborn	O
and	O
inveterate	O
Poxes	O
,	O
of	O
so	O
long	O
standing	O
that	O
the	O
vary	O
Bones	O
are	O
Infected	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Patient	O
so	O
deplorable	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
violent	O
fains	O
,	O
Victers	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
to	O
despair	O
of	O
ever	O
being	O
cured	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Method	O
and	O
Medicine	O
,	O
payroll	O
by	O
near	O
20	O
Years	O
successful	O
Practice	O
,	O
to	O
perform	O
in	O
each	O
Cases	O
a	O
speedy	O
,	O
last	O
effectual	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
insatiable	O
Cure	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Cronorrha	O
,	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reives	O
or	O
Clap	O
,	O
the	O
Infection	O
in	O
perfectly	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
and	O
the	O
Cure	O
Compleated	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
hindrance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
Days	O
time	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Golden	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
Passage	O
(	O
the	O
most	O
private	O
place	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
)	O
three	O
Doors	O
beyond	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Hony	O
Lane	O
Market	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
