TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1710	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
GARRARD	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tennet	I-pers
Icabod	B-pers
Dawkes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kelson	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Finchway	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Appleford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hutt	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Grosvenor	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Tredway	I-pers
John	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pannet	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Winkfield	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
Alex	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harwood	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
three	O
silver-hafted	O
Knives	O
,	O
three	O
silver-hasted	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Servant	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
stirring	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
speaking	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
alias	O
Riddal	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
four	O
broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
double	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
Clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Prudence	B-pers
Pollet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
a	O
washing	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
up	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
Felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
alias	O
Still	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
Stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Huntly	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Drugget	O
for	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Servant	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
reach	O
some	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
serving	O
a	O
Customer	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
saw	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
He	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
called	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
dropt	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
Catherine	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	O
Green	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
10	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Gloves	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missed	O
10	O
Pair	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
dropt	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hicks	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
alias	O
Read	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
pretending	O
to	O
direct	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
for	O
a	O
Charity	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
it	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
13	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
likewise	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
aKindness	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
.	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
they	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
18	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Mony	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
privately	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Feather	O
Pillow	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Barnaby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Stand	O
in	O
the	O
Lace	B-place
Chamber	I-place
,	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samson	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Horse	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
told	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
trac	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Dammasier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cutbert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
producing	O
substantial	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Table	O
Linen	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Henrious	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
sick	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
Person	O
down	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Occasion	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
12	O
d.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Annet	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Bed-Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
paying	O
10	O
counterfeit	O
Crown	O
Peices	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
in	O
counterfeit	O
Crown	O
Peices	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
buy	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
producing	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Maulden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Flock	O
Bed	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Callico	O
Quilt	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Pigion	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
'em	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Pigion	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
:	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Locket	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Coral	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
40	O
s.	O
4	O
gold	O
Rings	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
unlocked	O
her	O
Trunk	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
one	O
Tess	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
with	O
one	O
Rachel	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Felony	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butteridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Istleworth	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
100	O
bundles	O
of	O
Laths	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
apprehended	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
lac	O
'd	O
Holland	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt-Seller	O
,	O
a	O
Tortois	O
Shell	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
9	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
alias	O
Kennet	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
double	O
Guinea	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
Cloths	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Gold	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Ram	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Callico	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Unite	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
168	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
they	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stol'n	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Person	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
clearly	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Green	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Caudrie	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Shales	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Foot	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
4	O
Casements	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ledger	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stol'n	O
from	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hest	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Blue	O
and	O
White	O
Linnen	O
Scotch	O
.	O
Cloath	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cardell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fully	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
producing	O
several	O
substantial	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
;	O
three	O
Shirts	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Paxter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sheave	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clapham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
Maribon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
46	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
alias	O
Frederick	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
23	O
Ells	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Darlton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
was	O
sent	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
morning	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted-Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Widdow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Whitby	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cabel-Rope	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
double-headed	O
Shot	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Bomb-boat	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Direction	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
the	O
Bomb-boat	O
's	O
Woman	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
13	O
Fans	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gambell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
Adams	O
was	O
cheapening	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
Neal	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
Adams	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
alias	O
Gordon	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stuff-Curtains	O
,	O
3	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mekanys	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Sisters	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
High-Cross	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pigs	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
old	I-place
Artillery	I-place
Ground	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted-Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
that	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
apprehending	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Boreman	I-pers
alias	O
Essex	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
North	I-place
and	I-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dollison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
:	O
Upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wooton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
leaving	O
her	O
alone	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-Vintry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Frusherd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Coals	O
in	O
a	O
Wherry	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stol'n	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
April	O
19.	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Damaree	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
follow	O
,	O
were	O
Sworn	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Peter	B-pers
Lavign	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Breeden	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Charles	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Peter	B-pers
Laccuse	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Selman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Collis	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Damaree	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements-Danes	I-place
,	O
Waterman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
multitude	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
500	O
,	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
Swords	O
and	O
Clubs	O
,	O
raise	O
and	O
levy	O
publick	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Witness	O
,	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Talboy	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
That	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
Thousands	O
of	O
People	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
attended	O
upon	O
Dr.	O
Sacheverell	O
from	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
would	O
pull	O
down	O
Mr.	O
Burges	O
's	O
Meeting-House	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
others	O
were	O
for	O
pulling	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
ensuing	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
sort	O
not	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Event	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Sacheverell	O
's	O
Tryal	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
agreed	O
in	O
the	O
Design	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
differ	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Execution	O
,	O
which	O
however	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
2d	O
Witness	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Orril	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Leonard	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
Burges	O
's	O
Meeting-house	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
Service	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
Discoveries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
the	O
first	O
Place	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
Meeting-house	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
People	O
rifling	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
And	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Ten	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn-Fields	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bon-fire	O
made	O
with	O
the	O
Materials	O
brought	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Burges	O
's	O
Meeting-house	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
from	O
him	O
(	O
towards	O
Powis-House	O
)	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
headed	O
by	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
Badge	O
on	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
twirl	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
,	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
lead	O
you	O
on	O
,	O
God	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
Meeting-houses	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
lead	O
you	O
on	O
.	O
High-Church	O
and	O
Sacheverell	O
,	O
Hazza	O
!	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
that	O
part	O
was	O
divided	O
among	O
themselves	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Councel	O
of	O
Mob	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
others	O
objected	O
against	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
Hen	O
roost	O
,	O
and	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Meeting	O
was	O
worth	O
ten	O
of	O
that	O
in	O
Wild-street	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
quick	O
as	O
their	O
Leaderwould	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
High-Church	O
and	O
Sacheverell	O
,	O
Huzza	O
!	O
That	O
then	O
this	O
Witness	O
lost	O
him	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Ten	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
:	O
He	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
the	O
Brass-Sconce	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burges	O
's	O
Meeting-house	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
with	O
the	O
Utensils	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burges	O
's	O
Meeting	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
Procession	O
,	O
there	O
go	O
with	O
it	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
round	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
Huzzaing	O
with	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
High-Church	O
and	O
Sacheverell	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
flung	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
principal	O
Men	O
in	O
exciting	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Guards	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
active	O
in	O
assisting	O
,	O
animating	O
and	O
exciting	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
from	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Wood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lady	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
Coals	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
no	O
where	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
they	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Crowd	O
thro	O
'	O
Shere-Lane	O
into	O
Lincolns-Inn-Square	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Wicket	O
into	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
;	O
That	O
against	O
the	O
Wicket	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Cloth	O
,	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
They	O
they	O
would	O
dash	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
laid	O
Hands	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
Alehouse-keeper	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Ten	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
any	O
News	O
of	O
a	O
Fire	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
no	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
Charles	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
Wood	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
News	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
after	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
,	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Light	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
News	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Company	O
were	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
8	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
about	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
a	O
11	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
talking	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Giles	O
about	O
6	O
Doors	O
from	O
Water-Lane	O
;	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
one	O
Cummins	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
hauling	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Sport	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
going	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
Brother	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
in	O
Lincoln-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
did	O
see	O
a	O
Sconce	O
carry	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Queens	O
Coat	O
and	O
Badge	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
Man	O
in	O
black	O
Hair	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
carried	O
the	O
Sconce	O
round	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
distinguish	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
about	O
the	O
Fire	O
?	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
through	O
their	O
Legs	O
and	O
Arms	O
:	O
She	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
through	O
Great	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
Sconce	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
almost	O
burnt	O
to	O
Ashes	O
.	O
Sabella	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
Redding	O
's	O
Companion	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
replied	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Mob	O
opened	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
receive	O
those	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Wood	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Great	O
Queen-street	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
when	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
at	O
Strand-Bridge	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Harvey	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
May	O
Pole	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
piece	O
of	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
agreeing	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
agreeing	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Queens	O
in	O
many	O
Points	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
whom	O
the	O
greatest	O
Stress	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
laid	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
uncertain	O
and	O
contradictory	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Persons	O
Sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
for	O
Francis	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Breakspear	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hazzard	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
People	O
with	O
Swords	O
and	O
Clubs	O
,	O
did	O
Levy	O
publick	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
was	O
Talboy	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
his	O
Deposition	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Design	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
at	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
Dr.	O
Burges	O
's	O
Meeting	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lunt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
when	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
was	O
in	O
Hatten-Garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
Captain	O
that	O
Night	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Window-Curtain	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bradburies	O
Meeting-House	O
for	O
an	O
Ensign	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
display	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
burnt	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
with	O
the	O
Utensils	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bradburie	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Footman	O
with	O
a	O
Pole	O
and	O
a	O
Curtain	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
Standard	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
stepp	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Mony	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
High	O
Church	O
:	O
This	O
Witness	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
saw	O
in	O
Holborn	O
carrying	O
the	O
Colour	O
?	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
altered	O
by	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
like	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
what	O
Cloths	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
?	O
replied	O
,	O
either	O
Blue	O
or	O
Green	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
uncertain	O
which	O
:	O
Being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
saw	O
that	O
Man	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
waved	O
the	O
Curtain	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
?	O
Replied	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Turn-Keys	O
of	O
Newgate	O
being	O
Sworn	O
,	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
Whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Grove	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lunt	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
Whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Colours	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Council	O
moved	O
,	O
That	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Lunt	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
against	O
himself	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
Seventh	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
,	O
which	O
says	O
expresly	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
Person	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
shall	O
be	O
convicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
shall	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Orrill	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
particular	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
proved	O
the	O
general	O
Design	O
of	O
pulling	O
down	O
Meeting	O
Houses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
Defence	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
omit	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
Queen	O
's	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
Sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
for	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Furness	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Breakspear	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bearknife	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hazzard	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Multitude	O
of	O
People	O
Armed	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
levy	O
open	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Captain	O
Orrill	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Burges	O
's	O
Meeting-House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
Demolished	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fire	O
made	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Utensils	O
thereof	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Detachment	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Guards	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
law	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
made	O
with	O
the	O
Pews	O
and	O
other	O
Utensils	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
scattered	O
by	O
the	O
Guards	O
;	O
That	O
there	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
a	O
Bulk	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
pushed	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
theHorses	O
Breast	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
driven	O
from	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
small	O
Distance	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
That	O
then	O
this	O
Witness	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
opposing	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
he	O
opposed	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
taking	O
his	O
Advice	O
,	O
made	O
this	O
Reply	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
for	O
,	O
High-Church	O
and	O
Sacheverell	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
God	O
Damn	O
them	O
all	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Guards	O
)	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Mobb	O
,	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
come	O
on	O
Boys	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
lead	O
you	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
for	O
High-Church	O
and	O
Sacheverell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
lose	O
my	O
Life	O
in	O
the	O
Cause	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
run	O
resolutely	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
Pass	O
at	O
the	O
Officer	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
giving	O
a	O
large	O
,	O
Spring	O
,	O
beat	O
his	O
Sword	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
left	O
Flank	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
retir	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
lower	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guards	O
had	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
dispersed	O
all	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
knocking	O
down	O
about	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
:	O
As	O
this	O
Witness	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
say	O
,	O
They	O
would	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
Guards	O
to	O
Morrow	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
durst	O
not	O
fire	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Commanded	O
by	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
to	O
match	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
their	O
Bionets	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Mobb	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
were	O
all	O
drawn	O
into	O
one	O
Line	O
with	O
their	O
Tails	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
That	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Mobb	O
might	O
come	O
behind	O
;	O
That	O
Purchase	O
then	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
and	O
Huzza	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
thrust	O
himself	O
between	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
beaten	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Flats	O
of	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Guards	O
wheeled	O
about	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Mobb	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
for	O
?	O
Whether	O
for	O
High-Church	O
or	O
Low-Church	O
,	O
or	O
Dr.	O
Sacheverell	O
?	O
This	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Mobb	O
was	O
dispersed	O
there	O
.	O
One	O
Sutherland	O
,	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
that	O
drew	O
the	O
Grenadiers	O
up	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
there	O
saw	O
him	O
flourish	O
his	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
;	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
for	O
Sacheverell	O
:	O
This	O
Evidence	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
are	O
you	O
encouraging	O
the	O
Mobb	O
?	O
He	O
replied	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
for	O
Sacheverell	O
:	O
That	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Horsey	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
how	O
Troublesome	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Orders	O
from	O
the	O
Captain	O
to	O
cut	O
him	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
George	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
in	O
Flanders	O
;	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Guards	O
marched	O
from	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
quelled	O
the	O
Mobb	O
,	O
and	O
marched	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Mobb	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
struck	O
the	O
People	O
with	O
the	O
Flats	O
of	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
dispersed	O
them	O
;	O
This	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
make	O
a	O
Thrust	O
at	O
Captain	O
Hansberg	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
Kill	O
my	O
Officer	O
;	O
then	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
he	O
struck	O
down	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Point	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retired	O
under	O
a	O
Pent-House	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
rid	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
his	O
Sword	O
breaking	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Pent-House	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hansberg	O
,	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
Abroad	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Flanders	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence-produced	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had-been	O
drinking	O
from	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Broad	O
the	O
Balliff	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
contradicted	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
Sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
after	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
had	O
summed	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
Hours	O
,	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Points	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Special	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
four	O
Coils	O
of	O
Rope	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Chains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
2	O
Daniel	B-pers
Damaree	I-pers
,	O
Samson	O
Archer	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
21.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
alias	O
Green	O
,	O
Mary	O
Barlow	O
,	O
William	O
Barns	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Shales	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	O
Barn	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Southerland	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bearmen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Essex	O
Brown	O
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butteridge	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	O
Waler	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Edward	O
Whieby	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kennes	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	O
Peter	O
Units	O
,	O
John	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Petty	O
Larcenies	O
9.	O
Edward	B-pers
Warrington	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Maulden	O
,	O
Jane	O
Davis	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Bland	O
,	O
Hellena	O
Green	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
James	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
B	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
,	O
Fined	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
SToughton	O
's	O
great	O
Cordial	O
Elixir	O
:	O
Now	O
famous	O
throughout	O
Europe	O
for	O
the	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Blood	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
defended	O
in	O
the	O
Bais	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
prepar	O
'd	O
only	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
Apothecary	O
at	O
the	O
Un	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
set	O
forth	O
19	O
Years	O
:	O
It	O
makes	O
the	O
best	O
Purl	O
in	O
Beer	O
or	O
Ale	O
,	O
Purl	O
Royal	O
in	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
better	O
Draught	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
most	O
pleasant	O
Bitter	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
now	O
drank	O
by	O
most	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
their	O
Wine	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
,	O
much	O
exceeding	O
any	O
Bitter	O
made	O
with	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
so	O
excessive	O
hot	O
and	O
drying	O
,	O
thicken	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
dulls	O
the	O
spoils	O
the	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
recover	O
and	O
restore	O
a	O
weaken	O
'd	O
Stomach	O
or	O
lost	O
Appetite	O
beyond	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
taken	O
occasioned	O
by	O
hard	O
Drinking	O
or	O
Sickness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
certainly	O
carries	O
off	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
bad	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
too	O
many	O
die	O
of	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
incerted	O
in	O
the	O
Bills	O
with	O
It	O
almost	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
certainty	O
of	O
its	O
doing	O
this	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Occasions	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
made	O
publick	O
.	O
Sold	O
at	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
many	O
Booksellers	O
and	O
Coffee-houses	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
also	O
at	O
some	O
one	O
such	O
place	O
in	O
most	O
Cities	O
and	O
great	O
Towns	O
in	O
Europe	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Where	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
sold	O
,	O
any	O
Person	O
who	O
send	O
first	O
,	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
with	O
good	O
Allowance	O
,	O
many	O
now	O
selling	O
50	O
or	O
60	O
Dozen	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
some	O
more	O
.	O
Ready	O
Mony	O
expected	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Seal	O
on	O
each	O
Bottle	O
has	O
Richard	B-pers
Stoughton	I-pers
cut	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
THE	O
Office	O
of	O
the	O
Taylors	O
Friendly	O
Society	O
,	O
for	O
Insurance	O
upon	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
,	O
is	O
kept	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Witch	O
street	O
,	O
3	O
days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Tuesdays	O
and	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
from	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
1	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
to	O
7	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
,	O
every	O
second	O
and	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
every	O
Month	O
,	O
she	O
Trustees	O
constantly	O
meet	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
Thursday	O
at	O
the	O
crooked	O
Billet	O
in	O
Billeter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Spotted-Dog	O
in	O
Shoemaker-row	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryar	O
,	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Hours	O
.	O
Here	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
assuring	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
and	O
his	O
Wifes	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
when	O
1500	O
have	O
subscrib	O
'd	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
at	O
their	O
Deaths	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
which	O
Subscribes	O
upon	O
their	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
shall	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
all	O
such	O
shall	O
be	O
relieved	O
and	O
assisted	O
with	O
all	O
things	O
necessary	O
at	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Society	O
,	O
till	O
their	O
Claims	O
come	O
due	O
.	O
The	O
charge	O
which	O
each	O
Subscriber	O
pays	O
,	O
for	O
Policies	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
Entrance	O
and	O
first	O
being	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
second	O
Insurance	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Number	O
,	O
kept	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Places	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Arnicable	O
Society	O
,	O
whereby	O
any	O
Subscriber	O
to	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
whether	O
Male	O
or	O
Female	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
may	O
if	O
they	O
pleas	O
become	O
Subscribers	O
have	O
also	O
,	O
by	O
paying	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
10	O
.	O
Policy	O
Stamps	O
and	O
Entrance	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
Quarter	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
120	O
l.	O
be	O
divided	O
Quarterly	O
among	O
the	O
Executors	O
,	O
Administrators	O
or	O
Nominees	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
overtaken	O
which	O
shall	O
be	O
relieved	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Society	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
other	O
Benefits	O
which	O
are	O
too	O
large	O
here	O
to	O
mention	O
,	O
shall	O
therefore	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
Settlement	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
Print	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Gratis	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Office	O
is	O
kept	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
before	O
directed	O
.	O
THE	O
Charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
of	O
Curing	O
(	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
several	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Pattern	O
per	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
Charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinement	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
near	O
of	O
Relation	O
,	O
cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Methods	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
or	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
hazardous	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoin	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Scat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
received	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
peculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
curing	O
their	O
Gleets	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
Seminal	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
pertinent	O
Observations	O
relating	O
thereto	O
never	O
before	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
C.	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Curl	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Dial	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
MArten	O
's	O
Treatise	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
)	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infectig	O
;	O
the	O
N	O
or	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
;	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
Infected	O
or	O
not	O
:	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
infection	O
;	O
Easiness	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
Infected	O
;	O
Reasons	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
skillful-Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Moontebanks	O
,	O
Impostors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
or	O
Seminal	O
,	O
briefly	O
describing	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
their	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
did	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
published	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
Marten	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
and	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
A.	O
Collins	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
boy	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-pers
,	O
P	B-pers
renne	O
at	O
Se	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Hall	O
;	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Authors	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
THE	O
Famous	O
Cholick	O
Water	O
,	O
so	O
often	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Gazatte	O
,	O
and	O
published	O
base	O
Nine	O
Years	O
,	O
being	O
well	O
known	O
throughout	O
Great	O
Britian	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
the	O
only	O
One	O
Medicine	O
giving	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
in	O
Cases	O
of	O
W	O
in	O
the	O
Stomach	O
or	O
Bowels	O
,	O
Cholick	O
,	O
Vapours	O
of	O
both	O
Kinds	O
,	O
sinking	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
,	O
Stiches	O
and	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
sides	O
.	O
Gripes	O
,	O
Huxes	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
or	O
Loosness	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
indispositions	O
and	O
Weakness	O
of	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Bowels	O
(	O
immediately	O
digesting	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
continued	O
to	O
be	O
said	O
Places	O
only	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Old	O
Man	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
Alice	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Parliament	O
House	O
,	O
Richard	O
's	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clarks	O
Stationer	O
,	O
in	O
Birchin	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Bottle	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
putting	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
rich	O
Cordial	O
,	O
pleasant	O
to	O
take	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
immediate	O
Help	O
in	O
Fluxes	O
,	O
Gripes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
When	O
once	O
tried	O
,	O
none	O
will	O
be	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
every	O
Bottle	O
is	O
sealed	O
with	O
my	O
Seal	O
,	O
the	O
Sun	O
Flower	O
,	O
Mantle	O
and	O
Crest	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
those	O
Places	O
only	O
;	O
for	O
since	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
Publick	O
,	O
hath	O
obtained	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
fully	O
answered	O
the	O
end	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
others	O
that	O
publish	O
and	O
imitate	O
it	O
under	O
other	O
Names	O
and	O
Titles	O
,	O
who	O
live	O
only	O
by	O
thus	O
Pirating	O
upon	O
one	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
RUptures	O
or	O
broken	O
Bellies	O
Cured	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Success	O
,	O
and	O
Trusses	O
made	O
to	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
nicety	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
exceed	O
all	O
others	O
in	O
lightness	O
,	O
with	O
Springs	O
,	O
Joins	O
Screws	O
or	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
Totaly	O
the	O
like	O
are	O
not	O
made	O
,	O
Persons	O
living	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
by	O
sending	O
an	O
exact	O
measure	O
round	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
side	O
the	O
Rupture	O
is	O
on	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
fitted	O
by	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
2	O
Naked	O
Boys	O
in	O
St.	O
Johns	O
Lane	O
near	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
Women	O
may	O
apply	O
themselves	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
also	O
be	O
sitted	O
with	O
strait	O
stockings	O
.	O
The	O
Finest	O
Lucatelius	O
Balsam	O
,	O
THAT	O
ever	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
prepared	O
with	O
the	O
Choicest	O
ingredients	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
got	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
added	O
the	O
true	O
Balm	O
of	O
Gisead	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
other	O
Rich	B-pers
Balsamicks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
soon	O
discern	O
a	O
Difference	O
from	O
all	O
others	O
by	O
its	O
delicate	O
fragrant	O
cent	O
and	O
Taste	O
:	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
effectual	O
Medicine	O
(	O
as	O
thus	O
prepar	O
'd	O
)	O
for	O
tickling	O
Coughs	O
,	O
Shortness	O
of	O
Breath	O
,	O
Colds	O
,	O
Hoarsness	O
,	O
Soreness	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
or	O
Lungs	O
,	O
Pleutetick	O
Pains	O
,	O
Spitting	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
inward	O
Bruises	O
,	O
Strains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Healer	O
,	O
that	O
Chapt	O
Nipples	O
,	O
Lips	O
and	O
Hands	O
,	O
are	O
Cured	O
at	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
using	O
;	O
making	O
them	O
smooth	O
and	O
soft	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
sold	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
further	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
at	O
Mr.	O
How	O
's	O
in	O
Talbot-Court	O
,	O
in	O
Grace	O
Church	O
Street	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Gate	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
in	O
Russel	O
Street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Male	O
Glover	O
under	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
every	O
Pot	O
Sealed	O
with	O
the	O
Sun	O
Flower	O
,	O
Mantle	O
and	O
Crest	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
Nose	O
This	O
Sovereign	O
Balsam	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
on	O
to	O
answer	O
fully	O
what	O
is	O
said	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitledge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed	O
Lane	O
,	O
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Ave-Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
Booksellers	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Unrull	O
'd	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
or	O
plain	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
,	O
also	O
other	O
fine	O
Cuts	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
for	O
all	O
Sizes	O
of	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
Works	O
of	O
all	O
Sizes	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
in	O
Latin	O
.	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
Common-Prayers	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Psalms	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
Supplement	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
The	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vols	O
.	O
Washington	O
and	O
Wingate	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
The	O
Lord	O
Clarendon	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
in	O
Folw	O
and	O
Octavo	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
new	O
Transation	O
of	O
Esops	O
Fables	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Cuts	O
are	O
likewise	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
in	O
Mercers	O
Chappel	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Also	O
Bp	O
.	O
Beveridges	O
works	O
in	O
5	O
Vols	O
.	O
Dean	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Epistles	O
and	O
Gospels	O
,	O
in	O
4	O
Vol	O
.	O
The	O
Welch	B-pers
Common	I-pers
Prayer	O
.	O
AT	O
Mr.	O
Skinner	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Long	O
White	O
Peruke	O
,	O
in	O
Lamb	O
street	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
Liveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physitian	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
a	O
never-failing	O
Ointment	O
that	O
Cures	O
the	O
Gont	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
time	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
often	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
all	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
as	O
many	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
witness	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Powder	O
and	O
Bottle	O
,	O
which	O
Cures	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
Canker	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
Loose	O
to	O
admiration	O
.	O
Bottle	O
and	O
Powder	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Sold	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
,	O
at	O
Will	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
at	O
Steward	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Bolt-Cours	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Bolt	O
and	O
Tun-Inn	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
at	O
Ellor	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rain-bow	O
Coffee-House	O
at	O
Westminster-Hall-Gate	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Folks	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Little	O
East	O
Cheap	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Weigh-House	O
;	O
a	O
Painter	O
's	O
in	O
White-gate	O
Alley	O
in	O
Bishops-Gate-Street	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Peruke	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hastar-Lane	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Grigg	O
,	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Northumberland	O
House	O
,	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholly	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypocondriacal	O
Distempers	O
,	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fear	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Faintings	O
,	O
and	O
Sinking	O
of	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Burries	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
and	O
Disquitement	O
,	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Raisings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Hearty	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
sucessfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
Gods	O
,	O
Blessing	O
;	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Years	O
in	O
those	O
cases	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Printed	O
by	O
