TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
15th	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
GILBERT	B-pers
HEATHCOTF	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyres	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
James	B-pers
Oldsworth	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
John	B-pers
Elderton	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Burlace	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
George	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Batchellor	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lauton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Proof	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
shewn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
bargaining	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
one	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Muslen	O
.	O
Neckclothes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Alvares	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Beever	O
Hatts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dare	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
being	O
answer	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
being	O
busy	O
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
slipt	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Pettecoats	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephens	I-place
,	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
1	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Barbers	O
for	O
a	O
Peruke	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saving	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shewcross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Cocks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
Hens	O
,	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Fowls	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
he	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
prov	O
'd	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hammersmith	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Wether	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Pettecoat	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
Anterine	O
Pettecoat	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
6	O
Holland	O
Check	O
'd	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
from	O
her	O
Shop	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
boulted	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
go	O
from	O
thence	O
towards	O
the	O
Waterside	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
a	O
Boat	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
she	O
likewise	O
took	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Henry	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Tottnham-high-cross	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
putting	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
Life	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
5	O
Gowns	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
with	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Hill	O
;	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
:	O
the	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
.	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
3	O
listed	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
rushed	O
in	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
bound	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
fled	O
.	O
It	O
farther	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
Pursuit	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Wood	O
some	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
found	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
enabled	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Good	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Powder	O
Horn	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joshua	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joshua	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
all	O
Boys	O
,	O
going	O
a	O
Shooting	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
Bunhill	O
fields	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
(	O
by	O
telling	O
them	O
he	O
could	O
assist	O
them	O
in	O
Shooting	O
)	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Hornsey	B-place
Wood	I-place
,	O
bid	O
Bates	O
lay	O
down	O
his	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Things	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
bid	O
the	O
other	O
deliver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
a	O
considerable	O
Opposition	O
,	O
till	O
overcome	O
by	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
his	O
Knife	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
well	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Timber	O
Fore-Mast	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Astell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Quarter	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
one	O
another	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
there	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
might	O
lay	O
it	O
there	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Sennock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Cheapen	O
'd	O
Muslen	O
;	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
overtaken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
Jones	O
;	O
who	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cotham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Cotham	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Brinkwell	I-pers
alias	O
Randall	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Price	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
for	O
her	O
Clothes	O
;	O
leave	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
bulkey	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
wrap	O
'd	O
about	O
her	O
under	O
her	O
Clothes	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Porrage	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Compere	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ale	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
Porrage	O
Pots	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Price	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
suffocating	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
House	O
of	O
Easement	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallowes	B-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Worster	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
non	O
Compos	O
Mentis	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Jaculina	B-pers
Mountagne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimmaty	O
Curtain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Escut	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-clothes	O
laced	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
each	O
Indictment	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Facts	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
and	O
receiving	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
stolen	O
by	O
Margaret	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Christian	B-pers
Colebrant	I-pers
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeboakim	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharines	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pettecoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
Street	O
DoorKey	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Justice	O
Dyet	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
are	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stroude	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dyet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
6	O
Penny	O
Stamp	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Impression	O
thereof	O
upon	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Contrary	O
to	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
for	O
raising	O
a	O
Duty	O
upon	O
Stamp	O
'd	O
Vellom	O
,	O
Paper	O
and	O
Parchment	O
,	O
for	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
War	O
against	O
France	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
offended	O
against	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Secretaries	O
Office	O
,	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
By	O
virtue	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
his	O
Closet	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Papers	O
found	O
with	O
double	O
6	O
Penny	O
Stamps	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Counterfeit	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
a	O
Puncheon	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Stamps	O
were	O
made	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
those	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
uttered	O
divers	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Paper	O
impress	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Puncheon	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Paper	O
impress	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Puncheon	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
uttered	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
whole	O
Tryal	O
turning	O
upon	O
this	O
Point	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Puncheon	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
Quires	O
of	O
Stamp	O
'd	O
Paper	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
bad	O
been	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
formerly	O
in	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
several	O
Persons	O
;	O
which	O
Stamps	O
were	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
Puncheon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
agree	O
exactly	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
farther	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Puncheon	O
was	O
compared	O
with	O
those	O
made	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
disagree	O
from	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Puncheon	O
as	O
appropriated	O
to	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Puncheon	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
formerly	O
a	O
Commissioner	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Office	O
)	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
a	O
Crown	O
Stamp	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
Stamp	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Six	O
Penny	O
Dye	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
laid	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
by	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Secretary	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
by	O
him	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Paper	O
he	O
inserted	O
the	O
several	O
Particulars	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
sealing	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
Seals	O
,	O
deposited	O
in	O
a	O
Scrutore	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Office	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
having	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
have	O
access	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
it	O
at	O
pleasure	O
.	O
The	O
Secretary	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Puncheon	O
was	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
one	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
such	O
Information	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
one	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Remark	O
upon	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
being	O
insufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Puncheon	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ignatius	B-pers
Decasta	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Alice	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
6	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
Ravish	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
blew	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
receive	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
miss	O
'd	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Apron	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Henry	B-pers
Prichard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hepdon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Worsted	O
Coverlid	O
,	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Rugg	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missed	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
:	O
But	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Mantua	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
2	O
Silk	O
Pettecoats	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Pettecoat	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslen	O
laced	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Pinly	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jene	B-pers
Buttery	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Washenhoven	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
near	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Washenhoven	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Silk	O
Pettecoats	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Suffolk	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
4	O
l.	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Muslen	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
his	O
Daughter	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Muslen	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
pretended	O
the	O
Muslen	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Daughter	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
Roberts	O
forcibly	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
tyed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
and	O
sealed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
Bundle	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
nothing	O
but	O
old	O
Matting	O
,	O
Sand	O
,	O
Straw	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Dowlace	O
Sheets	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisonerabout	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
was	O
taken	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pales	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
opened	O
a	O
Casement	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
112	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
alone	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
be	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
4.	O
Ann	B-pers
William	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
Priscilla	O
Brinkwell	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shewcross	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Petty	O
Larcenies	O
,	O
8.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Ursula	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jone	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	O
Townsend	O
.	O
Ignatins	O
Decosta	O
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
.	O
I	O
John	B-pers
Bragnell	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
Kingstreet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Wopping	O
,	O
Stepney	O
,	O
being	O
inflicted	O
with	O
a	O
Cancer	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
eat	O
away	O
my	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
my	O
Life	O
was	O
despair	O
'd	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
Cures	O
daily	O
Perform	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
deplorable	O
Diseases	O
,	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Vanderplase	O
,	O
in	O
Upper	O
Shadwel	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
I	O
address	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
has	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Perfect	O
and	O
Sound	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
this	O
Certificate	O
may	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
others	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bragnell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Dr.	O
may	O
be	O
advis	O
'd	O
with	O
every	O
Day	O
at	O
Yates	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Pav'd-Ally	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall	O
Market	O
,	O
at	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Ldisworth	O
's	O
Record	O
Ink	O
Powder	O
,	O
is	O
made	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Each	O
Six-Penny	O
Paper	O
of	O
3	O
Ounces	O
makes	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Ink	O
,	O
or	O
Quart	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
Directions	O
,	O
sealed	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
proportion	O
,	O
for	O
greater	O
Quantities	O
)	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Stationers	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
chiefest	O
Cities	O
Towns	O
in	O
Great-Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
B.	O
LILBURN	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
;	O
lately	O
at	O
the	O
Soatboylers	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
;	O
now	O
lives	O
up	O
higher	O
,	O
over-against	O
Prusean	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Board	O
and	O
Ball	O
;	O
Who	O
makes	O
and	O
sells	O
the	O
WATER	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
for	O
near	O
Thirty	O
Years	O
)	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
As	O
likewise	O
an	O
Antiscorbutick	O
,	O
Histerick	O
,	O
and	O
Head	O
Pill	O
,	O
being	O
good	O
for	O
Kings	O
Evil	O
,	O
Cancers	O
,	O
Gout	O
,	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixer	O
for	O
the	O
Cholick	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Vial	O
,	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Half	O
Pint	O
.	O
An	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
fore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Hair	O
grow	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
a	O
Red	O
Face	O
,	O
Tetters	O
,	O
Ring-worms	O
,	O
or	O
Scabs	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
Bruises	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Strains	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
dissolve	O
Swellings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
As	O
likewise	O
Help	O
for	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
inward	O
Bruises	O
,	O
or	O
Hurts	O
on	O
their	O
Breasts	O
.	O
And	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Heaven	O
upon	O
Earth	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
best	O
Friend	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
worst	O
Times	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Legacy	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
James	B-pers
Janeway	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Marrow	O
of	O
the	O
Mathematicks	O
,	O
made	O
Plain	O
and	O
Ease	O
to	O
the	O
Understanding	O
of	O
any	O
ordinary	O
Capacity	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
Geometry	O
,	O
Astronomy	O
.	O
Gauging	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Sector	O
,	O
Surveying	O
,	O
Dyaling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Navigation	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
several	O
Cuts	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
Explanations	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
New	O
,	O
Compendious	O
,	O
Easy	O
Method	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Pickering	O
,	O
Merchant-Adventurer	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
.	O
Measuring	O
Surfaces	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
Plank	O
,	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Joiners	O
,	O
Carpenters	O
,	O
Bricklayers	O
,	O
Glasiers	O
,	O
Painters	O
and	O
Paviers	O
Work	O
:	O
Each	O
Proposition	O
being	O
wrought	O
Vulgarly	O
,	O
Decimally	O
,	O
Practically	O
and	O
Instrumentally	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
small	O
Tract	O
of	O
Gauging	O
Wine	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Six	O
New	O
Delightful	O
Novels	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
Unlucky	O
Fair	O
One	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Amounts	O
of	O
Milistrate	O
and	O
Prazimene	O
,	O
illustrated	O
with	O
variety	O
of	O
Chances	O
of	O
Fortune	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
Novels	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Three	O
Ingenuous	O
Spanish	O
Novels	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Loving	O
Revenge	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
Wit	O
in	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Lucky	O
Escape	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
silt	O
detected	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Witty	O
Extravagant	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
Fortunate	O
Lovers	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Cynthia	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
tragical	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Unfortunate	O
Loves	O
of	O
Almetine	O
and	O
Desdeinona	O
.	O
All	O
Printed	O
for	O
Eben	O
.	O
Tracy	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Bibles	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
1711	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Satyrical	O
Reflections	O
on	O
Club	O
,	O
in	O
2	O
Chapters	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Clubs	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
The	O
Vertuoso	O
Club	O
.	O
The	O
Knights	O
of	O
the	O
Golden	O
Fleece	O
.	O
The	O
Kit-Cats	O
Club	O
.	O
The	O
Beef-Stake	O
Club	O
,	O
&	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spye	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Advice	O
to	O
Youth	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Discourse	O
,	O
disswading	O
all	O
Younger	O
Persons	O
from	O
engaging	O
in	O
a	O
sinful	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Hopes	O
of	O
repenting	O
when	O
they	O
grow	O
older	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
Prayers	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Parishoners	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
A.	O
M.	O
Prebendary	O
of	O
Peterborough	O
,	O
and	O
Rector	O
of	O
Ussington	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
An	O
Epistolary	O
Discourse	O
,	O
proving	O
from	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Fathers	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Soul	O
is	O
a	O
Principle	O
naturally	O
Mortal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Henry	B-pers
Dodwell	I-pers
,	O
A.	O
M.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
;	O
and	O
corrected	O
from	O
great	O
Erratas	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
All	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
DR.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
,	O
also	O
his	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
Family	O
Prayer	O
,	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Laws	O
relating	O
to	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
Printed	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Printing-House	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vol	O
.	O
Wing	O
te	O
's	O
and	O
Washington	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
rul	O
'd	O
and	O
unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
and	O
without	O
;	O
also	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engraven	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
Books	O
and	O
Cuts	O
are	O
sold	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitledge	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
Avey-Mary-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
+++	O
The	O
Guilt	O
and	O
Provocation	O
of	O
taking	O
Encouragement	O
to	O
Sin	O
form	O
the	O
Mercies	O
of	O
God	O
;	O
represented	O
in	O
a	O
Sermon	O
,	O
preach	O
'd	O
Novemb	O
.	O
7th	O
,	O
1710.	O
being	O
a	O
Day	O
of	O
Publick	O
Thanksgiving	O
for	O
the	O
Successes	O
in	O
Spain	O
and	O
Flanders	O
,	O
By	O
Simon	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Minister	O
in	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
+++	O
The	O
Evil	O
and	O
Remedy	O
of	O
Scandal	O
;	O
a	O
Practical	O
Discourse	O
on	O
Psalm	O
119	O
.	O
165	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
+++	O
Hora	O
&	O
Lyrica	O
;	O
Poems	O
chiesly	O
of	O
the	O
Lyrick	O
kind	O
.	O
In	O
5	O
Books	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Sacred	O
to	O
Devotion	O
and	O
Piety	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
To	O
Vertus	O
,	O
Honour	O
and	O
Friendship	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Memory	O
of	O
the	O
Dead	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Watts	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
enlarged	O
.	O
+++	O
A	O
Method	O
for	O
Prayer	O
;	O
with	O
Scripture	O
Expressions	O
,	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
under	O
each	O
Head	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Henry	O
,	O
Minister	O
is	O
Chester	O
.	O
All	O
Printed	O
for	O
N.	O
Cliff	O
,	O
and	O
D.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
3	O
Crowns	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
+++	O
A	O
Letter	O
from	O
South	O
Carolina	O
;	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Soil	O
,	O
Air	O
,	O
Product	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Government	O
,	O
Laws	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
People	O
,	O
Military	O
Strength	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
that	O
Province	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
necessary	O
Charges	O
of	O
Settling	O
a	O
Plantation	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Annual	O
Profit	O
it	O
will	O
produce	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Swiss	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Friend	O
at	O
Bern	O
.	O
+++	O
The	O
Reasons	O
of	O
the	O
Absenting	O
Clergy	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
appearing	O
at	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
August	O
21	O
,	O
1710	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Address	O
from	O
the	O
Bishop	O
and	O
Clergy	O
of	O
London	O
was	O
propos	O
'd	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
.	O
Humbly	O
offer	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Clergy-Man	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Both	O
Sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Baldwin	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
1711	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
J.	O
Humfreys	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
)	O
for	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Baldwin	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
