TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BEACHCROFT	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Trevor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blincoe	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Phillip	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Denning	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Foscue	I-pers
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Westcomb	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Allin	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Barloe	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barloe	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parson	I-pers
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
John	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ashman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Alman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pallister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnorth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
receive	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lying	O
some	O
Gold	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
conveying	O
the	O
Gold	O
under	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
seeing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilmote	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
51	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
of	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
of	O
her	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
seeing	O
of	O
her	O
Face	O
while	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Blankets	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
Rugg	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Graine	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
a	O
Noise	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
to	O
corroborate	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cadden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Ely	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boddicote	I-pers
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Son-in-Law	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Copper	O
Funnel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Copper	O
Japan	O
Salvers	O
9	O
s.	O
1	O
Brass-Knocker	O
3	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
break	O
a	O
Square	O
of	O
a	O
Sash	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
following	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Long-Acre	O
into	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
throw	O
up	O
another	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Cecil	O
have	O
a	O
Diamond	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prickatt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
an	O
Undertaker	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
bury	O
a	O
Corps	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Coaches	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
white	O
Horse	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
three	O
Fields	O
of	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flung	O
a	O
Stone	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
him	O
much	O
Damage	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Ring	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
hind	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Ceveirs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
,	O
one	O
Pillow-bear	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
conveying	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
and	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
She	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Amy	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hamstead	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
off	O
the	O
Pales	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
working	O
,	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Sheets	O
where	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Sheets	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cuttell	I-pers
alias	O
Hartwell	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Caps	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Katherine	B-pers
Fuzzard	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
set	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Garret	O
Stairs	O
;	O
asking	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
one	O
Mason	O
.	O
But	O
mistrusting	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
searched	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
Pillow-bears	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Evidencewas	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
24	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Hair	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Wig	O
oyl	O
'd	O
and	O
powdered	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
rid	O
above	O
fifty	O
Mile	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
mistrusting	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
him	O
narrowly	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Hair	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
making	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
others	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
likewise	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
turning	O
up	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shut	O
to	O
the	O
Doors	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Hair	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Peruques	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Newth	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
Four	O
Shirts	O
10	O
s.	O
Four	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloaths	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
of	O
23	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Nineteen	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
:	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Shooes	O
off	O
Momford	O
's	O
Feet	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Huttons	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Shooemaker	O
that	O
made	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Huttons	O
Shooes	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
Mark	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
Flap	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Shooes	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bentham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Gold	O
Net-Scarf	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
broke	O
a	O
Sash	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Good	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
alias	O
Mason	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew-Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Hasted	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ludloe	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
Three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Defence	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Leather	O
Shooe	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Goodall	O
and	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Yarwood	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
.	O
Yarwood	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Goodall	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Cowards	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Goodall	O
and	O
Justice	O
Guilty	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
Coward	O
as	O
Accessary	O
.	O
[	O
Goodall	O
Justice	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Coward	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jerry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Spoon	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Crimshaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
Holland	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
Three	O
Ells	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mother	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
her	O
back	O
was	O
,	O
turned	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
Cup	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Foster-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trapp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Caps	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Poulterers	O
Man	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Peny	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
coming	O
to	O
Trapp	O
's	O
Shop	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
asking	O
of	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
calling	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
one	O
.	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hollow	O
Rings	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
other	O
Rings	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
a	O
Brass	O
one	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
hollow	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
above	O
half	O
so	O
much	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Owen	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
where	O
searching	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bolton	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wildman	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
King	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Warmen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
apper	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
Muslin	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Muslin	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
swore	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
but	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-Dresses	O
10	O
l.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Maynard	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
find	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
Person	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
regard	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
Collect	O
her	O
Rents	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
turn	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Head-dress	O
of	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Gardener	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
which	O
my	O
Lady	O
called	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
my	O
Lady	O
often	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
pawn	O
Goods	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
frequently	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
my	O
Lady	O
to	O
Fortune-tellers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
sometimes	O
she	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
my	O
Lady	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Phebe	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement's-Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Cholick	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
something	O
else	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
known	O
Man	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill.	O
She	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
drawn	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
Lye	O
in	O
handsomely	O
.	O
She	O
still	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
Cordial	O
Drams	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
;	O
but	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
tokens	O
of	O
a	O
Delivery	O
,	O
she	O
taxes	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
pulling	O
down	O
the	O
Bed-cloaths	O
to	O
the	O
feet	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
this	O
Deponent	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Footsteps	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
trac	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
quite	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
caus	O
'd	O
the	O
Vault	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
full	O
grown	O
Child	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
searching	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
no	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
given	O
an	O
Information	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioner	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
of	O
Wax-Candles	O
,	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
King	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
the	O
Excise	O
Officer	O
who	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
seized	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wizdell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
qalue	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Cibers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
No	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Sorrel	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kittle	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Field	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
seized	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
giving	O
any	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Tilman	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sayling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
23	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ben	B-pers
.	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Dutch	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
understanding	O
them	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
could	O
speak	O
Dutch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
then	O
buy	O
,	O
until	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
their	O
Husband	O
's	O
Consent	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Damask	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
following	O
the	O
Deponent	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Mantoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Damask	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Piece	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Craddock	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Holland	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
,	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
Sherbon-lane	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burbank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
felonionsly	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
1	O
Silk	O
and	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
1	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Sleeves	O
1	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
saying	O
very	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wareing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
19	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hosier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
1	O
Drugget	O
Suit	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Yarwood	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Goodale	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Chocolate-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tea-Pot	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Lamp	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Yarwood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
41	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Enoch	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
united	O
Company	O
of	O
Merchants	O
trading	O
to	O
East-India	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
1100	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Treasury	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mickelthwaite	O
,	O
Masters	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
House-keeper	O
:	O
accordingly	O
double-locking	O
the	O
outward	O
Gate	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Wooly	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wooly	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Masters	O
called	O
him	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
strict	O
Search	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
Scaffolding	O
in	O
the	O
Sale	O
Room	O
,	O
delivering	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Papers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mickelthwaite	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Treasury	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Silver	O
upon	O
the	O
Tables	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
upon	O
Examination	O
1100	O
Guineas	O
,	O
besides	O
Notes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
partly	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
an	O
Indisposition	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
calling	O
Dr.	O
Cromp	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Abram	O
had	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
Drops	O
of	O
Opium	O
he	O
took	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
this	O
Deponant	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
take	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
might	O
do	O
him	O
an	O
Injury	O
.	O
An	O
Apothecary	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
7	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Pint-Pot	O
40	O
s.	O
12	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
30	O
s.	O
2	O
Feather-Beds	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Mad-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
intrusted	O
Yates	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
nothing	O
with	O
them	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Order	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth-Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Clapt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	B-place
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Street	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Pallister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch-Case	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Petition	O
to	O
ask	O
Relief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Case	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
receiving	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Case	O
to	O
one	O
Paine	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rewlen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Lamp	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rudge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Petition	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Lamp	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Paine	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Percaine	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwall	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Men	O
going	O
aboard	O
the	O
Lighter	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
look	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
loading	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
Smith	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Ralph	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
Senior	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
Junior	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Willingdon	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	B-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
black	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bratham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Cows	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
17th	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
hearing	O
that	O
one	O
Arundell	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Cows	O
.	O
Arundell	O
swore	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Weeden	O
;	O
and	O
Weeden	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Cannon	O
Junior	O
;	O
Cannon	O
Junior	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Cannon	O
Senior	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
Junior	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
Cow	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
red	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
Frame	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
apyear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Cows	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
Gunpowder-Treason	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Ascote	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Cows	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Groome	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
proving	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hardis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Porter	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
9	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
over	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Women	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
tript	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
coming	O
his	O
Round	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Straw-hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Brathington	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Petticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
instant	O
.	O
No	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Money	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Acton	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
1	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Wastecoat	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
searching	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
behind	O
some	O
Babbins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Cannister	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gentel	I-pers
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmunton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gray	O
Gelding	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
Chase	I-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
proving	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
21	O
Yew	O
Sheep	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Ram	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ponter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
in	O
Hampshire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fowkes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
Yew	O
Sheep	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hockley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Fowkes	O
Riding	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
Ponter	O
's	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
Fold	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
called	O
one	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Drover	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Winchester	O
Market	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
3	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Shoredith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Morron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
divers	O
sums	O
of	O
Portugal	O
Mony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
500	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Wastcoat	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
alias	O
Rogers	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Red	O
Cloath	O
Petticoat	O
2	O
s.	O
6.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Wastcoat	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Straw	O
Hat	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cerbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheet	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Shirts	O
30	O
s.	O
three	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scosseer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Shifts	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
corrobrated	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
alias	O
Clarke	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Camlet	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
alias	O
Thomspon	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Wicked	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blincoe	O
,	O
in	O
personating	O
another	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Called	O
up	O
to	O
former	O
Sentence	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
12.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pallister	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prickatt	I-pers
,	O
Phebe	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hardis	I-pers
.	O
Called	O
up	O
to	O
former	O
Sentence	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
15.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Tilman	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sailing	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wizdoll	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burbank	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Money	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
Petit	O
Larcenies	O
11	O
.	O
Amey	O
Davis	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cuttell	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
M	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Perey	O
Ralph	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cerbert	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Ceviers	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
twenty	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
