TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1712	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Trevor	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Thay	I-pers
Stafford	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Sharples	I-pers
John	B-pers
Henthall	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Gravener	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pannet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Mulcaster	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wells	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dyer	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
,	O
33	O
Broad-pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
call	O
'd	O
Carolus	O
's	O
2	O
Jacobus	O
's	O
and	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
l	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
8	O
l	O
a	O
Cup	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
recover	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Pound	O
of	O
Coffee	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Henshaw	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Aniseeds	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
weighing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
something	O
rattle	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Paper	O
Bag	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Coffee	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
being	O
scatter	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
was	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
trusted	O
with	O
great	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
Honest	O
:	O
Which	O
weighing	O
much	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Winifred	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
7	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
her	O
Sister	O
Winifred	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
2	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Morgan	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
Offender	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Watt	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridget	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Brides	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Smith	O
's	O
in	O
Middle	O
Row	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Perukemaker	O
)	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
another	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Work	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
2	O
quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
2	O
quarts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pints	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Trenan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
that	O
goes	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Pots	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phebe	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Spencer	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Colemanstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Custer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Capmaker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
only	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ashwood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
77	O
yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
near	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
afterwards	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Callicoes	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
pursuit	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
upon	O
the	O
Outcry	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Shoplifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Dowcet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Stonehorse	O
,	O
valued	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Horse	O
being	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
the	O
next	O
Days	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
whereupon	O
being	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Johnson	O
;	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
and	O
said	O
theHorse	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Stratford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
selling	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Horse	O
stealing	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Goswell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Pocket-Case	O
with	O
Notes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
Fleet	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
justl	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
quick	O
about	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
Case	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
whereupon	O
seizing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
Companion	O
dropt	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gideon	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Eight	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
Pence	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Marriot	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Two	O
Half-pounds	O
of	O
Rice	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
Wood	O
was	O
buying	O
;	O
Gideon	O
fish	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
and	O
Birdlime	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
perceiving	O
something	O
of	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Whalebone	O
Being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
clammy	O
with	O
the	O
Birdlime	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
knew	O
Wood	O
,	O
as	O
Wood	O
did	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Rice	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Gideon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rigway	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Abchurch	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
11	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Drickill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
to	O
measure	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
concealed	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
Cadis	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
some	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Cadis-Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
6	O
Pounds	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
sworn	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
49000	O
of	O
Pins	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
fifth	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Lockwood	O
and	O
White	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
afterwards	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
suspected	O
there	O
was	O
ill	O
People	O
there	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Boys	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Boys	O
and	O
one	O
Woman	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
also	O
Pewter	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
Lockwood	O
and	O
White	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	O
Lucy	B-pers
Purchas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
30	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Stampt	O
Paper	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ebdon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Papers	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
assaulted	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
296	O
Pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raw	O
China	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
216	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Jacobson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
Coco-Nuts	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Beachcroft	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Silk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Hacket	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hacket	O
procur	O
'd	O
false	O
Keys	O
to	O
several	O
Warehouses	O
;	O
but	O
Hacket	O
being	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
got	O
the	O
false	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Concern	O
but	O
in	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pistol-Barrels	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
scolding	O
in	O
a	O
Crowd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
her	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Tavern	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Barrels	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
somewhat	O
that	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Barrels	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Five	O
Ewe-sheep	O
valued	O
Three	O
Pounds	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
permitted	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Ewes	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Butcher	O
who	O
cheapned	O
them	O
suspecting	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
nor	O
entrusted	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Widows	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wansed	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Ludgate-street	B-place
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Fellows	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
;	O
whereupon	O
turning	O
himself	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Black-fryars	O
with	O
several	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
throw	O
some	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Berkhead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Two	O
Women	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
off	O
a	O
Chair	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
another	O
Story	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Towne	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Tallow	O
Chandler	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
late	O
Statute	O
against	O
fraudulent	O
Concealment	O
by	O
Bankrupts	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
contracted	O
Debts	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Statute	O
was	O
thereupon	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
send	O
away	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
place	O
,	O
Writings	O
,	O
and	O
Books	O
of	O
Account	O
,	O
to	O
Holland	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Norris	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Concealment	O
,	O
were	O
shipped	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Lacquer-Boat	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
Sea-sick	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
ease	O
his	O
Stomach	O
over	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
Eight	O
hundred	O
Guineas	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
two	O
Bags	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
between	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
)	O
fell	O
over	O
Board	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boat	O
being	O
forced	O
on	O
Shoar	O
by	O
the	O
Weather	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
upon	O
his	O
Finger	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Particulars	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioner	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
he	O
owed	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
(	O
who	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Statute	O
)	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
one	O
Note	O
of	O
Seven	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Three	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
One	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Notes	O
being	O
view	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
by	O
Towne	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Thomas	O
counterfeited	O
;	O
as	O
was	O
also	O
the	O
Counterpart	O
of	O
an	O
Account	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
this	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
either	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
his	O
purpose	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
Rogue	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
and	O
patient	O
Hearing	O
,	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
wrap	O
up	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
Passage	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Meal	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
half	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Belladine	O
Silk	O
value	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
Cadis	O
and	O
a	O
Lace	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
Farrow	O
had	O
the	O
Boy	O
aside	O
,	O
Meal	O
stole	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
seen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
theSilk	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
Farrow	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
abetting	O
and	O
assisting	O
several	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
break	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
make	O
their	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rouse	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jeffreys	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Master	O
Turn-keys	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rouse	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
eighth	O
instant	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
private	O
Information	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Goal	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
communicated	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jeffreys	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
Search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
of	O
the	O
Hall	O
7	O
Inches	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Irons	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
were	O
saw	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
further	O
,	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
with	O
Wells	O
's	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
they	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jeffreys	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wilks	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
Wells	O
brought	O
the	O
Saw	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
Irons	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
procur	O
'd	O
the	O
Escape	O
of	O
Holloway	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
three	O
Persons	O
Deaths	O
.	O
All	O
things	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
dated	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliph	B-pers
Carn	I-pers
,	O
Captains	O
Servants	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdeademeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mohun	I-pers
,	O
Baron	B-pers
of	I-pers
Okehampton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
comforting	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
most	O
Noble	O
James	O
Duke	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
Brandon	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Mackartney	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Fifteen	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
.	O
Another	O
Indictment	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
comforting	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mohun	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Mackartney	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
;	O
in	O
murdering	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
Duke	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
Brandon	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
Three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Twelve	O
Inches	O
;	O
And	O
another	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
that	O
Murder	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Rice	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
's	O
Footmen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
was	O
affronted	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
,	O
before	O
a	O
Master	O
in	O
Chancery	O
.	O
Two	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Duel	O
;	O
That	O
parting	O
without	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
went	O
to	O
Whites	O
Chocolate-House	O
afterwards	O
supp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
the	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
that	O
Nobody	O
should	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
except	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
having	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
tarry	O
'd	O
there	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
:	O
That	O
this	O
Evidence	O
having	O
intimated	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Jos	O
.	O
Churchill	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
his	O
Lord	O
check	O
'd	O
him	O
severely	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
:	O
That	O
from	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
's	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
went	O
to	O
Sergeants-Inn	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
with	O
Col.	O
Churchill	O
,	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Lordship	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
supp	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Richmond	O
,	O
Colonel	O
Churchill	O
,	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
.	O
After	O
Supper	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
sent	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
find	O
his	O
Lord	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
about	O
Seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
having	O
still	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
Mischief	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
Hide-Park	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
Coach	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Park-wall	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
engag	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Lords	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
Seconds	O
)	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
Mackartney	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
fine	O
spot	O
of	O
Work	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Lord	O
being	O
help	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
reel	O
'd	O
about	O
Two	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
dy	O
'd	O
presently	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Sison	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rose-Tavern	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Gray	O
came	O
and	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
Stars	O
and	O
Garters	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
asking	O
for	O
Mackartney	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Gray	O
hearing	O
him	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
whose	O
coming	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
carry	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
help	O
themselves	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Gray	O
went	O
several	O
times	O
between	O
the	O
Duke	O
and	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	O
.	O
The	O
Duke	O
's	O
Porter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Fourteenth	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Mackartney	O
's	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
the	O
Duke	O
was	O
stirring	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
himself	O
,	O
told	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Business	O
of	O
Importance	O
from	O
the	O
North	O
to	O
communicate	O
.	O
That	O
Mackartney	O
came	O
again	O
at	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Duke	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
about	O
Six	O
,	O
with	O
Colonel	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
din	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
Eight	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Very	O
frequently	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lesly	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Dukes	O
Footman	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
to	O
the	O
British	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Rose-Tavern	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
by	O
Six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
get	O
himself	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Duke	O
would	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
about	O
Business	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Duke	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
drive	O
to	O
the	O
Park	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
morning	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
bid	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
drive	O
to	O
Kensington	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
Grass	O
between	O
the	O
Ponds	O
;	O
the	O
Duke	O
having	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
stay	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
met	O
Mackartney	O
going	O
towards	O
Kensington	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Dukes	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Duke	O
was	O
mortally	O
wounded	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Dukes	O
Coachman	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
Six	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Coach	O
ready	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
retir	O
'd	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
bid	O
him	O
drive	O
to	O
the	O
Park	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
the	O
white	O
Rails	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Mackartney	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Wastcoat-Buttons	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
melancholy	O
Posture	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
It	O
farther	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
about	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
melancholy	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
deep	O
Sigh	O
:	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
jocose	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
from	O
Bowstreet-end	O
to	O
the	O
Bagnis	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
and	O
Mackartney	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
'em	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
for	O
some	O
burnt	O
Wine	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
walk	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
those	O
were	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
telling	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
that	O
way	O
also	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
something	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
all	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Seconds	O
push	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
two	O
Lords	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
down	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
fall	O
over	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
Duke	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
behind	O
the	O
Lord	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
raise	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
deliver	O
'd	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Lords	O
were	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
theirs	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
beginning	O
to	O
Faint	O
,	O
Markartney	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
with	O
bleeding	O
inwardly	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Duel	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mackartney	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
very	O
crooked	O
and	O
bloody	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
Colonel	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
had	O
no	O
Blood	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
One	O
Morris	O
,	O
a	O
Groom	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Duel	O
;	O
That	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
having	O
push	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
closed	O
and	O
took	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
which	O
last	O
fell	O
and	O
groan	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Lord	O
Mobun	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Sword	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
dropping	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Wound	O
given	O
after	O
the	O
closing	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
shorten	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Amy	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
wound	O
by	O
a	O
Push	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
cut	O
the	O
Artery	O
and	O
small	O
Tendant	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
Arm	O
;	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Leg	O
,	O
Eight	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
a	O
Slash	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
large	O
;	O
another	O
small	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
Leg	O
near	O
the	O
instep	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
fourth	O
on	O
his	O
Leftside	O
between	O
the	O
second	O
and	O
third	O
Rib	O
,	O
which	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
most	O
forwards	O
,	O
having	O
pierc	O
'd	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
his	O
Midriff	O
and	O
gone	O
through	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
Wound	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
given	O
but	O
by	O
a	O
Thrust	O
coming	O
from	O
an	O
Arm	O
that	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
above	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
also	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
lord	O
Mohun	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
between	O
his	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
quite-through	O
his	O
Belly	O
another	O
about	O
Three	O
inches	O
deep	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Thigh	O
;	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Wound	O
about	O
Four	O
Inches	O
wide	O
in	O
his	O
Groin	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
small	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Left	O
Side	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fingers	O
of	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
were	O
cut	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Boussur	I-pers
another	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
Eleven	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
Footman	O
came	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Duke	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Duke	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
till	O
Morning	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
Mr.	O
Ferguson	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
Seven	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
Duke	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
him	O
take	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
Hide	O
Park	O
to	O
dress	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
occasion	O
.	O
That	O
not	O
being	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
sometime	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Dukes	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
between	O
his	O
Second	O
and	O
Third	O
Rib	O
to	O
enter	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
given	O
but	O
by	O
some	O
Push	O
from	O
above	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Arm	O
wound	O
hinder	O
the	O
holding	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
might	O
use	O
that	O
Arm	O
for	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
small	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
main	O
Tendant	O
that	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ferguson	O
give	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
November	O
15th	O
.	O
about	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
his	O
Master	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
made	O
him	O
promise	O
secrecy	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Challenge	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
vindicate	O
his	O
Honour	O
;	O
wherefore	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
get	O
Boussier	O
ready	O
to	O
attend	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
Need	O
;	O
but	O
Boussier	O
not	O
being	O
ready	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Duke	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
'till	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Noblemen	O
of	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
,	O
Gallant	O
,	O
Inoffensive	O
Man	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Duel	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
upon	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
enter	O
'd	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
Execution	O
done	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brittle	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
at	O
their	O
Exercise	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
grudge	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
now	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
whisper	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
part	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Tottenham-Court	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
saw	O
Two	O
Men	O
walking	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Cart	O
by	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Dead	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
Kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hanwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Ten	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
valued	O
Five	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
down	O
Holbourn	B-place
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
against	O
Two	O
Persons	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
committed	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
instant	O
,	O
at	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
17	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Belladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
a	O
Hat	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
along	O
with	O
other	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
pains	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
,	O
driving	O
a	O
Wheelbarrow	O
with	O
Fruit	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
maintain	O
his	O
sick	O
Mother	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
by	O
some	O
Milk-women	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
poor	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Coat	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
Edging	O
,	O
a	O
Buff	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
33	O
Shillings	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Farthing-Pye-House-Fields	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
four	O
Hot-pots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
parted	O
from	O
her	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
had	O
charged	O
other	O
Persons	O
with	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eustace	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
dozen	O
of	O
Sheepskins	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Dennis	O
's	O
in	O
Hog-lane	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Witness	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
pay	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Trade	O
of	O
Breeches	O
making	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rixton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Musgrave	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Man	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Chambers	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	B-place
pretending	O
to	O
sell	O
Blanks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
(	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stockins	O
and	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Person	O
proving	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clemson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
,	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
other	O
Plate	O
and	O
Jewels	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
wound	O
up	O
her	O
Lady	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Screws	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watches	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
while	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
were	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
also	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Butler	O
's	O
Room	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Noise	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
spread	O
,	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
Coachman	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Kicks-end	O
,	O
near	O
Barnet	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watches	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Clemson	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
Hughs	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
's	O
House	O
)	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
no	O
Locks	O
were	O
broken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Beatrice	B-pers
Bressenden	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Teddington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
matter	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
werefound	O
accordingly	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dickinson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
and	O
white	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
Four	O
Pound	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
two	O
Cows	O
from	O
Elstry	B-place
in	O
Hertfordshire	B-place
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Obrey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Moyne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
mistake	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
at	O
coming	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ing	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hog	O
,	O
value	O
fifty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Kidder	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Rumford	O
with	O
a	O
Drove	O
of	O
Hogs	O
,	O
one	O
dropp	O
'd	O
in	O
Spittle	O
fields	O
Market	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Information	O
of	O
a	O
Hog	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Hair	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Clark	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Twenty	O
seven	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Broad-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Tilden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
valued	O
Eight	O
Pence	O
,	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Crowd	O
in	O
Moor-fields	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manlove	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Gawse	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Bierly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
keeping	O
Company	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
valued	O
Fifty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
permitted	O
to	O
go	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
Doors	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Best	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
valued	O
Thirty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Noon	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Picklock	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
Boswell	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
White	O
,	O
the	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Furbelow-Scarf	O
,	O
valued	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
valued	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
her	O
Casement	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Trunks	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Sold	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Aprons	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
three	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
Two	O
Muslin	O
Bibs	O
and	O
Apron	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Zach	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
newly	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
fled	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
Refuge	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Cocks	O
,	O
valued	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Thirteen	O
Hens	O
,	O
valued	O
Seventeen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Allen	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Hen-house	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
what	O
hast	O
he	O
could	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Fowls	O
Kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
ty	O
'd	O
together	O
alive	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbor	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Crabb	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Gold	O
Medals	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
Jewels	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Bushel	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
so	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Crab	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
after	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Maids	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
to	O
Bushel	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
a	O
Room	O
and	O
two	O
Scrutores	O
were	O
broken	O
and	O
Bushel	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Crabb	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
after	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Annesley	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Intelligence	O
to	O
the	O
Customhouse	O
Officers	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Ports	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
were	O
after	O
sometime	O
seiz	O
'd	O
in	O
Wales	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Caermarthen	O
Goal	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
being	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Bushel	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Crabb	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Wine-Cellar	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Scrutore	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Crabb	O
got	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
induc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
But	O
Crabb	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
Bushel	O
set	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Picklock	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Contriver	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
finding	O
the	O
Matter	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gideon	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Landel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
abroad	O
to	O
a	O
Burial	O
,	O
and	O
fastned	O
her	O
Door	O
and	O
her	O
Windows	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
was	O
a	O
Dealer	O
with	O
Thieves	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
George	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
value	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sacks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Skiff	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Malt	O
and	O
Skiff	O
to	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
put	O
it	O
ashore	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
together	O
stole	O
the	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Grounds	O
near	O
Ware	B-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
thathe	O
kept	O
an	O
Inn	O
at	O
Waltham-Cross	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Metkins	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Innocent	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
three	O
Holland	O
Pillowbers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Foot	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
just	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
mistaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
body	O
hear	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
bolted	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
finding	O
it	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wine	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Levin	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
two	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
their	O
usual	O
Round	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Sheep	O
cut	O
asunder	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
in	O
their	O
Haversacks	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
brought	O
from	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hannaway	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
Windsor	O
Party	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
met	O
a	O
Butcher	O
with	O
nine	O
Sheep	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
having	O
his	O
Leg	O
broke	O
,	O
fell	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Skin	O
for	O
stripping	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
to	O
Witness	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Odel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
bargain	O
'd	O
for	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Odel	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
he	O
caus	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Odel	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
Pence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bentoft	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
comply	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Company	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
comply	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
very	O
lewdly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lauton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Linwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tasters	O
,	O
two	O
gilt	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Valentine	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Jack	O
,	O
value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Augustine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
9.	O
James	B-pers
Ashwood	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Dowcet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Towne	O
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Meale	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crabb	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Metkins	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
17	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Wells	O
,	O
alias	O
White	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gideon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clemson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Beatrice	B-pers
Bressenden	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Phebe	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Goswell	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ridgway	I-pers
,	O
Caleh	O
Lockwood	O
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Widows	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rixton	I-pers
,	O
Evan	B-pers
Obrey	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wine	I-pers
,	O
Levin	O
Reason	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
Fin	O
'd	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Meale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
.	O
THE	O
Publick	O
Divine	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
Practice	O
of	O
the	O
Primitive	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
publish	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Information	O
and	O
Instruction	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
Dissent	O
from	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Prefacely	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Brett	O
.	O
1713	O
.	O
THE	O
Great	O
Duty	O
of	O
Catechising	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
plain	O
and	O
tasy	O
Discourse	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Divine	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
under	O
his	O
Change	O
shewing	O
them	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
instructing	O
Youth	O
in	O
the	O
Principles	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
And	O
earnestly	O
persuading	O
them	O
to	O
teach	O
their	O
Children	O
the	O
Church	O
Catechism	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
cause	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
further	O
examin	O
'd	O
and	O
instructed	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
few	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
the	O
Excellency	O
of	O
that	O
Catechism	O
above	O
all	O
others	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Ports	O
.	O
Both	O
Sold	O
by	O
John	O
Morphew	O
,	O
near	O
Stationer's-Hall	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Ladies	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
at	O
may	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
,	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
living	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
who	O
lately	O
performed	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Care	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physician	O
.	O
A	O
Small	O
Parcel	O
of	O
very	O
fine	O
Malaga	O
Citrons	O
just	O
landed	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
near	O
Pudding-lane	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Morphew	I-pers
near	O
Stationers-Hall	O
,	O
1712	O
.	O
