TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1712-13	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Kettering	I-pers
Cave	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Ems	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wibert	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Marner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Garwich	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edy	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Abigal	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
48	O
yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stuff	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
came	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
going	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
another	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Pettycoats	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
produce	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
came	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
Whitacre	O
's	O
Ship	O
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
were	O
asleep	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
very	O
odd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Witness	O
should	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
call	O
somebody	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Cushaw	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael-Quern	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
by	O
Cheapside-Conduit	B-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
Bandbox	O
on	O
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
in	O
pursuit	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
strengthen	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
following	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Bandbox	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
out	O
the	O
Owner	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
9	O
Days	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
being	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gone	O
,	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Place	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chester	O
.	O
Immediately	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
also	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
pull	O
'em	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
'em	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Seaman	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Ticking	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Daley	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregory	I-place
by	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
at	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
and	O
Lamp	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
4	O
silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
other	O
Plate	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
embroider	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
rich	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Linen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Roberts	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
,	O
Daley	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
without	O
asking	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
whereupon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
a	O
Footboy	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
Daley	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
Madam	O
Cheney	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
ever	O
since	O
6	O
a-Clock	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
to	O
somebody	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Come	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
forc	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
gagg	O
'd	O
and	O
bound	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
Roberts	O
came	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
of	O
breaking	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
rumbling	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
shut	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
their	O
Mistress	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Roberts	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
also	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Scrutore	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass-d	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
s	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
also	O
some	O
Trunks	O
for	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Chamber-doors	O
were	O
look	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
Daley	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Passage	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Roberts	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
confes	O
'd	O
;	O
Daley	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
Roberts	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
Daley	O
had	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
former	O
Confession	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
agreeing	O
to	O
their	O
Price	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
Person	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marriot	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Mitchel	O
put	O
somewhat	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mitchel	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
any	O
Stockings	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Linker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridget	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Brides	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
down	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
justl	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dennidge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Marrying	O
Titus	B-pers
Hamin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Golding	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
the	O
6th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1702.	O
and	O
had	O
cohabited	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Children	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
now	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
seem	O
'd	O
pretty	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
somewhat	O
deficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ridgway	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Ridgway	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Robert	B-pers
Windor	I-pers
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
6	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Hand	O
was	O
thrust	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watches	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
running	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
ty	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
his	O
Servant	O
's	O
Call	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Parlor	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
String	O
which	O
ty	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
a	O
Cellar-window	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
fled	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Watches	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
would	O
procure	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
one	O
Lennard	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
'em	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
pretending	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
wanted	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
earnest	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Lennard	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
produc	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
Lennard	O
challeng	O
'd	O
'em	O
as	O
stoln	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
'em	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
delivering	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
Prosecuted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Warner	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watches	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
to	O
defraud	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Watches	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
Perjury	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
N	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
and	O
Letter	O
of	O
Advice	O
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
and	O
written	O
by	O
one	O
Branch	O
near	O
Bristol	O
,	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	O
Diston	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Callow	I-pers
;	O
and	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Callow	O
as	O
Indorser	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Diston	O
as	O
Accepter	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	O
in	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
sent	O
the	O
said	O
Bill	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
discounted	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Burt	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
try	O
what	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
try	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
done	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
appointed	O
a	O
Meeting	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Burt	O
,	O
having	O
some	O
mistrust	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Diston	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
accepted	O
any	O
such	O
Bill	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Correspondent	O
as	O
Branch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
also	O
being	O
somewhat	O
doubtful	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
appointed	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fitzhugh	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
Discounted	O
;	O
who	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Diston	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
N	O
-	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
about	O
400	O
l.	O
in	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
Notes	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
that	O
in	O
dispute	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
was	O
wholly	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
N	O
-	O
,	O
but	O
insufficient	O
against	O
Kennedy	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
acquitted	O
.	O
N	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeating	O
a	O
Note	O
under	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Messieurs	O
Stevenson	O
and	O
Acton	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Note	O
he	O
received	O
10	O
l.	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Eling	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Eling-Common	B-place
,	O
who	O
presenting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Horse	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
presented	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
shoot	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
any	O
further	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
follow	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
whom	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
near	O
Kensington	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
two	O
Pistols	O
stuck	O
in	O
his	O
Girdle	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
.	O
Being	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Coaches	O
that	O
Day	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
own	O
the	O
Confession	O
he	O
had	O
sign	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
it	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Seal	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Handy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Kegwin	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Trigg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
500	O
weight	O
of	O
Rope-Yarn	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
by	O
untiling	O
it	O
at	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
1000	O
weight	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Kennedy	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Handy	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
They	O
pretended	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
by	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Straw-Hats	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms-Yard	B-place
in	O
Warwick-lane	B-place
;	O
and	O
Information	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Hats	O
in	O
Liquorpond-street	O
,	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
was	O
procur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
;	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
accordingly	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Finchley	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco-stopper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Augustine	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
his	O
Desk	O
was	O
stole	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Way	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
Muslin	O
Neckloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linen	O
being	O
put	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Johnson	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Lad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Way	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Johnson	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Way	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pail	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pail	O
was	O
stoln	O
away	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
washing	O
the	O
Entry	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Fathom	O
of	O
Harser	O
,	O
value5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sandwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
the	O
Harser	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
coil	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
who	O
spoke	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Kirby	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lefever	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stainsmore	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
,	O
at	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
(	O
his	O
Wife	O
Prudence	O
being	O
then	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
Stainsmore	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
House-door	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Trunk	O
where	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
both	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Box	O
into	O
a	O
Stonecutters	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
directed	O
a	O
Young	O
Fellow	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Paddington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Jasper	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
home	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
at	O
Bay	B-place
's	I-place
Watering	I-place
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
on	O
Foot	O
;	O
who	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
got	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
help	O
;	O
who	O
going	O
in	O
pursuit	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Hampsted	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Work	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Baker	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
not	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
3	O
Jacobus	O
's	O
,	O
3	O
Carolus	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Double-Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
from	O
Joanna	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
break	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
were	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
;	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Sibbs	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
the	I-place
Chain	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
and	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
only	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
4	O
Years	O
Old	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
first	O
stripping	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Bodice-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
strangling	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Woolen	O
Lift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
by	O
an	O
Aunt	O
,	O
who	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
School	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Mistress	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
search	O
for	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
wander	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Glass	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
to	O
warm	O
it	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
know	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Parents	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
crying	O
Old	O
Hats	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
Berry-street	O
by	O
the	O
Jews	O
Synagogue	O
,	O
mending	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Hat	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Boddice-coat	O
,	O
Frock	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
The	O
Woman	O
afterwards	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Child	O
cry	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
whose	O
Cloaths	O
answer	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
which	O
having	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
meer	O
Chance	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Aunt	O
hearing	O
of	O
somebody	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stripping	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
Stripping	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Shirt	O
was	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
his	O
blue	O
Bib	O
sew	O
'd	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
mending	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Woolen	O
Garter	O
lying	O
upon	O
its	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mark	O
round	O
the	O
Neck	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
strangl	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
naked	O
all	O
but	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
kill	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
stript	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
concurring	O
Circumstances	O
made	O
the	O
Murder	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Powel	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
for	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Hanger	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Warrant	O
being	O
issu	O
'd	O
against	O
Roberts	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
commanded	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
;	O
That	O
accordingly	O
they	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bannister	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Roberts	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
Roberts	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Bannister	O
came	O
with	O
great	O
Rage	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Woman	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Bannister	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Roberts	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Sword	O
(	O
or	O
Hanger	O
)	O
into	O
Robert	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rogues	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
kill	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
flourish	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Assistants	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
who	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
,	O
Bannister	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
Sword	O
,	O
Stick	O
,	O
Knife	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
Weapon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
disprove	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
some	O
swearing	O
theDeceas	O
'd	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
others	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
both	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Warrant	O
was	O
shewn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
very	O
violently	O
upon	O
Bannister	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
alledg	O
'd	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
put	O
him	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
made	O
appear	O
that	O
Roberts	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Shusley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
and	O
2	O
Plates	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
going	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Bonner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
in	O
jest	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
fully	O
heard	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
Bonner	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Shusley	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
was	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
another	O
piece	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
bottom	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
several	O
Pieces	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
in	O
Gloucester-shire	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
way	O
to	O
disprove	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Beard	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Exeter-Exchange	B-place
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Sword	O
snatch	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
no	O
where	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Two	O
Gentlemen	O
swore	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
snatch	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
old	O
Excuse	O
for	O
his	O
Flight	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Islington	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Sheep	O
being	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
stopt	O
by	O
Bloomsbury-Watch	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Mutton	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
5	O
Joints	O
,	O
which	O
comparing	O
with	O
what	O
was	O
left	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sheep	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
5	O
pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
were	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
fully	O
appear	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Boddice	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Lapley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
'em	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Macklear	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
Goods	O
.	O
Shaw	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Shop	O
with	O
two	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrench	O
off	O
the	O
Padlock	O
,	O
and	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
other	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
entring	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Padlock	O
and	O
a	O
Betty	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Betty	O
and	O
knock	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Cockale	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfelon	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
two	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
and	O
56	O
Pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
swore	O
,	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
And	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
as	O
a	O
suspicious	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
with	O
the	O
Bacon	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
got	O
their	O
Hands	O
in	O
and	O
unbarr	O
'd	O
the	O
Shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
as	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Butter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
by	O
his	O
Comrade	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
were	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
satisfyed	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cubbidge	I-pers
alias	O
Shanks	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
Surgeons	O
Instruments	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cubbidge	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Jewry	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
who	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
him	O
his	O
Friend	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
robb'dhim	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
bustle	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
Plummer	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
.	O
Cubbidge	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
meet	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
wou	O
'd	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
remember	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
Plummer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
Cubbidge	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Mawley	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
nine	O
Weeks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gone	O
.	O
Being	O
taken	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hannaway	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Douglas	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Looking-Glasses	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pashley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Lambs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Buckeridge	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mackarty	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Hawkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Aunts	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
driven	O
to	O
Necessity	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Plates	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
clear	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
the	I-place
Chain	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach-seat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Blankets	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
Writ	O
of	O
Restitution	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Draper	O
,	O
for	O
eight	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Jenkins	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Tho	O
.	O
Moore	O
being	O
convicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
of	O
twenty	O
eight	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
'em	O
to	O
Turner	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
the	O
Maker	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Turner	O
being	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
reputable	O
Man	O
,	O
did	O
sell	O
the	O
eight	O
Pieces	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Writ	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
fairly	O
measur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
entred	O
in	O
his	O
Book	O
.	O
Several	O
very	O
good	O
Traders	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
justify	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
a	O
full	O
Market-price	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Writ	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
the	O
Defendant	O
should	O
pay	O
15	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5.	O
Ann	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Beard	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
20.	O
Frances	B-pers
Cushaw	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Daley	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Muchel	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Handy	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
Lesever	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sibs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cockale	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humby	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
11.	O
James	B-pers
Linker	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
Gorge	O
Twesves	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Macklear	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
and	O
Fin	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
N	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Fin	O
'd	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
