TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1714	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
STANIER	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
Jacob	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
,	O
Randolph	B-pers
Furnley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Court	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Player	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Albrittain	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stroed	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bavan	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Carns	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Roads	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hassard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stin	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bidfoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Stin	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
while	O
Bidfoy	O
was	O
cheapning	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Stin	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Witness	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
indictment	O
.	O
They	O
deny	O
'd	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
divers	O
Times	O
gone	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Times	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
contradicted	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Fustian	O
Value	O
9s	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Byram	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
cheapning	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Fustian	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
escaped	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Ticking	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Best	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Stephen	I-place
Colemanstreet	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Breeches	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Griffith	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	O
Bush	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
Jacob	O
Bush	O
and	O
herself	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
their	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Closet	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
pursuit	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	O
Bush	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Quest	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Quest	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
hers	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
doubting	O
her	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Bags	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
d.	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pound	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
together	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
(	O
Price	O
Three-pence	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
over	O
a	O
Door	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Wiltord	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
Salts	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Shackleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	B-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
was	O
admitted	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
written	O
,	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
with	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
sham	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Rainbow-Coffee-House	O
at	O
the	O
Ditch	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shackleton	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
his	O
Customer	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
Porter	O
all	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bringing	O
some	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Green	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Nine	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barley	O
,	O
Value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
wrong	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clover	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
Soper-Lane	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
sixty	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Callico	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sewel	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Pettycoat	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
immediately	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
Clover	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hulls	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
at	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
Hulls	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
Ten	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
Noise	O
above	O
Stairs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
calling	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
run	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
crying	O
for	O
Assistance	O
,	O
Pursuit	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
running	O
within	O
ten	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dropt	O
four	O
Picklock-Keys	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
and	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
Hull	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
little	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hillary	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dionis	I-place
Back	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dozen	O
Pair	O
of	O
black	O
worsted	O
Stockins	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
Veal	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
in	O
Leadenhall-Market	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
also	O
plainly	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holt	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ann	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Sattin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Lingham	B-pers
Asterly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Forest	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
thread	O
Sattin	O
for	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
pitch	O
upon	O
any	O
,	O
till	O
her	O
cousin	O
came	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
lik	O
'd	O
her	O
Fancy	O
;	O
immediately	O
after	O
which	O
Ridley	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bought	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
25	O
s.	O
which	O
they	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
suspected	O
for	O
Shoplifters	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
dragg	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
from	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brampton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Gold-beater	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
searching	O
for	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
Powders	O
in	O
Black	O
Copper	O
a	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Utensils	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Shilling	O
newly	O
cast	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
trying	O
Experiments	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
clear	O
to	O
prove	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Dewry	I-pers
,	O
Esq	B-pers
;	I-pers
alias	O
Sir	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Witherington	I-pers
,	O
Kt	B-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Newnham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tyndal	I-pers
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
last	O
Marriage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Obediah	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Honey	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
pairs	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
--	B-pers
-	I-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Roderick	O
Awdey	O
,	O
(	O
lately	O
executed	O
)	O
who	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
his	O
Box	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
some	O
Ground	O
to	O
believe	O
the	O
Evidence	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Blare	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
suspecting	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Haynes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
7	O
Dishes	O
and	O
other	O
Pewter	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
into	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
which	O
by	O
its	O
Bulk	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Pewter	O
)	O
at	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
as	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Bernard	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
borrow	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
a	O
mantle	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
assaulted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
reaching	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
then	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
broke	O
her	O
Hold	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Whitchurch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
Person	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
Stockins	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
2	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
compare	O
'em	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
which	O
pretending	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
,	O
struck	O
Mrs.	O
Whitchurch	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Stockins	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
and	O
sworn	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Whitchurch	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
Servants	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
contradict	O
so	O
plain	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Muslin	O
Neck	O
cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Duffin	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Porter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
It	O
appear'dthat	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
s	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
having	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
taken	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Laton	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
along	O
Holborn	B-place
with	O
his	O
coat	O
tied	O
behind	O
his	O
Saddle	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
it	O
suddenly	O
snatch	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
back	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
having	O
dropt	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
Locket	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.Fountain	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
with	O
another	O
Gentlewoman	O
pretty	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Gentlewoman	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
,	O
pretended	O
herself	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Bedside	O
,	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Fountain	O
hung	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
soon	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
coming	O
from	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
in	O
Somerest-Yard	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
her	O
Goods	O
seiz	O
'd	O
for	O
Rent	O
,	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
her	O
request	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
at	O
so	O
unseasonable	O
time	O
,	O
was	O
her	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
:	O
But	O
her	O
Confession	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Holyoak	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
10.s	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
drank	O
there	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
some	O
Company	O
had	O
a	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
drinking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
fill	O
'd	O
)	O
.	O
Being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Albion	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thompson	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
favourable	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
Value	O
3l	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shop	O
being	O
pretty	O
full	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Silk	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
reputation	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Shoplifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Poppleton	I-pers
alias	O
Douglas	B-pers
,	O
(	O
spelt	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
Jougla	B-pers
)	O
alias	O
Drake	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Malard	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
two	O
husbands	O
living	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
alias	O
Jougla	B-pers
her	O
First	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Michael	B-pers
Malard	I-pers
her	O
Second	O
Husband	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
owned	O
her	O
last	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
18	O
Years	O
past	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
Douglas	O
alias	O
Jougla	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Husband	O
for	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
her	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
said	O
first	O
Husband	O
was	O
still	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
lately	O
gone	O
beyond	O
the	O
Sea	O
.	O
Yet	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
or	O
convers	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Second	O
Marriage	O
good	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
void	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Michael	B-pers
Malard	I-pers
was	O
at	O
Liberty	O
to	O
marry	O
when	O
and	O
whom	O
he	O
pleases	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her/	O
B	B-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Rosewel	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Dowson	I-pers
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Wives	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
were	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
9	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
safe	O
home	O
;	O
where	O
,	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
wake	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
wake	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
not	O
home	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
but	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
Black-Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Concern	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
almost	O
100	O
l.	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
9	O
Broad-pieces	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
concurring	O
Circumstances	O
to	O
his	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brereton	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
John	O
Lord	O
Brereton	O
,	O
Baron	O
of	O
Lawly	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Pendulum	O
Clock	O
.	O
value	O
30	O
l	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Lord	O
Brereton	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
stoln	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Clock	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
upon	O
a	O
search	O
from	O
some	O
stoln	O
Pewter	O
,	O
the	O
Clock	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Stent	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
by	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
House	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
(	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
absconds	O
from	O
Justice	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
considered	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Deciers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Rump-Bone	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Commissaries	O
Office	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Establishment	O
as	O
a	O
Half-pay	O
Lieutenant	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Colonel	O
William	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
found	O
his	O
Name	O
left	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Drew	O
's	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
;	O
which	O
very	O
much	O
disturb	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
present	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Clerk	O
telling	O
him	O
a	O
Certificate	O
would	O
set	O
the	O
Matter	O
right	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
pacify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
upon	O
the	O
Parade	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Button	O
in	O
a	O
fury	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
wounded	O
.	O
Another	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
parrying	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
pushing	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Thrusts	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fought	O
till	O
the	O
Deaceas	O
'd	O
was	O
disabled	O
by	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Sword-wrist	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
who	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
found	O
how	O
ungentlemanlike	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
himin	O
the	O
Commissaries	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
him	O
immediately	O
in	O
the	O
Parade	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Commission	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
's	O
Regiment	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Mall	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
and	O
drew	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'	O
two	O
wounds	O
before	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
any	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Blow	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
drew	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
drew	O
first	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
again	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Wound	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
by	O
turning	O
round	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
making	O
so	O
full	O
a	O
thrust	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edminton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
was	O
broke	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
amongst	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
several	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
by	O
taking	O
down	O
a	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Wood	O
Green	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
the	O
Pursuer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Southam	I-pers
and	O
D	B-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
--	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Grounds	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Possession	O
of	O
Southam	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
T	O
--	O
-	O
to	O
vouch	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
positively	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Southam	O
had	O
as	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
15	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
and	O
particularly	O
,	O
a	O
Farmer	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
shod	O
the	O
Horse	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
Southam	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
it	O
now	O
had	O
on	O
was	O
of	O
his	O
making	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Southam	O
had	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Creditt	O
whop	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
good	O
Substance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Sheep	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Marsh	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Custom	O
house	O
Officer	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Marsh	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
57	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Rope	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Job	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fault	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bolted	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
at	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margate	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
by	O
squeezing	O
her	O
Head	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Near-wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
drove	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
moderate	O
rate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
extremely	O
troubled	O
at	O
the	O
Accident	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
the	O
Fields	O
in	O
a	O
languishing	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
Parish-Officers	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
rapt	O
it	O
in	O
Straw	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Pond-side	O
,	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Cirencester	O
in	O
Gloucstershire	O
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
midwife	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
afterwards	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
child	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Brick	O
kiln	O
near	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
Child	O
in	O
Straw	O
,	O
she	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
Kiln	O
while	O
it	O
was	O
burning	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
all	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
very	O
ramblingly	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Winesses	O
appearing	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
not	O
well	O
in	O
her	O
Senses	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
M	B-pers
--	I-pers
J	I-pers
--	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Ordway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Five	B-place
Bells	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Rhenish	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
believes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
from	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
alias	O
Hedgly	B-pers
,	O
Margate	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Margate	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
3	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Stent	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mellers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
40	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Mellers	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
down	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
11	O
and	O
3	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
saw	O
Cook	O
bring	O
the	O
Pewter	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
Davis	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Pewter	O
from	O
Hockly	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
is	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Cook	O
's	O
Wife	O
carrying	O
the	O
Plates	O
to	O
Nortonfalgate	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
go	O
and	O
own	O
them	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
that	O
Davis	O
and	O
Cook	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
Stent	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
8	O
Dishes	O
for	O
5	O
Shillings	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
last	O
being	O
only	O
hearsay	O
,	O
Stent	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
Cook	O
's	O
Wife	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
Coverture	O
;	O
and	O
Cook	O
and	O
Davis	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
--	I-pers
G	I-pers
--	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
1.s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney-Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
C.	O
G	O
--	O
-	O
down	O
in	O
Coventry-Street	B-place
;	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
with	O
what	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Fare	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
ill	O
language	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
can	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Sword	O
Cutler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wrote	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
asking	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
stay	O
'd	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
talking	O
with	O
some	O
People	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
torn	O
his	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
Bruise	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
's	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
beaten	O
as	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Complaint	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
His	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
severely	O
beaten	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
abroad	O
afterwards	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
blood	O
let	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
bleed	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
twice	O
more	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pluretick	O
Fever	O
,	O
his	O
greatest	O
Complaint	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
;	O
which	O
Evidence	O
was	O
strength	O
'd	O
by	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
Four	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
concer	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
examin	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
exactly	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Bruise	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Lungs	O
were	O
inflam	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
to	O
his	O
Chest	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Spoonful	O
of	O
Matter	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
gave	O
their	O
several	O
opinions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Pluretick	O
Fever	O
;	O
And	O
Dr.	O
Sloan	O
,	O
who	O
visited	O
him	O
,	O
declar	O
'd	O
upon	O
Oath	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
him	O
Medicines	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Coachman	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Coventry-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
in	O
doing	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
sat	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
18d	O
.	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
demanded	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
insolent	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
catching	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
tore	O
his	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
him	O
further	O
Mischief	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
clear	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
thrash	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
readily	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
anything	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
brought	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Cane	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
light	O
Thing	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Ferril	O
.	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
split	O
about	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
room	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
Instrument	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Bruise	O
as	O
was	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stokely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
from	O
Grass	O
at	O
Elding	B-place
in	O
Suffolk	B-place
;	O
And	O
a	O
Watchman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Mare	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
suspected	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
And	O
the	O
Owner	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bridle	O
under	O
her	O
feet	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Coddington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4lb	O
.	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hair	O
being	O
Bleeching	O
at	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
Grays-Inn	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wherry	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Skulls	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Meredy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Boat	O
from	O
Irongate	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
50	O
s.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Suit	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Butler	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
broke	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
Goods	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Girl	O
disturbing	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
without	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wedon	I-pers
of	O
South-Mims	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
loaden	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Shot	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
Tree	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seeing	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
innocently	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wedon	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
his	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
having	O
no	O
Prime	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
bid	O
him	O
prime	O
it	O
with	O
Oatmeal	O
,	O
thinking	O
him	O
but	O
in	O
jest	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
Powder	O
and	O
prim	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
got	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Tree	O
)	O
and	O
shot	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Tree	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fire	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
looking	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Boy	O
,	O
had	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
Victuals	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lov	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
harm	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
mightily	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
fall	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
he	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Witness	O
also	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Gun	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
charg	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
one	O
Hardam	B-pers
,	O
an	O
Unkle	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
,	O
undertook	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
stall	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Bugbert	B-pers
's	O
giving	O
a	O
Bond	O
to	O
indemnifie	O
him	O
from	O
any	O
Damage	O
that	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Non-Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
dark	O
Contrivances	O
were	O
found	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
Proceedings	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
Hardam	O
and	O
Bugbert	O
to	O
be	O
Prosecuted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Mayer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
three	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
while	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Children	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
their	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
was	O
putting	O
the	O
Children	O
to	O
Bed	O
in	O
an	O
inner	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
Husband	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
all	O
were	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Guineas	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ja	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bonner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
Steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Paintland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
Perukes	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-Cup	O
and	O
a	O
Thimble	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Doors	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Peacoe	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
for	O
stealing	O
Stuffs	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
's	O
Dye-House	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
;	O
where	O
shewing	O
them	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Snuff-Box	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
got	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Ring	O
again	O
for	O
three	O
Guineas	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
accuse	O
her	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Deleuce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
two	O
Perukes	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hats	O
,	O
Value	O
in	O
all	O
5	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
newly	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parlor-Window	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Sussex-street	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Sash	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
old	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
defence	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gumbel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
Farthings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
towards	O
Islington	B-place
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
seize	O
whoever	O
came	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
that	O
was	O
lately	O
committed	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
led	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
for	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
stript	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
him	O
lye	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
swearing	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
ventur	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
and	O
told	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Constables	O
first	O
Watch-Night	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
agreed	O
to	O
divide	O
themselves	O
into	O
three	O
Parties	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
about	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
search	O
they	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
London-Spaw	O
,	O
Perkins	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coat	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Hat	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swearing	O
positively	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter-Dish	O
and	O
three	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Moody	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
Wife	O
sick	O
in	O
the	O
inner	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
crawl	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taking	O
down	O
more	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
made	O
what	O
Noise	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
who	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
Picklock-Keys	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Emmanuel	B-pers
Francisco	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Padlock	O
was	O
wrench	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Tredder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Muslin	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Parsons	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Newton	O
,	O
which	O
Newton	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.and	O
Parsons	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
an	O
uninhabited	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Salway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Furnace	O
which	O
was	O
fastn	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
.	O
The	O
Furnace	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Morgan	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
being	O
against	O
Baker	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Holland	O
Coifs	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Coifs	O
were	O
lost	O
wet	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shed	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
150	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
Check	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Godding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
turn	O
up	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
lye	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Shoplifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Sheet	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ravenscroft	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Pettycoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
House	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Gown	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
bought	O
'em	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
old	O
Goods	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
robbing	O
George	B-pers
Wallom	I-pers
of	O
four	O
Pettycoats	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Caps	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
Part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edminton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
at	O
Winchmore	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pillowbers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Worsley	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
2	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
Taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Edminton	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
chance	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
new	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mistake	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cobier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Fraser	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Cotmore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Feathers	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Mill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
Bottles	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Billingsby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Judith	O
Fa	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Callico	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
that	O
goes	O
from	O
Shoreditch	O
towards	O
Old	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leading	O
the	O
Child	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
ragged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
neatly	O
clad	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
dogg	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
reached	O
a	O
bye-place	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
to	O
her	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
let	O
her	O
until	O
she	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
dreadful	O
Fright	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
threatn	O
'd	O
to	O
throw	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Pond	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
so	O
plain	O
a	O
Proof	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Satin	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Robson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Robson	O
swore	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
which	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Benworth	B-pers
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
her	O
Money	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Her	O
Neighbour	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
3	O
Persons	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
Burgis	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
They	O
has	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
who	O
lessen	O
'd	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
George	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wappin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
Pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
Iron	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
Chapman	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Tims	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Eleanor	O
Faulkner	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
W	B-pers
--	I-pers
B	I-pers
--	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
having	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
lik	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
but	O
indifferently	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
very	O
angry	O
.	O
Some	O
Gentlemen	O
(	O
among	O
whom	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
hard-by	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
said	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
so	O
very	O
great	O
Offence	O
(	O
believing	O
the	O
Words	O
were	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
perswaded	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
without	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deaceas	O
'd	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
engag	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
seen	O
who	O
struck	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
threw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
,	O
washed	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
;	O
only	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
chaleng	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
next	O
Morning	O
for	O
five	O
Shillings	O
.	O
They	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
not	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Complaint	O
of	O
any	O
Bruise	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
home	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
afterwards	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
to	O
outward	O
Appearance	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
Fit	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
himself	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Bruises	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
those	O
Bruises	O
might	O
be	O
got	O
by	O
his	O
Fall	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
two	O
Notes	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
4	O
l	O
.	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
Rudd	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Bond	O
travers	O
'd	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pass	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
19	O
.	O
Jacob	O
Bush	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Elliot	O
,	O
James	O
Powell	O
,	O
Jos	O
.	O
Hutton	O
,	O
Frances	O
Dye	O
,	O
William	O
Holyoak	O
,	O
Charles	O
Goodale	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
William	O
Dyer	O
,	O
Robert	O
Cook	O
,	O
alias	O
Hedgley	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Davis	O
,	O
John	O
Stokely	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Price	O
,	O
Robert	O
Porter	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Perkins	O
,	O
George	O
Horn	O
,	O
Ann	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
Mary	O
Billingsby	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
24	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Stin	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bidfoy	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Alice	O
Forest	O
,	O
Mary	O
Ridley	O
,	O
Charles	O
Clark	O
,	O
Ann	O
Williams	O
,	O
William	O
Hoskins	O
,	O
James	O
Decier	O
,	O
Deborah	O
Stent	O
,	O
T	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
B	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
James	O
Noland	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Noble	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Parsons	O
,	O
J	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
M	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
George	O
Coddington	O
,	O
Richard	O
Wells	O
,	O
Ann	O
Williams	O
,	O
Alice	O
Mayer	O
,	O
John	O
Wedon	O
,	O
John	O
Biddle	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Horn	O
,	O
Jane	O
Revel	O
,	O
George	O
Price	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
11	O
.	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
,	O
Henry	O
Map	O
,	O
William	O
Clark	O
,	O
Mary	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Tayler	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Newman	O
,	O
Ann	O
Clark	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cross	O
,	O
Mary	O
Munday	O
,	O
Richard	O
Mill	O
,	O
William	O
Walker	O
.	O
Alexander	O
Rudd	O
Fin	O
'd	O
5	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
in	O
3	O
Months	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
return	O
without	O
Licence	O
.	O
Henry	O
Morgan	O
Fin	O
'd	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	O
Stevenson	O
and	O
Ann	O
Edwards	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
THE	O
History	O
of	O
Nonconformity	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
Grounds	O
thereof	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Ministers	O
&	O
c	O
who	O
were	O
ejected	O
after	O
the	O
Restoration	O
of	O
K.	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
their	O
Apology	O
for	O
themselves	O
and	O
their	O
Adherents	O
;	O
their	O
Treatment	O
in	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
and	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Revolution	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Continuation	O
of	O
their	O
History	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
passing	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
against	O
Occasional	O
Conformity	O
in	O
1715	O
,	O
in	O
2	O
Volumes	O
.	O
By	O
Edmund	O
Calamy	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Price	O
14	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
certifie	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Child	O
being	O
violently	O
afflicted	O
with	O
Pain	O
and	O
other	O
Disorders	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
hard	O
Breeding	O
of	O
Teeth	O
,	O
that	O
famous	O
Remedy	O
prepared	O
for	O
those	O
Cases	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Perronet	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
was	O
used	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
Success	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
attribute	O
the	O
happy	O
Preservation	O
of	O
my	O
Child	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
next	O
under	O
God	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
that	O
excellent	O
Medicine	O
.	O
Witness	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
William	O
Clarke	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Peruke	O
in	O
Great	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
by	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
Peruke	O
Maker	O
.	O
This	O
Medicine	O
is	O
sold	O
at	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
per	O
Vial	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
Mr.	O
Perronet	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
Arms	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Dyot	O
Street	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alcross	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Coat-Boy	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Places	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Sir	O
Kenelm	O
Digby	O
's	O
Apoplectick	O
Powder	O
,	O
or	O
Snuff	O
,	O
which	O
effectually	O
cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
,	O
Vapours	O
,	O
Dizziness	O
,	O
Heaviness	O
,	O
Impostumes	O
,	O
Stoppages	O
and	O
Drowsiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Defluxion	O
of	O
Rheum	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Loss	O
of	O
Smell	O
,	O
and	O
Thickness	O
of	O
Hearing	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
;	O
dwelling	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
over-against	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
lately	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
since	O
cur	O
'd	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
THE	O
Gentlewoman	O
who	O
practised	O
Physick	O
in	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Sex	O
in	O
Wine-Office	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Hind-Court	O
,	O
being	O
now	O
returned	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
those	O
Ladies	O
who	O
have	O
lamented	O
her	O
Absence	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
poisonous	O
Mercurials	O
,	O
and	O
Bismuth	O
Powder	O
(	O
a	O
Preparation	O
made	O
up	O
with	O
Aqua-Fortis	O
)	O
sold	O
at	O
Chymists	O
,	O
Apothecaries	O
,	O
and	O
Powder-Shops	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
forced	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
her	O
excellent	O
Preparations	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
now	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
spoken	O
with	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Hart	O
and	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ridout	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
by	O
furnished	O
with	O
her	O
Cosmeticks	O
for	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
prepar	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
take	O
away	O
infallibly	O
all	O
Redness	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Scurf	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
likewise	O
prepares	O
the	O
Bavarian	O
Red	O
Liquor	O
,	O
which	O
gives	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Blushing	O
Colour	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
of	O
a	O
pale	O
Complexion	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
so	O
natural	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
nicest	O
Scrutiner	O
can	O
not	O
dinstinguish	O
;	O
and	O
gives	O
her	O
Advice	O
in	O
Physck	O
,	O
as	O
formerly	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Sex	O
,	O
who	O
thro	O
'	O
Modesty	O
can	O
not	O
relate	O
their	O
Disorders	O
to	O
a	O
Male	O
Physician	O
.	O
