TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
New	O
gate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
17	O
15/16	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PEERS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
John	B-pers
Luckin	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Lowick	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pestell	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hedgeabout	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smithies	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Weely	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Chadd	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Beatknife	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Gun	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Opportunities	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Llewellyn	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
on	I-place
London	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
(	O
also	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Child	O
and	O
Elias	O
Wynn	O
were	O
at	O
Play	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
without	O
their	O
Hats	O
;	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
his	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Boy	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wynn	O
's	O
,	O
whose	O
Child	O
also	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
both	O
Hats	O
were	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
Wyan	O
's	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
weak	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
considering	O
his	O
Youth	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Allcock	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Vedast	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Foster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Value	O
42	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Decembe	O
r	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Roger	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Naggs-Head	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
)	O
and	O
went	O
immediately	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
which	O
the	O
Cook-Maid	O
had	O
wash	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoons	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
convenient	O
Place	O
by	O
the	O
Sink	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
extraordinary	O
gay	O
and	O
genteel	O
,	O
and	O
complemented	O
away	O
his	O
Wine	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
very	O
often	O
to	O
the	O
Sink	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
making	O
Water	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
Cook	O
was	O
busied	O
in	O
dressing	O
a	O
Duck	O
for	O
some	O
Company	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
near	O
ready	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
Occasion	O
for	O
Spoons	O
to	O
the	O
Sauce	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
Circumstances	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
forthwith	O
sent	O
away	O
his	O
Servants	O
with	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
Taverns	O
about	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
twice	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
became	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Coffee	O
House	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
Track	O
and	O
in	O
Essex	O
Street	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
humbly	O
begged	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
being	O
insulted	O
by	O
the	O
Populace	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
complied	O
with	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
with	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
whom	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Friend	O
.	O
to	O
recover	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Goldsmith	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoons	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
by	O
Candle-light	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
short	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
conceal	O
his	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoons	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
young	O
Man	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
some	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
being	O
better	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
World	O
)	O
to	O
sell	O
those	O
Spoons	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
some	O
Spoons	O
that	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Mind	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
those	O
he	O
directed	O
his	O
Friend	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
believing	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Appearance	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Reputation	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
the	O
Confirmation	O
of	O
his	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
38	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dunton	I-pers
(	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
)	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
was	O
his	O
usual	O
Method	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
so	O
gay	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
suspected	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
Drawer	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dunton	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
apprehended	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
Fact	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Drawer	O
that	O
serv	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
One	O
Mrs.	O
Riley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
of	O
him	O
)	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
Spoons	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
questioning	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Spoons	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Her	O
Daughter	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Defence	O
by	O
taking	O
Advantage	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
Mr.	O
Dunton	O
's	O
Boy	O
gave	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Spoons	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
at	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
)	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Dunton	O
would	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
been	O
discover	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
towards	O
clearing	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
discovering	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Somerset	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
300	O
Weight	O
of	O
Cordage	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
One	O
Pollard	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cordage	O
stole	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
one	O
Luck	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
honestly	O
;	O
That	O
selling	O
and	O
buying	O
of	O
Cordage	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
That	O
no	O
Person	O
could	O
swear	O
absolutely	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
to	O
a	O
Rope	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
Several	O
Persons	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
when	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
could	O
clear	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
accordingly	O
heard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gabriel	I-place
Fenchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mumford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
one	O
Captain	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
leave	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
granted	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
describ	O
'd	O
his	O
Person	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
chance	O
had	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
apprehend	O
ed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Charge	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
made	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Currant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
Breadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
small	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Morehouse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
Newgate	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Gerrard	B-place
's	I-place
Hall-Inn	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Stables	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
clear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
who	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Eull	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
16	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	O
Boyden	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Boyden	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
Newgate	B-place
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
about	O
it	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Execution	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
kept	O
her	O
Hands	O
in	O
her	O
Pockets	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
push	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
save	O
herself	O
from	O
falling	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
:	O
But	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
she	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
who	O
she	O
thought	O
was	O
come	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
might	O
possibly	O
feel	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
She	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
she	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baldwin	O
made	O
it	O
plain	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Roast	O
Beef	O
and	O
Minc	O
'd	O
Pies	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
were	O
seen	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
with	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
he	O
sent	O
Man	O
and	O
Horse	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Examination	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
One	O
Bell	O
swore	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
3	O
Spoons	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
varied	O
in	O
his	O
Stories	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Companion	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
shaving	O
Mr.	O
Hollis	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
offering	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
(	O
who	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Honour	O
,	O
has	O
detected	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
upon	O
such	O
Accounts	O
)	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
his	O
last	O
,	O
Which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Chain-Traces	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Whip	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
made	O
it	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
Value	O
48	O
s.	O
1	O
Box	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
reasonable	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Grapling	O
Irons	O
,	O
Value	O
34	O
s.	O
1	O
Iron	O
Chain	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
1	O
Iron	O
Swivel	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
some	O
Friends	O
with	O
Orders	O
to	O
sell	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
their	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictment	O
under	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anne	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Iron	O
Choppers	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Choppers	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
Stole	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chopper	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pepperell	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wells	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
in	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ennis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
who	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
Defence	O
but	O
a	O
flat	O
Denial	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Forgery	O
in	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Attorney	O
for	O
120	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
in	O
this	O
Kind	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
suing	O
Broad	O
for	O
a	O
pretended	O
Debt	O
of	O
61	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
to	O
an	O
Execution	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Broad	O
's	O
Name	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
said	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Two	O
Letters	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
one	O
in	O
Broad	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
which	O
exactly	O
conform	O
'd	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Forgery	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nothing	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
litigious	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
)	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
a	O
Negro	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Collar	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Boy	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
and	O
complaining	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
long	O
on	O
his	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
fear	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Collar	O
would	O
betray	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Fruit-Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
broke	O
the	O
Collar	O
with	O
their	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
took	O
off	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Haslam	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Chennery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
Arthur	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clean	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
whose	O
Wife	O
seeing	O
her	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
quite	O
away	O
without	O
Notice	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
stol'n	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
Complaint	O
that	O
several	O
loose	O
Persons	O
harbour	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Play-House	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
lost	O
their	O
Watches	O
,	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
he	O
and	O
other	O
Servants	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
scour	O
the	O
Avenues	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
Persons	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
he	O
;	O
let	O
's	O
knock	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Fury	O
,	O
broke	O
his	O
Thumb	O
to	O
Shatters	O
,	O
bruised	O
his	O
Legs	O
and	O
Body	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
also	O
noted	O
for	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pictures	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
my	O
Lady	O
Copley	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
a	O
Joyner	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
Pictures	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Lady	O
Copley	O
saying	O
there	O
wanted	O
some	O
Rings	O
to	O
fix	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
the	O
Pictures	O
;	O
my	O
Lady	O
Copley	O
thinking	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
Servant	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
hung	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
known	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoo	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hoo	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Captain	O
Hoo	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Passenger	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Captain	O
at	O
the	O
New-England	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
presently	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dry	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
return	O
immediately	O
.	O
Her	O
Maid	O
saw	O
the	O
Hilt	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Story	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hoo	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shorey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
he	O
as	O
Principal	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
slight	O
Partition	O
between	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Briant	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Briant	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
proper	O
Times	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
Pierce	O
.	O
The	O
Place	O
was	O
once	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chest	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
in	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prudam	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
90	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cherry	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Perks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
against	O
him	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Hen	O
Turkey	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
15	O
Capons	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Hens	O
,	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathan	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jewish	O
Poulterer	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plain	O
that	O
Samuel	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Tutt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Brass	O
Porridge-pot	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Robert	O
Tutt	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Tenement	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Tutt	O
had	O
his	O
;	O
who	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Poultry	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
suspicious	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hand-saw	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church-yard	I-place
in	O
Spittle	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
These	O
Goods	O
were	O
also	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Passmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pottle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Passmore	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
in	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Wool	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lemmet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
;	O
and	O
Pottle	O
,	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Passmore	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Pottle	O
received	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
very	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
brought	O
Passmore	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Bartley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
Fife	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Tower-hill	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
met	O
Katherine	O
Ely	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
such	O
,	O
sort	O
of	O
Persons	O
,	O
complied	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Church	B-place
Lane	I-place
by	O
Rag-Fair	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
some	O
strong	O
Drink	O
and	O
Geneva	O
.	O
White	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
try	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bartley	O
,	O
who	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Resistance	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
his	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Breast-Buttons	O
off	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
where	O
meeting	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
supposing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Bullies	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Headborough	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Thoughts	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
hearing	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
me	O
too	O
,	O
was	O
mightily	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Who	O
had	O
injur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Transaction	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Courage	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
White	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Buckles	O
,	O
on	O
Condition	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Thus	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
stifly	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
most	O
impudent	O
Prostitute	O
,	O
whose	O
extraordinary	O
Progress	O
in	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Wickedness	O
had	O
gain	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Pretty	O
Lady	O
,	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
Fife	O
chuck	O
'd	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Chin	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Fire	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
replied	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Her	O
the	O
Buckles	O
for	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
Evidence	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
into	O
Custody	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
extraordinary	O
Impudence	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Daton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
6	O
Gawze	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
Silk	O
Ditto	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Barlow	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tweedee	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Tweedee	O
was	O
a	O
Washing-Woman	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Hand	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Downes	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
his	O
Door	O
unlocked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
some	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Glass	O
.	O
Have	O
I	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
then	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
very	O
trifling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Toby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Veal	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
1	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
2	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
swore	O
;	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
his	O
Youth	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Proof	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
West-Minster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Callicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
with	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Tablecloths	O
,	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fellow	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Quilt	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
32	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Handy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Handy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Lodging	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
leave	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
Duty	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
contented	O
but	O
what	O
vex	O
'd	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
lie	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
after	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
But	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
tell	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
32	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Pocket	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
who	O
next	O
Morning	O
felt	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
thought	O
his	O
Wife	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
contentedly	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cozens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Measures	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Footman	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
)	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
between	B-place
Stratford	I-place
and	O
Ilford	B-place
in	O
Essex	B-place
,	O
he	O
met	O
three	O
Highway-men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
his	O
Spurs	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
Bow	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
and	O
Stevens	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
demand	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Horse	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
they	O
set	O
spurs	O
to	O
their	O
Horses	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
close	O
at	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
quitted	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
leap	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
a	O
Field	O
;	O
hereupon	O
Mr.	O
White	O
gave	O
his	O
Servant	O
a	O
small	O
Gun	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
fir	O
'd	O
twice	O
at	O
the	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
(	O
his	O
Gun	O
being	O
loaded	O
with	O
small	O
Shot	O
)	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Cullinder	O
of	O
his	O
Scull	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
is	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
kill	O
or	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
we	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
taken	O
alive	O
:	O
Let	O
's	O
turn	O
upon	O
them	O
and	O
fire	O
;	O
our	O
Lives	O
are	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
theirs	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
charge	O
his	O
Gun	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
Pebble	O
Stones	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
hit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Highway-man	O
was	O
also	O
taken	O
by	O
another	O
Mr.White	O
,	O
no	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
accidentally	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
appris	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
leap	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Ditch	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Hanger	O
drawn	O
:	O
Stephens	O
seeing	O
himself	O
hard	O
put	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
presented	O
two	O
Pistols	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
bid	O
him	O
fire	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
cleave	O
his	O
Scull	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
seeing	O
his	O
Companion	O
already	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
surrendred	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
his	O
Pistols	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
two	O
Musquetoons	O
and	O
a	O
Screw	O
Pistol	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
Make	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
unfair	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
loaded	O
with	O
3	O
Bullets	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
with	O
2	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
swore	O
,	O
Four	O
Men	O
came	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
to	O
his	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
being	O
lame	O
with	O
a	O
Cut	O
on	O
the	O
Knee	O
,	O
one	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Farrier	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
cure	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
cur	O
'd	O
,	O
Smith	O
's	O
Brother	O
came	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
by	O
the	O
Farrier	O
,	O
who	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Cure	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
making	O
nothing	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
of	O
the	O
Opinion	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
This	O
Desperado	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Bail-Dock	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
thought	O
the	O
safest	O
Place	O
for	O
such	O
Persons	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Spurling	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hold	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
on	O
Saturday-Night	O
,	O
(	O
while	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Keepers	O
were	O
employ	O
'd	O
about	O
another	O
Cause	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
some	O
other	O
Criminals	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
over	O
the	O
Spikes	O
into	O
the	O
further	O
Passage	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
fetter	O
'd	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
.	O
Stevens	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
this	O
Sessions	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Eckersly	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katharines	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Eckersly	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shagg	O
,	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
1	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
several	O
Drawers	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
sorts	O
of	O
Slop	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Jesson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
;	O
and	O
Walton	O
as	O
Accessory	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Eckersly	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Walton	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Eckersly	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Deborah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Worsted	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
17	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Medcalfe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Hope	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Horse	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
Home	O
as	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
him	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
in	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
wanting	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
That	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
wonder	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
upon	O
a	O
Car-man	O
's	O
Horse	O
with	O
his	O
Harness	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
inquire	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
thrown	O
by	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Pond	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Hampstead	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
tir	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
the	O
Devil	O
had	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
a	O
Trooper	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
thought	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
harmless	O
Frolick	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Dearn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dearn	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
ingenious	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
Drawers	O
(	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Things	O
aforesaid	O
were	O
stole	O
)	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
desiring	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
a	O
small	O
Time	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
Room	O
enough	O
in	O
her	O
Son	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Writings	O
(	O
of	O
Consequence	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
that	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
56	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
Nails	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
some	O
Plates	O
,	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
Duncomb	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Duncomb	O
's	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
H	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
broke	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
as	O
did	O
also	O
the	O
Women	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
flat	O
Denial	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
the	O
Affair	O
into	O
their	O
Consideration	O
brought	O
H	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
H-	O
T-	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Douglass	O
and	O
Nightingale	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Way	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
,	O
provided	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
light	O
him	O
home	O
:	O
He	O
complied	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
conducted	O
to	O
the	B-place
Ship	I-place
in	O
Church-lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Knight	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Hopkins	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Allcock	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
H	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
V	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wells	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Chennery	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shorey	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Bartley	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Eckersly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
8.	O
William	B-pers
Llewellyn	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Currant	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Passmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Veal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Fin	O
'd	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Pregnant	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
WHereas	O
James	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
alias	O
Footman	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
(	O
with	O
Irons	O
on	O
,	O
by	O
leaping	O
over	O
the	O
Spikes	O
of	O
the	O
Bail-Dock	O
and	O
the	O
Rails	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
37	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
5	O
Foot	O
10	O
Inches	O
high	O
,	O
much	O
Pock-fretten	O
,	O
has	O
many	O
Freckles	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
Hands	O
,	O
a	O
wide	O
Mouth	O
,	O
down	O
Look	O
,	O
speaks	O
very	O
broad	O
,	O
a	O
reddish	O
beard	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
wear	O
a	O
brown	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
lately	O
live	O
at	O
Aylesbury	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Nape	O
of	O
the	O
Neck	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
since	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
Wound	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
small	O
Pieces	O
of	O
his	O
Scull	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Whoever	O
can	O
discover	O
the	O
said	O
Person	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
shall	O
receive	O
Twenty	O
Pounds	O
Reward	O
from	O
Bodenham	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
Head	O
Turnkey	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
ARithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
,	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edit	O
.	O
Pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
.	O
Length	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper-Plates	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
London	O
new	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
distinctly	O
and	O
perfectly	O
:	O
By	O
learning	O
them	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Letters	O
in	O
the	O
several	O
usual	O
Prints	O
,	O
the	O
true	O
Sounds	O
of	O
Dipthougs	O
,	O
then	O
Syllables	O
of	O
2	O
,	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
Letters	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Spelling	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
exemplified	O
in	O
Several	O
Chapters	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Chapters	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Stops	O
and	O
Marks	O
,	O
the	O
Numeral	O
Letters	O
and	O
Figures	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
usual	O
Abbreviations	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
may	O
immediately	O
pass	O
from	O
Learning	O
this	O
Book	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
Time	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Book	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School-Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
Schools	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
;	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Care	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
At	O
Her	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Red	O
Ball	O
in	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
,	O
Liveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
she	O
hath	O
an	O
Ointment	O
call	O
'd	O
The	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Goat	O
and	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
giving	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
at	O
Home	O
or	O
Abroad	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
experienc	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
that	O
have	O
carried	O
it	O
with'em	O
into	O
Foreign	O
Parts	O
,	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
)	O
and	O
compleats	O
the	O
Cure	O
;	O
as	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
used	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testifie	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
fastening	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
alters	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
delicate	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
Brown	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
.	O
Her	O
Hours	O
are	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
to	O
6	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Removed	O
from	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
.	O
