TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
1716/17	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
,	O
and	O
sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
Several	O
of	O
It	O
is	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Jos	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Forsit	I-pers
Jos.Tucker	B-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hoffman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Polliday	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Speakman	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
Williams	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
Williams	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Davenish	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Argus	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
alias	O
Pool	B-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Stow	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Stow	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Stall	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Stow	O
standing	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
alias	O
White	B-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
James	I-pers
at	O
the	B-place
Rummer	I-place
in	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Ring	O
.	O
Val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
35	O
l.	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
while	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosector	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
slipping	O
privately	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
lay	O
concealed	O
till	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
when	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
being	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
a	O
Chamber-door	O
where	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
alias	O
Downs	B-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Woman	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Prier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Mary	O
Pearse	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
for	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
missing	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Toy-shop	O
with	O
Sarah	O
Cook	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Cook	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mary	O
Pearse	O
being	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
where	O
the	O
Holland	O
lay	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
into	O
Custody	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Cook	O
having	O
other	O
Things	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
desiring	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
she	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
Holland	O
to	O
Mary	O
Pearse	O
,	O
who	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
and	O
conceal	O
it	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
Mistress	O
of	O
Dexterity	O
enough	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
unperceiv	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
alias	O
Benson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linsey-Woolsey	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
another	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
known	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
great	O
Straits	O
;	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Homeby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Turbot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
Horn	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
Hornesy	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
indeed	O
he	O
did	O
carry	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Turbot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Durrel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Alice	O
Turbot	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
new	O
Service	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
to	O
clean	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Spot	O
of	O
Grease	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Key	O
again	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Alice	O
Turbol	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
both	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
uppermost	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Interim	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Turbot	I-pers
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
called	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Shilling	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
lend	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
imploy	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
Business	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
probably	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
gotten	O
it	O
.	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Farendine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
Drover	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Billingey	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
Inn	I-place
in	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Nightime	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Towels	O
,	O
value	O
I	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Malden	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Burglary	O
,	O
swore	O
it	O
positively	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
affirming	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Billingey	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
try	O
'd	O
on	O
that	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
alias	O
Newman	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Dane	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Dehew	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Oldridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Yeoman	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	B-place
from	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
two	O
Fellows	O
with	O
Sticks	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stopped	O
his	O
Mouth	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
murder	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
Dehew	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
16	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
having	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Box	O
into	O
a	O
larger	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Return	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
little	O
Box	O
broke	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
behind	O
the	O
great	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Absence	O
of	O
Ann	O
Fox	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
immediately	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bell	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
Stepney	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
like	O
Soldiers	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
ring	O
,	O
suspected	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
following	O
them	O
,	O
got	O
them	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
were	O
12	O
Bells	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
hang	O
at	O
Gates	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
He	O
therefore	O
got	O
the	O
Bells	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
owned	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
swore	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
's	O
Bell	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bell	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Anstead	O
's	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Drasdel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Shoemaker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
defraud	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brind	I-pers
of	O
30	O
s.	O
by	O
pawning	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cup	O
washed	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Silver	O
one	O
,	O
avouching	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Sterling	O
.	O
Which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
positively	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
and	O
not	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
nay	O
,	O
even	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
for	O
Security	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proposal	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
alledg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Trade	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
kept	O
Country-Fairs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
short	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
again	O
when	O
Money	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Testimonials	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Practices	O
committed	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
North	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
unwrought	O
Looking-Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grumby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
One	O
Shilling	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
William	B-pers
North	I-pers
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
some	O
that	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
walking	O
by	O
her	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
push	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
pain	O
left	O
her	O
Glasses	O
should	O
be	O
broke	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
humour	O
him	O
did	O
taste	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
using	O
some	O
threatning	O
Expressions	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
the	O
Candle	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
comes	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pretended	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
17	O
s.	O
She	O
to	O
clear	O
her	O
Innocency	O
,	O
suffer	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
undress	O
'd	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
Halfpence	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
Neal	O
the	O
Landlord	O
imprudently	O
gave	O
to	O
North	O
;	O
but	O
North	O
would	O
then	O
have	O
the	O
Glasses	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Watchman	O
she	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
trick	O
the	O
Woman	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Glasses	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
very	O
reportable	O
Account	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
Neal	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Contrivance	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
new	O
Shoe	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Propriety	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jekil	I-pers
,	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Shoe-maker	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoe	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Shoe	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Gallons	O
of	O
English	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Cask	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Bolman	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Bolman	O
swore	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
bringing	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet-Ridinghood	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
.	O
Which	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Erasmus	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
last	O
Session	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
14	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Lignum	O
Vitae	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roop	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
398	O
Sticks	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
committing	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
The	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
fall	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
12	O
Sticks	O
wanting	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Boat	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Lignum	O
Vitae	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Boat	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Boat	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Wood	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Evasion	O
had	O
no	O
better	O
Effect	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
saluted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Countryman	O
;	O
Will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
?	O
And	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
promise	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	B-place
,	O
and	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
so	O
rude	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
scarce	O
set	O
down	O
e'er	O
she	O
intruded	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
accompany	O
'd	O
with	O
another	O
a	O
ragged	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
familiar	O
Sort	O
of	O
Creatures	O
,	O
who	O
however	O
were	O
all	O
so	O
mannerly	O
as	O
to	O
keep	O
their	O
Distances	O
in	O
such	O
several	O
Positions	O
as	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
;	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
presuming	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
remov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
down	O
at	O
Table	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Chair	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
attempting	O
great	O
Familiarities	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
so	O
resented	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thrust	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
perhaps	O
thinking	O
his	O
Passion	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
come	O
into	O
a	O
better	O
Temper	O
,	O
takes	O
the	O
same	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
another	O
Attempt	O
to	O
be	O
meddling	O
with	O
something	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
which	O
so	O
inrag	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
2	O
Pints	O
being	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
calls	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
the	O
Drawer	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
for	O
2	O
Pints	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
feeling	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
Score	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
thought	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Squire	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
)	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
setting	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
all	O
in	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
Search	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Drawer	O
not	O
liking	O
Confinement	O
,	O
opposed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
ragged	O
Woman	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pickt	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
ragged	O
Woman	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
rudely	O
intrude	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
ragged	O
Woman	O
neither	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
a	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
upon	O
Promise	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
apiece	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Settlement	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Overplus	O
on	O
the	O
Maidenhead	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Maidenhead	O
having	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
getting	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Huff	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ragged	O
Woman	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
detain	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
indeed	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
:	O
And	O
no	O
Watch	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Dozen	O
and	O
9	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
24	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
House	O
in	O
Forestreet	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
Conversation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
she	O
stole	O
his	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
left	O
with	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
single	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Cousin	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
better	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ashdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
seizing	O
him	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
his	O
Business	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
might	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Johnson	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winchurst	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Murder	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Abetting	O
in	O
that	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
Third	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Statue	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Kelson	O
,	O
Shaw	O
,	O
and	O
Calson	O
,	O
three	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
their	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
quarrelsom	O
Humour	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
Walking	O
Watch	O
?	O
They	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
We	O
are	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
,	O
You	O
'll	O
dance	O
all	O
Day	O
long	O
after	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
replying	O
,	O
We	O
ask	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
sooner	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
my	O
Sword	O
in	O
your	O
Guts	O
shan	O
Three	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
kill	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
you	O
for	O
that	O
Many	O
,	O
or	O
Words	O
to	O
that	O
Effect	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Winchurst	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
would	O
be	O
too	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
They	O
thinking	O
them	O
bent	O
upon	O
Mischief	O
,	O
(	O
having	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
for	O
such	O
Enterprizes	O
)	O
to	O
avoid	O
a	O
Fray	O
turned	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
Colson	O
's	O
Court	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
the	O
Horseshoe-Tavern	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
a	O
Chair	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
persuaded	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Watchman	O
light	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Watchman	O
lighted	O
him	O
along	O
.	O
They	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Holford	B-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
leaning	O
their	O
Heads	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
presently	O
Mr.	O
Winchurst	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
also	O
Mr.Bardet	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
jostled	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Woman	O
very	O
rudely	O
,	O
Winchurst	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
very	O
bawdy	O
obscene	O
Language	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
made	O
no	O
other	O
Return	O
,	O
but	O
Fie	O
!	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Why	O
are	O
you	O
so	O
uncivil	O
?	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
affront	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
?	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
Language	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
Prevocation	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Winchurst	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Draw	O
,	O
Burder	O
,	O
draw	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Burdet	O
,	O
draw	O
,	O
urging	O
him	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Burdet	O
not	O
drawing	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
two	O
Offers	O
to	O
draw	O
Mr.Burdet	O
's	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
Burdet	O
having	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Hilt	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
permit	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
drew	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
presenting	O
the	O
Point	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
toward	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
who	O
feeing	O
Burdet	O
's	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
also	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
his	O
present	O
unhappy	O
Condition	O
would	O
permit	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
Burdet	O
retreated	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
back	O
,	O
flourishing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
advanced	O
with	O
great	O
Fury	O
,	O
running	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
thrust	O
him	O
quite	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
bore	O
him	O
down	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
receiving	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Chin	O
by	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Horseshoe-Tavern	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
thither	O
with	O
one	O
Mary	O
Lewis	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
had	O
Three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Coach	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
provided	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
ready	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
going	O
away	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
Reckoning	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
his	O
Mistress	O
perceiving	O
that	O
the	O
Captain	O
going	O
out	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Chair	O
that	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
immediately	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
least	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
some	O
loss	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
with	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
stept	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
askt	O
the	O
Chairmen	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
about	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
the	O
Captain	O
home	O
:	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
ply	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
did	O
them	O
follow	O
immediately	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
carried	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
they	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
near	O
them	O
they	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
Mr.Burdet	O
run	O
violently	O
upon	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
bearing	O
him	O
down	O
backwards	O
and	O
falling	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
about	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Breast	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
but	O
carrying	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
soon	O
found	O
where	O
't	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
come	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
first	O
being	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
Chairmen	O
and	O
himself	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
as	O
Mary	O
Lewis	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
who	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
their	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
who	O
corroborated	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Depositions	O
in	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
material	O
Circumstances	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Johnson	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
when	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
having	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
Winchurst	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Alley	O
was	O
narrow	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
they	O
might	O
jostle	O
one	O
another	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
so	O
designedly	O
:	O
He	O
likewise	O
insulted	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
Sword	O
nor	O
Stick	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
the	O
Mischief	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Sieze	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
Sieze	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Watch	O
acknowledged	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
so	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
Beginner	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
most	O
violent	O
Promoter	O
of	O
this	O
Disaster	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
Plea	O
of	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
answer	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Bury	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
,	O
That	O
those	O
Persons	O
who	O
went	O
upon	O
such	O
Adventures	O
,	O
first	O
to	O
pick	O
Quarrels	O
with	O
peaceable	O
Persons	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
unknown	O
to	O
them	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
kill	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
Malice	O
against	O
all	O
Mankind	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
indeed	O
had	O
so	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Barbarity	O
and	O
Inhumanity	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boreman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Will	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Headberth	I-pers
,	O
value	O
35	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Royal	O
Ann	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thornhil	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Russel-street	I-place
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
own	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
to	O
boot	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Evidences	O
confirm	O
'd	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
the	O
Effects	O
of	O
Liquor	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Haslum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Dane	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
he	O
hung	O
the	O
Mare	O
's	O
Bridle	O
upon	O
a	O
Post	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
Sale	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
suspecting	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Matter	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
Circumstances	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
render	O
'd	O
it	O
improbable	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Copper	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
sending	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flanel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Pinner	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Harling	B-pers
Dowdswell	I-pers
:	O
But	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
alias	O
Newman	B-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Dehew	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Oldridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Richard	O
Yeoman	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whithead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
2	O
Keys	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
an	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Young	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Young	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wollen	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
afterwards	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Trunk	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hulks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
her	O
late	O
Majesty	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Ganum	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hains	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
robbing	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
on	O
the	O
Penthouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hammer	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
fastening	O
the	O
Doors	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Part	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
600	O
l.	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	O
Hains	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1713	O
.	O
Michael	O
Ganum	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
Lead	O
by	O
small	O
Parcels	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
and	O
share	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
Ganum	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Criminal	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
many	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dumbleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Stamp	O
for	O
stamping	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
an	O
Impression	O
with	O
that	O
Stamp	O
upon	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
contrary	O
to	O
two	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
12th	O
Years	O
of	O
her	O
late	O
Majesty	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
Counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
use	O
or	O
have	O
any	O
such	O
Counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
30	O
s.	O
six	O
Diaper	O
Clouts	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
Periwigs	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwellinghouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
Meers	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
Room	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforementioned	O
were	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
Money	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
without	O
their	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
by	O
direct	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wanting	O
Money	O
which	O
he	O
owed	O
her	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
bid	O
her	O
pawn	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
redeem	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
13	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
their	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Weeks	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
helpful	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
their	O
sight	O
been	O
very	O
liberal	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
not	O
only	O
was	O
born	O
of	O
very	O
wealthy	O
Parentage	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
fallen	O
to	O
decay	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
industrious	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Bread	O
in	O
an	O
honest	O
Calling	O
.	O
Many	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Neighbours	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
indifferent	O
a	O
Character	O
on	O
several	O
accounts	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
as	O
having	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
Religion	O
from	O
a	O
Protestant	O
to	O
a	O
Papist	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
again	O
from	O
a	O
Papist	O
to	O
a	O
Protestant	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Things	O
had	O
been	O
pawned	O
and	O
redeemed	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Aversion	O
to	O
Pawning	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Beads	O
and	O
Crucifix	O
were	O
now	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
It	O
looking	O
like	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Broadbent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joanna	B-pers
Sisson	I-pers
a	O
Pocket	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
off	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Shop-keeper	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
commit	O
the	O
like	O
Fact	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
commit	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Cloth	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Tenter	O
Racks	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1714	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Cloth	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Truss	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Chapman	O
and	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
for	O
15	O
s.	O
but	O
Sam	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
.	O
Chapman	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
depending	O
intirely	O
upon	O
Truss	O
's	O
single	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whithead	I-pers
,	O
Walgrave	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
300	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gargrave	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Shutters	O
were	O
cut	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Young	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Sarah	O
Flower	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
how	O
they	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
Callico	O
;	O
that	O
attempting	O
to	O
strike	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
their	O
Tinder	O
was	O
damp	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
catch	O
Fire	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
light	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
leaving	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
lighted	O
the	O
Tinder	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
a	O
Candle	O
:	O
They	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
13	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Sarah	O
Flower	O
for	O
35	O
l.	O
but	O
received	O
but	O
33	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
all	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whitehead	O
and	O
Freer	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Flower	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Baynam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Gaynum	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bray	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
Boynum	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
Bray	O
,	O
and	O
Bray	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Kettle	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Wash-house	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
Michael	O
Gaynum	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
some	O
Mony	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
willingly	O
get	O
some	O
against	O
christmas	O
:	O
And	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Kettle	O
,	O
one	O
Chapman	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
for	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
Of	O
this	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Diana	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.Sepulchre	I-place
's	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
suppose	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
knowing	O
where	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
24	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nonothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
Excuse	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Higs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
out	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
returning	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
her	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
carried	O
off	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
trifling	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
Three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
John	O
Young	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
10	O
Yards	O
off	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaak	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Dollam	I-pers
alias	O
Franklin	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Night	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
very	O
early	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
empty	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Pot	O
down	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Woman	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
Pot	O
,	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
for	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
that	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
Winchelsea	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Trader	O
in	O
that	O
Mystery	O
of	O
Iniquity	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
imposed	O
upon	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
power	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
Mont	O
.	O
The	O
Fraud	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peter	I-place
ad	I-place
Vincula	I-place
in	O
the	O
Tower	B-place
Liberty	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
outward	O
Shutter	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
was	O
bored	O
full	O
of	O
Holes	O
with	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
about	O
5	O
Inches	O
Square	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sculk	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seizing	O
him	O
found	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
and	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
broken	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Ashdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
16	O
Silk	O
Hankerchiefs	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Window-Shutter	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
John	O
Day	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
Shutter	O
with	O
2	O
Chissels	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Asbdon	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold'em	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Ashdon	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
so	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Tittle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Marybone	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taswell	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
stuff	O
Ridinghood	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
stoln	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
6	O
d.a	O
Table-Cloth	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
returning	O
home	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
not	O
wet	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Ayry	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moon	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
two	O
Damask	O
Sattin	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
two	O
Damask	O
Sattin	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
other	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
four	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
House	O
being	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
having	O
each	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
forced	O
their	O
way	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
bound	O
her	O
Hands	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
gagg	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
only	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
before	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Servant-Maid	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
House	O
was	O
indeed	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
had	O
her	O
Mouth	O
stop	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
swore	O
as	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Robbers	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Men	O
whose	O
Persons	O
were	O
remarkable	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
so	O
much	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
she	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
good	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
especially	O
they	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
any	O
Disguise	O
upon	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
apprehended	O
till	O
12	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
were	O
near	O
Neighbours	O
and	O
Tradesmen	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
so	O
many	O
reputable	O
Persons	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
looked	O
with	O
so	O
ill	O
an	O
Aspect	O
of	O
being	O
Malicious	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
only	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
their	O
Request	O
had	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
granted	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followith	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
19.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Homeby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Teoman	I-pers
alias	O
Newman	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Asbdon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Colsen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Farendine	I-pers
,	O
Johnson	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winchurst	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Haslam	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baynam	I-pers
,	O
Walgrave	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tittle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Higs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Broadbent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
whose	O
Judgement	O
was	O
respited	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
9.	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
alias	O
White	O
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Erasmus	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
4.	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drasdel	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Shoemaker	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Boreman	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humpbreys	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Mary	O
Freeman	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
:	O
Mary	O
Pearse	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Higs	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Higs	O
only	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stock	O
Market	O
.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Self-Examinant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
earnest	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Daily	O
Self-Examination	O
;	O
with	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Directions	O
and	O
Ejaculations	O
for	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
and	O
Happy	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
l.	O
or	O
two	O
Guineas	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Devont	O
Christian	O
's	O
Preparative	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
Erasmus	O
,	O
now	O
render	O
'd	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Sick	O
and	O
Dying	O
Persons	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
Funerals	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
Guineas	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Both	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Waren	I-pers
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
Rector	O
of	O
Charlton	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School-Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succioct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
4th	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Capeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
;	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
Use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
30	O
Copper-Plates	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Protestant	O
Union	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
main	O
Principles	O
of	O
Religion	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
,	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
Articles	O
and	O
Homilies	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Lovers	O
of	O
Curiom	O
Inventions	O
,	O
THAT	O
there	O
is	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Art	O
in	O
this	O
Nature	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
invented	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Wonderful	O
ASTRONOMICAL	O
and	O
MUSICAL	O
CLOCK	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
surprisingly	O
entertains	O
the	O
Company	O
with	O
so	O
many	O
various	O
Curiosities	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
most	O
ingenious	O
declare	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
infinitely	O
beyond	O
what	O
any	O
can	O
expect	O
:	O
It	O
shewing	O
the	O
Motion	O
of	O
the	O
Heavens	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Perfection	O
,	O
imitates	O
the	O
melodious	O
Singing	O
of	O
Birds	O
of	O
Several	O
Kinds	O
,	O
and	O
performs	O
on	O
the	O
Organ	O
,	O
Flute	O
and	O
Flageolet	O
;	O
the	O
performance	O
being	O
so	O
curious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Particulars	O
so	O
many	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
too	O
tedious	O
to	O
mention	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
in	O
Charlos	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
strand	O
near	O
Hungerford-Market	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Moving	O
Skeleton	O
is	O
shewn	O
.	O
)	O
N.B	O
.	O
Attendance	O
is	O
given	O
from	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
shewn	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
Christopher	B-pers
Pinchbeek	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
dwelling	O
is	O
at	O
Smithfield-Bars	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occansioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
lustturus	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Watch-Makers	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
Ladies	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
Lovers	O
of	O
Curiosities	O
.	O
THE	O
MOVING	O
SKELETON	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Skeleton	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
performs	O
such	O
strange	O
and	O
wonderful	O
Actions	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
can	O
Credit	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
already	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
has	O
given	O
a	O
general	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
less	O
surprising	O
to	O
the	O
Spectators	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
Inserted	O
its	O
several	O
Performances	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
)	O
1	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Case	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
skeleton	O
stands	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
immediately	O
flies	O
open	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Curtain	O
which	O
hangs	O
before	O
it	O
gently	O
draws	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
which	O
presents	O
to	O
your	O
View	O
,	O
a	O
Humane	O
skeleton	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Hour-Glass	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dart	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
raises	O
that	O
Hand	O
with	O
the	O
Hour-Glass	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
a	O
few	O
sands	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
those	O
are	O
spent	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
He	O
raises	O
the	O
other	O
Hand	O
with	O
the	O
Dart	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
Three	O
Offers	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
stricking	O
at	O
a	O
Person	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
opens	O
his	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Groans	O
3	O
times	O
most	O
surprisingly	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
again	O
with	O
his	O
Jaw	O
,	O
strikes	O
the	O
Hour	O
past	O
on	O
a	O
Bell	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
He	O
lets	O
down	O
his	O
Hand	O
with	O
the	O
Hour-Glass	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
He	O
lets	O
down	O
his	O
Hand	O
with	O
the	O
Dart	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
A	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
he	O
lights	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
He	O
blows	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
and	O
smoaks	O
his	O
Pipe	O
as	O
naturally	O
as	O
any	O
living	O
Person	O
can	O
do	O
,	O
till	O
being	O
gently	O
mov	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
opens	O
his	O
Jaw	O
for	O
the	O
Pipe	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
Curtain	O
then	O
falls	O
down	O
into	O
its	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
is	O
over	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
First	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Left-Hand	O
in	O
Charles-Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
strand	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Wonderful	O
Machine	O
the	O
Astronomical	O
and	O
Musical	O
Clock	O
is	O
shewn	O
.	O
At	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
Red	O
Ball	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Craners	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
incomparable	O
Wash	O
to	O
beautifie	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
far	O
exceeds	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
extant	O
,	O
as	O
abundance	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Quality	O
have	O
found	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
It	O
takes	O
out	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Wrinkles	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Redness	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Sun-born	O
,	O
Yellowness	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Mercurial	O
poisonous	O
Washes	O
:	O
It	O
also	O
plumps	O
and	O
softens	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
as	O
smooth	O
and	O
tender	O
as	O
a	O
sucking	O
Child	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
Young	O
it	O
always	O
keeps	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
it	O
makes	O
appear	O
Fair	O
and	O
Young	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
nothing	O
of	O
Paint	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
doth	O
any	O
Person	O
know	O
the	O
Secret	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
from	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
Ponatums	O
,	O
White-pots	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
compared	O
with	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Powder	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
them	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Snow	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Secret	O
to	O
prevent	O
Hair	O
from	O
falling	O
,	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
grow	O
wherever	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
.	O
She	O
alters	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
delicate	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
Brown	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
.	O
She	O
shapes	O
the	O
Eye-brows	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
them	O
beautiful	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
delicate	O
paste	O
to	O
whiten	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Red	O
Pomatum	O
to	O
colour	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
prevents	O
their	O
chopping	O
in	O
Winter	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
insallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Toothach	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Remov	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
PHILLIPS	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchras	O
Back	O
Gate	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spar	O
Streer	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
1717	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
