TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Fryday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
11th	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
1717-8	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWEN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
,	O
and	O
Baron	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
with	O
Several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hambden	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Axtell	I-pers
James	B-pers
Leadbeater	I-pers
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sussex	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
George	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltby	I-pers
Isaiah	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bell-mettal	O
Pot	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lartham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
deposed	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
,	O
inquired	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
raking	O
into	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
Cynders	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
embroidred	O
Housings	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
embroider	O
'd	O
Holster	O
Laps	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Captain	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
at	O
lighting	O
from	O
Horse	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Mans	O
Horse	O
and	O
his	O
,	O
being	O
troublesome	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
the	O
said	O
Furniture	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
by	O
accident	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
a	O
Smiths	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Family	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Ferrers	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
fellow	O
made	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
's	O
Gentleman	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Pistol	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
lik	O
'd	O
it	O
mightily	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
Money	O
to	O
;	O
his	O
varying	O
his	O
Story	O
made	O
much	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
that	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
Lord	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
and	O
well	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
him	O
Service	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Batlis	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
and	O
bought	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Remnant	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
them	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Riding-hood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
perhaps	O
fall	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
;	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
90	O
Yards	O
of	O
Russia	O
Linnen	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bailis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Linnen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
should	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
cut	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cross	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
this	O
Story	O
being	O
too	O
improbable	O
to	O
be	O
beliv	O
'd	O
against	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
val	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
standing	O
over	O
against	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Boy	O
drop	O
'em	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
the	O
privately	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shammy	O
Gloves	O
val.3	O
l.12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bunton	I-pers
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
hid	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
others	O
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
offering	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
Goods	O
he	O
took	O
home	O
to	O
work	O
upon	O
.	O
and	O
those	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sale	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
served	O
Funerals	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Circumtances	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
this	O
Excuse	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
take	O
to	O
wife	O
Alice	B-pers
Redge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
did	O
also	O
take	O
to	O
wife	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Yarnly	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
were	O
fully	O
proved	O
and	O
the	O
Wives	O
both	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hamlet	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ward	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Hamlet	I-pers
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
married	O
again	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
James	O
Hamlet	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
some	O
time	O
absent	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
Edward	O
Ward	O
used	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
Courtship	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
desirous	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
Marriage	O
private	O
.	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
pass	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Freedom	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
which	O
Jest	O
she	O
carried	O
on	O
till	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
earnest	O
.	O
The	O
Marriages	O
were	O
both	O
proved	O
.	O
She	O
alledg	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
Hamlet	O
had	O
another	O
Wife	O
at	O
Plymouth	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Steps	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Desk	O
and	O
Shop-book	O
val.3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
William	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Desk	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
a	O
Man	O
promised	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
drink	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
val.6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tune	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
pardoned	O
by	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
val.4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Wigg	O
powder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
took	O
the	O
Wigg	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Pin	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wine	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
38	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Cloak	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cloak	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Hugh	B-pers
Melone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
comes	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
claims	O
Acquaintance	O
and	O
Kindred	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Cloak	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
drank	O
two	O
Glasses	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
none	O
;	O
and	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
neither	O
liked	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
not	O
their	O
Kindred	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
demanded	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
Glasses	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
paying	O
,	O
She	O
calling	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
putting	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
the	O
ugliest	O
Air	O
imaginable	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
Pox-hunters	O
here	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
tore	O
his	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Cloak	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
Three	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
strange	O
Woman	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
Wine	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
Brandy	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
only	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
any	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mackperson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Redford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	O
Wise	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Wise	O
was	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
stirring	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
bring	O
out	O
Goods	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
where	O
Elizabeth	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
and	O
Mary	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Hogs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hogs	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Drover	O
,	O
and	O
driving	O
about	O
60	O
Hogs	O
from	O
Rumford	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
him	O
that	O
Service	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
yet	O
interceded	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Swaby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Morgan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
,	O
he	O
put	O
off	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
seen	O
hanging	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
one	O
Edw	B-pers
Barkham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
also	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
sell	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Man	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	I-pers
alias	O
Toby	B-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lumbard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
52	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Potmore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
opening	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
himself	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Holes	O
;	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
.10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Chickley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Thatcht-House	B-place
in	O
Ave	B-place
Mary	I-place
Lane	I-place
,4	O
Persons	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
run	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
force	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
flung	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
near	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
and	O
Note	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
That	O
Chickley	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Scout	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
a	O
Watch	O
)	O
whereupon	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Thatcht	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Chickley	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
deposed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
the	O
Note	O
for	O
9	O
l.	O
to	O
one	O
Platt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
to	O
one	O
Harding	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
inveighed	O
against	O
Obadiah	O
Leman	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
several	O
more	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
of	O
his	O
Wigg	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
missing	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
dropped	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bargeham	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Ninn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
Seven	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Likewise	O
they	O
indicted	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
Carmen	O
,	O
were	O
driving	O
their	O
Carts	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Load	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Robert	O
Ninn	O
,	O
being	O
first	O
Cart	O
,	O
Bargeham	O
to	O
intercept	O
him	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Cart	O
short	O
to	O
Stop	O
Ninn	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
run	O
the	O
Cart	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
squeezed	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
Ninn	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
;	O
but	O
Bargeham	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
of	O
him	O
of	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
passing	O
along	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
scraping	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thinking	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
Women	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
uncapable	O
and	O
he	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
falling	O
both	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
rest	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
being	O
over-power	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
Assistance	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
a	O
Women	O
about	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
just	O
got	O
into	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Women	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Companion	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
that	O
Guinea	O
to	O
flog	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
Companion	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
quarter	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
near	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
quilts	O
,1	O
Rug,5	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
St	O
,	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
there	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Nights	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
giving	O
them	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
longer	O
Entertainment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
To	O
whom	O
after	O
several	O
improbable	O
pretences	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
acquainting	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
3	O
Beds	O
stripped	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
into	O
Southwark	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
though	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Gorman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
fellow	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
apprehension	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
retun	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
probably	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
alias	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
Apostles	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
Widdow	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
among	O
whom	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbouring	O
Gentlemans	O
Servant	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
Company	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pot	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
talking	O
of	O
Horses	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Broad	O
Way	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
5	O
good	O
Horses	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
to	O
hire	O
,	O
and	O
proffer	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Journey	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
designing	O
to	O
take	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
again	O
about	O
2	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
in	O
taking	O
in	O
Coals	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pass	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
her	O
Drink	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
not	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
Silver	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pot	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
enquiring	O
for	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
emptied	O
the	O
Drink	O
into	O
the	O
Chamberpot	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Daughter	O
seeing	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
a	O
Wigg	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
also	O
cast	O
this	O
present	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Larner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
and	O
Cutlerry	O
Ware	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
leading	O
her	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
Corn	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
perceived	O
the	O
Person	O
and	O
3	O
others	O
loitering	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
doging	O
her	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
that	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
and	O
coming	O
over	O
against	O
White-Chappel	B-place
Church	I-place
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
steps	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
pretends	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
Ilford	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Inn-yard	O
,	O
she	O
leaving	O
her	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
cut	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
used	O
the	O
Newgate	O
Plea	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
pretence	O
would	O
not	O
avail	O
against	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Heifers	O
value	O
7	O
l.10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Teton	I-pers
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Beast	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
taking	O
earnest	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
not	O
paid	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Buyer	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
tol	O
'd	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
helping	O
a	O
Drover	O
to	O
drive	O
some	O
Beasts	O
,	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
some	O
Grounds	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
driving	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Heifers	O
perchance	O
might	O
come	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
discovered	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
up	O
till	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
such	O
trifling	O
excuses	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
40	O
pieces	O
in	O
similitude	O
of	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
similitude	O
of	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Offenders	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
constantly	O
Coining	O
.	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Warrant	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Sunderland	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
then	O
make	O
a	O
show	O
of	O
discovering	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
committed	O
into	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Messenger	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
retaken	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
strongest	O
Grounds	O
for	O
presumption	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
even	O
in	O
the	O
Interval	O
,	O
in	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
retaken	O
;	O
There	O
were	O
27	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Faulkener	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
buy	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
of	O
Abigal	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
,	O
before	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
used	O
to	O
coyn	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
:	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Crown-Court	B-place
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
did	O
coyn	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
that	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
every	O
Night	O
with	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
19	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
coyn	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Moulds	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
fling	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
discovery	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
make	O
new	O
ones	O
every	O
time	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Mathoon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
9	O
Months	O
ago	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
this	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
Newstead	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
himself	O
and	O
therefore	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
several	O
Pounds	O
of	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hands	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
now	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
a	O
Fig	O
for	O
any	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wootton	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
putting	O
off	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Culpepper	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Messenger	O
,	O
to	O
whose	O
Custody	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
as	O
much	O
Time	O
out	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
within	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
then	O
confined	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
)	O
he	O
would	O
stock	O
the	O
Nation	O
with	O
bad	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
more	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
Crowns	O
,	O
but	O
Half-Guineas	O
and	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
apprehended	O
him	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
had	O
27	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
enquiring	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
discovered	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
coining	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
a	O
Blanket	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
broke	O
the	O
Moulds	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
intirely	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
apprehended	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
in	O
Holborn	O
in	O
Gaming	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
27	O
Shillings	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Messenger	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
not	O
one	O
Farthing	O
of	O
Money	O
She	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
27	O
Shillings	O
to	O
hold	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
buy	O
a	O
Bun	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Interim	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Information	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
hard	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
had	O
plied	O
him	O
with	O
Drink	O
and	O
Geneva	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
Names	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
of	O
necessity	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
injuring	O
innocent	O
People	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
at	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
concerned	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
about	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
innocent	O
Persons	O
.	O
But	O
all	O
these	O
Allegations	O
of	O
his	O
were	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Persons	O
on	O
whom	O
he	O
fixed	O
the	O
vile	O
Aspersions	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
Persons	O
of	O
such	O
Credit	O
on	O
whom	O
they	O
could	O
rely	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
bore	O
but	O
little	O
Weight	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
of	O
his	O
Demeanour	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
bespoke	O
him	O
a	O
hardned	O
and	O
incorrigible	O
Villain	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
making	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
,	O
William	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
preventing	O
the	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
1697	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
receive	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Money	O
at	O
a	O
lesser	O
Rate	O
and	O
less	O
value	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
coined	O
and	O
did	O
import	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Faulkener	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	B-place
in	O
Clare-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
the	O
common	O
Resort	O
of	O
the	O
Utterers	O
of	O
this	O
bad	O
Money	O
:	O
That	O
Abigail	O
Newstead	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
out	O
to	O
those	O
Customers	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Blanch	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
twice	O
per	O
Week	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
seen	O
Newstead	O
give	O
unit	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Back-Room	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
her	O
take	O
this	O
Money	O
of	O
Newstead	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
give	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
since	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kimberly	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
buy	O
connterfeit	O
Money	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Michael	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Seager	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
condemned	O
lately	O
at	O
Kingston	O
Assizes	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Abigail	O
Newstead	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
last	O
April	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
remember	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
per	O
Piece	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kimberly	I-pers
being	O
examined	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
as	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
near	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
some	O
Credit	O
and	O
Reputation	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
led	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
that	O
pernicions	O
Acquaintance	O
and	O
Practice	O
.	O
So	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
not	O
excepted	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Carlton	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
uttering	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sampson	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
selling	O
Sausages	O
,	O
Puddings	O
&	O
c.	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
bought	O
something	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
offering	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
shewed	O
it	O
the	O
Baker	O
;	O
who	O
seeing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
nought	O
,	O
questioned	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
eat	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
a	O
good	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
seeming	O
to	O
recollect	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
pay	O
without	O
changing	O
,	O
catches	O
up	O
the	O
Shilling	O
,	O
then	O
pretends	O
she	O
ca	O
n't	O
and	O
lays	O
down	O
the	O
bad	O
One	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
acted	O
after	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
in	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
discovering	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
found	O
Three	O
Half-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
before	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
dogged	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
played	O
the	O
same	O
Game	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dispute	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
hid	O
themselves	O
backwards	O
in	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
found	O
the	O
one	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
Lap	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
offence	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Faulkener	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
Abigal	O
Newstead,30	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
at	O
2	O
d	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
-	O
Parsons	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
buy	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
for	O
20	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
false	O
Money	O
at	O
Kingstone	O
Assizes	O
,	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
ill-affected	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
seduce	O
Persons	O
from	O
their	O
Allegiance	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
did	O
say	O
King	O
George	O
was	O
an	O
Usurper	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
owed	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
all	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
they	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
about	O
publick	O
Affairs	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spake	O
very	O
flightingly	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Title	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
replied	O
,	O
You	O
Clergymen	O
pray	O
for	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
indeed	O
the	O
Expression	O
,	O
Ye	O
shall	O
pray	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
King	O
George	O
is	O
an	O
Usurper	O
,	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Tull	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
having	O
complained	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owed	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
cost	O
him	O
a	O
Farthing	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Newington	O
,	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Biddle	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
notice	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Biddle	O
's	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Expressious	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
Pretender	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
was	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Bastard	O
,	O
then	O
King	O
George	O
was	O
an	O
Usurper	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
persisted	O
in	O
such	O
Talk	O
it	O
might	O
perchance	O
lead	O
him	O
into	O
ill	O
Conveniencies	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
say	O
so	O
as	O
long	O
he	O
breathed	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
perhaps	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
breath	O
long	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
his	O
Business	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
Biddle	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
then	O
parted	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Biddle	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
laid	O
him	O
down	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
tore	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Biddle	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
tearing	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
rearing	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Biddle	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
not	O
going	O
,	O
but	O
keeping	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
meeting	O
accidentally	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Castle-Inn	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
In	O
some	O
Discourse	O
he	O
remembered	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Words	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
the	O
Pretender	O
,	O
so	O
called	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Bastard	O
,	O
both	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
and	O
King	O
George	O
were	O
Usurpers	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
being	O
apprehended	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
only	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
tearing	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
composed	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
Prosecute	O
him	O
upon	O
those	O
Expressions	O
but	O
they	O
declining	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
But	O
Sir	O
John	O
considering	O
afterwards	O
that	O
such	O
Expressions	O
were	O
of	O
ill	O
Consequence	O
to	O
be	O
tolerated	O
,	O
sends	O
for	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
binds	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
recriminated	O
upon	O
Biddle	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
enquiring	O
of	O
him	O
what	O
News	O
:	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
All	O
you	O
Jacobite	O
Rogues	O
are	O
spoiled	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bastard	O
the	O
Pretender	O
was	O
fled	O
beyond	O
the	O
Alps	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
if	O
the	O
Pretender	O
was	O
a	O
Bastard	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
King	O
George	O
was	O
an	O
Usurper	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
Commitment	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fryer	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
before	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Biddle	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tull	O
,	O
had	O
declined	O
prosecuting	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
these	O
Expressions	O
,	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
should	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
oblige	O
them	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
As	O
to	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
answered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fryer	O
's	O
hearing	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
)	O
that	O
their	O
Opinion	O
did	O
differ	O
from	O
his	O
in	O
that	O
Matter	O
:	O
for	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
tolerating	O
Persons	O
to	O
talk	O
after	O
that	O
seditious	O
manner	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
very	O
pernicious	O
Consequence	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Title	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
did	O
not	O
depend	O
upon	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
being	O
a	O
Bastard	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
and	O
legal	O
Title	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Pretender	O
was	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
Persons	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
another	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
which	O
indeed	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
.	O
One	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
pray	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
)	O
another	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
drink	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Health	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
had	O
little	O
avail	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
the	O
Fact	O
plain	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigail	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
forging	O
and	O
coining	O
of	O
40	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
base	O
Metal	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
and	O
Similitude	O
of	O
Half	O
Crown	O
;	O
and	O
40	O
other	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
of	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
the	O
destructive	O
and	O
pernicious	O
Consequences	O
of	O
such	O
Practices	O
and	O
these	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
and	O
prevent	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Sunderland	O
having	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
an	O
Information	O
laid	O
before	O
him	O
against	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Persons	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
an	O
Order	O
or	O
Warrant	O
to	O
Captain	O
Mills	O
High-Constable	O
of	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
Diligence	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
coined	O
Money	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
coined	O
at	O
one	O
Time	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Room	O
in	O
Tyburn	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
coined	O
about	O
20	O
l.	O
That	O
they	O
used	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Clare-Market	B-place
,	O
one	O
-	O
Parson	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
others	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
selling	O
the	O
Shillings	O
at	O
two	O
Pence	O
per	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
half	O
Crowns	O
for	O
five	O
Pence	O
per	O
Piece	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kimberly	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Black	O
Jack	O
,	O
in	O
Diet	O
street	O
near	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
there	O
Coyn	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
particularly	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Plaister	O
of	O
Pallace	O
,	O
and	O
mixing	O
it	O
with	O
Water	O
made	O
it	O
like	O
Paste	O
;	O
then	O
made	O
it	O
into	O
two	O
square	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
a	O
Mould	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
Gutter	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
a	O
Shilling	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
tied	O
the	O
two	O
Parts	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
String	O
;	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Pewterers	O
to	O
fetch	O
Tin	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
and	O
melted	O
it	O
,	O
poured	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Mold	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
laying	O
the	O
coyned	O
Money	O
as	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mould	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Hearth	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
she	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
coyned	O
15	O
s.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissers	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
jagged	O
pieces	O
round	O
the	O
Edge	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
filed	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
File	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
graining	O
,	O
then	O
boiled	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Water	O
and	O
Ashes	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
little	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
scoured	O
it	O
with	O
Sand	O
and	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
of	O
all	O
took	O
her	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
rubbed	O
the	O
Money	O
thereon	O
to	O
dull	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
dirting	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
)	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kimberly	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Lad	O
of	O
about	O
16	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coyning	O
in	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
pour	O
the	O
Mettal	O
into	O
a	O
Mould	O
,	O
like	O
what	O
Boys	O
use	O
to	O
cast	O
Chuckers	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
Room	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Mother	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
their	O
Room	O
one	O
Morning	O
to	O
light	O
some	O
Small-coal	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
lying	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
over	O
the	O
Fire	O
boiling	O
in	O
Water	O
and	O
Ashes	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
taking	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
such	O
ill	O
and	O
dangerous	O
Practices	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
very	O
light	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
venture	O
her	O
life	O
to	O
serve	O
her	O
Friend	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Mackoon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
had	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
of	O
her,20	O
half	O
Crowns	O
at	O
one	O
Time	O
at	O
5	O
d.	O
per	O
Piece	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Jack	O
a	O
Dandy	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
privately	O
in	O
Faulkner	O
's	O
Company	O
this	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
ever	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Kimberley	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
urged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Evidences	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
falsly	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
Life	O
for	O
the	O
Lucre	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
hearing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howlet	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Kimberly	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Merit	I-pers
,	O
Blanch	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Milback	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
uttering	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coffoy	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gascoyn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Hats	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
High-gate	B-place
Stage-Coach	I-place
.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
coming	B-place
from	I-place
Hamstead	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Little	O
Fish	O
,	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pecks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Calves	O
Skins	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
dressed	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Court	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Frolick	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
influence	O
them	O
to	O
think	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hitchin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Parlour	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Sash	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Van	I-pers
Hannum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Dryton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
riding	O
Hood	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashew	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
mending	O
Work	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Peerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
lost	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dunkhall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merrifield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
The	O
Property	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Maid	O
being	O
sent	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
turn	O
round	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Casebrook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Aney	I-pers
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
both	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Carpenter	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
set	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
gives	O
a	O
Porter	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
Drink	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
laid	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
rather	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
or	O
Frolick	O
,	O
than	O
a	O
down-right	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Sheep	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
coming	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
hired	O
to	O
drive	O
by	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
Sewett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
receiving	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
certainly	O
what	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatcht	O
2	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
bid	O
her	O
swallow	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
slip	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
so	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
confirm	O
his	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Stephen	O
de	O
la	O
Force	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Melehizelleck	B-pers
Gosset	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
l.10	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Glass	O
window	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Abthorp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
at	O
the	O
Crown-Tavern	B-place
in	O
Katharine-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
shown	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
sitting	O
down	O
with	O
that	O
Assurance	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Fire	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fire	O
above	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
so	O
familiar	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Mutton	O
Drops	O
,	O
(	O
alias	O
Chops	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
of	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
himself	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
Friend	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Gold	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
searching	O
her	O
they	O
found	O
Guineas	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
Besides	O
1	O
she	O
took	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
more	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
Stocking	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Friend	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
perceived	O
her	O
to	O
place	O
something	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
as	O
she	O
walked	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
places	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
drink	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
till	O
by	O
their	O
Urgency	O
,	O
and	O
pushing	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
giving	O
her	O
inducing	O
Language	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
one	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
attempted	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
permit	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
bring	O
some	O
Oil	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Feathers	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Pewter-Dish	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
penniworth	O
of	O
Whipcord	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
either	O
flog	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
Flogging	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
them	O
that	O
Day	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
received	O
7	O
l.19	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
for	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Forks	O
.	O
A	O
Person	O
deposed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
Day	O
paid	O
him	O
that	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Margaret	B-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Rut	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
after	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
as	O
of	O
a	O
Women	O
in	O
Labour	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
nail	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
Hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
this	O
Noise	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
Spoil	O
all	O
;	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
presently	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
receive	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Cloth	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Child	O
cry	O
twice	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
toward	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Rut	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
blow	O
her	O
Match	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
the	O
Child	O
aside	O
,	O
all	O
would	O
be	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Overseers	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
desiring	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
neglected	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
Ann	O
Douglass	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Pot	O
,	O
something	O
larger	O
than	O
a	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
large	O
hole	O
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Poll	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
bulging	O
up	O
and	O
appearing	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
hole	O
,	O
the	O
Face	O
being	O
downwards	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
enquiring	O
of	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
she	O
stept	O
hastily	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
shuts	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
fastning	O
three	O
Doors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
5	O
Midwives	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
their	O
Opinion	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
alledg	O
'd	O
we	O
was	O
a	O
marry	O
'd	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
if	O
true	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
support	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Powers	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Gaming-House	O
in	O
Convent-Garden	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
won	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Pounds	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
lost	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
desired	O
Powers	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
he	O
promising	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Bradshaw	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Dr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Treasury	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	B-place
in	O
the	O
Pallmall	B-place
to	O
Dine	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
Dinner	O
they	O
proposed	O
playing	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
the	O
Box-keepers	O
at	O
the	O
Gaming	O
Houses	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
paid	O
him	O
his	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
still	O
good	O
Fortune	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
won	O
more	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
choaked	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
3	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Bradshaw	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
corroborated	O
Mr.	O
Power	O
's	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
meeting	O
at	O
the	O
Gaming-House	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
propose	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Meeting	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Guinea	O
he	O
borrowed	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
hoping	O
to	O
engage	O
him	O
to	O
play	O
;	O
that	O
thinking	O
themselves	O
not	O
a	O
Match	O
for	O
Mr	O
.	O
Powers	O
,	O
they	O
proposed	O
one	O
Dr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
who	O
consented	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
not	O
Money	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Share	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Cranborn	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
for	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Treasury	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Powers	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
to	O
Dinner	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Dispute	O
arising	O
about	O
a	O
Bet	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
high	O
Word	O
grew	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
fight	O
him	O
who	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Powers	O
,	O
who	O
flung	O
his	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
Wright	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
following	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
almost	O
throttled	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
got	O
him	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Howell	O
's	O
Gaming-House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
(	O
on	O
Bradshaw	O
's	O
Request	O
)	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
next	O
Morning	O
Bradshaw	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
go	O
pay	O
the	O
Guinea	O
to	O
Powers	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
excused	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
Business	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
ask	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
any	O
;	O
that	O
Bradshaw	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
one	O
Dr.	O
Wright	O
would	O
meet	O
him	O
.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
in	O
some	O
Business	O
of	O
Concern	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
promise	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
not	O
Money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Wright	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
in	O
Cranborn	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
Money	O
at	O
an	O
easy	O
Rate	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
for	O
6	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Wright	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Treasury	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
Powers	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
his	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
Dinner	O
Bradshaw	O
and	O
Wright	O
promoted	O
Play	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Box	O
and	O
Dice	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
all	O
Play	O
;	O
that	O
Powers	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
Guinea	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
insisted	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
promise	O
that	O
Bradshaw	O
and	O
Wright	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
paid	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
playing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bet	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
which	O
he	O
won	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
Wright	O
and	O
Bradshaw	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
serving	O
him	O
so	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
provoked	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Powers	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
be	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
cursing	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Rogue	O
,	O
Villain	O
and	O
Rascal	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
fight	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
likewise	O
run	O
his	O
Fist	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
down	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
rise	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
3	O
Guineas	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
malicious	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Warrant	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
obtain	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
End	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
Bread	O
and	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
abundance	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
11.	O
Ann	B-pers
Harrup	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Chickley	I-pers
,	O
Abigail	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
alias	O
Newstaff	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Adsey	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
4.	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hamlet	O
,	O
alias	O
Ward	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bargeham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
Sentences	O
was	O
Respited	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Steps	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Larner	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mackperson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Gorman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	O
de	O
la	O
Force	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dunkhall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Dryton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Van	I-pers
Hannum	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hitchin	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Compassion	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
largness	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
and	O
Poverty	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
laid	O
no	O
greater	O
Penalty	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Newstaff	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Adsey	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
Acquaint	O
the	O
Curious	O
.	O
THAT	O
the	O
New	O
Astronomical	O
and	O
Musical	O
Clock	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Art	O
never	O
yet	O
parallel	O
'd	O
;	O
its	O
Performances	O
so	O
curious	O
,	O
its	O
Harmony	O
so	O
Delightful	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
Variety	O
of	O
Parts	O
so	O
surprising	O
,	O
as	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
conceiv	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
but	O
those	O
that	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
Is	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Grocers	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Globe	O
and	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlbourough	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
that	O
show	O
'd	O
at	O
Stocks-Market	O
is	O
Disposed	O
of	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
this	O
for	O
exceeding	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
made	O
by	O
Christopher	B-pers
Pinchbeck	I-pers
.	O
There	O
is	O
lately	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
Search	O
after	O
Religion	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
many	O
Modern	O
Pretenders	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Offer	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Perusal	O
of	O
all	O
who	O
are	O
dancing	O
to	O
the	O
Pipes	O
of	O
those	O
false	O
Prophets	O
and	O
Teachers	O
Christians	O
are	O
warn	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
heed	O
of	O
.	O
Like	O
diligent	O
Bee	O
,	O
From	O
every	O
Tree	O
,	O
To	O
the	O
Hungry	O
my	O
Honey	O
I	O
'll	O
bring	O
,	O
But	O
for	O
Truth	O
's	O
hidden	O
Foes	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pluck	O
off	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Their	O
Shame	O
I	O
'll	O
disclose	O
,	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
smart	O
or	O
die	O
for't	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
leave	O
'	O
em	O
my	O
Sting	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Address	O
and	O
Petition	O
to	O
King	O
Jesus	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Keimer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
listed	O
Soldier	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
peaceable	O
Subject	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
.	O
The	O
uncommon	O
Methods	O
of	O
late	O
taken	O
to	O
suppress	O
and	O
decry	O
this	O
Piece	O
,	O
obliges	O
the	O
Author	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
uncommon	O
publication	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Authors	O
Preface	O
to	O
his	O
Christian	O
Reader	O
,	O
he	O
recommends	O
his	O
Book	O
to	O
the	O
Sheep	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
who	O
regard	O
not	O
the	O
Voice	O
of	O
the	O
Hireling	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gives	O
a	O
faithful	O
Narration	O
of	O
Facts	O
of	O
his	O
searching	O
for	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
Salvation	O
as	O
appointed	O
by	O
Christ	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
many	O
Hireling	O
Priests	O
and	O
Soul-Brokers	O
,	O
near	O
40	O
of	O
whose	O
Names	O
he	O
has	O
inserted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
sorts	O
in	O
this	O
Land	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Cheats	O
,	O
false	O
Teachers	O
,	O
and	O
Soul-destroyers	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Account	O
he	O
gives	O
of	O
the	O
Separating	O
Hirelings	O
he	O
concludes	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Priests	O
who	O
many	O
Miles	O
would	O
run	O
ye	O
,	O
Who	O
'd	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
trip	O
,	O
and	O
leap	O
like	O
Hare	O
or	O
Coney	O
,	O
Not	O
for	O
your	O
Souls	O
sake	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
get	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
And	O
after	O
he	O
has	O
related	O
a	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
few	O
of	O
the	O
Pranks	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Prophets	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
he	O
adds	O
,	O
All	O
these	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
such	O
like	O
Soul	O
Brokers	O
,	O
I	O
've	O
heard	O
,	O
or	O
read	O
their	O
Works	O
who	O
're	O
Hell-fire-Stoakers	O
,	O
And	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
Devil	O
,	O
as	O
Glass-house	O
Men	O
use	O
Poakers	O
.	O
This	O
Book	O
is	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
Court	O
on	O
Ludgatehill	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Reader	O
,	O
but	O
read	O
my	O
Book	O
with	O
serious	O
Mind	O
,	O
Thou'lt	O
own	O
it	O
Truth	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
thou'rt	O
blind	O
.	O
THe	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Press-Yard	O
:	O
or	O
a	O
Brief	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
and	O
Occurrences	O
that	O
are	O
put	O
in	O
Practice	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
that	O
Antient	O
Repository	O
of	O
Living	O
Bodies	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Goal	O
NEWGATE	O
in	O
London	O
:	O
Wherein	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Descriptions	O
and	O
Characters	O
never	O
before	O
made	O
Publick	O
,	O
are	O
inserted,1	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Unfortunate	O
Florimel	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
State	O
Prisoners	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
Confin	O
'd	O
there	O
upwards	O
of	O
Twenty	O
one	O
Years.2	O
.	O
An	O
Interview	O
with	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
:	O
The	O
Manner	O
of	O
his	O
turning	O
Confessor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Method	O
used	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Office.3	O
.	O
The	O
Manner	O
of	O
the	O
Reception	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
from	O
Preston	O
there.4	O
.	O
Young	O
Mr.	O
Botairs	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Action	O
between	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Troops	O
and	O
the	O
Rebels	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
true	O
Causes	O
of	O
their	O
Surrender.5	O
.	O
The	O
Escape	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Forster	O
;	O
the	O
Demeanour	O
of	O
Col.	O
Oxburge	B-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Gascoigne	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Paul	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
after	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
with	O
several	O
Original	O
Letters	O
from	O
them	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Crimes	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
suffer	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Dukes	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
,	O
Argyle	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Likewise	O
one	O
from	O
Sir	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
B	O
-	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gascoigne	O
.6	O
.	O
The	O
Usuage	O
and	O
Sickness	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Francia	O
the	O
Jew	O
:	O
The	O
Escapes	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Radcliff	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Budden	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
George	O
Flint	O
:	O
The	O
Releasement	O
of	O
the	O
author	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Original	O
Letters	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Noble	O
English	O
Peer	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Hardships	O
the	O
Preston	O
Prisoners	O
labour	O
'd	O
under	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
Moor	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard,1718	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
Printer	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
affected	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rhuematism	O
:	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
entirely	O
lost	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
rendered	O
uncapable	O
of	O
working	O
for	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
last	O
past	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
advice	O
of	O
several	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
Prescriptions	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
:	O
As	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
of	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
who	O
prescribed	O
me	O
Medicines	O
.	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
but	O
received	O
no	O
Benefit	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
over	O
all	O
hopes	O
of	O
being	O
cur	O
'd	O
.	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
that	O
inestemable	O
Secret	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
,	O
given	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Celebrated	O
Anodyn	O
NECKLACE	O
,	O
for	O
Children	O
's	O
TEETH	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
only	O
but	O
twice	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Hand	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
's	O
strength	O
again	O
:	O
and	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
not	O
above	O
Twice	O
Times	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
restored	O
to	O
the	O
perfect	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
am	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Amazement	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
and	O
Acquaintence	O
.	O
Any	O
Person	O
may	O
be	O
farther	O
fully	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
of	O
this	O
my	O
miraculous	O
Cure	O
at	O
the	O
Places	O
following	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
attest	O
the	O
Truth	O
thereof	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hubbock	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Falcon	O
St.	O
Southwark	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Last	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mr	O
Grimstead	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Fortune	O
of	O
War	O
in	O
Pye	O
Corner	O
near	O
West	O
Smithfield	O
who	O
with	O
abundance	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
Spectators	O
of	O
my	O
Condition	O
.	O
Witness	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
J.	O
Wolfe	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewoman	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
the	O
whole	O
(	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
.	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queens-Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Watch-makers	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
who	O
performed	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
.	O
