TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
10th,11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
,	O
of	O
September,1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	O
LEWEN	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
Fortesene	O
Aland	O
,	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
Several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lisse	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
James	B-pers
Baldrey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Farts	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Muniton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ravener	I-pers
John	B-pers
Histon	I-pers
William	B-pers
Aley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
William	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Daniel	B-pers
Duitty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
K	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
500	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
shop	O
broken	O
upon	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Holland	O
in	O
Kings	O
street-Holbourn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lanner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Clifson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
and	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Wash-House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Copper	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Beck	O
near	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Almshouses	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mother	O
Huffle	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Valentine	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Kingsbury	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mother	O
Huffle	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Wisdal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
and	O
stealing	O
15	O
Hats	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mother	O
Huffle	O
for	O
9	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hayward	O
deposed	O
his	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pasture	O
at	O
Denham	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
Country	O
to	O
New-Market	O
about	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
business	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Horse	O
which	O
cost	O
him	O
6	O
l.	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
but	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
here	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
availing	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Frock	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Grablart	I-pers
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
and	O
pretend	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
a	O
Cake	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Frock	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
frock	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
alias	O
Dyton	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
small	O
Linnen	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Several	O
Persons	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
she	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Linnen	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Pewter	O
plates	O
and	O
2	O
Dishes	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Plates	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
he	O
stop	O
them	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Plates	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stollen	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
producing	O
that	O
Friend	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stowbum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Queenhithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
small	O
Tacks	O
value	O
6	O
s.8	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Watch-movements	O
2	O
l.7	O
s.	O
the	O
,	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
suspected	O
him	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Trunk	O
found	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
given	O
35	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
intice	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
expected	O
,	O
threatned	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
blow	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
this	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
Halter	O
and	O
Headstall	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walmsley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Withey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Servants	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
Kerseys	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
bargin	O
'd	O
for	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
20	O
l.	O
which	O
being	O
sent	O
in	O
.	O
on	O
condition	O
of	O
Paying	O
ready	O
Money	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
shuffled	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
pretending	O
his	O
Partner	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
Cash	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
but	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
mov	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
premises	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
added	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stole	O
the	O
Cane	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Joy	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Violet	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
and	O
5	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ranbrook	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Cornhill	B-place
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Pocket	O
fall	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Frances	B-pers
Baldock	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
value	O
1.s.12	O
Guinea	O
's	O
2	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
receive	O
Money	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
Street	O
,	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Wood-street	B-place
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flung	O
from	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Fact	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ar	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
of	O
Dukes	B-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Israel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
work	O
there	O
as	O
a	O
Plastever	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Velvet	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pasnter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
alias	O
Butler	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
.	O
Chain	O
,	O
Hook	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat,6	O
l.	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Head-dress	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
lac	O
'd	O
Ruffels	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
80	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Mascal	I-pers
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
at	O
the	O
4	B-place
swans	I-place
in	O
Bishops-gate-street	B-place
to	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
by	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
observed	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
suspicious	O
Felloys	O
lurking	O
about	O
,	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
farther	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
round	O
the	O
Coach	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Masehall	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Pye	O
near	O
Bishops-gate	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bett	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
wet	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
;	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
John	O
Hill	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Lads	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
and	O
play	O
at	O
Skettles	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
perceiving	O
to	O
be	O
wet	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
John	O
Hill	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
allowing	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
plead	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Jane	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
nor	O
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
these	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
John	O
Hill	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Head-cloth	O
and	O
Valleince	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brightridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Sheet	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
only	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
necessity	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
and	O
return	O
it	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20s.5	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Amy	B-pers
Shorting	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
Coyning	O
20	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
similitude	O
of	O
Guineas,20	O
in	O
the	O
similitude	O
of	O
Crowns,20	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Kingston	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
Belt	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
suspecting	O
show	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bucknell	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
likewise	O
thinking	O
it	O
not	O
good	O
examined	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
willingly	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
piece	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
they	O
borrowed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
lighter	O
than	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
acquainted	O
Justice	O
Perry	O
with	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
examination	O
prevaricating	O
in	O
his	O
Answers	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bucknell	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Crucible	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
some	O
Metal	O
looking	O
something	O
like	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
several	O
Papers	O
of	O
several	O
sorts	O
of	O
Powders	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
then	O
enquiring	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
doing	O
satisfactorily	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
ingenuous	O
in	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
owning	O
that	O
one	O
Dampney	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
his	O
and	O
himself	O
had	O
Coin	O
'd	O
that	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
about	O
50	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
where	O
he	O
himself	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
Dampney	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
found	O
Flasks	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Materials	O
for	O
Covning	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
41	O
s.	O
in	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
Shillings	O
were	O
procured	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
only	O
alledging	O
that	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
was	O
coyn	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
blowing	O
the	O
Fire	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Holbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Husband	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
Stollen	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
and	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
May	I-pers
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
Dodd	O
ripp	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Sider	O
with	O
a	O
Chiffel	O
,	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
prevented	O
doing	O
any	O
more	O
damage	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
sold	O
the	O
Lace	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Bradley	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Ash	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
that	O
was	O
confronted	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dad	I-pers
with	O
Henry	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
stealing	O
60	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
8	O
l.6	O
yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
at	O
Salt	O
Peter	B-pers
Bank	I-pers
with	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Harvey	O
,	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
Southwark	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
met	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
together	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
a	O
Prey	O
,	O
and	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
Tools	O
,	O
he	O
objected	O
against	O
their	O
attempting	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Dad	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
should	O
get	O
Tools	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
gotten	O
Chiffels	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
wear	O
,	O
Dad	O
ripp	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Sashes	O
;	O
May	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Whale	O
and	O
Harvey	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
absconded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
them	O
for	O
them	O
9	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
foot	O
which	O
they	O
shared	O
among	O
them	O
at	O
36	O
s.	O
per	O
Man	O
,	O
spending	O
1	O
s.	O
per	O
piece	O
and	O
Richard	O
Pollard	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bignal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
2	O
Gowns	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Periwig	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gamble	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
Francis	O
Smith	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
quartered	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coach-Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
and	O
Psalm	O
Book	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
and	O
having	O
stollen	O
the	O
Goods	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Sneep-pens	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
the	O
Prayer-book	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Glasses	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Fretchurch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
Drinking	O
in	O
an	O
Ale	O
House	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
one	O
by	O
him	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pick	O
Pockets	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
it	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
feeling	O
found	O
his	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
so	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
transportation	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Head-Clothes	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
Felony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Silver	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Box	O
Combs	O
value	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Business	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
things	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
She	O
calling	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Hair	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
some	O
pieces	O
and	O
parts	O
of	O
Silk	O
Shoes	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
stollen	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
perceived	O
3	O
Men	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
boring	O
the	O
Shutter	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
de	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
,	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
belonging	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Goosetill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	B-place
House	I-place
at	O
Highgate	B-place
,	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
another	O
Man	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value.10	O
s.	O
a	O
Seat	O
Cloth	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
.	O
This	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Barnet	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Garments	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Katherines-Lane	I-place
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nevertheless	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Beyworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot,2	O
Saucepans	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Snuff-Pan	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
Guineas	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gumly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
9	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
value	O
4	O
l.2	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
application	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
enquiry	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
sell	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
wherein	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
another	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
apprehended	O
and	O
in	O
Newgate	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
for	O
his	O
Fees	O
,	O
coming	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Burton	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
very	O
good	O
Families	O
did	O
perswade	O
him	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
he	O
should	O
make	O
a	O
jump	O
at	O
once	O
i.e	O
.	O
to	O
rob	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
Masters	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
mer	O
to	O
beat	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
pieces	O
with	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
compass	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
advice	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
rope	O
,	O
afterwards	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Pantry	O
Window	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Burton	O
,	O
for	O
13	O
l.	O
However	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilky	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Sudbury	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Back	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
while	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
seeing	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Meal	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elisha	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
Landed	O
on	O
the	O
Wharf	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benedict	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bascomb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
after	O
wards	O
apprehended	O
be	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
bought	O
himself	O
Clothes	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
had	O
48	O
s.	O
of	O
it	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Machappin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Levingstone	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
Machappen	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Mackdonald	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lardon	I-pers
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Goodchild	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darnel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Saws	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Joyners	O
Tools	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
lost	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
from	O
Home	O
,	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Saws	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wise	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
was	O
his	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Floyd	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
since	O
Convicted	O
at	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Self	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
claim	O
to	O
the	O
Hen	O
as	O
hers	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
Felony	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bandown	I-pers
and	O
Stealing	O
Pewter	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Twist	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
to	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
him	O
self	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
positive	O
Proof	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mols	I-pers
alias	O
Chadwick	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
the	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Guineas,24	O
s.	O
in	O
Money,1	O
double	O
Guinea,2	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
of	O
Istleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Orway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stole	O
the	O
Spoon	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
2nd	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
also	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Spoon	O
;	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Katherine	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
alias	O
Horton	B-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
the	O
Marriages	O
were	O
both	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money,2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sedan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
calling	O
persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Spreggs	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Anderson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Marybone	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,2	O
old	O
Holsters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Vallentine	O
Judge	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Pistols	O
were	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stables	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Pistols	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lying	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
waked	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unbuckling	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Things	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Guineas	O
and	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphery	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
giving	O
any	O
notice	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Kingstreet	B-place
desiring	O
a	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Rhenish	O
and	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
the	O
Drawer	O
leave	O
the	O
Spoon	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
stir	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
leaving	O
3	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
this	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Rhenish	O
and	O
Sugar	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Spoon	O
leaving	O
3	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
following	O
him	O
overtook	O
him	O
and	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Spoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Glove	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
together	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
happened	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Gloves	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Futler	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lewis	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Stachey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Lodger	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
confess	O
'd	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
to	O
Guineas,1	O
Carolus	O
broad	O
piece.15	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
dying	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
had	O
left	O
this	O
money	O
by	O
Will	O
to	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Christ-Church	O
Hospital	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
possesion	O
by	O
the	O
Governours	O
of	O
the	O
Hospital	O
and	O
there	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
arose	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bed	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
told	O
her	O
bedfellow	O
the	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Garrets	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
Thieves	O
.	O
Being	O
taxed	O
with	O
a	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
let	O
in	O
one	O
John	O
Green	O
a	O
Porter	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
all	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Terrour	O
to	O
avoid	O
going	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
having	O
promised	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
would	O
confess	O
no	O
trouble	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Walnen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
did	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
necessitated	O
but	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
Gent	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Raper	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Comelly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
heard	O
his	O
Friend	O
was	O
killed	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Long	B-place
Acre	I-place
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
admitted	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
near	O
the	O
Chimney	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Side	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
enquiring	O
who	O
had	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
informed	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Ryan	O
,	O
he	O
thereupon	O
goes	O
to	O
Justice	O
Hillon	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
he	O
must	O
do	O
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
prefer	O
'd	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Ryan	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
his	O
Friend	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Daneer	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Ryan	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
House	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
enquiring	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
for	O
Dinner	O
and	O
being	O
answered	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
left	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
that	O
something	O
might	O
be	O
got	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Drinking	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
who	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answered	O
no	O
Body	O
he	O
knew	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
you	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
but	O
getting	O
up	O
again	O
be	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
you	O
Rascal	O
.	O
you	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
you	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Ryan	O
being	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
be	O
cosy	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
drunk	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sober	O
why	O
should	O
we	O
quarrel	O
?	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pushed	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
naked	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
jumping	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chairman	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
his	O
sword	O
lay	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
following	O
him	O
and	O
pushing	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
there	O
leaning	O
backward	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Thrust	O
defending	O
himself	O
with	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Stair	O
head	O
and	O
Cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
who	O
staid	O
for	O
him	O
below	O
stairs	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
said	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
's	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
waited	O
there	O
for	O
one	O
Captain	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
hearing	O
the	O
Bustle	O
above	O
Stairs	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Mahan	I-pers
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
waiting	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mischief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Mahone	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tully	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
Drinking	O
with	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Captain	O
Dove	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Drank	O
some	O
Wine	O
,	O
Captain	O
Dove	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Captain	O
Dove	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
therefore	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
supposing	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
presently	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Landlady	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
about	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
left	O
unpaid	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Landlady	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
pretty	O
close	O
together	O
and	O
striking	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leaning	O
backwards	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
calling	O
him	O
Rascal	O
,	O
Villain	O
,	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
strike	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
parried	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
stagger	O
'd	O
back	O
but	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
violently	O
again	O
.	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
closed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
disarmed	O
him	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
both	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
saying	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
let	O
go	O
your	O
Sword	O
I	O
Scorn	O
to	O
hurt	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
disengaged	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
grow	O
very	O
pale	O
,	O
staggered	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
supposed	O
that	O
in	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
ran	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
falling	O
Mr.	O
Ryan	O
made	O
off	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
finding	O
him	O
wounded	O
ran	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
cam	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
enquiring	O
for	O
one	O
Captain	O
Cockeril	B-pers
and	O
asking	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
him	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
Cooks	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Rack	O
,	O
Lemons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
into	O
Punch	O
had	O
eat	O
his	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Time	O
while	O
he	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
Friend	O
remembered	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Play	O
of	O
Hamlin	O
and	O
was	O
reading	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
in	O
great	O
fury	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
.	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
Rascal	O
you	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
be	O
then	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
pray	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
be	O
easie	O
why	O
should	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
fall	O
out	O
and	O
injure	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
drunk	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sober	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
perssisted	O
in	O
swearing	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
him	O
opprobrious	O
Names	O
,	O
pushing	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
starting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
put	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Arm	O
extending	O
,	O
retreating	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
laid	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Sword	O
and	O
Cane	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
following	O
him	O
and	O
pushing	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
bend	O
backward	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
thrust	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
Hand	O
as	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
them	O
parrying	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
with	O
his	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
nothing	O
would	O
pacify	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Life	O
in	O
imminent	O
Danger	O
,	O
he	O
slept	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
off	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
defended	O
himself	O
therewith	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
rather	O
then	O
hurry	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
till	O
help	O
came	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
stagger	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
violently	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
and	O
closed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
disarmed	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
both	O
their	O
Swords	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mabone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
his	O
Wound	O
in	O
running	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
for	O
be	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
Wounded	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
fall	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
disengaged	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
closed	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
did	O
endento	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
then	O
so	O
directed	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
rather	O
have	O
stabbed	O
himself	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
does	O
suppose	O
was	O
occasioned	O
either	O
by	O
the	O
pangs	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
as	O
a	O
stab	O
of	O
Revenge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
above	O
twice	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
occasionally	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Gentleman	O
when	O
sober	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
purely	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
peaceable	O
and	O
quiet	O
temper	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Diaper	O
,	O
value	O
80	O
l.	O
in	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Diaper	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Family	O
,	O
which	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
a	O
Parlour	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
his	O
Lady	O
being	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
thither	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
his	O
Lady	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
bring	O
up	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Diaper	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
her	O
backing	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
up	O
another	O
Box	O
:	O
his	O
Lady	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
right	O
Box	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
other	O
Box	O
was	O
empty	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
when	O
his	O
Lady	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
the	O
enquired	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Diaper	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
past	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
be	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
be	O
deny	O
'd	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
down	O
and	O
putting	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
and	O
making	O
Search	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
Box	O
from	O
thence	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
finding	O
the	O
Coachman	O
he	O
showed	O
him	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
and	O
left	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
having	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
Boxes	O
down	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
he	O
remembered	O
the	O
Number	O
but	O
mistook	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thinking	O
the	O
Box	O
that	O
Linnen	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
Box	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Clothes	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
get	O
another	O
Box	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
put	O
that	O
Box	O
and	O
the	O
Diaper	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
again	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
discovered	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
admitting	O
his	O
Plea	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
George	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket,14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Blood-Stone	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
an	O
Eagle-Stone	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
at	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
the	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
not	O
have	O
carried	O
her	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
pretending	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
Home	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Burying	O
at	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
insisting	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
then	O
Six	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
carry	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
carried	O
her	O
farther	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
afterwards	O
must	O
other	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
finding	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
return	O
it	O
with	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Pocket	O
at	O
the	O
Coach-door	O
,	O
having	O
let	O
down	O
a	O
Gentlewomen	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Rarl	O
of	O
Stafford	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Callimore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
by	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Mopstick	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
breast	O
,	O
Belly	O
and	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
portal	O
Bruises	O
and	O
Contusions,21st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
brother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
deposed	O
her	O
husband	O
then	O
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
put	O
by	O
the	O
Parish	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Nurse	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
barborously	O
tied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
being	O
sick	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
seeing	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
two	O
Day	O
before	O
it	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
July	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
beat	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
stamp	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
using	O
it	O
very	O
cruelly	O
;	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
lying	O
cross	O
a	O
Chair	O
with	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
feet	O
handing	O
down	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
blaming	O
her	O
for	O
letting	O
him	O
e	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
dying	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
die	O
:	O
He	O
blamed	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Barharicy	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
matter	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
lookt	O
into	O
its	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
beating	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
,	O
being	O
arraiged	O
the	O
same	O
Bar	O
for	O
starving	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Artillary	B-place
Ground	I-place
Spittle-fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
Catherine	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
,	O
kicking	O
,	O
and	O
bruising	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
toes	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
languished	O
and	O
languished	O
liv	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Francis	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Peticoat-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
out	O
Henry	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
who	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
in	O
the	O
Artillary	B-place
Ground	I-place
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
drinking	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
a	O
Scuffl	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
her	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pusht	O
and	O
kickt	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
mention	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pendal	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
to	O
her	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
whispering	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
ear	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
convenient	O
Room	O
above	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went-up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sitting	O
very	O
disconsolate	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
giving	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
her	O
out	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
getting	O
up	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
struck	O
her	O
several	O
Hour	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
kicked	O
her	O
full	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
violence	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
feared	O
he	O
would	O
kick	O
out	O
her	O
Brains	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
interposed	O
between	O
then	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
be	O
should	O
not	O
to	O
bear	O
,	O
kick	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
she	O
fell	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
will	O
you	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
aferwards	O
he	O
pulled	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Henry	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pendal	I-pers
should	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
mad	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
feared	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
murdered	O
the	O
Child	O
within	O
her	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Pendal	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
deposed	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
bring	O
there	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
scuffle	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
either	O
strike	O
beat	O
her	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
that	O
Ni	O
ght	O
after	O
the	O
falling	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
till	O
past	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
off	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
kicked	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Toe	O
of	O
his	O
Shoe	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
Deceased	O
of	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
forehead	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
she	O
her	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Signs	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
's	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
her	O
Labour	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
never	O
can	O
him	O
stroke	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
she	O
but	O
govern	O
her	O
Tongue	O
she	O
might	O
live	O
as	O
happy	O
as	O
any	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dress	O
'd	O
a	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
but	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
stripe	O
'd	O
and	O
wash	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
Head	O
to	O
foot	O
in	O
cold	O
Water	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
fresh	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
newly	O
wash	O
'd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
London	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
threw	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Quater	O
Pot	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
indeed	O
see	O
the	O
Prisner	O
first	O
at	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
all	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pendal	I-pers
said	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
one	O
that	O
served	O
then	O
with	O
Brandy	O
giving	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
lunch	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drank	O
so	O
freely	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
afterward	O
fell	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
all	O
past	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
there	O
drank	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
teach	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
All-fours	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
Carraways	O
,	O
Wormwood	O
,	O
Angelico	O
and	O
Anniseed	O
Water	O
)	O
which	O
she	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
let	O
down	O
he	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
cas	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Charecter	O
of	O
a	O
Peacerole	O
Quiet	O
Man	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Jame	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
and	O
Carnally	O
Knowing	O
Mary	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
8	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
the	O
Mother	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Child	O
ill	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
manner	O
unusual	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Nature	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
she	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
Money	O
was	O
offered	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Nature	O
in	O
her	O
Linnen	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
ailed	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Gravel	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Signs	O
on	O
her	O
Linnen	O
were	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Age	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
it	O
came	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
Penetration	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pollxen	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
the	O
Grandmother	O
brought	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
linnen	O
foul	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
part	O
very	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Opinion	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
examined	O
the	O
Parts	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
torn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
a	O
Probe	O
,	O
he	O
introduced	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Passage	O
had	O
been	O
widened	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
her	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
entred	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
what	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
:	O
One	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
examining	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
did	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
abased	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
by	O
some	O
Boy	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Mother	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Rogue	O
Pickers	O
;	O
that	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
whisper	O
'd	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Child	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Picket	O
that	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Running	O
upon	O
it	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
accused	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
falling	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mother	O
having	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
said	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
finger	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
being	O
young	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
her	O
Oath	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Ten	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Fact	O
been	O
Proved	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Rape	O
in	O
the	O
Eye	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Esan	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
173	O
pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
;	O
thereupon	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Esan	O
Vincent	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
stealing	O
1000	O
pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Katherine	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Green-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
carrying	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
Find	O
13	O
s.4	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bread	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
201.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Waggoner	O
deposed	O
his	O
Waggon	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloth	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pack	O
between	B-place
Hounslow	I-place
and	I-place
London	I-place
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Carrier	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Bohemis	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Waggon	O
going	O
on	O
before	O
,	O
Jack	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
cut	O
the	O
Pack	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
afterwards	O
proved	O
it	O
for	O
31	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
and	O
2	O
pound	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Waggoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
bargained	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Brentwood	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
a	O
Truss	O
of	O
Goods	O
sent	O
from	O
a	O
Shopkeeper	O
in	O
London	O
to	O
his	O
Chapman	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
pack	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
pack	O
was	O
opened	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
surpris	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
wanting	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
old	O
Rags	O
and	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
so	O
carefully	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Chapman	O
in	O
Town	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Jackson	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
cut	O
open	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Rags	O
and	O
old	O
Shoes	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
the	O
Vacancy	O
,	O
and	O
sow	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Rags	O
and	O
old	O
Shoes	O
were	O
preserv	O
'd	O
and	O
pr	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Carrier	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
Followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
or	O
death,13	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Violet	I-pers
alias	O
Filewood	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
;	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	O
Dod	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,42	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Quitty	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
,	O
Tabias	B-pers
Tawner	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Wisame	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Bulter	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
alias	O
Dyton	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stonum	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Withey	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Joy	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
alias	O
Butler	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Millbourn	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bignal	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Turpin	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilty	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
,	O
Benedict	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
James	B-pers
Wanrel	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Willam	O
Rutt	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,1	O
.	O
John	O
Horton	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
,	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
Joseph	O
Clement	O
Esau	O
Vincent	O
fined	O
a	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lately	O
Published	O
in	O
Two	O
Neat	O
Pocket	O
Volumes	O
,	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Tryals	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Session-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
Forty	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
for	O
Murthers	O
High	O
Way	O
Robbing	O
,	O
Pyracy	O
,	O
House-breaking	O
,	O
Foot-padding	O
,	O
Rapes	O
,	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
Bestiality	O
Polygamy	O
,	O
Fortune-stealing	O
,	O
Trepanning	O
,	O
Kidnapping	O
,	O
Shop-Lifting	O
Perjury	O
,	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
,	O
Exchequer-Bills	O
,	O
Bank-Notes	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
Originals	O
,	O
Books	O
of	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Papers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Paul	B-pers
Lorrain	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Wykes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
several	O
Ordinaries	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Even	O
from	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Printing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
Authentick	O
Narratives	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Philips	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Botherton	O
and	O
W.	O
Meadows	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
Price	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Two	O
Volumes	O
bound	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
against	O
York	O
.	O
Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
A	O
Banquet	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
:	O
Consisting	O
of	O
Nine	O
Tragi-Comical	O
Novels	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Treachorus	O
Friend	O
,	O
The	O
Jealous	O
Husbands	O
,	O
The	O
Friendly	O
Cheat	O
.	O
Jealousy	O
without	O
Cause	O
.	O
The	O
Cuckold	O
turn	O
'd	O
Confessor	O
.	O
The	O
Prodigal	O
Reclaim	O
'd	O
and	O
Virginity	O
Restor	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Unfortunate	O
Lovers	O
,	O
The	O
Cruel	O
Mother	O
.	O
The	O
Bacchanalians	O
.	O
Intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
several	O
Pleasant	O
and	O
Delightful	O
Tales	O
and	O
Stories	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Female	O
Policy	O
detected	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Arts	O
of	O
a	O
Designing	O
Women	O
laid	O
open	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Authur	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
and	O
Trip	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
Treating	O
I	O
of	O
their	O
Allurements	O
,	O
Inconstancy	O
,	O
Love	O
,	O
Revenge	O
,	O
Pride	O
and	O
Ingratitude	O
II	O
,	O
A	O
pleasant	O
and	O
profitable	O
Discourse	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
Married	O
Men	O
,	O
against	O
peevish	O
,	O
fretful	O
,	O
scolding	O
Wires	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
noble	O
examples	O
of	O
the	O
Mischiefs	O
and	O
Miseries	O
which	O
have	O
attended	O
their	O
lust	O
and	O
Pride	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
A	O
true	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Vertous	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Wife	O
indeed	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Poetical	O
Description	O
of	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
shortly	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Universal	O
Jester	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
house	O
contracted	O
an	O
Evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
Sworn	O
and	O
Experienced	O
Midwife	O
;	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Tin-Shop	O
near	O
Exetur	O
change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Cure	O
upon	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cares	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Parging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymisd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Duck-lane	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
true	O
spirit	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
.	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Ground-Ivy	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
Bottle	O
Likewise	O
,	O
a	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
effectual	O
for	O
that	O
Cure	O
of	O
any	O
yet	O
known	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
To	O
prevent	O
and	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
preserve	O
and	O
fasten	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
most	O
successful	O
Plaister	O
to	O
prevent	O
Miscarriages	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
help	O
'd	O
beyond	O
expectation	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
hope	O
of	O
Relief	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
,	O
Self-Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
fully	O
explicated	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self-	O
Abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Aurther	O
of	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
.	O
This	O
Book	O
is	O
given	O
Gratis	O
only	O
at	O
the	O
four	O
following	O
places	O
and	O
no	O
others	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
a	O
Milleners	O
Shop	O
right	O
against	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Taverns	O
by	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garway	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Gate	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Unicorn	O
on	O
St	O
:	O
Margaret's-Hill	O
,	O
Southmark	O
.	O
LONDON	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Back-Gate	O
in	O
Gilt-Spur-Street	O
next	O
Newgate	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane.1718	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
