TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powts	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Apppleby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Thurstfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Radley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hager	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coleby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheely	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smithies	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Childe	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
James	B-pers
Cringe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Flitch	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Bacon	O
and	O
150	O
Eggs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
Mason	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
rose	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
Hours	O
after	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Seeing	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
a	O
Shed	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
cleaning	O
the	O
Bacon	O
;	O
they	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
jumpt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
own	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spurgin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
Mary	O
Stiles	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Spurgin	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drying	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Stiles	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
Coals	O
to	O
dry	O
them	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Spurgin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
23	O
Coats	O
and	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
knockt	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
on	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Killison	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
by	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
42	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
toward	O
Fresh	B-place
Wharf	I-place
he	O
met	O
Dickson	O
with	O
an	O
Apron	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
fill	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
Killison	O
in	O
the	O
Gutter	O
on	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Apron	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
:	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hole	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Kilson	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
up	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Gutter	O
;	O
and	O
Dickson	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Waterside	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gatliff	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Richardson	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Buckles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
buying	O
any	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
which	O
Green	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
presently	O
mist	O
his	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
at	O
Milk-Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Buckles	O
was	O
dropt	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
near	O
Richardson	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
Milk-Street	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Buckles	O
dropt	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Crowd	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
Richardson	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
lay	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Richardson	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
handled	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
left	O
only	O
one	O
was	O
found	O
Richardson	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Green	O
at	O
the	O
eg	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
;	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
understood	O
the	O
Weight	O
better	O
than	O
himself	O
,	O
Green	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
Green	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Richardson	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Fathom	O
of	O
Tow-Line	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
aboard	O
the	O
Hoy	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
himself	O
discover	O
'd	O
would	O
have	O
thrown	O
it	O
overboar	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
hetcht	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
and	O
encangled	O
it	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Rods	O
from	O
the	O
Hoy	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
fathom	O
of	O
Cable	O
Rope	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
fathom	O
of	O
small	O
Rope	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Lime	O
Shop	O
heard	O
the	O
Hoy-Boy	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
Peter	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
accus	O
'd	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
Wilson	O
shoving	O
tho	O
Boat	O
to	O
the	O
Hoy	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
at	O
the	O
Hoy	O
stern	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
accused	O
each	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
:	O
themselves	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holloway	B-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
value	O
29s	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sayers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sayers	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
the	O
prisoners	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Shoplisters	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	O
Scott	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
Holloway	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Yard	O
wide	O
Tammy	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Holloway	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-rings	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisgner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
small	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
up	O
together	O
in	O
her	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
rather	O
give	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
than	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
those	O
in	O
Brass	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Ear-rings	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
a	O
Shirt,2	O
Cravats	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
riding	O
down	O
Snow-hill	B-place
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Church	O
porch	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Devis	I-pers
cut	O
the	O
Bags	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Horse	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
coming	O
up	O
Snow-hill	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Chymists	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
they	O
seiz	O
'd	O
them	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Bags	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Bags	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Bags	O
by	O
the	O
Church	O
porch	O
in	O
the	O
dry	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brunt	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
Sarah	O
Brunt	O
for	O
stealing	O
certain	O
Camblet	O
,	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
29	O
l.	O
from	O
Andrew	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brunt	I-pers
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
3	O
Months	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
some	O
Shagreen	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
warn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
be	O
mist	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Brunt	O
's	O
Custody	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Fer	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
passing	O
for	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
)	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
,	O
up	O
in	O
Apparel	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
parcels	O
;	O
Ferk	O
had	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Brunts	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
wherein	O
she	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
took	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
Fern	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
she	O
said	O
Goods	O
cheap	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
Ferm	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
Distinction	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brunt	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
15	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mays	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Stocks	B-place
Market	I-place
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Coach-men	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stoping	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
cry	O
out	O
Pick-pockets	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
think	O
of	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
seeling	O
for	O
it	O
he	O
mist	O
it	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Mob	O
run	O
.	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
loose	O
Customers	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
's	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
dicharg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Mays	O
bound	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
G	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
whose	O
Bosom	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
the	O
Wig	O
into	O
was	O
a	O
notorious	O
Pick-pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Essings	I-pers
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
3	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
8	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,2	O
Holland	O
Shirts,10	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Towels	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kingsbury	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Danger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Fryers	I-place
Precinct	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cadwalader	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
39	O
Guineas	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Lead	O
opened	O
from	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Hooks	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Yard	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Cadwolader	O
deposed	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
the	O
suspected	O
Thieves	O
were	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
so	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
bolted	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Closet	O
Broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
lost	O
between	O
40	O
and	O
50	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
wherein	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kingsbury	I-pers
who	O
had	O
been	O
their	O
Servant	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
help	O
'd	O
a	O
Boy	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
open	O
and	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
20	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Handful	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
taken	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
saying	O
here	O
's	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
I	O
bought	O
with	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
at	O
a	O
Dancing	O
School	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
which	O
she	O
made	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Danger	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailiff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
sheet	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
sheet	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hand-Saw,7	O
Planes	O
,	O
a	O
Jointer	O
,	O
3	O
Chissels	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
but	O
pleaded	O
in	O
excuse	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
Job	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
2	O
Days	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop-bulk	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
slip	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Bulk	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
hung	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
his	O
following	O
him	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
the	O
Witness	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephens	I-place
Coleman-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Flitch	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
he	O
was	O
tript	O
up	O
by	O
him	O
yet	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
Help	O
came	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
former	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Flitch	O
of	O
Bacon	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Bacon	O
lay	O
by	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Pistol	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Slug	O
,	O
Prim	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Cock	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Pistol	O
and	O
Slug	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Fellmonger	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Stepney	O
to	O
pay	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Pistol	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
safety	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
no	O
Mischief	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boy	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Backchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Glimpse	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
under	O
her	O
Clothes	O
suspected	O
her	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
her	O
drap	O
them	O
;	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
who	O
seeing	O
a	O
bustle	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Stockings	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
tamper	O
'd	O
with	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
bought	O
one	O
pair	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Credit	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
Lieutenant	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
Brandy	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
2	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Night	O
Cap	O
,	O
Napkin	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
Pale	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
whom	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
civil	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
and	O
talking	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
lye	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
out	O
of	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
readily	O
consented	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
set	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
hearing	O
a	O
rumbling	O
above	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
rose	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Sister	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Room	O
very	O
foul	O
and	O
nasty	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
drunk	O
over	O
Night	O
)	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Sheets	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Three	O
Days	O
after	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Sheets	O
.	O
The	O
Broker	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
2	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Higham	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
117	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blackbeard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
secure	O
at	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
his	O
Bar	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Turner	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
7	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
that	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
boring	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
Evidence	O
she	O
had	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
sufficient	O
;	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
by	O
Ester	O
Watson	O
's	O
Information	O
be	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
(	O
who	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
)	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
after	O
the	O
following	O
manner	O
they	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Bulk	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
pains	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
bent	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
had	O
room	O
to	O
unlock	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
took	O
down	O
2	O
Shutters	O
,	O
then	O
enter	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
present	O
and	O
assisted	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
Carrying	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
Design	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
clear	O
'd	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
the	O
Watchman	O
beating	O
his	O
Rounds	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
their	O
Booty	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
Esther	O
Watson	O
for	O
7	O
l.	O
dividing	O
it	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
34	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
Watson	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
Chissels	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
Piercer	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
shown	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
,	O
Watson	O
and	O
Cryer	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
old	O
Oftenders	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
Isaac	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Back	O
bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cadwallader	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Bedlam	I-place
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
with	O
Bread	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
being	O
there	O
a	O
washing	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Victuals	O
and	O
some	O
strong	O
Drink	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
Farthing	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
strong	O
Drink	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
's	O
and	O
there	O
have	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
because	O
she	O
always	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
hear	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
Washing	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Cadwalader	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
eat	O
such	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
welcom	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
reach	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
his	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
Wife	O
Bitch	O
and	O
Toad	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
Names	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Clarkenwell	O
Crew	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
work	O
for	O
her	O
Pride	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
go	O
like	O
a	O
Vagabond	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
gon	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
she	O
would	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
run	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Blood	O
runs	O
out	O
,	O
pray	O
come	O
and	O
Help	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Cadwalladar	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
wished	O
Man	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
you	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
your	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Wives	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
be	O
bang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Lowrd	O
Cadwallader	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
languishing	O
Condition	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
four	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
and	O
penetrated	O
the	O
Trunk	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4	O
th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
bought	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
after	O
them	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
along	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Woman	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
buy	O
Cheese	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cheese	O
and	O
her	O
Riding	O
hood	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
her	O
buying	O
of	O
Cheese	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
pretence	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
found	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
in	O
the	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
She	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wenham	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
buy	O
any	O
waste	O
Paper	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
near	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulling	O
out	O
some	O
Money	O
dropt	O
a	O
Half-peny	O
which	O
she	O
stoopt	O
for	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
mist	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
Chimney-piece	O
,	O
and	O
concluded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
take	O
it	O
while	O
she	O
stoopt	O
for	O
the	O
half-penny	O
,	O
she	O
hearing	O
the	O
Candle-sticks	O
ring	O
at	O
that	O
Juncture	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
throttle	O
her	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
her	O
Hood	O
off	O
her	O
Head	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
and	O
white	O
Cloak	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
plainly	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
two	O
Lamps	O
(	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
Door	O
)	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
liv	O
'd	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
fourteen	O
Months	O
ago	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
l.	O
I	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Note	O
under	O
her	O
Hand	O
(	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
Note	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
arrested	O
her	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Boom	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
arrested	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hoopt	O
Petticoat	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
had	O
been	O
reputed	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
called	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Domes	O
to	O
discredit	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
trouble	O
to	O
rout	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
every	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
denyed	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Meal	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Civil	O
industnious	O
Woman	O
and	O
made	O
Perriwig-Calls	O
for	O
her	O
Livelyhood	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
Barbers	O
and	O
Perriwig-makers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
House	O
of	O
good	O
Repute	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
affaulted	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
swear	O
against	O
her	O
and	O
so	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bold	O
audacious	O
Fellow	O
,	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Fist	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
called	O
him	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
enquir	O
'd	O
af	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
agreed	O
it	O
up	O
both	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Arnold	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Queenhith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
128	O
pound	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Soap	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
Boat	O
at	O
Queenhith	B-place
,	O
and	O
rowed	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
the	O
Waterman	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sterlings	O
at	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse-man	O
's	O
Coat	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Windsor-Row-Barge	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Snapes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
either	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictmen	O
's	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
32	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Isherwood	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
Sick	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
help	O
his	O
under	O
Ostler	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
giving	O
any	O
Notice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
inised	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Trunk	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Saying	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
came	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
told	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Discovery	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
begged	O
of'em	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confesed	O
it	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
now	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Purse	O
value	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
19	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
upon	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
satisfy	O
his	O
Curiosity	O
in	O
viewing	O
the	O
Publick	O
Buildings	O
&	O
c.	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gratified	O
his	O
Eye	O
with	O
that	O
fine	O
Structure	O
and	O
the	O
Effegies	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
and	O
Queens	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
returning	O
Home	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
who	O
looking	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
sure	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Country-man	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
Essex	O
,	O
near	O
Colchester	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Country-man	O
born	O
at	O
Colchester	O
,	O
and	O
named	O
several	O
Persons	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
so	O
near	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan-Tavern	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
shewn	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
their	O
Wine	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
having	O
beg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
for	O
disturbing	O
them	O
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
dropt	O
it	O
there	O
:	O
not	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
Consequence	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
nothing	O
of	O
value	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
soon	O
found	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bill	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Feet	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
glad	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
mightily	O
rejoyc	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
good	O
Luck	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
engag	O
'd	O
in	O
private	O
Business	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
joyn	O
Company	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Pint	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Country-man	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
together	O
and	O
talk	O
of	O
their	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
After	O
drinking	O
a	O
Glafs	O
or	O
two	O
about	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
shewed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Tricks	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
lay	O
Wagers	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
prompted	O
him	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
rougher	O
Language	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
40	O
s.	O
nor	O
could	O
not	O
command	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
provok	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Expressions	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
searching	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Walder	O
in	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
soon	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Walder	O
having	O
paid	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
viz	O
19	O
Guineas	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
all	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
refusing	O
to	O
play	O
or	O
lay	O
Wagers	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
snatch	O
his	O
Bag	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
pretending	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
finding	O
himself	O
thus	O
trickt	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
ABOIT	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stupp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
by	O
a	O
Drawer	O
for	O
the	O
Rockoning	O
;	O
the	O
Drawer	O
presently	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
bit	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
to	O
conceal	O
himself	O
among	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
use	O
that	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
return	O
it	O
and	O
accordingly	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
the	O
Bearer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
nor	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
procure	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
plainly	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Confederate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
went	O
like	O
a	O
Country-man	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
like	O
a	O
Quaker	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
was	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
7th	O
or	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
for	O
defrauding	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Barret	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburga	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fromantle	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Formautle	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
a	O
Constables	O
,	O
Staff	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
;	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
then	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
with	O
some	O
Common-Council-Men	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
also	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
come	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
gold	O
Chink	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
without	O
any	O
Headclothes	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
immediately	O
dec	O
lared	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
clear	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
was	O
carryed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knowing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
Gold	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Purse	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
A	O
Drawer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
for	O
Change	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
some	O
Company	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
her	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
Silver	O
enough	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
some	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
chang	O
'd	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Uprear	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mistress	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
turning	O
her	O
pocket	O
inside	O
outward	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Price	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Fromantle	O
dragg	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
rude	O
and	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Price	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
change	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
pull	O
out	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
knock	O
Mrs.	O
Fromantle	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
tear	O
her	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
An	O
Oyster	O
Woman	O
that	O
sat	O
hard	O
by	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
Mrs.	O
Fromantle	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Head-clothes	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
turn	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Andrew	O
Fromantle	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Tavein	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
with	O
some	O
Common-Council-Men	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
Fromantle	O
,	O
so	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
force	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
as	O
wou	O
'd	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
call	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ruddle	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
their	O
first	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
directly	O
up	O
Stairs	O
while	O
Mrs.	O
Framantle	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rooms	O
above	O
Stairs	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Common	O
Nightwalker	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
confest	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Cornill	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
that	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
down	O
Stair	O
's	O
held	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
continued	O
to	O
have	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
employed	O
in	O
holding	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
Alley	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
enough	O
Mrs.	O
Framantle	O
to	O
touch	O
her	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
Mrs	O
Fromantle	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
struck	O
or	O
abus	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
Mr.	O
Fromantle	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
assaulted	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
striking	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Sessions	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wingham	O
Mr.	O
Howel	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Somerset	O
severally	O
confirmed	O
what	O
was	O
before	O
sworn	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ruddle	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
was	O
Constable	O
last	O
Year	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
Fromantle	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
search	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barham	O
,	O
Church-Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
and	O
Common-Council	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
Mrs	O
Fromantle	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
light	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
that	O
she	O
threatned	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
other	O
Common-Council-Men	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
Disorderly	O
Persons	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
Complaints	O
against	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fromantle	O
had	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
nature	O
on	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
he	O
only	O
swore	O
the	O
Peace	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fromanstle	O
's	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Several	O
persons	O
of	O
Distinction	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
ordered	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
certain	O
Tea	O
,	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
seducing	O
a	O
Girl	O
he	O
kept	O
,	O
to	O
robb	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Hawkins	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Grocer	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Washerwoman	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
poor	O
Girl	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
keep	O
and	O
bring	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
advising	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
himself	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
ruin	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Girl	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
his	O
Tea	O
,	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Companions	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
treat	O
therewith	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tea	O
twice	O
at	O
her	O
desire	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cannister	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Room	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
carryed	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
also	O
induced	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Drawer	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
the	O
Box-Money	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
her	O
self	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
starch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
deposed	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
3	O
Candles	O
,	O
handfuls	O
of	O
Starch	O
and	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
produced	O
no	O
Evidence	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ramsdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Peacok	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Featherbed	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
23	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coverlead	O
,	O
a	O
Frying	O
Pan	O
and	O
a	O
Porridge-Pot	O
from	O
Randal	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Golden	B-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
her	O
them	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
well	O
formerly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-coat	O
,	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Jame	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ed	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk-Handkerchief	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
MarthaMoon	B-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
observing	O
Williams	O
lurk	O
about	O
her	O
Window	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Glass	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
pursued	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Williams	O
at	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
a	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Woodward	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
bloody	O
,	O
being	O
cut	O
by	O
the	O
Glass	O
he	O
broke	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
both	O
mark	O
'd	O
alike	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
with	O
a	O
Jerusalem	O
Mark	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
make	O
;	O
and	O
produced	O
his	O
Mark	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dillon	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Linnen	O
and	O
agreed	O
for	O
two	O
Shirts	O
at	O
16	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
Guineas	O
for	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
wanting	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Present	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
none	O
herself	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
any	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
stay	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
forc	O
'd	O
himself	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
telling	O
his	O
Money	O
over	O
mist	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
just	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
a	O
Good	O
Estate	O
should	O
indemnifie	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
search	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Ensign	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
handled	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ealing	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Scant	O
Tool	O
and	O
Scraper	O
,	O
from	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Price	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Town	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty/	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
and	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Oneal	I-pers
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Cellar	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
lighted	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
White	O
Lilly	O
Root	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
without	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Linnen	O
of	O
the	O
Line	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Cloak	O
of	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Both	O
Indictments	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
them	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
Riding-Hood	O
and	O
black	O
Hood	O
from	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Read	I-pers
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Six	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Fabruary	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
away	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4s	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Till	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
serv	O
'd	O
so	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
contest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10.	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Mullinor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2s	O
.	O
7d	O
.	O
Half-penny	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Second	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
Bake	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Drawer	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooly	I-pers
alias	O
Sewet	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold-Rings	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
look	O
the	O
Rings	O
of	O
his	O
finger	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Hopson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way-with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Mask	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
on	O
Ealing	B-place
Common	I-place
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
small	O
Gun	O
,	O
presented	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
without	O
his	O
Mask	O
as	O
he	O
rid	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
rode	O
from	O
it	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
him	O
again	O
with	O
his	O
Mask	O
off	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
rid	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
rid	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
immediately	O
persued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
rode	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
broad	O
piece	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
offering	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
they	O
swore	O
wrongfully	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
towards	O
Uxbridge	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
Two	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dowdwell	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
inciting	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
to	O
commit	O
a	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
the	O
23d	O
or	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
private	O
;	O
(	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
lookt	O
very	O
earnestly	O
at'em	O
,	O
perceiving	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
asking	O
their	O
Business	O
,	O
Dowdwell	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
to	O
find	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
thousand	O
Pound	O
;	O
nay	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
many	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
procure	O
stout	O
Men	O
to	O
perform	O
their	O
part	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
proposed	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Cook	O
in	O
Wormwood-Street	B-place
near	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
Cainchair	O
maker	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
an	O
ancient	O
Maiden	O
Gentlewoman	O
who	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
some	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
Boxes	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
out	O
Money	O
to	O
use	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
only	O
Opportunity	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
to	O
convey	O
in	O
some	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
and	O
conceal	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Saw-pit	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
Night	O
to	O
let	O
their	O
Companions	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
secure	O
two	O
sturdy	O
psenticos	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
refractory	O
,	O
and	O
Dowdwell	O
beg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
without	O
committing	O
Murder	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
possibly	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
replied	O
that	O
people	O
when	O
they	O
go	O
about	O
such	O
matters	O
must	O
defend	O
their	O
Lives	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
they	O
can	O
;	O
the	O
persons	O
being	O
thus	O
secured	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
easy	O
matter	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
underneath	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
fetch	O
more	O
;	O
the	O
Room	O
opposite	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
they	O
'd	O
find	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Drawers	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
without	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
must	O
take	O
a	O
particular	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
resolute	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
underneath	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lay	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
mighty	O
desirous	O
that	O
neither	O
the	O
Woman	O
nor	O
her	O
Child	O
should	O
be	O
Hurt	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
told	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
matter	O
as	O
before	O
recited	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Description	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
and	O
exact	O
;	O
that	O
Dowdwell	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
5	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
poor	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
her	O
self	O
without	O
giving	O
any	O
Notice	O
or	O
paying	O
Rent	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
confest	O
the	O
Matter	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
when	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Dowdwell	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Captain	O
's	O
Window	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
now	O
reduc	O
'd	O
,	O
Wright	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
places	O
where	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
Imprisonment	O
for	O
six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
John	O
Murry	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
alias	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
Barronet	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackneal	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
above	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
Mary	O
Mackneal	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
and	O
whipt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
them	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
Leg	O
over	O
his	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
Body	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
her	O
Face	O
being	O
towards	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
Lady	O
nor	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
Goal	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
she	O
spoke	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
:	O
That	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
second	O
attempt	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
staid	O
from	O
Wednesday	O
till	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
while	O
absent	O
from	O
her	O
Mother	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
deposed	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
shifted	O
her	O
self	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
washing	O
her	O
Child	O
's	O
Shift	O
on	O
Thursday	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
task	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
undertook	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
beyond	O
her	O
skill	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
advised	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
Inflamation	O
,	O
Running	O
and	O
Redness	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
and	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Laceration	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fitzgerald	O
strengthened	O
the	O
Mothers	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
Mr.	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
she	O
might	O
stay	O
there	O
two	O
Days	O
,	O
which	O
be	O
readily	O
,	O
provided	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
content	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
till	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
Monday	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
Mothers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
11	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
:	O
Elis	O
Watts	O
deposed	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
sight	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dress	O
'd	O
and	O
underss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Linnen	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
order	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
make	O
any	O
Complaint	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
merry	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
impudently	O
to	O
the	O
Poorman	O
,	O
let	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
into	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
who	O
laid	O
there	O
an	O
Hour	O
:	O
brought	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
spite	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Clothes	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
familier	O
,	O
he	O
kist	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
into	O
the	O
bed	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
John	O
Jones	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
deposed	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
behavio	O
ur	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
Saturday	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
betimes	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
for	O
whether	O
she	O
came	O
so	O
soon	O
from	O
South	O
work	O
she	O
said	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
pattern	O
(	O
or	O
clog	O
)	O
in	O
korl	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
Iquall	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
rs	O
heard	O
her	O
complaint	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shale	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
difference	O
between	O
the	O
Examination	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Examination	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bretland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
offering	O
20	O
Guineas	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Marsh	I-pers
not	O
to	O
appear	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
a	O
Cause	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
Court	O
of	O
Admiralty	O
against	O
Mr	O
.	O
Trot	O
,	O
for	O
burning	O
a	O
Ship	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Seas	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
insur	O
'd	O
400	O
l.	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
arresting	O
him	O
in	O
large	O
Actions	O
where	O
by	O
he	O
was	O
prevented	O
giving	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Argument	O
by	O
the	O
Counsel	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
could	O
not	O
(	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
proper	O
Evidence	O
)	O
maintain	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitchurch	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Salap	O
Attorney	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
like	O
wise	O
for	O
procuring	O
them	O
to	O
personate	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
to	O
swear	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
was	O
false	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
new	O
Tryal	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
.	O
Francis	O
Wright	O
deposed	O
that	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
Jordan	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye-Alehouse	O
near	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
one	O
Dress	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Cause	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
new	O
Tryal	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
Jordan	O
had	O
some	O
discourse	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Devil	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
meet	O
Jordan	O
,	O
who	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Draught	O
of	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
to	O
be	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Jorden	O
's	O
Request	O
he	O
procured	O
Frecmen	O
as	O
another	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
Sunday	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Half-Moon	B-place
in	O
Bell-yard	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
J	O
ames	O
Burgess	O
Tallow	O
Chandler	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Wine	O
Cooper	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
telling	O
them	O
that	O
by	O
swearing	O
in	O
wrong	O
Names	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
or	O
come	O
into	O
any	O
Trouble	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
they	O
went	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
said	O
Affidavit	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Necessitous	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Jordan	O
's	O
Solicitations	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
Money	O
in	O
all	O
8	O
Giuneas	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
swear	O
she	O
said	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
hearing	O
they	O
were	O
detected	O
,	O
Jordons	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
to	O
justifie	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
:	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sworn	O
in	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
false	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
Wright	O
had	O
swore	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
meeting	O
at	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
in	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
since	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
that	O
at	O
Jordan	O
's	O
Request	O
he	O
did	O
appear	O
at	O
Westminster	O
to	O
justifie	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
sworn	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
pleased	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
very	O
justly	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
Jordan	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
was	O
about	O
32	O
s.	O
and	O
owned	O
all	O
his	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
false	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Storman	O
corroberated	O
what	O
Wright	O
and	O
Freeman	O
had	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
after	O
Freeman	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
by	O
the	O
Tipstaff	O
,	O
Jordon	O
applyed	O
himself	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
harm	O
in	O
it	O
than	O
in	O
drinking	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Rum	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
privately	O
to	O
a	O
Judges	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
swear	O
in	O
a	O
wrong	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
wards	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
discovered	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chirtwood	I-pers
was	O
produced	O
on	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
Jordan	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
Wright	O
and	O
Freeman	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
at	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
in	O
Bell-Yard	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
what	O
he	O
drew	O
they	O
dictated	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
James	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Rogue	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Jordan	O
heard	O
Wright	O
and	O
Freeman	O
give	O
their	O
false	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
she	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
or	O
ill	O
Character	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
Attorneys	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Subornation	O
.	O
And	O
his	O
Council	O
insisting	O
on	O
some	O
Points	O
of	O
Law	O
the	O
Court	O
admitted	O
him	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
decided	O
by	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
next	O
Term	O
.	O
Hannaniel	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
cheating	O
a	O
Shopkeeper	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
A	O
year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
alias	O
Violet	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gabriel	I-place
Fenchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
with	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Cabet	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cabet	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
that	O
Evening	O
and	O
was	O
Set	O
down	O
at	O
New	O
Round	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stroud	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
hired	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
Portmanteau	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
angry	O
for	O
his	O
staying	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Old	O
Rogue	O
and	O
Old	O
Rascal	O
for	O
making	O
him	O
wait	O
;	O
got	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
cutting	O
his	O
Hand	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
.	O
Thief	O
,	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
coming	O
by	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
James	O
Horris	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
prest	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Whore	O
who	O
was	O
now	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
further	O
said	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
although	O
his	O
Master	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
away	O
unless	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
to	O
confirm	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
,	O
Paper	O
wrote	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Harris	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
contained	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
provided	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
20	O
l.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
tampering	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
by	O
him	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
Infant	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
deposed	O
that	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Rape	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
Body	O
in	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
stops	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Mother	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
kist	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
said	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entie	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
,	O
in	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Coats	O
were	O
up	O
all	O
round	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
indeed	O
were	O
not	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
privy	O
Parts	O
were	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Child	O
begg	O
'd	O
her	O
not	O
for	O
fear	O
her	O
Friends	O
should	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
time	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
the	O
Child	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
with	O
her	O
Coats	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
Fit	O
of	O
Sickness	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
.	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
kist	O
,	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
entie	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
Shells	O
and	O
other	O
playthings	O
:	O
This	O
Evidence	O
also	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Shift	O
of	O
hers	O
stain	O
'd	O
with	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
work	O
was	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
J.	O
Philips	O
,	O
Journyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
san	O
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
leyn	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
both	O
forwards	O
and	O
backward	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
fool	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
layn	O
with	O
her	O
both	O
ways	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whether	O
he	O
never	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
owed	O
Money	O
to	O
,	O
be	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Parual	I-pers
and	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
corroborated	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Donglas	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
inspected	O
the	O
Child	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
privy	O
parts	O
inflam	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
Child	O
cry	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Finger	O
in	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
inflam	O
'd	O
;	O
then	O
be	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
some	O
Oyl	O
and	O
his	O
Finger	O
came	O
out	O
Bloody	O
;	O
he	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
Injury	O
was	O
received	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Surprise	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
extorted	O
by	O
their	O
promising	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
harm	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Walbank	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
have	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
his	O
Daughter	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
unless	O
their	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
abused	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
Child	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
appoint	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
their	O
Surgeon	O
should	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Surgeon	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
again	O
at	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
not	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
were	O
denied	O
admittance	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
Master	O
was	O
within	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
this	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Phillips	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
owed	O
his	O
Master	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Walbank	O
and	O
Mr	O
Pappet	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
again	O
declared	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
that	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
be	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
him	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Instractions	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
swear	O
.	O
Mr	O
Walbank	O
and	O
Mr	O
Pappet	O
confirmed	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
find	O
Philips	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stingy	O
Fellow	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
4	O
l	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
went	O
against	O
his	O
Conseience	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
Walbank	O
also	O
confirmed	O
what	O
was	O
swore	O
before	O
concerning	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Condition	O
as	O
pretended	O
,	O
after	O
such	O
Usage	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
mentioned	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
,	O
,	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattons	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
bruising	O
and	O
Kicking	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Cow	O
in	O
Eastcheap	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
together	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
overtook	O
them	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
joyn	O
'd	O
Company	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
chuck	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
under	O
the	O
Chin	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
cock	O
his	O
Chin	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pinch	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Sides	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Nose	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
continued	O
their	O
Affronts	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
wrencht	O
his	O
Stick	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pitching	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
against	O
the	O
Kenel	O
put	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
joint	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cow	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
dress	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
bath	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
lift	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
weakand	O
languishing	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
belived	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Fishing	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gun-Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
thence	O
overtook	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Words	O
the	O
Deceased	O
broke	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
field	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
knotted	O
Crubstick	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
began	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
joint	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
reduced	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
a	O
flight	O
Bruise	O
of	O
Scratch	O
in	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Injury	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
afterwards	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
only	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
he	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
stir	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
strengthening	O
er	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
this	O
Fray	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
.	O
Therewere	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
abroad	O
since	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
only	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
no	O
Bruise	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
at	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Sessions	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Head	O
's	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
struck	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
matter	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
Process	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
quiet	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
12.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kingsbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
alias	O
Violet	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
William	O
,	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Killison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarak	O
Brunt	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
29.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Arnold	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cringin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Spargin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
alias	O
Holloway	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
alias	O
Rideway	O
alias	O
Windham	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Morre	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Pilkinton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailiff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wedsward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Mathew	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Jones	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wailloux	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooly	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Spurgin	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
Hennaniel	O
barges	O
,	O
one	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
Margaret	B-pers
Doudwell	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kingsbury	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brunt	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
