TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
being	O
the	O
3d,4th	O
and	O
5th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September,1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
more	O
as	O
Followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Roberts	B-pers
Langdale	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marsland	I-pers
,	O
Williams	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
Phillip	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Livingstone	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burchett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brightridge	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramly	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
Long	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
Sisters	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Crow	O
'd	O
on	O
Long	O
Hill	O
,	O
stopt	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
politive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hyfield	I-pers
alias	O
Byfield	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Gold	O
Cypher	O
Rings	O
value	O
38	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Charewoman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
one	O
near	O
the	O
Hospital	O
Gate	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
in	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
Mistress	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
by	O
one	O
Shilling	O
per	O
Week	O
till	O
the	O
whole	O
Money	O
should	O
be	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
failing	O
in	O
her	O
Payments	O
occasioned	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
in	I-place
Old-Fish-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Berrisford	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Plad	O
Night-Gown	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Berrisford	O
Baker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
his	O
Gown	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Gown	O
hang	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Coat	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
ragged	O
Condition	O
he	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
to	O
some	O
others	O
who	O
came	O
by	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Gown	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
a	O
pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
His	O
Examination	O
was	O
also	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
2	O
Holland	O
Necks	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Tennant	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Ticket	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	B-place
in	O
Bear	B-place
Lane	I-place
by	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
(	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
)	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
she	O
clapt	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
and	O
sollowed	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
pickt	O
the	O
two	O
Necks	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
whip	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Rods	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
whip	O
him	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
contented	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
whip	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Necks	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ridgewell	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Scott	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Honey-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Callicoe	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
pais	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
tumbled	O
several	O
pieces	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
bought	O
two	O
yards	O
,	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
hang	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
got	O
away	O
)	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Paul	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Lawrence	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
who	O
confirmed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
Piece	O
was	O
found	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
taken	O
from	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
to	O
Cloath	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
by	O
calling	O
her	O
Landlord	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
that	O
Morning	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
Callicoe	O
for	O
the	O
Children	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
sling	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Molesworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattons	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mush	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
Hours	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
enquiring	O
among	O
themselves	O
how	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Candlelocks	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
stretcht	O
himself	O
out	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Change	O
,	O
there	O
by	O
giving	O
his	O
Companions	O
the	O
better	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Sister	O
perceiving	O
the	O
matter	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
them	O
,	O
brought	O
back	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
dropt	O
in	O
their	O
Flight	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
their	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Candle-sticks	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
plainly	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
between	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Judge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Humfries	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tiking	O
Breeches	O
value	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
finding	O
out	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
visit	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
frequently	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
some	O
soul	O
Linnen	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
among	O
the	O
Linnen	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
well	O
and	O
kept	O
Servants	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
7	O
s.6	O
d.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
was	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
Charlesworth	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
took	O
his	O
Wig	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
Everess	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mitre	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
where	O
they	O
wrung	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Farthings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Rings	O
in	O
the	O
Scussle	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
decain	O
'd	O
him	O
there	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Everess	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
and	O
had	O
formerly	O
Arrested	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sued	O
for	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
said	O
Debt	O
;	O
and	O
could	O
never	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
into	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mitre	O
Tavern	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
,	O
then	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
It	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Ground	O
for	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
from	B-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jumpt	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
hung	O
in	O
Chains	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Well	O
overtaken	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lookt	O
behind	O
her	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
beset	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
that	O
Answer	O
,	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
her	O
Bosorn	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
she	O
has	O
good	O
Clothes	O
on	O
,	O
strip	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
walk	O
home	O
in	O
Smack	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
her	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
.	O
James	O
Grace	O
confirmed	O
her	O
Complaint	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
raised	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Prosecutor	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
that	O
day	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lambert	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
is	O
his	O
Tenant	O
,	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Rent	O
,	O
due	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
Neck	O
of	O
Mutton	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
Plate	O
of	O
Mutton-Pye	O
and	O
some	O
Apple-Pye	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
again	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bustal	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Lonners	O
,	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
in	O
his	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
Rebacca	B-pers
Witcraft	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Maid	O
)	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
two	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
being	O
ill	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Worth	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Jewry	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
57	O
yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
leave	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephens	I-place
Coleman	I-place
street	I-place
and	O
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
Shenly	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Shift,4	O
Aprons	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Winifred	O
Shenly	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
in	O
Thornton	O
,	O
a	O
poor	O
Girl	O
(	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
Errands	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
little	O
Service	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Shenly	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Shenly	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Cushions	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pettifer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
Coach	O
at	O
a	O
Funeral	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
home	O
the	O
Hammercloth	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Foot	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
stoopt	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Cushions	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
the	O
seats	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Gullty	B-place
Hole	I-place
by	O
Fleet	B-place
Bridge	I-place
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boxell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Roan	O
colour	O
'd	O
Mare	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
hi	O
s	O
Mare	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
a	O
Boy	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
set	O
him	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mare	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
it	O
;	O
though	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
he	O
owned	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
bring	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Kennet	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carryed	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
suspecting	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
carryed	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
driving	O
it	O
among	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
his	O
Son	O
after	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
rode	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
selling	O
it	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Ground	O
where	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
.	O
lay	O
next	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
the	O
Gate	O
might	O
be	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Sheep	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
34	O
Sheep	O
at	O
St.	O
Ives	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
34	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
value	O
4	O
l.10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Absolom	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Cheating	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
18	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
buying	O
them	O
brought	O
his	O
Money	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
landed	O
the	O
Waterman	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
Fare	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Withie	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Part	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threatning	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Waterman	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
he	O
complied	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thank	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
Civility	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Trendy	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
Withie	O
and	O
Drake	O
wentforward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
needs	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Door	O
together	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
knockt	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
body	O
hear	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Barber	O
's	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
hitting	O
up	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Gold	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
the	O
Barbers	O
Boy	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
and	O
keep	O
safe	O
for	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Barber	O
's	O
Boy	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
bringing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
deposed	O
.	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
safe	O
home	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
back	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
left	O
with	O
him	O
just	O
now	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Boy	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
were	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Withie	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
Night	O
upon	O
that	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Murray	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
Murray	O
,	O
who	O
now	O
absconds	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gill	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
odges	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Colemane-street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
farthest	O
,	O
eat	O
his	O
supper	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
any	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
25th	O
because	O
her	O
Husband	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
that	O
Day	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
confirmed	O
what	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
said	O
relating	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
Another	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
the	O
time	O
because	O
she	O
paid	O
her	O
Rent	O
the	O
next	O
Morning.2d	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Morning	O
her	O
Landlord	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
Rechester	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
invalidate	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
particularly	O
that	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Withie	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Withie	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
by	O
Gaming	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Withies	O
Guardian	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Friends	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
hansomly	O
to	O
live	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
wild	O
Young	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
consisidering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Cheapside	O
Conduit	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
comb	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
through	O
Newgate	O
into	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
perceiving	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
separated	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
ran	O
towards	O
Pye-Corner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
carryed	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
Door	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Wig	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
two	O
others	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Wig	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chadwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Door	O
locks	O
and	O
bolted	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Watchhouse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisonner	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
his	O
silent	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
rush	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Sherbourn	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
through	O
Dove-Court	O
,	O
caling	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
through	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
struct	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
staff	O
and	O
mist	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
who	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
having	O
a	O
child	O
to	O
be	O
Christen	O
'd	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Frind	O
in	O
Woods	O
Close	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
Godfather	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
till	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
Bole	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
at	O
Stocks-Market	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
threaten	O
the	O
Watchman	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Arms	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
stick	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Friend	O
conformed	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
Godfather	O
to	O
his	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drinking	O
of	O
Punch	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats,2	O
black	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Apron	O
and	O
a	O
Deal	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
helping	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
to	O
remove	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
George	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pounds	O
of	O
Red-wood	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whitchurch	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Brudenell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons,2	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Strainer	O
,	O
a	O
smelling	O
Bottle	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brandlin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Gotigh	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
first	O
Floor	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
bilket	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
diligent	O
search	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Goldsmith	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Plate	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
looke	O
'd	O
upon	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
pretending	O
not	O
to	O
like	O
the	O
Fashion	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Plate	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
weight	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Mary	O
Francis	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Vansittars	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
Francis	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket,2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
enamel	O
'd	O
Ring	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Clausina	B-pers
Vansittars	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rachel	O
Taylor	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mary	O
Francis	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Chare-woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
above	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
helping	O
them	O
to	O
remove	O
some	O
Goods	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
took	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
to	O
Tayler	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Fork	O
and	O
some	O
went	O
Linnen	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
Taylor	O
conselt	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
according	O
to	O
their	O
direction	O
.	O
A	O
Goldsmith	O
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Buttons	O
of	O
Taylor	O
for	O
14	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Taylor	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Mary	O
Francis	O
came	O
together	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
small	O
Ring	O
for	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
Gold	O
Studs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
examining	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
Taylor	O
said	O
her	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Sweetheart	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	O
Francis	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mary	O
Francis	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Medal	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Medal	I-pers
alias	O
Southers	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pillows,2	O
Quilts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cuiverwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Willmot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Yeo	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
long	O
Saw	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Saw	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Browne	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisonor	O
for	O
16	O
s.6	O
d.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dowlas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
privately	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chest	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
meeting	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Westbrook	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
it	O
's	O
full	O
Growth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
born	O
alive	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stoner	I-pers
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
full	O
Growth	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
still-born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
lost	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Help	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
fix	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
bad	O
with	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
Stomach	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
it	O
lookt	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
looking	O
for	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Her	O
Master	O
's	O
Daughter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
waked	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
(	O
before	O
fix	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Chollick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
wake	O
herseveral	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
her	O
self	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
wake	O
her	O
young	O
Mistress	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
till	O
near	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reckoned	O
she	O
had	O
6	O
Weeks	O
longer	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
from	O
a	O
Chair	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
felt	O
the	O
Child	O
Stir	O
Since	O
;	O
She	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Fall	O
,	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
further	O
deposing	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
helpt	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Linnen	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
Childrens	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
her	O
Mistress	O
deposed	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Nurse	O
who	O
Nurst	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Illness	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
her	O
Sister	O
of	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
Choaking	O
and	O
Drowning	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Ideot	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Sister	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
wash	O
her	O
Face	O
at	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
fall	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ursley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pound	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
same	O
.	O
Julia	B-pers
Pound	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
her	O
Brother	O
)	O
Hester	B-pers
Pendrick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Sourhampton-Row	B-place
by	O
my	B-place
Lady	I-place
Russel	I-place
's	I-place
Wall	I-place
with	O
Goods	O
on	O
their	O
Heads	O
,	O
singing	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
Road	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drove	O
his	O
without	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
any	O
Fare	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
paying	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
Brother	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
replyed	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
whipt	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Poll	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
struck	O
the	O
Basket	O
off	O
her	O
Brothers	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
belived	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
stop	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Brother	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
whipt	O
Horses	O
upon	O
her	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Hester	O
Pendrik	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Girl	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
)	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
second	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
sing	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
stopt	O
;	O
that	O
be	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
Hait	O
,	O
and	O
Whip	O
his	O
Horses	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
on	O
the	O
Temporal	O
Muscle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Concussion	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
his	O
Brain	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
present	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
willfully	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
whipt	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
Hay	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
encourage	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
turning	O
his	O
Horses	O
after	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
over	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
Russel	O
Street	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Sober	O
,	O
Civil	O
,	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
Lad	O
from	O
his	O
Youth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
respected	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herbet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Brittle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Lumley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	O
Brittle	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
Lumley	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Watch	O
from	O
her	O
side	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
Pall-Mall	B-place
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
loose	O
Girl	O
was	O
selling	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
to	O
Ann	O
Brittle	O
in	O
Newtonors	O
Lane	O
,	O
carryed	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
;	O
that	O
Herbers	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
Lid	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
and	O
kicks	O
it	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Steps	O
of	O
an	O
Oil	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Neats	O
Tongues	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
my	O
Lady	O
went	O
in	O
from	O
her	O
Coach	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
lost	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
other	O
Girls	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Ann	O
Brittle	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
imployed	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brittle	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
acquint	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
Girl	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
come	O
cheap	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
Lady	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Britle	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Pav	O
d	O
Stones	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
as	O
he	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quarter-Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
when	O
she	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
of	O
Feltham	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Lock	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hole	O
broke	O
in	O
his	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Stock	O
by	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
His	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
Homes	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Harvest	O
time	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
it	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
sought	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Hedge	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
Want	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
there	O
to	O
rest	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
40	O
l.	O
Reward	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tufton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
115	O
l.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
from	O
Katharine	B-pers
Rowder	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
robbe	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
3	O
Hours	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Sterrey	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dewer	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
decoy	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Marybone-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
of	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
as	O
often	O
promissed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
growing	O
impatient	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	O
show	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
a-Clock	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
another	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
secur	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Sterry	O
dropt	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
Dewer	O
gave	O
a	O
Woman	O
a	O
quarter	O
Jacobus	O
to	O
change	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Watchman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dewer	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
put	O
two	O
Six-pences	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
,	O
down	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Sterry	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
Dewer	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
by	O
whose	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
forc	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
promising	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
formerly	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
now	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
trouble-some	O
ill	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Husters	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
26	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
Swan	O
the	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
two	O
Foot-Pads	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
short	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
quit	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
short	O
Man	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
having	O
Known	O
him	O
well	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Another	O
corrobarated	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
by	O
deposing	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
declare	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
Fellow	O
go	O
through	O
Islington	O
together	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
towards	O
Highgate	O
.	O
Another	O
Person	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pocket	O
Pistols	O
to	O
Shoot	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
what	O
use	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
in	O
Clerkenwell-Ciose	O
)	O
from	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
till	O
seven	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
would	O
make	O
Oath	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heward	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
till	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
10	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
parted	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Land-lord	O
's	O
Daughter	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Charteshouse-Lane	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
10	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
drunk	O
and	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
an	O
Old	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
home	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
.	O
His	O
Landlord	O
and	O
Landlady	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
10	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Philippa	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Earthen	O
Cups	O
,	O
one	O
Horn	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Hukkaback	O
Napkin	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Grammar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hand-saw	O
,	O
a	O
Smoothing	O
Plain	O
,	O
2	O
Chissels	O
,	O
an	O
Ax	O
,	O
an	O
Adds	O
,	O
a	O
Square	O
and	O
a	O
Roll	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Tools	O
out	O
of	O
Marybone	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Chissel	O
,	O
Hand-saw	O
,	O
and	O
Square	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
is	O
a	O
Joyner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Tools	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
desiring	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Rose	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas,6	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
some	O
Silver	O
and	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gilder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
)	O
did	O
not	O
refuse	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Oake	I-place
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
down	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
clapt	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
his	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gold	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Silver	O
was	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
comply	O
,	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
that	O
stripp	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
all	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Table	O
Cloth,2	O
Perriwings	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
dozen	O
of	O
Calve	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
230	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Langthorne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Caulton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Greatorix	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
his	O
cousin	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Legacy	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
Derbyshire	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
fetcht	O
down	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
remaining	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hatfield	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Closet	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
concluded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
Legacy	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
sometimes	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Relation	O
;	O
but	O
denyed	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Servants	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
alias	O
Johnson	B-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
and	O
a	O
Purse	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Door	O
and	O
bound	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
that	O
Ward	O
and	O
Robbins	O
came	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
Dutton	O
came	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
tyed	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Puise	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Ward	O
forc	O
'd	O
something	O
very	O
bitter	O
down	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
supposed	O
was	O
to	O
cause	O
her	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
A	O
Warder	O
deposed	O
that	O
.	O
Dutton	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
not	O
being	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
Lid	O
that	O
Mary	O
Stone	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
care	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
of	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
long	O
herself	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
along	O
to	O
Produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
Duttan	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
Purse	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jakes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
half	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Watson	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Latch	O
which	O
was	O
litred	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
her	O
Six	O
Pence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Nowland	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Constantine	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
John	O
Nowland	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Talboy	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
1713.	O
at	O
a	O
private	O
House	O
in	O
Blue-Ball	B-place
Alley	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Mint	I-place
.	I-place
Southwark	I-place
;	O
and	O
to	O
Constantine	O
Boone	O
last	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
both	O
Marriages	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
was	O
no	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
Husband	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Monster	O
,	O
a	O
Hermaphrodite	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
shown	O
as	O
such	O
at	O
Southwark-Fair	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Places	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
one	O
whereof	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
a	O
Girl	O
in	O
Apparel	O
and	O
at	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
handle	O
the	O
Needle	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
12	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
Man	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
Hermaphrodite	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
shown	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
more	O
predominant	O
in	O
her	O
than	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
alias	O
Schock	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Graystock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
where	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes,3	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings,1	O
pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings,3	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Slippers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
One	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Windows	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
Green	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Shoes	O
on	O
.	O
and	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
bought	O
of	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
matter	O
on	O
Graytock	O
nor	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
on	O
Greens	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
Graytock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Greens	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Gates	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
agreed	O
together	O
for	O
one	O
at	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
her	O
Civility	O
she	O
fetch	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Rum	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
reacht	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
Dish	O
of	O
Sugar	O
to	O
Sweeten	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Dish	O
upon	O
the	O
Sugar	O
were	O
the	O
Rings	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liked	O
the	O
Rum	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
a	O
penny	O
worth	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
fetch	O
another	O
Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dish	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
borrowed	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Gates	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
lend	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
an	O
Allowance	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Forrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Word	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sturtembow	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Child	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
cry	O
'd	O
Huzza	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
said	O
Good	O
Girl	O
,	O
Huzza	O
for	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
Huzza	O
for	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
Hazza	O
for	O
the	O
Pretender	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Life	O
to	O
Lose	O
I	O
'd	O
lose	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Pretender	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
believing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Conges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
l.10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Brother	O
's	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
over	O
Night	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Six	O
Pence	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisner	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
for	O
a	O
Loaf	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
change	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
verily	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Sixpence	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
bent	O
and	O
batter	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
particularly	O
mark	O
'd	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
wihtin	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
without	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
that	O
Sixpence	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
none	O
of	O
this	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
unseasonable	O
Hours	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
six	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
entrusted	O
him	O
confiderably	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death.5	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boxell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Brudenell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,2	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ursly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Judge	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,25	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Kennet	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dowlas	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
alias	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jakes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Yeo	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rose	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Cheapside	O
Conduit	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
try	O
'd	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
Fined	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Wounding	O
a	O
Waterman	O
at	O
Black	O
fryers	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Transportation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
and	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Brudenell	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Belies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
is	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
,	O
pr.8	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Barly	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smysbies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
cow	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
Portions	O
at	O
the	O
Psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
shewing	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
what	O
Psalms	O
and	O
Hyams	O
are	O
proper	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopeims	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sterubold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tate	O
.	O
And	O
Directions	O
for	O
parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Pial	O
son	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
B.S	O
.	O
Shentox	O
;	O
and	O
Recommended	O
by	O
P.	O
Jonson	O
,	O
D.	O
Warner	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Five	O
Tunes	O
,	O
containing	O
their	O
Cantms	O
,	O
Medias	O
and	O
Bassan	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Joseph	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflection	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verle	O
.	O
Indicated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instrud	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practia	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
famatter	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Ergstions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
,	O
demonstreting	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
5	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
;	O
Or	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Plamest	O
and	O
camest	O
Method	O
of	O
Working	O
SUPRITAND	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
complex	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Trayals	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Borley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
agree	O
'd	O
on	O
Thi	O
rty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Pr.1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
A	O
Guide	O
of	O
English	O
Juries	O
:	O
Setting	O
forth	O
their	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
and	O
Statutes	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Auther	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordiance	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackney-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
,	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directer	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
All	O
Melawcholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypocondriack	O
Distempers	O
,	O
WHich	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
and	O
diseal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Fainrings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Horries	O
,	O
Restlesness	O
and	O
Dilquietment	O
(	O
Little	O
understood	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
means	O
)	O
also	O
Plains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
Rifings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caused	O
by	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Son	O
and	O
Successor	O
to	O
a	O
late	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
30	O
Years	O
successful	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
Deplorable	O
Cases	O
)	O
he	O
also	O
Cures	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
justly	O
inform	O
you	O
;	O
living	O
at	O
No	O
1.	O
in	O
Burn-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Kuberines	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occassion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answered	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
A	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
near	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
SturuyGrass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
The	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
last	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-2ly	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rheumatison	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Anatomical	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
-3ly	O
.	O
Arational	O
Account	O
on	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
,	O
Self-abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labouers	O
,	O
Misearringes,8tc	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
hoirld	O
Mesure	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
sutaible	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self-Abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toyshop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
