TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th,9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Bury	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cheesebrook	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
Job	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayliff	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Patrick	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
down	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
there	O
was	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
Quakers	O
,	O
which	O
as	O
he	O
past	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
about	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereup	O
on	O
he	O
felt	O
and	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
pickt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
on	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Defence	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Mackoy	I-pers
alias	O
Lewis	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
Shore-ditch	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
Pillow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Lodger	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
2	O
,	O
Womans	O
House	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
but	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Brokers	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Master	O
had	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
their	O
Daughter	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
saw	O
William	O
Perry	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
down	O
a	O
Cellar	O
was	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
Collier	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
'em	O
easy	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
come-again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
affect	O
Collier	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
Perry	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gossage	I-pers
:	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Masters	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
from	O
Burts	O
lying	O
without	O
the	O
Gate	O
(	O
he	O
using	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
the	O
Offenders	O
were	O
gone	O
)	O
now	O
planted	O
himself	O
without	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
more	O
ready	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
off	O
Hoops	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Fire	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
the	O
Watch	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Casks	O
were	O
brought	O
home	O
that	O
Evening	O
with	O
the	O
Hoops	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
he	O
found	O
9	O
Hoops	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
Casks	O
from	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Hoops	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Cooper	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Casks	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
Hoops	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
Casks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
but	O
no	O
Adds	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
wherewith	O
to	O
knock	O
off	O
the	O
Hoops	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Cooper	O
(	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
)	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
this	O
dry	O
Weather	O
the	O
Hoops	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
without	O
Adds	O
,	O
even	O
by	O
bare	O
Hands	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Four	O
Doors	O
below	O
to	O
a	O
Brandyshop	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
were	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Country-man	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
Warwick-Shire	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
was	O
his	O
Country-woman	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
her	O
Ivitation	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
next	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
directing	O
his	O
Discourse	O
to	O
his	O
Country-woman	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
except	O
two	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
still	O
directing	O
his	O
Discourse	O
to	O
his	O
Country-woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Crowns	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Country-Woman	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
who	O
replyed	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
Home	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
four	O
times	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
find	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bully	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Country-woman	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
Candle	O
at	O
the	O
Brandyshop	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
half	O
Pints	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
liked	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
's	O
Company	O
better	O
than	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
wanted	O
more	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Bed	O
was	O
Rolled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Woman	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Till	O
where	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
Passengers	O
Earnest	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	B-place
Boar	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
having	O
been	O
pickt	O
of	O
16	O
s.	O
Some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
overlook	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
without	O
being	O
seen	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
liking	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Tapster	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
open	O
the	O
Till	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
down	O
for	O
another	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Till	O
while	O
the	O
Taster	O
drew	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Yards	O
fetch	O
him	O
some	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Till	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
mov'done	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Accquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
of	O
St.Giles	B-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
Prosecute	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
searching	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breeches	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lay	O
them	O
down	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
wake	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
their	O
Room	O
.	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Dard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hoply	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
stealing	O
thence	O
6	O
Cheshire	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hugh	O
Hoply	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
House	O
safe	O
shut	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Cellar-Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Gregory	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
were	O
card	O
to	O
Long	O
Alley	O
and	O
hid	O
under	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
James	O
Dard	O
,	O
whom	O
Gregory	O
then	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Boy	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Cheese	O
,	O
striving	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Devil	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Knock't	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
broad	O
Day	O
light	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Gregory	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Gregory	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
they	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Dard	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
being	O
up	O
early	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Cheese	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Bulk	O
in	O
Ivy	O
Lane	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Lighterman	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
but	O
3	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
though	O
now	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
charg	O
'd	O
Dard	O
with	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
Dard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Gregory	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ayre	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sowden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Pountney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Flemish	O
Pot-Ashes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
)	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Pipe	O
on	O
her	O
left	O
Cheek	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
21th	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sureties	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
were	O
Partners	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
Milk	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
owed	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
uneasie	O
,	O
but	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Note	O
for	O
it	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
deliver	O
up	O
the	O
Trade	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
living	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Houses	O
owed	O
him	O
also	O
Money	O
for	O
Rent	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
distrain	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
them	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
settle	O
matters	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Customers	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Eagle	B-place
and	I-place
Tree	I-place
in	O
Moor	B-place
Lane	I-place
to	O
drink	O
and	O
discourse	O
further	O
on	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
high	O
Words	O
arose	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
fill	O
'd	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
it	O
lighted	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
warmly	O
discoursing	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
giving	O
him	O
very	O
provoking	O
Language	O
,	O
he	O
pusht	O
the	O
small	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Pipe	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
swoned	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Calcupp	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
Orb	O
of	O
the	O
Left	O
Eye	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
long	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
deep	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
Splinter	O
of	O
the	O
Pipe	O
dropt	O
off	O
under	O
her	O
Eye	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
mortal	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
cured	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
very	O
malignant	O
Fever	O
ensued	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
complained	O
to	O
him	O
only	O
of	O
the	O
Accident	O
and	O
her	O
Head-ach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
for	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
deep	O
the	O
Wound	O
might	O
be	O
when	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
imposthumated	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
Intention	O
to	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
push	O
or	O
dart	O
his	O
Pipe	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
much	O
provok	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
doppiag	O
down	O
to	O
avoid	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Fever	O
on	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
White-Fryars	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Duroy,48	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
l.15	O
s.2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Arnold	B-pers
Shipwrang	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
th	O
e	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Holliday	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shipwrang	O
in	O
Water-lane	B-place
in	O
White-Fryers	B-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
two	O
Shillings	O
per	O
Week	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Holiday	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
for	O
ready	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
was	O
writ	O
out	O
and	O
cast	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
above	O
mentioned	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
enough	O
about	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
his	O
Man	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Man	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
charging	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
with	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
Holliday	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
new	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
above	O
two	O
Hours	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
lay	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Ale-house	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
drink	O
for	O
his	O
Trouble	O
in	O
waiting	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Holliday	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
leaving	O
word	O
with	O
his	O
new	O
Landlady	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlady	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Holliday	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
first	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
Holliday	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Holliday	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
new	O
Lodgers	O
never	O
came	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Holliday	O
's	O
Wife	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
Evidence	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
swore	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
Holliday	O
's	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
bought	O
and	O
not	O
stole	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Condition	O
of	O
Sale	O
,	O
being	O
for	O
ready	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
till	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
thereof	O
was	O
not	O
transferr	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
till	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
should	O
be	O
received	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Intention	O
of	O
Holliday	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
him	O
any	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Urphane	B-pers
Mackhoule	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Paschal	B-pers
Canny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Nosegays	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
Dram	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
laid-down	O
his	O
Buckles	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Anniseed	O
the	O
Prisner	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Basket	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
thinking	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
white	O
Metal	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Halfpenny-worth	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Scarf	O
;	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gorbin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Jame	B-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown,4	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-pot	O
,	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Consent	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Caffoy	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Caffoy	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
Chairmen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
cutting	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
the	O
Chairs	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Goods	O
over	O
the	O
Rails	O
in	O
the	O
Privy	O
Garden	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
wrapt	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
reaching	O
some	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Gown	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
being	O
drunk	O
fell	O
off	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
getting	O
up	O
to	O
drive	O
the	O
Coach	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Seats	O
were	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Yard	O
where	O
the	O
Coach	O
stood	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drove	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Seats	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
(	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Seats	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Seats	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Pullin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
value	O
25	O
s.2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Pullin	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
his	O
evil	O
Practices	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
Dye-house	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
then	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Corner	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
Spoons	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Can	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
in	O
some	O
Dirt	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
both	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
one	O
Tho	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Plate	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
Ship	O
at	O
Chatham	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
the	O
Plate	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
having	O
so	O
long	O
constantly	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mark	O
being	O
thereon	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dary	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Smock	O
value	O
3	O
s.3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Edging	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Pocket-Pieces	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
for	O
4	O
s.3	O
d.	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Mothers	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Edging	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Aprons	O
on	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
she	O
threatned	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
vindicate	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Pocket-pieces	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
considering	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
might	O
be	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
parting	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
accordingly	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
two	O
Pence	O
more	O
for	O
them	O
than	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Husband	O
being	O
arrested	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
this	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
ser	O
on	O
Foot	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
Alice	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Alice	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
going	O
out	O
that	O
Morning	O
left	O
her	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
open	O
lockt	O
,	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
Door	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
latch	O
'd	O
the	O
Outer	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
from	O
her	O
Chamber	O
to	O
her	O
Outer	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
jumpt	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bed	O
naked	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
dropping	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
denyal	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Regulus	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Spelter	O
Metal	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Grunwin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
mend	O
a	O
Drein	O
which	O
ran	O
through	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
occasion	O
to	O
come	O
often	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Water	O
ran	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Spelter	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
venture	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
afterwards	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
however	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
one	O
Man	O
was	O
like	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
workt	O
there	O
besides	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pontin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Marzaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Hendon	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
into	O
Bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
often	O
abused	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
sometimes	O
he	O
borrowed	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
would	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
Money	O
by	O
Violence	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
paying	O
her	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
,	O
fetch	O
him	O
the	O
Note	O
;	O
which	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
him	O
(	O
he	O
perceiving	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
themselves	O
)	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
knockt	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
tock	O
the	O
3	O
Guineas	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
foot	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Marry	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
quiet	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
marry	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
disgrace	O
him	O
every	O
where	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
Son	O
and	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Boiloe	O
a	O
Gardener	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
four	O
Years	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
Gardener	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Berkshire	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
Neceilitous	O
;	O
also	O
two	O
others	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
very	O
often	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
fince	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
has	O
been	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
loved	O
him	O
beyond	O
all	O
the	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
now	O
bound	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
between	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Shutter	O
again	O
,	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Parlour	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
opposite	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
well	O
again	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
perfectly	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
the	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
,	O
House-breakers	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
lookt	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
concluded	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
so	O
followed	O
him	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
Knife	O
at	O
a	O
Black	O
Dog	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
forward	O
and	O
not	O
backward	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
along	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Asistance	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mee	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Votler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Darby	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Westphalia	O
Ham	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hocky	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
opened	O
his	O
Drawer	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Money	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sackvil	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
by	O
Temple-Bar	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
being	O
near	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposing	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
wet	O
Weather	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Dirt	O
on	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Craft	I-pers
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Eggleston	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
62	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Red	O
Wood	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Burrolds	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Fenchurch	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Wood	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Chequer	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
at	O
Ralphs	B-place
Key	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
John	O
Eggleston	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
only	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stains	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Stains	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
took	O
1	O
l.13	O
s.	O
for	O
Bridle	O
Saddle	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Earnest	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
rest	O
when	O
he	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
Inn	I-place
at	O
Stansted	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cap	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
William	O
James	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
from	O
Pitchcot	B-place
near	O
Ailesbury	B-place
in	O
Buckinghamshire	B-place
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
James	I-pers
his	O
Brother	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
living	O
in	O
Town	O
Advertised	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
Print	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Hart	O
street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
it	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
again	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
nor	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Soloman	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Wooden	O
Skulls	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cornwell	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tortoise-Shell	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hossington	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Snuff-Mill	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
,	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Colter	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Fan	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Childish	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
Fair	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three-Ton-Tavern	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
a	O
Bargain	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
pay	O
her	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
stand	O
a	O
Search	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
himself	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
readily	O
consented	O
;	O
and	O
turning	O
out	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
an	O
Ivory	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
some	O
Farthings	O
and	O
two	O
Crusts	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Snuff-Box	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Fan	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Mount	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Three-Ton-Tavern	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
before	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
;	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
that	O
Tavern	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hasely	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indict	O
ed	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
34	O
Sheep	O
Skins	O
value	O
24s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
and	O
related	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
his	O
Master	O
examined	O
him	O
about	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wish	O
'd	O
the	O
Devil	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
10	O
Skins	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
by	O
himself	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
who	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Churcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
the	O
Master	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Churcher	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
needs	O
thrive	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
buy	O
such	O
Bargains	O
as	O
10	O
Skins	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
10	O
Skins	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
but	O
a	O
dozen	O
and	O
10	O
Skins	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Churcher	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
his	O
Goods	O
cheaper	O
than	O
ordinary	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
Beginner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
,	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
his	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
none	O
without	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
rais	O
'd	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
Churcher	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
15	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Hose	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
Board	O
of	O
Hose	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
who	O
lives	O
right	O
against	O
him	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
look	O
three	O
times	O
through	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Shop	O
clear	O
,	O
he	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Grate	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
poor	O
Defence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Latherton	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
William	O
Latherton	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
for	O
Promoting	O
,	O
Abetting	O
and	O
Assisting	O
him	O
therein	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
,	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
kept	O
a	O
Cellar	O
against	O
Somerset	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
Durham	O
was	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
3	O
Soldiers	O
more	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
Cellar	O
refused	O
to	O
entertain	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
Women	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
Words	O
the	O
Woman	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
Latberton	O
the	O
Drummer	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
Latberton	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
had	O
once	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
beating	O
;	O
that	O
Latberson	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
the	O
worse	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
Harding	O
bid	O
them	O
not	O
quarrel	O
but	O
have	O
a	O
care	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
Latberson	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
beat	O
two	O
Men	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Comrade	O
would	O
see	O
any	O
two	O
Men	O
out	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
go	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
Latberson	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
fight	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
hop	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
both	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
Harding	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
up	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Comrade	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Durbam	O
,	O
that	O
Harding	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
after	O
them	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
Durbam	O
held	O
her	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
Latberson	O
and	O
Henly	O
fought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Comrade	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
suck	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
thereby	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Durbam	O
did	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
saint	O
;	O
that	O
Harding	O
brought	O
a	O
Bed	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Durbam	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
Harding	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Comrade	O
deposed	O
that	O
Durbam	O
prevented	O
his	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Some	O
Evidence	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
more	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
rather	O
lose	O
her	O
Reckoning	O
than	O
have	O
Quarrelling	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
80	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
stealing	O
260	O
yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
(	O
a	O
Hot-presser	O
s	O
)	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Masters	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
several	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
lived	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
Dyed	O
for	O
several	O
Mercers	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Goods	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
a	O
Piece	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
a	O
Bundle	O
with	O
10	O
Pieces	O
before	O
Witness	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
Piece	O
before	O
a	O
second	O
Bundlecould	O
be	O
brought	O
;	O
whereupon	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
laid	O
wait	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Pawn-Broaker	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
14	O
Pieces	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
had	O
suffered	O
so	O
these	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
suspecting	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
reredeem	O
them	O
agaim	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Gause	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barkham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Lodger	O
,	O
who	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
Warning	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Spoon	O
(	O
the	O
top	O
where	O
the	O
Mark	O
was	O
being	O
broke	O
off	O
)	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
or	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
asleep	O
on	O
a	O
Beach	O
behind	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
more	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Landlord	O
refused	O
to	O
draw	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
kickt	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
and	O
remembring	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
busy	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
wak	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
finding	O
himself	O
pursued	O
and	O
hard	O
set	O
,	O
jumpt	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
who	O
happen	O
'd	O
accidentally	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
fear	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
carryed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
playing	O
at	O
Nine-Pins	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
drunk	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
play	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
Money	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Landlord	O
kickt	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
among	O
the	O
Nine	O
Pins	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
,	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Riddlesden	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup,6	O
Spoons,2	O
Salts,300	O
Books	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Riddlesden	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglery	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Temperance	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
Temperance	O
Walker	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Steel	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
his	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
that	O
against	O
Walker	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Steel	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
also	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Childrens	O
Blankets	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Frock	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
who	O
hanging	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
Sale	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
cryes	O
old	O
Clothes	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Frock	O
,	O
but	O
call	O
'd	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchrees	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
Words	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
1717	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	B-place
with	I-place
the	I-place
Prisoner	I-place
near	O
Hickes	B-place
's	I-place
Hall	I-place
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
that	O
King	O
George	O
was	O
not	O
Hair	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
but	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Toirdis	O
is	O
the	O
true	O
Hair	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
two	O
Women	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
have	O
drank	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
by	O
that	O
Title	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refused	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Arren	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
Words	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
assisting	O
the	O
Mob	O
at	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
Captain	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
a	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Sam	B-pers
Bains	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Child	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
and	O
Assaulting	O
divers	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
tearing	O
their	O
Gowns	O
made	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Major	O
Hardwick	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
Dilturbance	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Weavers	O
being	O
met	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Riorous	O
and	O
cumulruous	O
manner	O
,	O
assaulting	O
all	O
Women	O
they	O
met	O
that	O
were	O
drest	O
in	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
tearing	O
their	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
committing	O
other	O
Disorders	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last,4	O
Companies	O
of	O
the	O
Militia	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
raised	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
they	O
gathered	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
advice	O
that	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Brown	B-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
some	O
Women	O
in	O
Callicoe	O
Gowns	O
,	O
marcht	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Lieutenant	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Lane	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
ralt	O
marcht	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
accordingly	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Bains	O
and	O
Picket	O
clad	O
in	O
Callicoe	O
to	O
the	O
Waste	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Ringleaders	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Callisses	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Major	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
Bains	O
and	O
Picket	O
drest	O
in	O
Callicoe	O
to	O
the	O
Waste	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hundred	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
flourishing	O
it	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Callicoes	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
through	O
Wide-Gate-Alley	O
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
Woman	O
go	O
before	O
him	O
drest	O
in	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pitty	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
wore	O
;	O
whereupon	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
Five	O
or	O
Six	O
Guineas	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
encourage	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hoped	O
to	O
have	O
Ten	O
for	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
reinfore	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Norwich	O
Weavers	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Business	O
would	O
be	O
done	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
acquaint	O
him	O
how	O
the	O
matter	O
went	O
on	O
from	O
Day	O
to	O
Day	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brisco	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Humphrey	O
's	O
was	O
a	O
Ringleader	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
at	O
Salisbury-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
brag	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pillington	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Charles	O
Child	O
going	O
a	O
long	O
the	O
Square	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
with	O
a	O
vast	O
number	O
,	O
swearing	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
Shot	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
Meat	O
and	O
Drink	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
when	O
the	O
Justice	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
being	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
well	O
she	O
was	O
over	O
Against	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
whereupon	O
another	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Justice	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
no	O
Eyes	O
by	O
Night	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
bellowing	O
and	O
crying	O
and	O
encouraging	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appeared	O
that	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
would	O
have	O
cur	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
John	O
Humphreys	O
pleaded	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	O
Child	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
accidentally	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
with	O
Packthread	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Pack-thread	O
Spinner	O
)	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
was	O
shot	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Leg	O
himself	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
recommending	O
Charles	O
Child	O
to	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Larmony	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mattoon	I-pers
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
into	O
Bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
wherein	O
were	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Threepence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Price	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
People	O
sitting	O
at	O
their	O
Doors	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
Callicoe	O
;	O
Weavers	O
,	O
Weavers	O
,	O
Whereupon	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
Gown	O
off	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
her	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
tore	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
Larmony	O
was	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
off	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
lying	O
near	O
his	O
Loom	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
Pocket	O
nor	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Martoon	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Callicoe	O
Bitch	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
Boys	O
and	O
Girls	O
that	O
tore	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Larmony	O
there	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Palo	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
in	O
Crown	O
Court	O
saw	O
Larmony	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
Mobb	O
'd	O
.	O
Andrew	O
du	O
Bruel	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Larmony	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Rout	O
began	O
Larmony	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Garden	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
Bread	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
sleep	O
in	O
a	O
whole	O
Skin	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Children	O
threw	O
pieces	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
stood	O
at	O
her	O
Gate	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
and	O
big	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
about	O
100	O
Boys	O
and	O
Girls	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Door	O
forward	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
,	O
she	O
seeing	O
him	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
Garden	O
Wall	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
Man	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
sworn	O
the	O
same	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
deposed	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
swore	O
against	O
Mastoon	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Callicoe	O
Bitch	O
;	O
however	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
on	O
Rosamond	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
Rosemary	B-place
Lane	I-place
with	O
Mrs.	O
Maddox	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Dean	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rubb	O
'd	O
against	O
Mrs.	O
Dean	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
Harry	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
D-m	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Knife	O
and	O
whet	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Shoe	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
frighted	O
ran	O
in	O
a	O
Doors	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Maddox	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Dean	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Maddox	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Soul	O
from	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Bed	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
them	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
draw	O
him	O
any	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
weaver	O
?	O
here	O
's	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Knife	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
Pipe	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
drunk	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
draw	O
him	O
any	O
Drink	O
:	O
that	O
some	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
leaning	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followith	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,10	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Cap	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,2	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dary	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,29	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hutchings	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gossage	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sowden	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wier	I-pers
,	O
Urphane	B-pers
Mackhoule	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Currey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
Darby	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Mackoy	I-pers
alias	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
who	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
twelve	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Baines	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
are	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
and	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
Charles	O
Child	O
to	O
suffer	O
Three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
.	O
Pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
Mary	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
Sarah	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
not	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
condernn	O
'd	O
for	O
selling	O
Counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
THE	O
Original	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Parging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
near	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s	O
,	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
1st	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Curet	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-	O
aly	O
,	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rhenntatison	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Auatomical	O
Observa	O
tions	O
and	O
Experience	O
-3ly	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Carse	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
,	O
Self-Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
fall	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self-	O
A	O
buses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-	O
LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toyshop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
said	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
;	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr.8	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
cantaining	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
portions	O
of	O
the	O
psalons	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tone	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
shewing	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
what	O
Psalms	O
and	O
Hymns	O
are	O
proper	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sternhold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tate	O
.	O
And	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Plams	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
B.S.Sbenton	O
;	O
and	O
Recommended	O
by	O
P.Joynson	O
,	O
D.	O
Warner	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Singing-Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Five	O
Tunes	O
,	O
containing	O
their	O
Canses	O
,	O
Medies	O
and	O
Basses	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
p	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reslections	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
.	O
Issustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Piates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instruct	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briesly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
samiliar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demoastrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
,	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
SHORT-HAND	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
.	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
coriously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Pr.1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
A	O
Guide	O
to	O
English	O
Juries	O
:	O
Setting	O
for	O
their	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
and	O
Statutes	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackney	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chaucellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
direds	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
At	O
the	O
Red	O
Ball	O
in	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Globe-Ale-House	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
Three-Cranes	O
.	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
incomparable	O
wash	O
to	O
beautify	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
far	O
exceeds	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
extant	O
,	O
as	O
abuedance	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Quality	O
have	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
Experience	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
It	O
takes	O
out	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Wrlinkles	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Bimples	O
,	O
reduess	O
,	O
Morphew	O
;	O
Sunburo	O
,	O
Yellowness	O
,	O
cansed	O
by	O
Mercurial	O
poisonous	O
washes	O
:	O
It	O
also	O
plumps	O
and	O
softens	O
the	O
skin	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
as	O
smooth	O
,	O
and	O
tender	O
as	O
a	O
sucking	O
Child	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
it	O
keeps	O
always	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
it	O
makes	O
appear	O
fair	O
and	O
young	O
to	O
admiration	O
:	O
It	O
has	O
nothing	O
of	O
paint	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
doth	O
any	O
Person	O
know	O
the	O
Secret	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
from	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
bettle	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
pomatums	O
,	O
white	O
pots	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
compared	O
with	O
;	O
also	O
fine	O
Spanish	O
,	O
Woal	O
,	O
and	O
Portugal	O
Dishes	O
,	O
which	O
gives	O
a	O
glorious	O
Colour	O
to	O
the	O
Cheeks	O
and	O
Lips	O
,	O
a	O
powder	O
for	O
the	O
teeth	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
them	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
snow	O
;	O
she	O
bath	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Secret	O
to	O
prevent	O
Hair	O
from	O
falling	O
,	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
grow	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
;	O
she	O
alters	O
red	O
or	O
grey	O
hair	O
to	O
a	O
delicate	O
light	O
or	O
brown	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
;	O
she	O
bath	O
a	O
delicate	O
paste	O
to	O
and	O
makes	O
them	O
beautiful	O
;	O
the	O
bath	O
a	O
delicate	O
paste	O
to	O
whiten	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
pomatum	O
to	O
colour	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
prevent	O
their	O
chopping	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
cortain	O
and	O
infallible	O
core	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
without	O
drawing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
paig	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
;	O
she	O
cuts	O
Hair	O
very	O
fine	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
a	O
light	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
