TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
Octob	O
.	O
1719	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WARD	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
,	O
John	O
Roby	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
Several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Juror	O
's	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hasle	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fislder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Leepidge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Janes	B-pers
Max	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Farerell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamstar	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
,	O
Middlesx	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clift	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
Abrahan	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pashley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingr	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
Dariel	B-pers
Audrass	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Proccedings	O
were	O
as	O
followerth	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
by	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joshua	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Fish	O
street-hill	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
Water	O
at	O
Billinsgate	O
to-go	O
to	O
Deptford	O
,	O
one	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Friend	O
thereabouts	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
through	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
brought	O
him	O
there	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Green	O
Horn	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Noggin	O
of	O
Gin	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
held	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopt	O
his	O
Mouth	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
(	O
and	O
he	O
bit	O
her	O
Fingers	O
)	O
whilst	O
the	O
others	O
risted	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
fleet	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
purso	O
'd	O
'em	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Cellar	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Five	O
others	O
deposed	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took-her	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
whose	O
Fingers	O
he	O
bit	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
her	O
Fingers	O
were	O
bit	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
strange	O
Woman	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
trifling	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marvell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
in	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nathaneal	B-pers
Sirmas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
liked	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
they	O
mist	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
sought	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
describing	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Lock	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
on	O
,	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Marvell	O
the	O
Hangman	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Beadles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
Daughter	O
were	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Compter	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
if	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
by	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
several	O
having	O
bore	O
him	O
an	O
III	O
Will	O
for	O
performing	O
his	O
Office	O
in	O
cutting	O
off	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Derweutwaser	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
Honest	O
and	O
Industrious	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
declare	O
he	O
resolved	O
to	O
continue	O
so	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
be	O
would	O
rather	O
beg	O
than	O
steal	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
stealing	O
but	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
his	O
very	O
Character	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
sometimes	O
beg	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
relieved	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
any	O
Corporal	O
Punishment	O
they	O
should	O
think	O
fit	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
willingly	O
submit	O
to	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
a	O
Mile	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Furroughs	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Shoes	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pamp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
two	O
Daughters	O
,	O
one	O
about	O
13	O
the	O
other	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
officious	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
dress	O
and	O
undress	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Sabbath-Day	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Daughters	O
would	O
have	O
brought	O
their	O
Clothes	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
lay	O
'em	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Drawer	O
.	O
That	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Two	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
deposed	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
and	O
pawning	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
necessitous	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
and	O
designed	O
to	O
redeem	O
and	O
restore	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
Excuse	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
of	O
Alhalows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Guinea	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	O
Cannard	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Labourer	O
employed	O
in	O
the	B-place
Mint	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
carrying	O
a	O
Tray	O
of	O
Guineas	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
lock	O
up	O
.	O
In	O
turning	O
his	O
Hard	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
whip	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
weighing	O
the	O
Tray	O
again	O
mist	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Knees	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
within	O
the	O
Linings	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Press	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Guinea	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Knee	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Breeches	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
also	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
not	O
withstanding	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
whence	O
it	O
slipe	O
down	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
against	O
such	O
strong	O
Evidence	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
and	O
Amy	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
persuading	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
alias	O
Saunders	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyger	I-pers
to	O
give	O
false	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Jams	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Tryal	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
for	O
scandalous	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Parties	O
alike	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Faiths	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Boucy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
mist	O
his	O
Handker-chief	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cadlock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Ells	O
of	O
German	O
Holland	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
5	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
4	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
printed	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
do	O
business	O
about	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
at	O
Nights	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
Days	O
,	O
when	O
having	O
a	O
Maid	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Furdier	O
occasion	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
has	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
at	O
her	O
Linings	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
some	O
between	O
her	O
Bed	O
and	O
Bed-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
on	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Wright	B-pers
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Christs	O
Church	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
15l	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
for	O
any	O
who	O
should	O
bring	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Tankard	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
Warwicklaus	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
Apron	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
broken	O
Glass	O
and	O
old	O
Clothes	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
.	O
One	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Neal	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
White-Horse	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
all	O
in	O
Rags	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
had	O
new	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Clothes	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
her	O
Friends	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
and	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
Hole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Tankard	O
on	O
her	O
Apron	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Mescas	O
's	O
the	O
,	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
and	O
Joshua	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Botolph	B-place
Aldgate	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Stove	O
Great	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Male	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Joshua	O
Drake	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
against	O
Thomas	O
Cane	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
also	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rope	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
October	O
1717	O
.	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Dursly	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	O
Tippin	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
married	O
Richard	O
Bird	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
to	O
Ann	O
Dursley	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
1713	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Richard	O
Bird	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
Husband	O
.	O
By	O
other	O
Evidences	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
or	O
two	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
arrested	O
for	O
her	O
Debts	O
,	O
has	O
paid	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Rape	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
over	O
since	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
his	O
second	O
Wife	O
had	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
left	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
4	O
l.	O
Good	O
Will	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Mins	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
she	O
mov	O
'd	O
off	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
:	O
That	O
Moreland	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
)	O
had	O
stirr	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
marry	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Elizabeth	O
Rope	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Goods	O
or	O
Clothes	O
but	O
the	O
Red	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
Moreland	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Thought	O
or	O
Intention	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Wife	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
no	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Defrauding	O
Roger	B-pers
Brierly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
several	O
Yards	O
of	O
Suss	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fancock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Lead	O
Weights	O
for	O
sash	O
Windows	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Mistake	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
a	O
Sweet	O
Bottle	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sibbilla	B-pers
Tost	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Purse	O
(	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
contest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
all	O
her	O
Goods	O
again	O
except	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
swore	O
this	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bunter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
.	O
and	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Landlady	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
spare	O
;	O
however	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
lye	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
shewed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
something	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
wonder	O
why	O
she	O
staid	O
so	O
long	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sadly	O
Griped	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Sister	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Pot	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Holiday	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
Landlady	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
together	O
,	O
her	O
having	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
n	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
complaining	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
:	O
she	O
deposed	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Chamber-Pot	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Gown	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
lusty	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wade	O
,	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Boards	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
belived	O
it	O
came	O
before	O
it	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Hurt	O
upon	O
it	O
but	O
what	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Tongs	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
5	O
Weeks	O
before	O
her	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
Linnen	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
rid	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
10	O
Miles	O
in	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
occasion	O
her	O
coming	O
before	O
her	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
while	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
Evidences	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
cry	O
,	O
nor	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
Birth	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
grown	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
,	O
at	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fusee	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Pittols	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
90	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Boy	O
on	O
Show	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
ashore	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Fusee	O
and	O
Pistols	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blanchflower	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Bed-Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanker	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
two	O
Rooms	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
another	O
Lodging	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
Husband	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
lye	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
mist	O
her	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
pawned	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
'em	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Susannah	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Lace	O
Pinner	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	O
Slade	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Slade	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
7	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
mist	O
her	O
Goods	O
strangely	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Friends	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Friends	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
were	O
importun	O
'd	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
having	O
a	O
dread	O
upon	O
him	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
Home	O
tho	O
'	O
late	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
her	O
Husband	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
at	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
for	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
Weeks	O
after	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Service	O
about	O
14	O
Doors	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
they	O
kept	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
prosecution	O
against	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
prostitute	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
prison	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
them	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
places	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbs	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
within	O
14	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
3	O
Weeks	O
and	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
her	O
Service	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
ruined	O
her	O
self	O
by	O
Marrying	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
but	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
kept	O
a	O
Disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
his	O
Daughter	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
unless	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
her	O
Mistress	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Her	O
Master	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
contradict	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Repeating	O
Watch	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
a	O
plain	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
18	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
value	O
90	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Katharine	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
sight	O
by	O
a	O
violent	O
Fever	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Dark	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
for	O
his	O
Diversion	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
tell	O
pleasent	O
Stories	O
of	O
his	O
Travels	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Nights	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
Door	O
shut	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
Chamber	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
Keys	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Pockets	O
were	O
pickt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Keys	O
,	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Finch	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
kept	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Locks	O
,	O
for	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
his	O
Portmanteau	O
too	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
concluded	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
and	O
remembering	O
his	O
Stories	O
of	O
his	O
Travels	O
,	O
concluded	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Land	O
with	O
his	O
Boory	O
;	O
wherefore	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Hungerford	O
Stairs	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
enquired	O
among	O
the	O
Watermen	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
most	O
noted	O
Stairs	O
be	O
past	O
along	O
,	O
describing	O
and	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
arrived	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
hearing	O
of	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
luck	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
Waterman	O
who	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
Billinsgate	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
in	O
his	O
Passage	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
journey	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
from	O
chelensford	O
to	O
Harwich	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
Paquet-Boat	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
got	O
this	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
several	O
Obstacles	O
and	O
Disappointments	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
made	O
such	O
Expedition	O
in	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Hanwich	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Noble	B-pers
Rance	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Northolt	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Mantle	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Women	O
's	O
Waistcoats	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
Child	O
's	O
Waistcoat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
for	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Church	B-place
of	I-place
Northolt	I-place
,	O
and	O
to	O
Steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chanels	O
thereof	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
broke	O
a	O
Pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
House	O
theneat	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stones	O
where	O
the	O
Bars	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guinea	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
deals	O
in	O
Coals	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
some	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
about	O
the	O
7	B-place
Dials	I-place
enquired	O
his	O
Way	O
into	O
Halbourn	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
told	O
him	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
feel	O
his	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Attempts	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
dived	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
possitive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
'em	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
into	O
,	O
pretended	O
one	O
was	O
Sick	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Brittan	O
's	O
in	O
Nov	O
Lane	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
Brittan	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
compound	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
arrested	O
Bristols	O
for	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
out	O
of	O
Revenge	O
had	O
Stir	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
29	O
yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
convited	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
for	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Same	O
)	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
1717	O
.	O
It	O
plainly	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
a	O
Dyer	O
in	O
to	O
his	O
Glass	O
.	O
Pritchards	O
House	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
piece	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Joseph	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pritchards	O
Servant	O
had	O
stolen	O
great	O
many	O
pieces	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
where	O
white	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
that	O
any	O
bad	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
ready	O
Money	O
within	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Servant	O
denyed	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
never	O
took	O
in	O
white	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
produced	O
his	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
,	O
their	O
Servant	O
should	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
should	O
bring	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
notice	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	O
James	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
it	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
His	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
William	O
Jones	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
in	O
Newzate	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
fetcht	O
the	O
Piece	O
down	O
very	O
readily	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
freely	O
to	O
search	O
:	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
regularly	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
William	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
Money	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
no	O
prosecution	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
had	O
been	O
undyed	O
Goods	O
sold	O
by	O
a	O
Hotpresser	O
.	O
That	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
found	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Goods	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
who	O
changed	O
him	O
with	O
3	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pieces	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
any	O
brought	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
Others	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
careful	O
in	O
taking	O
in	O
pawns	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
persons	O
whom	O
he	O
question	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
stopt	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
Advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Gazatte	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
Owner	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sidwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Negoes	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Pall	B-place
Mall	I-place
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wig	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pinnor	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Seal	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
it	O
being	O
defaced	O
,	O
he	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
certain	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Maker	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pinnor	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
Wig	O
or	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinnor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
but	O
suspecting	O
by	O
the	O
price	O
set	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
produce	O
some	O
to	O
justifie	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
again	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
an	O
Answer	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Wig	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Beanhood	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Trouble	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
porter	O
and	O
goes	O
of	O
Erranes	O
for	O
my	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Track	O
of	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
a	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Drawn	O
Sward	O
under	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Death	O
14	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee	B-place
house	I-place
(	O
where	O
they	O
also	O
sold	O
Wine	O
)	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
had	O
Cap	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
that	O
Major	O
Thompson	O
gave	O
(	O
the	O
Landlady	O
)	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
to	O
engage	O
him	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Dies	O
of	O
the	O
Bacman	O
and	O
together	O
,	O
till	O
Mrs.	O
Carser	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
did	O
not	O
suffer	O
any	O
Gaming	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
without	O
any	O
Prevention	O
Struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
Blows	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
draw	O
his	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
got	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
run	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
through	O
the	O
Coat	O
other	O
into	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retired	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
even	O
till	O
his	O
Back	O
touch	O
'd	O
the	O
Window	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
upon	O
his	O
Several	O
Gentlemen	O
the	O
Bench	O
and	O
others	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
peaceable	O
Department	O
and	O
Quiet	O
Temper	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
waching	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
550	O
dozen	O
of	O
Leather	O
Soles	O
for	O
shoes	O
value	O
150	O
l.	O
30	O
dozen	O
Calve	O
skins	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sections	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
pleading	O
Guilty	O
)	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Laugthorse	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stole	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Harbouring	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Clarke	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Goods	O
continually	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
himself	O
sink	O
in	O
the	O
Word	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
almost	O
ruined	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
his	O
servants	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Servants	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Information	O
that	O
one	O
Mary	O
Clark	O
:	O
(	O
convicted	O
last	O
Settings	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Prosector	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
small	O
parc	O
is	O
of	O
Leather	O
for	O
the	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
several	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
rake	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
fill	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
low	O
Rate	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
16	O
l.	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Justice	O
wanted	O
him	O
his	O
Warrant	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
there	O
.	O
it	O
appeares	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Journemen	O
and	O
Apprentices	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	O
Clarks	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Children	O
Shoes	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
for	O
them	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
saying	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
bought	O
4	O
l.	O
worth	O
,	O
and-she	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Servents	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Mary	O
must	O
ruin	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
sold	O
that	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
s.	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
often	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Mistress	O
that	O
the	O
4	O
l.	O
worth	O
lasted	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
Mary	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
wards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
Parlour	O
:	O
that	O
Mary	O
brought	O
Soles	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Skins	O
in	O
a	O
Hand-basket	O
or	O
her	O
Apron	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
weat	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
without	O
asking	O
any	O
Questions	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
The	O
Soles	O
for	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Leather	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
having	O
his	O
Mark	O
on	O
the	O
.	O
Mary	O
Clarke	O
's	O
Conviction	O
by	O
pleading	O
Guilty	O
last	O
Sections	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
the	O
bought	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	O
Clarke	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
those	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
bstole	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
invalidate	O
tha	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
temperit	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
till	O
the	O
Tryal	O
should	O
be	O
over	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
calied	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
some	O
12	O
other	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
Honest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sherwill	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
and	O
3	O
Aprons	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
had	O
washt	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
hung	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
Yard	O
to	O
dry	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
late	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
wet	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
cry	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
;	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Prisioner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
John	O
Tirkup	O
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
Giles	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
Three	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
)	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
coming	O
form	O
Edger	O
to	O
London	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Nights	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
within	B-place
10	I-place
Yards	I-place
of	I-place
Tyburn	I-place
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Trickup	O
who	O
tyed	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
put	O
down	O
his	O
Breaches	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
serve	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Toll	O
Gate	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Bridle	O
off	O
the	O
Mere	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
loose	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
long	O
before	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
between	O
Syburn	O
and	O
Paddington	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
of	O
Horte	O
Hair	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
ty	O
d	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Paddington	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
loosed	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
Blackman	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
unty	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
so	O
right	O
that	O
his	O
Hands	O
swell	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sorc	O
'd	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Cerd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Landlord	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
has	O
will	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Castle	O
street	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
come	O
in	O
before	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
themselves	O
well	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Canserioury	O
Coach	O
his	O
Landlord	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
about	O
goods	O
being	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
bound	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
South	B-place
Mins	I-place
,	O
was	O
in	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Geese	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
provd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Drenford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
.	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicated	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Falthory	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
in	O
the	O
Basket	O
our	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
met	O
by	O
another	O
,	O
sat	O
there	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
takes	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Winifred	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Beating	O
and	O
Wounding	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	O
Thomas	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Larrock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
shift	O
the	O
Bed	O
mist	O
the	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Smock	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
Another	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
charged	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
Spight	O
she	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Srratagem	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
who	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
deposed	O
.	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
would	O
Prosecute	O
his	O
Lodger	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
trisling	O
matter	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
laid	O
a	O
Child	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
her	O
Transported	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
too	O
.	O
He	O
deposed	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
who	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
stole	O
the	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Several	O
appeared	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
Honest	O
Industries	O
Person	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
Opportunities	O
of	O
being	O
otherwise	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
always	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Johanna	B-pers
Behoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Whitesone	I-pers
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
Whitesone	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
something	O
fall	O
like	O
a	O
Spoon	O
over	O
Head	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
opened	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
her	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
nothing	O
was	O
taken	O
or	O
removed	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mabus	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
driving	O
three	O
Horses	O
fastned	O
to	O
a	O
Cart	O
loaded	O
with	O
Bricks	O
,	O
the	O
Fore	O
Horse	O
cast	O
the	O
Child	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
off	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
giving	O
it	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Last	O
side	O
thereof	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Lydeas	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
Dyal	O
in	O
Goswell-street	B-place
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Swan	B-place
Alley	I-place
End	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
crossing	O
the	O
Road	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Fore	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
of	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
neither	O
make	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hear	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
sad	O
Misfortune	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
doing	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jumpt	O
off	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
dead	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bricks	O
not	O
lying	O
right	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
his	O
Horses	O
and	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
shafe	O
to	O
place	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horses	O
went	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
put	O
on	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
careful	O
,	O
pains	O
taking	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Butt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Sarah	O
Talmash	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
7	B-place
Dials	I-place
;	O
that	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
by	O
force	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Back	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
proposed	O
to	O
lay	O
an	O
obscene	O
Wager	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
talked	O
very	O
lewdly	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
such	O
filthy	O
Actions	O
as	O
are	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
mention	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
this	O
would	O
not	O
draw	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
unmercifully	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Murther	O
being	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Talmosb	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
then	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Persons	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
after	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meals	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hen	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Kenelon	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
Hen	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Onslow	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Burras	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
Marry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Michael	O
Connor	O
to	O
Dorcas	O
Burras	O
at	O
Drummond	B-place
Parish	I-place
in	O
Ireland	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
1714	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
3	O
Weeks	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
mean	O
Character	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
Marrying	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Bride	O
Dweas	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
first	O
Wife	O
Dorcas	O
in	O
Custody	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirmed	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Mary	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
400	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Captain	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
300	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
more	O
after	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Death	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
Courted	O
her	O
about	O
10	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Married	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Disparagement	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
Tradesmans	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
by	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
Guineas	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Pockets	O
would	O
not	O
hold	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
other	O
Wife	O
than	O
Mary	O
Onslow	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
their	O
Marriage	O
privated	O
(	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Brothers	O
)	O
till	O
a	O
Law-suit	O
between	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
them	O
should	O
be	O
over	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
first	O
Marriage	O
being	O
full	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hanks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goose	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Gander	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hepkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sturgran	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
35	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Eden	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Staff	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
a	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
Following	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
One	O
Whitworth	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Candles	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Arlington	O
Street	O
in	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
high	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
twice	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
stagger	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
not	O
drawn	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
third	O
Blow	O
,	O
which	O
fetch	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Heads	O
and	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
once	O
after	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Cellar	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Words	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
presently	O
but	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
going	O
Home	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Moon-Light	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Blow	O
,	O
then	O
two	O
more	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
heard	O
more	O
Blows	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lookt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lye	O
cross	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
eight	O
Foot	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
stab	O
me	O
!	O
get	O
up	O
you	O
Dog	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
your	O
Braius	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carryed	O
him	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Dover	O
Street	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Voice	O
cry	O
Down	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
stick	O
me	O
?	O
It	O
was	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Voice	O
who	O
stood	O
some	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
and	O
broke	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
hung	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threatened	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
draw	O
it	O
in	O
he	O
would	O
break	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
abused	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
.	O
John	O
Cook	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
past	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
Good	O
Watchman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
and	O
not	O
troublesome	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Westbreek	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
St.	O
Jame	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
dangerous	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
depend	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
Judgement	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
consult	O
what	O
was	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
to	O
proceed	O
to	O
the	O
Trepan	O
;	O
but't	O
was	O
concluded	O
to	O
try	O
one	O
Medicine	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Hopes	O
of	O
some	O
Success	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
sensible	O
tho	O
'	O
Speechless	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
grew	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Rest	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
Affairs	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gheekir	O
now	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
preserve	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
open	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
a	O
Contusion	O
and	O
small	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
congealed	O
Blood	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
were	O
sufficient	O
to	O
kill	O
any	O
Man	O
.	O
Others	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
advised	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
times	O
enough	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Others	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
being	O
Speechless	O
,	O
the	O
forcing	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Round-house	O
and	O
his	O
Leg	O
lying	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Beadle	O
of	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Robberies	O
having	O
been	O
committed	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
their	O
Duty	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
walk	O
from	O
11	O
to	O
4	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
performing	O
his	O
Duty	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
Country	O
People	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
quiet	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
pass	O
civilly	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
.	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
quite	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
threatning	O
to	O
stick	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
be	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
But	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
diligent	O
in	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
seducing	O
and	O
inciting	O
John	O
Westfold	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
of	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Silk	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
lose	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
his	O
Customers	O
treatning	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
their	O
Silk	O
always	O
wanted	O
Weight	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
he	O
detected	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
John	B-pers
Westfold	I-pers
,	O
who	O
at	O
first	O
made	O
several	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
close	O
questioned	O
he	O
confest	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seduced	O
by	O
Saunders	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
that	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
20	O
d.	O
John	O
Westfold	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
set	O
him	O
to	O
scaning	O
he	O
sold	O
his	O
first	O
Ends	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sounders	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
Rubbish	O
;	O
sent	O
her	O
Servant	O
out	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
shewed	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
might	O
cut	O
the	O
Scanes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
receive	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
2	O
Ounces	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
brought	O
so	O
little	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
carryed	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Ounces	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
s6	O
d.	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquaintted	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
his	O
Master	O
caught	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Ounce	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
whereas	O
the	O
proper	O
Ends	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
sold	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
he	O
sold	O
in	O
all	O
about	O
3	O
pound	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
persons	O
of	O
Worth	O
who	O
appeared	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
some	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
20	O
and	O
some	O
30	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
above	O
70	O
Year	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Memory	O
much	O
impalr	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lest	O
off	O
her	O
Business	O
to	O
her	O
Daughter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Moor	O
alias	O
Murray	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sidwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tacker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Duttom	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Devies	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
.	O
Note	O
,	O
The	O
Six	O
last	O
were	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
small	O
Felonies	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Discharged	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
14.	O
William	B-pers
Marwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tadlock	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Joshna	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blanchflower	I-pers
,	O
Noble	B-pers
Rance	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Clarka	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	O
Lownon	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Low	O
and	O
Mary	O
Yates	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
Elizabeth	O
Low	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Tates	O
Not	O
Quick	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	O
Parker	O
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve-Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
geat	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
sine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bd	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psaltody	O
.	O
The	O
Deont	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
,	O
with	O
select	O
porrions	O
of	O
the	O
psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Roles	O
for	O
ing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Ears	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
shown	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
what	O
psalms	O
and	O
ymm	O
are	O
proper	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hop	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sev	O
told	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
dy	O
and	O
Mr.	O
tase	O
.	O
And	O
Directors	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
psalms	O
on	O
Occ	O
.	O
B.S	O
.	O
Sbeusan	O
;	O
and	O
Recommended	O
by	O
p.	O
,	O
D.	O
w	O
ner	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Fouro	O
Edition	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Five	O
Tunes	O
,	O
containing	O
Their	O
Cansan	O
,	O
Medim	O
and	O
Bassan	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
farmer	O
Editions	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
s.	O
Alip	O
;	O
s	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflections	O
,	O
improved	O
by	O
Sir	O
Rozer	O
L	O
'	O
E	O
mge	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
.	O
with	O
Cots	O
curiously	O
cogr	O
on	O
Copper	O
Pates	O
.	O
Very	O
&	O
Direct	O
and	O
yound	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
cafie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
cow	O
taught	O
and	O
practis'ed	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
on	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
Briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illaftrated	O
with	O
such	O
tamiliar	O
Examples	O
as	O
way	O
suit	O
the	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
succined	O
Treate	O
if	O
Deci	O
Fre	O
with	O
Complex	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extent	O
it	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
this	O
Naw	O
.	O
the	O
fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Cap	O
land	O
,	O
P	O
ice	O
hound	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximam	O
in	O
Minimum	O
:	O
O.	O
Mr.	O
Jermi	O
b	O
Rib	O
's	O
pens	O
Dextec	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
SHORT-HAND	O
to	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
:	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawness	O
and	O
other	O
who	O
take	O
Trya	O
's	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Ne	O
dune	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Betley	O
The	O
whole	O
g	O
'd	O
Trucy	O
Copper	O
lates	O
Pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
to	O
E	O
luries	O
:	O
Setting	O
serth	O
their	O
Antiquire	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
and	O
Statures	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
person	O
a	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Ancor	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
R	O
gol	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackave	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
made	O
,	O
p	O
5	O
th	O
'd	O
and	O
Deciar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
direct	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	O
Marshal	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Ble	O
in	O
Street	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Coat	O
Hospital	O
Gate	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Martin	O
Luther	O
's	O
and	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Catvin	O
's	O
Opinion	O
coacering	O
the	O
Trinity	O
:	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
price	O
6	O
d.	O
2.	O
and	O
Impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Prote	O
,	O
its	O
present	O
State	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Omen	O
a	O
Edit	O
Price	O
6	O
l.	O
3	O
.	O
Child	O
's	O
Delight	O
,	O
or	O
Instructions	O
Children	O
and	O
Youth	O
,	O
adotned	O
with	O
Copper	O
Cops	O
,	O
to	O
Read	O
,	O
and	O
Cast	O
compts	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
interpreting	O
hard	O
Wores	O
and	O
Names	O
,	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Keecb	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
creat	O
Golpe	O
Grace	O
or	O
Faith	O
.	O
being	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
sever	O
i	O
sermons	O
on	O
John	O
17	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
8.	O
prce	O
6	O
d.	O
5.	O
brief	O
D	O
and	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
Do	O
of	O
the	O
Tr	O
:	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
and	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
Christ	O
.	O
by	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Cment	O
.	O
The	O
seventh	O
:	O
dation	O
,	O
price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Bat	O
all	O
personss	O
desirous	O
to	O
promoted	O
so	O
useful	O
a	O
Bood	O
as	O
this	O
the	O
Dect	O
ine	O
of	O
the	O
Trimty	O
,	O
by	O
givng	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
may	O
them	O
10	O
s	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Bound	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Golpel-Grunds	O
and	O
Evidences	O
of	O
the	O
Faith	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Elect	O
;	O
left	O
in	O
manuscript	O
for	O
his	O
Wafo	O
's	O
Meditations	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Owen	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
price	O
B	O
5	O
s.	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
best	O
Mi	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Melody	O
of	O
Sin	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
Spiritual	O
Hy	O
ns	O
on	O
divers	O
Occasions	O
.	O
By	O
Mr	O
Wright	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
spirit	O
of	O
the	O
Marturs	O
revived	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
Passages	O
and	O
living	O
Tekimoaics	O
of	O
the	O
Cherch	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
her	O
Faithful	O
Manv	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Ages	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
4	O
price	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
9	O
.	O
A	O
Pradical	O
Dilcourse	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Sovereignty	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
Material	O
E.	O
The	O
7th	O
Edition	O
.	O
All	O
sold	O
as	O
above	O
at	O
the	O
Biole	O
in	O
New	O
-	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
supplyed	O
with	O
the	O
best	O
Japan	O
lok	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
into	O
that	O
will	O
not	O
change	O
on	O
turn	O
Yellow	O
,	O
as	O
other	O
lak	O
will	O
do	O
.	O
Likewise	O
Ro	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Park	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Daniei	O
Pratc	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
Against	O
York	O
Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
A	O
Baoqott	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
,	O
coassting	O
of	O
Nine	O
N	O
the	O
Friend	O
.	O
The	O
prodigal	O
Reclamed	O
.	O
the	O
Husband	O
,	O
or	O
Virginity	O
te	O
ed	O
.	O
The	O
Friendly	O
Cheat	O
.	O
The	O
Unfortunate	O
Lover	O
.	O
Jealousie	O
with	O
a	O
Couse	O
.	O
The	O
Cruel	O
Mother	O
.	O
The	O
Cucko	O
'd	O
turn	O
'd	O
Consellor	O
.	O
The	O
B	O
cc	O
andlians	O
;	O
intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
many	O
Pleasent	O
and	O
Delightl	O
and	O
stence	O
.	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Editio	O
.	O
The	O
Universal	O
Jetter	O
:	O
O	O
,	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Book	O
of	O
Containing	O
A	O
pleasant	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Jetts	O
,	O
Irish	O
Jetts	O
,	O
Oxford	O
Jetts	O
,	O
Combridges	O
jetts	O
,	O
Coffee-House	O
jetts	O
,	O
Stories	O
,	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
in	O
an	O
Up	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
A	O
between	O
the	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
.	O
Female	O
Policy	O
decided	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
a	O
Designing	O
Woman	O
laid	O
open	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Jama	O
:	O
Treating	O
or	O
Allotments	O
,	O
ocntiancy	O
,	O
Love	O
,	O
Resenge	O
,	O
price	O
and	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
Pleasant	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Discourse	O
in	O
defence	O
Married	O
Men	O
,	O
against	O
pe	O
,	O
scolding	O
Wa	O
;	O
several	O
examples	O
the	O
mitchets	O
and	O
have	O
their	O
lu	O
and	O
2.	O
a	O
virtuous	O
,	O
or	O
;	O
to	O
discription	O
of	O
s	O
Widow	O
,	O
Accomp	O
Ladies	O
Delight	O
,	O
n	O
resorting	O
,	O
phy	O
,	O
and	O
Cont	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
P	O
and	O
c	O
dying	O
and	O
flowers	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
and	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
co	O
;	O
in	O
and	O
C	O
;	O
a	O
new	O
recipts	O
releting	O
to	O
the	O
lair	O
Sex	O
,	O
they	O
with	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
Guide	O
,	O
or	O
Directions	O
for	O
Fowl	O
,	O
and	O
better	O
the	O
newest	O
at	O
the	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
making	O
&	O
The	O
emale	O
lad	O
rivers	O
5.	O
the	O
Complex	O
of	O
all	O
of	O
and	O
Howers	O
.	O
The	O
enlarg	O
'd	O
All	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hystercial	O
and	O
Hypocondrieck	O
D	O
stempers	O
,	O
WHich	O
variously	O
after	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
and	O
de	O
nal	O
Apprehentions	O
;	O
Fantings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirts	O
,	O
great	O
Horries	O
,	O
and	O
di	O
ment	O
(	O
itle	O
undcttood	O
and	O
feld	O
on	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
)	O
also	O
Paios	O
and	O
Giddinels	O
of	O
teh	O
Head	O
;	O
Ris	O
ogs	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sick	O
F	O
,	O
Trembligs	O
,	O
Oppre	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
o	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
cauled	O
by	O
Various	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
6	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Phy	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
Sun	O
and	O
to	O
physician	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
than	O
,	O
50	O
Years	O
successful	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
Deplotable	O
Ca	O
)	O
he	O
also	O
Cures	O
all	O
Kins	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
Range	O
and	O
violnc	O
(	O
if	O
cerale	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
win	O
justly	O
inform	O
you	O
:	O
living	O
at	O
No	O
1.	O
in	O
Bary-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Katberines	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
where	O
there	O
that	O
have	O
occation	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letrece	O
and	O
they	O
be	O
ipeedily	O
answered	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
it	O
de	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Iith	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
stiching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necesity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
else	O
of	O
,	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
A	O
Downing	O
Chy	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Bell	O
in	O
George	O
Coness	O
in	O
St.	O
Johns	O
Le	O
by	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
near	O
West	O
field	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
.	O
she	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
S-Grafs	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
price	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellence	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
ectb	O
and	O
dearing	O
them	O
the	O
Scurry	O
,	O
Pricela	O
s.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
The	O
practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Conftiuctions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salieations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-	O
aly	O
,	O
The	O
New	O
system	O
of	O
the	O
GOU	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Automical	O
Observation	O
and	O
Experience	O
3ly	O
,	O
ARational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
ature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
perfirm	O
after	O
former	O
Cure	O
,	O
Over-trainings	O
,	O
SelfA	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriagea	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Borrid	O
Nacure	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
Miserable	O
Conferences	O
of	O
Sel-Abufes	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Boods	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Edition	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toy	O
shop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Chadles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerfond-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Stand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs-Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchang-gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
LONDON	O
Printed	O
for	O
J	O
phillips	O
,	O
by	O
M.	O
Jemour	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulure	O
's	O
Back-Gate	O
in	O
Gilt-Spur-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Wrick	O
Lane	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisement	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
