TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th,9th	O
,	O
and	O
11th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April,1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Prass	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Littlefield	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Catchmead	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehorn	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mauld	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Surrup	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Bavan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kindrick	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beatnasse	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prator	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Dishes,36	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
Pot,2	O
Brass	O
Stew-pans	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
Mead	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
after	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
owned	O
he	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
so	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
then	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Pewter	O
was	O
melted	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pot	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
and	O
buy	O
it	O
out-right	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Newman	O
(	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
)	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Winsmore	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Quartern	O
Pot,3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Bags	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Winsmore	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
Joyners	O
Work	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
about	O
6	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
and	O
conceal	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Back	O
House	O
till	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Quartern	O
Pot	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Lid	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Pawn-broker	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burcher	I-pers
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
Number	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
Long-Lane	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
wou	O
'd	O
scrape	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Boot	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
Room	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
Red-Cross-Street	B-place
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Crow	O
'd	O
about	O
two	O
Women	O
that	O
were	O
fighting	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
feeling	O
her	O
Hand	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
:	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
deposed	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
.	O
Night-walker	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
'd	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
or	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
together	O
the	O
drinking	O
of	O
one	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
offering	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
Reputation	O
stained	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sarsenet	O
value	O
29	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Dyehouse	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
deals	O
in	O
Mercery	O
Wares	O
.	O
and	O
instructed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
sell	O
Goods	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
but	O
she'took	O
the	O
Sarsnet	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Customers	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
she	O
could	O
buy	O
Goods	O
cheaper	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
3	O
Years	O
to	O
serve	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indictcted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
Devil	B-place
Tavern	I-place
at	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
,	O
and	O
and	O
midling	O
his	O
Goods	O
went	O
the	O
25th	O
to	O
Goldsmiths	O
Hall	O
and	O
publish	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
describing	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
a	O
Silver-Smith	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Forks	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Fork	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
9	O
s.10	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
4	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
accordingly	O
and	O
brought	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
Forks	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
)	O
having	O
then	O
recived	O
the	O
afore	O
said	O
Advertisement	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fork	O
and	O
Spoons	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Fork	O
only	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
Old	O
Acquaintance	O
at	O
the	O
Exchange	O
very	O
Gentleelly	O
drest	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Dorchester	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Fork	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
But	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Person	O
nor	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Duppa	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Spoons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Spoons	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Defence	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattons	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Rasors	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Hone	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
and	O
a	O
Rasor-Case	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lyon	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
speak	O
:	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Christie	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
scrap	O
'd	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Talk	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
off	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Family	O
wanted	O
Bread	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Christie	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
must	O
try	O
them	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
considering	O
his	O
Necessity	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
too	O
little	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Gervas	B-pers
Northam	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Flatt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Old	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
alias	O
Dean	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
by	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Brookhouse	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
for	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
another	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Hanckerchief	O
between	O
his	O
Legs	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Batchet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
street	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch,2	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
last	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
delivering	O
her	O
key	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
her	O
Maid	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Tea	O
Canister	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Desk	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Desk	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
Desk	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Cart-knife	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
knowing	O
there	O
were	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Cannister	O
her	O
self	O
for	O
fear	O
any	O
thing	O
should	O
be	O
missing	O
,	O
therefore	O
gave	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
out	O
the	O
Cannister	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Watches	O
and	O
Spoon	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Cowly	I-pers
(	O
who	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
)	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Mistress	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Mistress	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Darbam	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Desk	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
c	O
being	O
her	O
Lodging	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
very	O
plain	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
were	O
Partners	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
out	O
Money	O
in	O
small	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
in	O
Pawns	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Manager	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
several	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
borrow	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
it	O
without	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Watches	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Crony	O
,	O
had	O
them	O
and	O
a	O
General	O
Release	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
An	O
Officer	O
who	O
had	O
arrested	O
Elizabeth	O
Sutton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
for	O
security	O
for	O
her	O
forth-coming	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
from	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
to	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
The	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
was	O
like	O
wife	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dated	O
the	O
4th	O
if	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
stole	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
Mrs	O
Hatchet	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
,	O
who	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
turbulently	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Walbrook	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Horse	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Lady	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Mayer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Coachman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lame	O
with	O
a	O
Nail	O
in	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
a	O
Farrier	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
shoe	O
and	O
cur	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Hurt	O
received	O
by	O
the	O
Nail	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Heels	O
being	O
greasy	O
and	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
carryed	O
him	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
till	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
well	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Farrier	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Lady	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
recover	O
,	O
and	O
urg	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
fell	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Farrier	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Lady	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
for	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Crown	O
more	O
if	O
it	O
did	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Butler	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
with	O
its	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
hire	O
Men	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Collar-maker	O
at	O
Cierkenwell	O
;	O
whereupon	O
his	O
Lady	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
inquire	O
into	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
very	O
diligently	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
deposed	O
the	O
Farrier	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
five	O
whereof	O
he	O
paid	O
in	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
calling	O
upon	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Nawgate	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
going	O
with	O
his	O
Lady	O
to	O
Highgate	O
the	O
Horse	O
got	O
a	O
Nail	O
in	O
his	O
Foot	O
and	O
was	O
same	O
,	O
whereupon	O
his	O
Lady	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
Penny-worth	O
of	O
Oil	O
of	O
Turpentine	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Farrier	O
,	O
who	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Shoe	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Lady	O
forbid	O
the	O
Farrier	O
dressing	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
for	O
10.s	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
him	O
to	O
Farrier	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Hounds	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
perswaded	O
the	O
Farrier	O
to	O
make	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Lady	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
she	O
demanded	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Lady	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
Keeping	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
he	O
told	O
it	O
afterward	O
for	O
4l	O
.	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
Brick-Cart	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
cost	O
him	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Keeping	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
18	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
pound	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
15	O
d.	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
more	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
thinking	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Drink	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
back	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Cover	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Stands	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Coat	O
tuckt	O
up	O
taking	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
tuckt	O
up	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
strange	O
rate	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
run	O
out	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
also	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
with	O
her	O
Money	O
(	O
about	O
18	O
d.	O
)	O
loose	O
amongst	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
wildly	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
several	O
mad	O
Actions	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
persons	O
in	O
Court	O
who	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
one	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
19	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
run	O
mad	O
when	O
life	O
lay	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
first	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
found	O
since	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
had	O
intervals	O
of	O
Sense	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sometimes	O
raving	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
other	O
times	O
Melanecholy	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Horse	O
and	O
appeared	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
Another	O
than	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
with	O
her	O
confirmed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Lunatick	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
dance	O
naked	O
in-the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
who	O
kept	O
her	O
children	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
for	O
killing	O
her	O
two	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
forgoing	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
Collonel	O
Pagets	O
Name	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
deceive	O
Mr.	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
cheat	O
him	O
of	O
21	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
and	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
18th	O
or	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
the	O
South	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Needham	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
some	O
Hollands	O
and	O
Muslin	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Trunk-makers	O
near	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Needham	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Nandoe	O
's	O
Coffee	O
house	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
from	O
a	O
handsome	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
tye	O
Wig	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Trick	O
,	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Needbam	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
tell	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
back	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
the	O
Message	O
Mr.	O
Needbam	O
had	O
sent	O
,	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
for	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Bills	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Needbam	O
for	O
the	O
Letter	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
wrote	O
another	O
Letter	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Needbam	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
give	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Needbam	O
deposed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Porter	O
delivered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
relating	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
about	O
the	O
Letter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Needbam	O
's	O
Servant	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
were	O
both	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Collonel	O
Paget	O
deposed	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Servant	O
he	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Collonel	O
Paget	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
interested	O
him	O
with	O
500	O
l.	O
but	O
the	O
Col	O
contradicted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
others	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
spoke	O
respectfully	O
of	O
Col.	O
Paget	B-pers
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
with	O
a	O
more	O
(	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
)	O
and	O
itaid	O
there	O
from	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Noon	O
till	O
near	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
the	O
Day	O
more	O
Particularly	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
writting	O
a	O
Letter	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
the	O
Letter	O
away	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
burnt	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
40	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
remain	O
their	O
till	O
his	O
Fine	O
is	O
paid	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adson	I-pers
alias	O
Addison	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plumridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
the	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
go	O
from	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
knock	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
A	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Shop	O
she	O
bolted	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Ship-mate	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
Brandy	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
and	O
a	O
Lamp	O
with	O
2	O
Lights	O
burning	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
gone	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
shop	O
for	O
Geneva	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
any	O
forcing	O
the	O
Bolt	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Dagenham	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Dolt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
Thread	O
some	O
Tape	O
,	O
a	O
Thimble	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pigs	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Servants	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Huggat	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Hogs	O
for	O
Rent	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
driving	O
them	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Joyce	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
mist	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
of	O
him	O
found	O
him	O
bid	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
hid	O
between	O
two	O
Boards	O
bard	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Feum	I-pers
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
set	O
down	O
his	O
Fair	O
in	O
Hand-Alley	B-place
near	O
Grays-in-Lane	B-place
and	O
that	O
afterward	O
the	O
Seats	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowron	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Boy	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Seats	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach-man	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
Parple	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
Seat	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
the	O
Father	O
ran	O
away	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fenn	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Coach-Seats	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Furbelow	O
'd	O
Scarf	O
,	O
Lace	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
Mrs.	O
Goddard	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Stepney	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
now	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
clear	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
alias	O
Fletcher	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chints	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Tinkler	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
and	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
lay	O
longer	O
a	O
Bed	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
for	O
her	O
Maid	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Maid	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
she	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
her	O
great	O
surprise	O
found	O
that	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
under	O
Lock	O
and	O
key	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
lockt	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
the	O
Chints	O
Gown	O
,	O
Riding-hood	O
and	O
lac	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
also	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
alias	O
Staples	B-pers
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
alias	O
Staples	O
and	O
Katherine	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
Feather	O
Pillow	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
them	O
ready	O
furnisht	O
by	O
the	O
Week	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
paid	O
their	O
Rent	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
asking	O
for	O
clean	O
Linnen	O
they	O
suspected'em	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
mist	O
the	O
Sheets	O
and	O
Pillow	O
.	O
Phebe	B-pers
Pomroy	I-pers
deposed	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
William	O
Lucas	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
arrested	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
his	O
Wife	O
might	O
Pawn	O
them	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
clear	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
Pleaded	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
her	O
Landlord	O
to	O
clear	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
lend	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
raise	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Goods	O
they	O
lay	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Martins	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
11	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Peregrine	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Peregrine	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
George	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
George	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
3	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
30	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Wig	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
George	O
declared	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
now	O
give	O
above	O
35	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
now	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
some	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
his	O
Excuse	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Tyon	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rasor	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
4	O
Nights	O
,	O
then	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
mist	O
when	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
:	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
saying	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
.	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
confess	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
deposed	O
she	O
hung	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
that	O
missing	O
of	O
them	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
oustop	O
Thief	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
she	O
saw	O
drop	O
them	O
.	O
Her	O
Daughter	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
being	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bed	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
searching	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Augustine	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
her	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
the	O
Princess	O
of	O
Wales	O
,	O
spitting	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
no	O
Princess	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
make	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Princess	O
of	O
a	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Wife	O
;	O
King	O
George	O
is	O
an	O
Usurper	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
no	O
business	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Somerset-House	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
several	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
Cursing	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
God	O
Curse	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
replyed	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
King	O
George	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
,	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
rather	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
his	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
she	O
'd	O
stick	O
him	O
with	O
that	O
Knife	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
King	O
George	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
she	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
denyal	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
of	O
St.Jame	B-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vokins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
going	O
out	O
in	O
house	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stocking	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
before	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
necessary	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
mistook	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
(	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
simple	O
Fellow	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
value	O
7	O
s.out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.Walker	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
pleased	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
a	O
second	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
but	O
none	O
were	O
large	O
enough	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
3	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
of	O
St.Leonard	B-place
Shoreditch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
boyling	O
Pot	O
,	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Nolton	I-pers
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
him	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
Plate	O
with	O
John	O
Nolton	O
writ	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Porridge-Pot	O
he	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
One	O
Plate	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nolton	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
Patterns	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
match	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
match	O
one	O
pair	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Mistress	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
advising	O
her	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
deposed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
searching	O
of	O
her	O
very	O
narrowly	O
found	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
behind	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Shirts,13	O
Turnovers	O
and	O
3	O
long	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
from	O
Isabella	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Weekly	O
Servant	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
owning	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
and	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sheet	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sponcer	O
deposed	O
she	O
let	O
her	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
mist	O
the	O
Sheet	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-clothes	O
and	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Headclothes	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Sheet	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
stollen	O
Goods	O
of	O
Williams	B-pers
Tring	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
,	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
70	O
yards	O
of	O
Ferreting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
on	O
Shrove-tuesday	O
last	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Sixpenny	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ferret	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
No	O
Name	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
and	O
two	O
Utensils	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Glass-House	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Glass-House	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
under-rate	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
bound	O
over	O
for	O
buying	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
but	O
being	O
out	O
upon	O
Bail	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Rodgers	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
two	O
Petticoates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
Hungerford	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Market	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
very	O
Morning	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
Clothes	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Butcher-Row	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
trusted	O
with	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jessop	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
speaking	O
scandalous	O
Words	O
against	O
on	O
the	O
5	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Tall	O
d	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
she	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
.	O
Mair	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
Words	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Plow-shares	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Isles	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Plow-share	O
,	O
a	O
Colter	O
and	O
Tuck	O
of	O
a	O
Plow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hugget	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
lost	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Whit	O
Chapel-Lane	O
offering	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
sale	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
both	O
Facts	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
denyed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Highgate	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Seats	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
five	O
Shillings	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
for	O
5	O
Shillings	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
not	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
spent	O
a	O
Shillings	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
's	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
own	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
used	O
the	O
same	O
Method	O
to	O
have	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
but	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
at	O
worst	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
Trick	O
to	O
get	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chantrel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Witchurch	B-place
,	O
alias	O
Stanmore	B-place
,	O
alias	O
Stanmore	O
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Church	O
and	O
sucrileglonsly	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
2	O
Velvet	O
Carpets,2	O
Velvet	O
Cushions	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
17th	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
put	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Tools	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
Tools	O
they	O
did	O
further	O
Mischief	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
several	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Velvet	O
Carpet	O
which	O
hung	O
over	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carnarvans	O
Pew	O
the	O
Gold	O
Tossels	O
of	O
an	O
Anthem	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
Velvet	O
Carpet	O
of	O
the	O
Altar	O
and	O
the	O
Velvet	O
of	O
4	O
Cushions	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
attempted	O
several	O
Robberies	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
effected	O
any	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
a	O
Bulk	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
Design	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
Booty	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
case	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
themselves	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
as	O
being	O
little	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Hughes	O
and	O
Bradsber	O
went	O
in	O
while	O
Chantrel	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
watch	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Walk	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
was	O
plac	O
'd	O
behind	O
the	O
Parsonage	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Whistle	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
our	O
great	O
Bundles	O
under	O
their	O
Arms	O
and	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
to	O
Tyburn-House	O
,	O
but	O
dropt	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Bundles	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
18	O
d.	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
:	O
That	O
Chantrel	O
wak	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Bulk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
followed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
Places	O
,	O
particularly	O
at	O
Tyburn-House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
searching	O
Tyburn-House	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
and	O
called	O
Joseph	O
cox	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
watch	O
'd	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Walk	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Nat	O
.	O
Chanerel	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
ill	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
workt	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
several	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
for	O
Victuals	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
12	O
Weeks	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
their	O
Friends	O
ready	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
try	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hatt	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
knew	O
Lewis	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
War	O
was	O
declared	O
against	O
Spain	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Hour	O
because	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
came	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
his	O
Bed-fellow	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
10	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Evidedce	O
visit	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
War	O
declared	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Bond-Chapel	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Posts	O
till	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Another	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
appeared	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
There	O
likewise	O
appeared	O
several	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
Hughes	O
and	O
Chanerel	O
,	O
and	O
Masters	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
;	O
particularly	O
one	O
for	O
Chanerel	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
favours	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
carnarvan	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
him	O
any	O
ways	O
Guilty	O
of	O
tho	O
Crime	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
Also	O
two	O
Masters	O
they	O
all	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
summing	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
mature	O
Consideration	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Flemming	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
by	O
suffocating	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
two	O
severally	O
tryed	O
before	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
deposed	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Waggon	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Mar	O
was	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
taken	O
our	O
of	O
the	O
Truss	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Sessions	O
before	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
alias	O
Jackson	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
for	O
2	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Holmes	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
1717	O
.	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Marks	O
on	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
off	O
and	O
she	O
tore	O
;	O
and	O
concluded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Woman	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
and	O
afterward	O
another	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
Constable	O
search	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Goods	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
them	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
such	O
a	O
Thief	O
as	O
Carlisle	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
shewed	O
his	O
Books	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
the	O
Constable	O
confirm	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Luiture	O
deposed	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
that	O
Jackson	O
alias	O
Carlisle	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
till	O
the	O
Customers	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
measur	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Marks	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Execution	O
against	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
that	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
as	O
for	O
as	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Bottle	O
in	O
Possession	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
and	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
cut	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Nose	O
;	O
took	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Possession	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Stockwell	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
his	O
Wig	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
without	O
it	O
,	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
M.	O
Mussen	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
without	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
he	O
prevented	O
his	O
being	O
Murder	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Stockwell	O
came	O
runing	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
thrust	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
Violence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
Knocker	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
pulling	O
the	O
Door	O
too	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
Sword	O
nor	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
but	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wig	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
over	O
the	O
Rails	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wig	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
Stockwell	O
s	O
Affidavit	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
move	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Wig	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
whereas	O
he	O
now	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
feloniously	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
manifest	O
Contradiction	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
his	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
regarded	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
alias	O
Cole	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitmore	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Trevers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
assaulting	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
there	O
with	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Right	O
Side	O
near	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
peter	O
Trevers	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
between	O
his	O
Ribs	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
bled	O
inwardly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
quickly	O
died	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
talk	O
about	O
fighting	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Trebers	O
did	O
him	O
trouble	O
himself	O
about	O
his	O
own	O
Businets	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
followed	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Jordoin	I-pers
went	O
after	O
them	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mischief	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
one	O
cry	O
draw	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Pitmore	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pushing	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
beat	O
down	O
their	O
ds	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
,	O
but	O
Travers	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
and	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
part	O
them	O
.	O
Tho	O
,	O
Jordain	O
con	O
going	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
Pitmore	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Decease	O
said	O
,	O
ye	O
Fool	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
for	O
Jer	O
.	O
Dawson	O
deposed	O
that	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Confort	O
of	O
Musick	O
with	O
Pitmore	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
learnt	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
Williams	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
learnt	O
this	O
Half	O
Year	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
grudge	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
Landlords	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Pitmore	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
Words	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
lay	O
their	O
Hands	O
on	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
concluded	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Grudge	O
.	O
His	O
Landlady	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
a	O
Wig	O
for	O
Pitmore	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
divers	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Pitmore	O
villified	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
after	O
him	O
where-ever	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Pitmore	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Confort	O
6	O
Months	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Dinner	O
there	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
very	O
lovingly	O
together	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Quarreling	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Trever	O
and	O
himself	O
came	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
nd	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
must	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Trevers	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
another	O
way	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Church	O
yard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
.	O
Draw	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
retir	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pent	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
th	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Grudge	O
or	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
intended	O
amy	O
manner	O
of	O
Hurt	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
all	O
Day	O
at	O
the	O
Comfort	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
Words	O
of	O
Quarerlling	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Second	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Stratagem	O
to	O
draw	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
home	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Commerciance	O
to	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Stay	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
nor	O
his	O
Adversary	O
's	O
Sword	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thankt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
sight	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Friends	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
Friends	O
with	O
Pitmore	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
spend	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
not	O
be	O
reconcil	O
'd	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Rogue	O
.	O
Trevers	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Club	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
they	O
stept	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
go	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
Dark	O
he	O
slipt	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
they	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
their	O
Fighting	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
so	O
violent	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
Trevers	O
and	O
found	O
Pitmore	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carrent	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Yeoman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Caruthers	I-pers
,	O
did	O
Conspire	O
,	O
Consult	O
and	O
combine	O
falsely	O
to	O
charge	O
and	O
accuse	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
certain	O
felonies	O
,	O
viz	O
that	O
he	O
aberred	O
consulted	O
and	O
procured	O
the	O
Robbing	O
of	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
,	O
thereby	O
bringing	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
support	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Carrent	O
gave	O
Carlile	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
said	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
on	O
,	O
not	O
doubting	O
but	O
she	O
'd	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Carlile	O
to	O
pay	O
14	O
s	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holiday	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mr.	O
smith	O
for	O
abetting	O
and	O
procuring	O
the	O
robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
40	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
Carrent	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
all	O
Charges	O
:	O
that	O
Carrent	O
should	O
say	O
to	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
Smith	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
prosecute	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
Rigour	O
of	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
pardoned	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
interest	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Nobleman	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
Carrent	O
said	O
that	O
smith	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
had	O
soft	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
convicted	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pound	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Carrent	O
observed	O
that	O
even	O
what	O
was	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
supposing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
good	O
the	O
indictment	O
and	O
then	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
Scott	O
.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mile	O
yet	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
those	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Fools	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
been	O
made	O
Men	O
.	O
That	O
Smith	O
set	O
Holiday	O
,	O
Williams	O
and	O
Cheshire	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
going	O
to	O
Smith	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Black-Horse-Alley	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
betimes	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
Smith	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Letters	O
were	O
forting	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
separate	O
their	O
Horses	O
or	O
they	O
'd	O
betray	O
'em	O
.	O
that	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
help	O
them	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
whereupon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
now	O
he	O
has	O
set	O
us	O
on	O
and	O
drawn	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
betray	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
would	O
have	O
called	O
many	O
more	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
have	O
proved	O
the	O
Matter	O
against	O
Smith	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
having	O
before	O
been	O
a	O
Great	O
deal	O
of	O
time	O
spent	O
in	O
hearing	O
the	O
Counsel	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Occasion	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
plainly	O
appeared	O
that	O
Carrent	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
probable	O
Cause	O
for	O
prosecuting	O
the	O
said	O
Smith	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
Indictment	O
of	O
abetting	O
,	O
consulting	O
and	O
procuring	O
Williams	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,5	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
W	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
Gervas	B-pers
Northam	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Flatt	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,21	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
C	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
alias	O
Dean	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bats	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Troes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Diana	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
alias	O
Cole	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
Owen	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Rodgers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,1	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitmore	I-pers
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
Fined	O
40	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
remain	O
there	O
till	O
his	O
Fine	O
is	O
paid	O
.	O
Augustin	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Somerset-House	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
Fined	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jessop	I-pers
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Not	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Duck-lane	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
true	O
spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Ground-Ivy	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Likewise	O
,	O
a	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth	O
ach	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
effectual	O
for	O
that	O
Cure	O
of	O
any	O
yet	O
known	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
To	O
prevent	O
and	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
preserre	O
and	O
fasten	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
most-successful	O
plaister	O
to	O
prevent	O
Miscarriages	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
help	O
'd	O
beyond	O
expectation	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
hope	O
of	O
Relief	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Some	O
Books	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmond	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
in	O
Lomberd	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr.8	O
d.	O
M.	O
Jordaine	O
's	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Two	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Duodicimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Saperticies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Gauging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tuns	O
and	O
Casks	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Vulgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
Useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Writing	O
Midlers	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
Svo	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Jesop	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflection	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
:	O
Verse	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instruct	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
cantaining	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
Psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Psalms	O
and	O
Hymns	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sternhold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Yate	O
,	O
adapted	O
to	O
the	O
Tunes	O
;	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Psalms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition,8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
A	O
Guide	O
to	O
English	O
Juries	O
:	O
Setting	O
forth	O
their	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common-Law	O
and	O
Statutes	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
.	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackney-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
All	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypocondriack	O
Distempers	O
,	O
WHich	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Feats	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Painting	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlesness	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caused	O
by	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
Successor	O
to	O
a	O
late	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
30	O
Years	O
successful	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
Deplnrable	O
Cases	O
)	O
he	O
also	O
Cures	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
justly	O
inform	O
you	O
:	O
living	O
at	O
No	O
1.	O
in	O
Burr-Street	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answered	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-2ly	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUR	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reasort	O
cal	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
,	O
-3ly	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
on	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
used	O
ding	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-stra	O
I	O
Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wherein	O
as	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self-Abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK	O
-	O
LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toyshop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
against	O
:	O
St.	O
Sepulchsres	O
Back-Gate	O
in	O
Gilt-Spur-Street	O
near	O
Newgate	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane.1718	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
