TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
Sept.	O
1720	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortesque	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jarman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bache	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tax	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
Charles	O
Young	O
William	O
King	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atlee	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Berchett	I-pers
,	O
Adrian	B-pers
Westerbourn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
jostled	O
him	O
and	O
past	O
by	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
them	O
as	O
making	O
Water	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
feeling	O
of	O
him	O
draw	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bow-Lane	B-place
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand-before	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Grudge	O
:	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
13	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Copper	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Niblett	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
Sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
4	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Tablecloth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Spark	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Spoons	O
.	O
Abigail	O
Partington	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Spoon	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
her	O
Trunk	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
through	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
at	I-place
Queenhith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
5	O
Aprons	O
,	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Godby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
and	O
Valentine	B-pers
Coultson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barr	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Cock	I-place
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
5	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
Silver	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Susan	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
(	O
who	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
searcht	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
ript	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
sewed	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Silver	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
's	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
took	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
because	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
pass	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ripping	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
the	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
was	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
K.	O
Charles	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Groat	O
of	O
K.	O
Henry	O
VIII	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
brought	O
an	O
Apron	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
13	O
l.	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
an	O
Officer	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Suit	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
the	O
Warrant	O
on	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
5	O
Months	O
ago	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
answer	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
now	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
an	O
ill	O
Gang	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
already	O
Executed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
having	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Guineas	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Egglinton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
nor	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Alshear	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
32	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Upper-Leathers	O
for	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Bryon	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
some	O
Work	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
16	O
pair	O
of	O
Upper-Leathers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Fellow	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
selling	O
the	O
other	O
13	O
pair	O
.	O
Two	O
others	O
confirmed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
3	O
pair	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jerrom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Merry-making	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Chick	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Mugg	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
several	O
Muggs	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
certainly	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Women	O
run	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
after	O
grumbling	O
for	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
shoved	O
her	O
headlong	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
China	O
Ale	O
,	O
then	O
more	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
Ale	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Times	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Usquebaugh	O
,	O
let	O
down	O
his	O
Breaches	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
went	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
held	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
entrusted	O
her	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lieth	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
married	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Cook	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Bedford	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
living	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
her	O
this	O
very	O
Day	O
.	O
Two	O
Evidences	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
One	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
D	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
in	O
Marriage	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
married	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
thus	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Brass	O
Pulleys	O
50	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Case	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
New-River-Water	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
after	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tuttle	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
2	O
Pulleys	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
went	O
for	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
brought	O
Iron	O
and	O
Lead	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Swore	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Witherell	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Bennet	B-place
Gracechruch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Zachary	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
by	O
Lombard-street	B-place
he	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
(	O
the	B-place
Raven	I-place
in	O
Fetter-Lane	B-place
)	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
removed	O
to	O
another	O
Room	O
further	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
throwing	O
the	O
Drink	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
immediately	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
put	O
the	O
Tankard	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
trifling	O
excuse	O
not	O
availing	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bonnet	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
Trunk	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
with	O
her	O
Maid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bonnets	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
22	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
a	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
into	O
her	O
Trunk	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
let	O
it	O
stand	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hasp	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
close	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Bill	O
into	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Money	O
twice	O
over	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Trunk	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
for	O
some	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lockt	O
the	O
Trunk	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
(	O
Thursday	O
)	O
her	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Trunk	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Hasp	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
open	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
the	O
Bill	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nutmegs	O
tumbled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
being	O
surprised	O
she	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bonnet	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
)	O
who	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
rise	O
and	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Bill	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
let	O
a	O
Man	O
lie	O
down	O
there	O
on	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
civilly	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
long	O
story	O
which	O
turned	O
rather	O
to	O
his	O
Disadvantage	O
than	O
service	O
,	O
as	O
how	O
Margaret	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
should	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
Jackson	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
would	O
be	O
seized	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
High-way	O
Men	O
and	O
House	O
Breakers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Goods	O
worth	O
above	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
Box	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
called	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
to	O
discredit	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hasp	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
got	O
Drunk	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Bill	O
:	O
he	O
also	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
Mary	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
Samuel	O
Bonnet	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
Musquetoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
his	O
Pistols	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Katharine	O
Wheel	O
in	O
Blackman	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
valued	O
them	O
at	O
5	O
l.	O
Charles	B-pers
Biew	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
those	O
Pistols	O
to	O
him	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
did	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
15	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
F.	O
Smart	O
graved	O
on	O
them	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
called	O
on	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Smart	O
for	O
Sword	O
Scabbards	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
surely	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
low	O
with	O
the	O
Captain	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
take	O
Pistols	O
for	O
your	O
Scabbards	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Captain	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
it	O
was	O
little	O
better	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
he	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
stole	O
all	O
the	O
Weights	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Whore	O
who	O
betrayed	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Pistols	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
and	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
)	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fitzwater	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bloomer	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Quill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bugg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
Dukes	O
Place	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Standard	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
;	O
that	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
he	O
stopt	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
7	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Fobb	O
under	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
together	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
her	O
Discourse	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
knew	O
several	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
,	O
particularly	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
who	O
he	O
also	O
knew	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
drew	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
fasten	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Watch	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
think	O
of	O
his	O
Guineas	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
fear	O
her	O
coming	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
her	O
Gloves	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
staying	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
askt	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
went	O
also	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
sooner	O
;	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
by	O
going	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
frequently	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
his	O
Tenant	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Months	O
ago	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
expose	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
(	O
being	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
)	O
taken	O
two	O
Rooms	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Friends	O
who	O
supt	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
raised	O
this	O
false	O
Report	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
flouted	O
at	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
past	O
by	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
love	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hate	O
a	O
Pick	O
Pocket	O
Whore	O
:	O
she	O
Arrested	O
him	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
to	O
clear	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
Her	O
Landlord	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
Rooms	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
Friends	O
supt	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
)	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
's	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
but	O
they	O
knowing	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
described	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
Pock-broken	O
,	O
Red	O
Hair	O
,	O
her	O
Eyes	O
black	O
with	O
beating	O
and	O
a	O
cut	O
cross	O
her	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Seven	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Standard	O
Tavern	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
's	O
Servant	O
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
:	O
She	O
likewise	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
observed	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
her	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
so	O
often	O
,	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
enquire	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
nor	O
elsewhere	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
describe	O
a	O
Person	O
the	O
very	O
reverse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
base	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gumley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Coppinger	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
30	O
Bales	O
taken	O
our	O
of	O
the	O
Italian	O
Merchant	O
and	O
put	O
aboard	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Lighter	O
to	O
Pump	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bales	O
was	O
cut	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
Lighter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Bowman	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
Bowman	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Richards	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Ellin	B-pers
Skillicorn	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Stout	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Plates	O
rattle	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
without	O
staying	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leap	O
off	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Plates	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Plates	O
and	O
Bag	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plates	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Bag	O
on	O
the	O
Dresser	O
and	O
the	O
Plates	O
were	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Saws	O
,	O
1	O
Hatchet	O
2	O
Plains	O
,	O
3	O
Chissels	O
,	O
1	O
Box	O
Rule	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Blomley	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Tools	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
disposing	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Desk	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
near	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Bag	O
by	O
itself	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
12	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
who	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Eleven	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ratford	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
her	O
Mistress	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
7	O
half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
called	O
a	O
Spanish	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mayling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wilson	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corral	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Kicking	O
,	O
Beating	O
,	O
Wounding	O
,	O
and	O
Bruising	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Groin	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Lamb	B-pers
Dyson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Haymakers	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Dinner	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
Rake	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Wife	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
and	O
fit	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
twitcht	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tript	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
kickt	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
that	O
's	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Rake	O
,	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
cleave	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Rake	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tript	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
sickly	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Shoulders	O
with	O
a	O
Rake	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tript	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Kick	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Bruise	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
him	O
Groin	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
threatned	O
to	O
Split	O
his	O
Scull	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
him	O
any	O
Mischief	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
,	O
Orderly	O
,	O
Well-behaved-Man	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Grudge	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Assaulted	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
ill	O
from	O
his	O
Work	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Catlin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
it	O
was	O
strangled	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
clean	O
her	O
House	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Fit	O
of	O
the	O
Collick	O
by	O
eating	O
Cabbage	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Snake-Root	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
;	O
that	O
perceiving	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Wet	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Cat	O
had	O
thrown	O
down	O
the	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Sister	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
and	O
Mopt	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
still	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
that	O
the	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Labour	O
or	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
;	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Coal	O
Vault	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Catlin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
about	O
Noon	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
being	O
at	O
Dinner	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
Dined	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Coal	O
Vault	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprise	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
alive	O
or	O
dead	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rutland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
brought	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
viewed	O
it	O
,	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
viewed	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
believes	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Birth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
near	O
her	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
designed	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
lie-in	O
at	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
alone	O
.	O
Some	O
Child	O
Linnen	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
s	O
ore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
for	O
that	O
use	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brancom	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Frock	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
Scarf	O
and	O
Cap	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
18	O
s	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Moleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
George	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Bails	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
redeemed	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
amends	O
:	O
the	O
Evidence	O
nor	O
affecting	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
George	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Evening	O
aforesaid	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
by	O
themselves	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Guineas	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
first	O
.	O
One	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
below	O
Stairs	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pickt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Scipiers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
Shillings	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Brown	O
Paper	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
dead	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
fetch	O
3	O
Full-Pots	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
All-Fours	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
his	O
Wives	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
and	O
hal	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
,	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Oath	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
might	O
better	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
Robert	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Layton	O
Buzzard	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
with	O
2	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
who	O
rode	O
with	O
them	O
near	O
to	O
Tyburn	B-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
one	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
such	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gate	O
House	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Mare	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
rode	O
the	O
same	O
Mare	O
when	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bedcott	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clap	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Glenister	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
same	O
Road	O
with	O
a	O
Charge	O
of	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
and	O
one	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rid	O
a	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
crost	O
a	O
Head	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
clapt	O
Spurs	O
and	O
rode	O
back	O
to	O
Paddington	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chasin	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
Stable	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mare	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
trembling	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
answering	O
the	O
Description	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
wait	O
for	O
him	O
against	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
clapt	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
Apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
loaded	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
against	O
such	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
and	O
12	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
about	O
11	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Acton-Fair	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
his	O
Master	O
there	O
,	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
when	O
taken	O
he	O
owned	O
on	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
pieces	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
bought	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Striped	O
Muslin	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
perceiving	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Muslin	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Maid	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Striped	O
Muslin	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
then	O
carried	O
her	O
backward	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
pieces	O
more	O
of	O
plain	O
Muslin	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
down	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
5	O
pieces	O
of	O
Muslin	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
before	O
deposed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
of	O
St.Margaret	B-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Half-Guinea	O
From	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
16s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Homer	I-pers
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Half	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
wages	O
due	O
on	O
the	O
Queenborough	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Chatham	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Warwick-Lane	B-place
they	O
clapt	O
two	O
Pistols	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Half	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
well	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
them	O
3	O
Days	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wilson	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
himself	O
John	O
Homer	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
Evidence	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
Homer	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
for	O
House-breaking	O
and	O
the	O
High-Way	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
White-Horse-Inn	O
by	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
Homer	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
Threats	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Stag	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Foot-Pads	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
went	O
to	O
Chatham	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
Houses	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
things	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
their	O
Expectation	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
plenty	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
thence	O
by	O
Water	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
at	O
Warwick-Lane	O
end	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
Homer	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
snd	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
Men	O
ran	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
followed	O
Wilson	O
up	O
Ivy	O
Lane	O
into	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
thereof	O
.	O
-	O
Hooper	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Market	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Wilson	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
his	O
Pistol	O
under	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shambles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
10	O
yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
,	O
1	O
yard	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
7	O
Moiders	O
,	O
50	O
Guineas	O
,	O
20	O
half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
20l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	O
Wright	O
as	O
Accessary	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Edward	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
consulted	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
mark	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
and	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Drawer	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
Drawer	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
5	O
of	O
the	O
Mark	O
'd	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Drawer	O
broke	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
18d	O
.	O
then	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
then	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
his	O
Mother	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
they	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Five	O
of	O
the	O
Mark	O
'd	O
Guineas	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
before	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
blown	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
New	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
which	O
stuck	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
fine	O
Lace	O
,	O
Lustring	O
,	O
Velvet	O
,	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Julius	O
Caesar	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
pardon	O
her	O
Son	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
askt	O
her	O
Son	O
whether	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
Quantities	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Draper	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
consult	O
how	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
notcht	O
the	O
Guineas	O
with	O
a	O
File	O
just	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
23	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Drawer	O
,	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Basis	O
to	O
look	O
through	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
lifting	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
it	O
and	O
beg	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Twinborough	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
when	O
the	O
Guineas	O
were	O
markt	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
agree	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
should	O
lie	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Boy	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
above	O
50	O
l.	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
gain	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Junior	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
at	O
times	O
above	O
60	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Mountfort	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
when	O
the	O
Guineas	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	O
Wright	O
brought	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
's	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
whose	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
by	O
her	O
Consent	O
for	O
51	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
if	O
any	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dorrel	I-pers
deposed	O
she	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
pay	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Markt	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
Hang	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Frivolous	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
it	O
being	O
to	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Edward	O
Wright	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	O
Wright	O
his	O
Mother	O
as	O
Accessory	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Simmons	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
500	O
Pins	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Pins	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Pins	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Isaac	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
striking	O
and	O
bruising	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
with	O
a	O
Musket	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Corporal	O
in	O
the	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
private	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Marching	O
to	O
the	B-place
Tower	I-place
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very	O
quarrelsom	O
,	O
changed	O
his	O
Ranks	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
trod	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Heels	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
trip	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
very	O
abusive	O
Language	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
replied	O
G-d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tread	O
on	O
your	O
Heels	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Piece	O
against	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
rim	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
be	O
got	O
by	O
falling	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scotch-Cloth-Shirt	O
2	O
Half	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
also	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Studs	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Barry	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tents	O
in	O
Burleigh-Street	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
then	O
somewhere	O
else	O
,	O
they	O
led	O
him	O
through	O
the	B-place
Change	I-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Barry	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
things	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Barry	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Qualand	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Barry	O
,	O
Elliott	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tents	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Barry	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
into	O
the	O
Three	O
Texns	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
led	O
him	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
dead	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Cheston	O
,	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
Flexmore	B-pers
Dakins	I-pers
Esq	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dakins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
from	O
Barnet	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
Highgate	B-place
,	O
who	O
by	O
his	O
riding	O
seem	O
'd	O
intended	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
turn	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
gallop	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
whipt	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Brest	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Deliver	O
;	O
dismounted	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
time	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
put	O
up	O
your	O
Sword	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
the	O
trampling	O
of	O
Horses	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
put	O
up	O
your	O
Sword	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Pistol	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stock	O
to	O
screw	O
it	O
on	O
that	O
would	O
turn	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
the	O
long	O
Barrel	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
scrue	O
on	O
was	O
not	O
about	O
him	O
)	O
Powder	O
,	O
Bullets	O
,	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Nails	O
and	O
two	O
Moulds	O
to	O
cast	O
Bullets	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
dragging	O
him	O
along	O
he	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
Major	O
Bealing	B-pers
;	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Assistance	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Pistol	O
he	O
charged	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
a	O
Bullet	O
Mould	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
's	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Bealing	O
.	O
The	O
Pistol	O
(	O
or	O
Gun	O
)	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
before	O
mentioned	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pitford	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Bullet	O
Gun	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Shooting	O
Match	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
the	O
Gun	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
.	O
Days	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
Barrel	O
to	O
screw	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Langborn	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dakins	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Matthew	B-pers
Cheston	I-pers
,	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
near	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
abouts	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
lick	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
levelled	O
his	O
Guns	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
at	O
Highgate	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
began	O
with	O
whipping	O
for	O
the	O
Road	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
past	O
one	O
another	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
they	O
whipt	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
gave	O
him	O
enough	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Gun	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Whipping	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
on	O
a	O
Cart-Horse	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
Spurs	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
into	O
Dr.	O
Longborn	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Dakins	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
talking	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Road	O
he	O
whipt	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
askt	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Gun	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
prosecute	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Impudence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
whipping	O
for	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
his	O
Horse	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
heavy	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
whom	O
have	O
had	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
last	O
Year	O
he	O
rented	O
Forescore	O
Pound	O
a	O
Year	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
Church	I-place
of	I-place
Wanstead	I-place
in	O
Essex	B-place
,	O
which	O
said	O
John	O
Burton	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Assizes	O
held	O
at	O
Brent	O
Wood	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Executed	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
Henry	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Burton	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
a	O
Padlock	O
to	O
carry	O
Goods	O
into	O
his	O
Shed	O
at	O
any	O
Hour	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
New	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
Effectual	O
transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
fomerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
transported	O
among	O
the	O
last	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
from	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Convicts	O
forced	O
into	O
Vigo	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
lawful	O
Cause	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Middlesex	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
a	O
Broadpiece	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
.	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
by	O
Somerset	B-place
Gate	I-place
between	O
to	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
private	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
into	O
Somerset-House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
to	O
spare	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
making	O
some	O
Noise	O
Mr.	O
Dunkley	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Corporal	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Lodge	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
8	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swallow	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
aking	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
made	O
her	O
Spit	O
out	O
7	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Broad-piece	O
and	O
Half	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dunkley	O
confirmed	O
her	O
restoring	O
the	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Broad-piece	O
and	O
Half	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Susan	B-pers
Deval	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jull	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jull	I-pers
.	O
Mary	O
Jull	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
above	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden-Market	I-place
;	O
that	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
that	O
Deval	O
came	O
and	O
bought	O
at	O
Sive	O
of	O
Cherries	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Roll	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
on	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
helpt	O
her	O
up	O
twice	O
and	O
the	O
Roll	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
mist	O
her	O
Money	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
a	O
Bag	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
that	O
Deval	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Another	O
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
Jull	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Armpit	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
London	O
Tryals	O
,	O
except	O
Edward	B-pers
Jarman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Foreman	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
Challenged	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
swore	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bowers	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
that	O
Evening	O
about	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
drinking	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
Musick	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bid	O
them	O
play	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
's	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
objected	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
proposed	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
Drink	O
his	O
Health	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Honest	O
Gentleman	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Rogue	O
and	O
a	O
Lyer	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Rebel	O
to	O
his	O
Country	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
immediately	O
both	O
clapt	O
their	O
Hands	O
to	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
Endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
past	O
at	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Half-Way	O
out	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
Through	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
before	O
the	O
Pass	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
lying	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
fallen	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Dispute	O
,	O
stopt	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
both	O
rise	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
and	O
Wounded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
an	O
Instant	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
at	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Feet	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
till	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
it	O
drawn	O
and	O
lying	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knockells	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
supported	O
by	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
Men	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
Spirits	O
to	O
Smell	O
to	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
come	O
in	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
French	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
any	O
had	O
seen	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Material	O
Thing	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
then	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
drawn	O
.	O
That	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
he	O
perceived	O
his	O
Sword	O
lie	O
drawn	O
by	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Left	O
Side	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
opened	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
through	O
the	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Heart	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunliff	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
French	O
at	O
the	O
Ram-Inn	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
Musick	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
's	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
objected	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Health	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Turn	O
to	O
Drink	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
's	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
them	O
who	O
wore	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Cloth	O
to	O
bear	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
immediately	O
drew	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
follow	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
so	O
pinn	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunliff	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
intruded	O
himself	O
into	O
their	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bid	O
the	O
Musick	O
play	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
's	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
them	O
cease	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
proposed	O
his	O
Health	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
agreeable	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
Thrust	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Confusion	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mischief	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Realing	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Ram-Inn	O
to	O
shelter	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
Rain	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
against	O
the	O
Box	O
where	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
drinking	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
well	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
other	O
Expressions	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
resented	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
sat	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
but	O
telling	O
some	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Tilt-Yard	O
Coffee-House	O
what	O
a	O
sad	O
Accident	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Ram	O
Inn	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Action	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Read	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
from	O
the	O
Rain	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
an	O
Uproar	O
,	O
lookt	O
in	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
drawn	O
immediately	O
before	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Hary	O
Croox	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
Sword	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
Jane	O
Fox	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
it	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
Left	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
up	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
broke	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bickerstaff	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
him	O
up	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
not	O
his	O
Sword	O
till	O
Jane	O
Fox	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
People	O
to	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Crowd	O
stood	O
off	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
drawn	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Fox	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
naked	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Quiet	O
,	O
Civil	O
,	O
Courteous	O
,	O
Good-Humour	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Reverse	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
one	O
Turbott	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Hewett	O
nor	O
Read	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sparrow	O
was	O
also	O
called	O
to	O
discredit	O
Mr.	O
Hewett	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
stirr	O
'd	O
out	O
only	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Debates	O
arising	O
among	O
them	O
about	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hewett	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowers	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunliff	O
were	O
called	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Questions	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
desired	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Bowers	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
use	O
the	O
Expression	O
,	O
Take	O
Care	O
of	O
you	O
self	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
his	O
Back	O
being	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
believed	O
if	O
the	O
Words	O
were	O
spoke	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
spoke	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
confirmed	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Hewett	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
from	O
that	O
Box	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
outermost	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
where	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
)	O
and	O
yet	O
not	O
those	O
within	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunliff	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
such	O
Words	O
were	O
or	O
were	O
not	O
spoke	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mischief	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Confusion	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
after	O
long	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
(	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
further	O
informed	O
themselves	O
by	O
the	O
Re-examination	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
declared	O
they	O
were	O
satisfied	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
Credit	O
to	O
the	O
Affirmative	O
and	O
Positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
disproved	O
by	O
the	O
Negative	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Hewett	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Honest	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ailesby	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Bible	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ailesby	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Whips	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ailesby	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Rag	O
tone	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
Window-Board	O
,	O
her	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Books	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
open	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
2	O
Whips	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lockt	O
his	O
Stable-	O
Door	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
White	O
's	O
Orchard	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
Fruit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Whips	O
under	O
the	O
Tree	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
be	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
White	O
's	O
Stable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Perjury	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
did	O
deliver	O
in	O
a	O
false	O
Schedule	O
by	O
omitting	O
to	O
discover	O
past	O
of	O
his	O
Estate	O
and	O
swearing	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Schedule	O
,	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
his	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
Collectors	O
for	O
the	O
Window	O
Lights	O
did	O
under	O
Colour	O
of	O
their	O
Office	O
,	O
fraudulently	O
exact	O
and	O
receive	O
divers	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Persons	O
not	O
Assessed	O
in	O
their	O
Book	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
each	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
.	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Obrion	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
lower	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Vine	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Wildstreet	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Haylin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stayes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cackler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Bickerstaff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
1719	O
His	O
former	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Locket	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
Mary	O
Bickerstaff	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Breeches	O
only	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carreck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	B-place
of	I-place
Malborough's-Head	I-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
mischance	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
it	O
again	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Frankling	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Sword	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
beat	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Hands	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
gave	O
his	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
's	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
Old	O
Fashion	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
to	O
buy	O
another	O
and	O
Change	O
that	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
happened	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
his	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transporatation	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Homer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Crompton	O
John	B-pers
Tomlimson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
5.	O
Giles	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
25.	O
Michael	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higden	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Rowt	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Brancome	I-pers
,	O
Marry	O
Harris	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Haylin	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carreck	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
3.	O
Alice	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evens	I-pers
,	O
all	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
M	O
-	O
B	O
-	O
for	O
their	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
each	O
.	O
