TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
March	O
,	O
1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hamblin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durrant	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beatknife	I-pers
,	O
Emmery	B-pers
Argus	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kilgower	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Witherel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handker-chief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
near	O
Finch-Lane	B-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedaft	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Pussendorf	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Europ	O
,	O
a	O
Journal	O
,	O
Fitzherbert	O
's	O
Natura	O
Brevium	O
,	O
the	O
Clerk	O
's	O
Tutor	O
in	O
Chancery	O
,	O
Boyce	O
on	O
the	O
39	O
Articles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Shop	O
or	O
Stall	O
in	O
Gutter-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Slater	O
's	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Slater	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
him	O
12	O
Books	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Day	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
Boyce	O
on	O
the	O
39	O
Articles	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
suspecting	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
Mr	O
Slater	O
's	O
Daughter	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Books	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
he	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bourke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Pountney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drybutter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
recommending	O
him	O
to	O
Trade	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
new	O
Chap	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
just	O
after	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Customhouse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
lookt	O
upon	O
some	O
Hose	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Pountney	O
Hill	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
Third	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
lived	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Evans	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Hair	O
Twist	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
pound	O
of	O
Mohair	O
Twist	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Everingham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Twist	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
seeing	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rawlinstone	I-pers
a	O
Broker	O
the	O
back	O
side	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinstone	O
's	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
offering	O
more	O
Goods	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Twist	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinstone	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
deposed	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Manwaring	O
deposed	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
his	O
Working	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
none	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
than	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Camfield	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Grey	O
Twist	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
)	O
was	O
her	O
Working	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dely	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Deling	B-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Botolph	I-pers
without	I-pers
Bishopsgate	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Whiteman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Doors	O
were	O
fast	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
throttle	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
saved	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
till	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Sledge	O
Hammer	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
another	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Bloody	O
at	O
the	O
Neck	O
and	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
watcht	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
out	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
(	O
about	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Latch	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
hide	O
himself	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
till	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Neck	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Bag	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
and	O
Penknife	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
Weekly	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
fell	O
down	O
behind	O
a	O
Chest	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
Sleep	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
awoke	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
bed	O
side	O
and	O
shock	O
him	O
to	O
awake	O
him.	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
cut	O
nor	O
wound	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
7	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Coxsell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
he	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
on	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coursey	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
other	O
People	O
were	O
passing	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Garlickhith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ticking	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sarsenet	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Kenting	O
Hood	O
and	O
a	O
Blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Foster	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Foster	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
attending	O
her	O
Business	O
at	O
Market	O
about	O
to	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Elsemore	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
shut	O
Just	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
carry	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Seabite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
,	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Guinea	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
Holbourn-bridge	B-place
,	O
who	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
before-mentioned	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
hard	O
by	O
who	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
,	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
pickt	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
have	O
gone	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
his	O
Lustful	O
Desires	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ingleton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Bartlets	O
Buildings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Boy	O
with	O
one	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
going	O
down	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
without	O
any	O
resistance	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
overtook	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Door	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Creditor	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
over-against	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
26	O
Ells	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
Cloth	O
.	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
perceived	O
her	O
to	O
shuffle	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Joseph	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Austin	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
stood	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
above	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
followed	O
,	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
her	O
Lunatick	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
also	O
affected	O
to	O
act	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
)	O
Another	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
700	O
l.	O
to	O
her	O
Portion	O
,	O
but	O
marryed	O
an	O
ill	O
Husband	O
who	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
belived	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stitchton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stitchcock	I-pers
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
6	O
Tablecloths	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	O
Stitchcock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingham	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulcheres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Low	I-pers
on	O
the	O
:	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
sat	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
under	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
reacht	O
over	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Price	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Tea-Cannister	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Middlecomb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Middlecomb	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Tun	I-place
Taven	I-place
at	O
Bilinsgate	B-place
.	O
Joseph	O
Middlecomb	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hired	O
a	O
Boat	O
to	O
carry	O
'em	O
to	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Waterman	O
Burges	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
wherein	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Snelgrove	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
him	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
China	O
Plates	O
a	O
China	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
2	O
China	O
Basons	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Lining	O
of	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Meriton	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gardener	O
going	O
away	O
abruptly	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
other	O
things	O
being	O
missing	O
he	O
turned	O
away	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
her	O
Place	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
his	O
Curtains	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
torn	O
away	O
and	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
some	O
under	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
others	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
.	O
His	O
Coachman	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wichels	O
in	O
Globe	O
Yard	O
on	O
Fish-street	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
taken	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
And	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
when	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
:	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Wichels	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
accommodated	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Whichels	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
50	O
l.	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Rhodea	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
10	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-clothes	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Dec.	O
5th	O
last	O
.	O
Rhodea	O
Peck	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
in	O
the	O
Cambridge	O
Coach	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
set	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
down	O
at	O
Lincolns	B-place
Inn-Fields	I-place
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
to	O
Hand	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
the	O
Coach	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
and	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
Mrs.	O
Peck	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
make	O
more	O
haste	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
who	O
dropt	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rule	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Stephen	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Hamper	O
value	O
18	O
d	O
16	O
Cocks	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
16	O
Hens	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Jarvis	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Reading	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
Secure	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
Beauford	O
Buildings	O
3	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
jumpt	O
down	O
for	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
the	O
Hamper	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
is	O
sure	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Thomas	O
Kingsmay	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
the	O
Wall	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
smash	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
then	O
ran	O
between	O
the	O
Coaches	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
and	O
himself	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
Carts	O
and	O
Coaches	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
the	O
Rope	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Hamper	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Shops	O
and	O
the	O
Lamp	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloth	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wrenn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smithson	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Horton	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
16	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
4	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
Wood	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chambers	O
(	O
No	O
7.	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	B-place
)	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Doors	O
and	O
Shutters	O
fast	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Stone	O
in	O
his	O
Lock	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
his	O
Key	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Porter	O
with	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Stone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
found	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
Chambers	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
jumpt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
shutter	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Lasinby	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
cut	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Window-shutter	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Chambers	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
sent	O
round	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Stone	O
into	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
surprizing	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
round	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
their	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
in	O
Bed	O
about	O
Noon	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Transported	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
consefs	O
'd	O
nor	O
deny	O
'd	O
this	O
Fact	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Downing	O
had	O
been	O
condemn	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
pardon	O
'd	O
by	O
King	O
George	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Swore	O
against	O
him	O
now	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Firth	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
a	O
Lace	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
lighted	O
her	O
while	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Yard-Door	O
Wrencht	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
suspected	O
one	O
Tho	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
his	O
Friends	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
searcht	O
their	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
a	O
Picklock	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Instrument	O
they	O
forc	O
'd	O
the	O
Bolt	O
with	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
where	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Will	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
enticed	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
lifted	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
helped	O
him	O
over	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Green	O
Apron	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Smitb	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Boy	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Husband	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
Serjeant	O
Cheshire	O
)	O
at	O
Thistleworth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Nephew	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
and	O
suffer	O
'd	O
great	O
Hardships	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
want	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
being	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
,	O
fill	O
'd	O
his	O
Belly	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
introduce	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
4	O
more	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
about	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
bound	O
and	O
gagg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Evidence	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Thistleworth	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
said	O
Briggs	O
he	O
did	O
well	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
Morgans	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
this	O
Evidence	O
liv	O
'd	O
)	O
with	O
such	O
another	O
Story	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
Nephew	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
remembring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
at	O
Thistleworth	O
with	O
Briggs	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
Serjeant	O
Cheshire	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
called	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
)	O
to	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Chew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminer	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
23	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
confession	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
she	O
took	O
on	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hozrobin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Deal	O
Board	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
4	O
half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
Jan.	O
11.	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Reed	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Hay-Market	B-place
,	O
two	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
tore	O
her	O
Pocket	O
off	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
6	O
Doors	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boon	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
David	B-pers
Pritchet	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
Pritchet	O
took	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Accomplices	O
in	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
in	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
Micheal	O
Boon	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
in	O
Custody	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
John	O
Boon	O
had	O
not	O
peacht	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Men	O
to	O
bail	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
look	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
the	O
Prisner	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
all	O
Charges	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
J	O
.	O
Boon	O
)	O
should	O
be	O
well	O
rewarded	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mercia	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Crape	O
Shroud	O
,	O
Pillow	O
and	O
Mittins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mercia	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
fine	O
Suit	O
for	O
the	O
Lady	O
Overquerque	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
Way	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
would	O
kiss	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
Mercia	O
Porter	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
striving	O
with	O
M.	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
something	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
stick	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
pursued	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
his	O
Penknife	O
into	O
a	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
who	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
who	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
along	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
his	O
Knife	O
into	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Hat	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knockt	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
whereupon	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Higgins	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
striving	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
2	O
s.	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Penknife	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
saw	O
some	O
People	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
he	O
ran	O
also	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
also	O
that	O
Roger	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
did	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Lucre	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jana	O
De	O
la	O
Rue	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
'	I-place
,	O
Westminster	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hampden	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Winship	O
met	O
him	O
between	B-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Road	I-place
and	I-place
Hide	I-place
Park	I-place
Corner	I-place
;	O
that	O
Winship	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
you	O
,	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
England	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hampden	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
Saddle	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lett	O
out	O
to	O
Coker	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shandois	I-pers
's	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
hire	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Coker	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
2	O
Highway-men	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
their	O
Horses	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Lord	O
's	O
Stables	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
his	O
Mare	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winship	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Whip	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Coker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Mare	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Shandois	O
's	O
Servants	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bocket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
servant	O
gave	O
her	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Cup	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Oxendon-street	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
all	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Victuals	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
drank	O
up	O
the	O
drink	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Cup	O
under	O
her	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Pawn-Broker	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Cup	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
her	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Trelawny	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
High	O
Way	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
a	O
Watch	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
Dec.	O
16	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
horseback	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
between	O
the	O
Lord	O
Ranelaugh	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Buckingham	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winship	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Buckingham	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
52	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
had	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
the	O
Head	O
being	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
sick	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
Widow	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Jane	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Botley	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Jane	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
to	O
him	O
in	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
Married	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Chappel	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
16	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
living	O
within	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
Her	O
Brother	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Portion	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
paid	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Browne	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Ivy	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Widower	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Brandy	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Married	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
present	O
but	O
the	O
Minister	O
and	O
the	O
Clerk	O
:	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
Right	O
to	O
him	O
than	O
herself	O
had	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Browne	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
his	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
never	O
to	O
trouble	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
deposed	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
his	O
second	O
Marriage	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
his	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Landlady	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Geneva	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
wisht	O
him	O
Joy	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
two	O
Days	O
together	O
with	O
Geneva	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Browne	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
Bedded	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sober	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Treat	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
the	O
second	O
Night	O
to	O
make	O
merry	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
the	O
second	O
Night	O
,	O
Clary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Morning	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
be	O
Married	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
Milk-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
26	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
Moidores	O
and	O
25	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Poultry	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
Country	O
Mand	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
Hertfordshire	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
so	O
was	O
he	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
together	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
last	O
Guardian	O
to	O
two	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Purchase	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
hear	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
about	O
Seven	O
Score	O
Pound	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Mitre-Tavern	B-place
near	O
Woodstreet	B-place
,	O
where	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
sat	O
down	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Paper	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
250	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
dropt	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Note	O
again	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Pint	O
,	O
so	O
sat	O
down	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
Justifie	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
very	O
notably	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
laid	O
Wagers	O
together	O
5	O
Guineas	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
Wager	O
'd	O
for	O
150	O
l	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Card	O
sealed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
enough	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
more	O
and	O
returned	O
quickly	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
enough	O
then	O
,	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
some	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Wager	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
to	O
win	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
love	O
these	O
Scotch-men	O
nor	O
Papishes	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
borrow	O
60	O
Pound	O
's	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
to	O
lend	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
gave	O
their	O
Note	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
then	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
again	O
Prisoner	O
catcht	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
interrogated	O
at	O
the	O
reqeust	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
borrowed	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
lend	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lend	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
good	O
Will	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
arrested	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
suit	O
by	O
his	O
Consent	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
lay	O
it	O
down	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
Procecutor	O
might	O
not	O
appear	O
as	O
a	O
Confederate	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
lest	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Dispute	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
for	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
Man	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
borrow	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
out	O
60	O
l	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
Note	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Harding	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
signed	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cheat	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
11	O
s	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
1718	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
at	O
Ware	O
,	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
several	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
left	O
Guardian	O
and	O
wanting	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
a	O
Purchase	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Feathers	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
him	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
Line	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
dated	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
two	O
Tail	O
'd	O
Wig	O
very	O
fine	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
Note	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
overjoy	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Note	O
again	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Purse	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Shilling	O
from	O
them	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
as	O
much	O
haste	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
civil	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
a	O
pretty	O
Fancy	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Trick	O
he	O
proposed	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
thought	O
very	O
strange	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
but	O
trying	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
mist	O
doing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
50	O
l.	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
21	O
Pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
in	O
that	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Poket	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Guineas	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Frend	O
's	O
hand	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whether	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
part	O
Friendly	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Read	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
10	O
l.	O
that	O
Day	O
in	O
part	O
for	O
Work	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
him	O
20	O
Guines	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
nor	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
else	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
1718.	O
and	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
he	O
was	O
lately	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
,	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
bit	O
;	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stanwell	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bratley	I-pers
;	O
and	O
2	O
Males	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
in	O
Opening	O
the	O
Indictment	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
the	O
Post	O
Boy	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Males	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Letters	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Bank	O
Bills	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Letters	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Boy	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
loose	O
himself	O
,	O
gather	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Letters	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Post-Master	O
sent	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
st	O
p	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
such	O
Bills	O
as	O
were	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
secure	O
any	O
who	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
a	O
Bill	O
No	O
43.	O
which	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Post	O
House	O
at	O
Bristol	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
Letter	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
in	O
London	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
Number	O
and	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Council	O
calling	O
their	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
on	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
any	O
farther	O
Trouble	O
;	O
I	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
I	O
stand	O
indicted	O
for	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Bills	O
;	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
more	O
Hopes	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
great	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Letters	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fann	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Dukes	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Callicoe	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Hester	O
Lee	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Maid	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
and	O
Head	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Lee	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
owned	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
3	O
several	O
indictments	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
enticing	O
or	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
perswade	O
or	O
solicit	O
John	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
Weaver	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
Woolcomb-Maker	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gaton	I-pers
,	O
Worsted	O
Weaver	O
;	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
into	O
France	O
to	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
the	O
Woollen	O
Manufactory	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
breach	O
of	O
an	O
Act	O
made	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Purkes	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
one	O
Paget	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Brown	O
here	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
bought	O
several	O
Wool-Combs	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
than	O
he	O
wanted	O
Artificers	O
to	O
go	O
thither	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
,	O
who	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Scotland	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
proving	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
an	O
ill	O
Name	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Paget	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Condition	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
10l	O
.	O
paid	O
him	O
here	O
,	O
6l	O
.	O
for	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
4l	O
.	O
for	O
his	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Encouragement	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Mills	O
at	O
Young	O
's	O
Wharf	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Cranes	O
,	O
shipping	O
of	O
Woolcombs	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Woollen	O
Manufacture	O
as	O
for	O
Scotland	O
,	O
but	O
indeed	O
for	O
France	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
Mills	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
two	O
Weavers	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
and	O
one	O
Robinson	O
;	O
that	O
Mills	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
entertain	O
them	O
as	O
Artificers	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
but	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Guinea	O
each	O
for	O
their	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Day	O
for	O
their	O
Subsistance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
good	O
Encouragement	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
thither	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
promised	O
Richard	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
and	O
two	O
more	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Ship	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
divers	O
Times	O
with	O
Mills	O
and	O
Pages	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
very	O
intimate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mills	O
gave	O
him	O
Directions	O
where	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Paget	O
;	O
that	O
Knot	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
a	O
Woolcomb-maker	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
few	O
of	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
useful	O
for	O
the	O
Woollen	O
Manufacture	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Mills	O
promised	O
him	O
20	O
Livres	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Work	O
at	O
his	O
Trade	O
of	O
Woolcomb-making	O
in	O
France	O
;	O
that	O
Gaton	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
promised	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
make	O
Provision	O
for	O
their	O
Passage	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
himself	O
Robinson	O
and	O
Shields	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Thames-Street	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
Shipt	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
Mills	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Boat	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
aboard	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
well	O
received	O
;	O
but	O
making	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
ashore	O
again	O
for	O
some	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
apprehended	O
Mills	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
Purkes	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
Mills	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Gaton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mills	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Commission	O
to	O
contract	O
with	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
Encouragement	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
-	O
him	O
20	O
Livres	O
a	O
Week	O
when	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Mills	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
Shipt	O
off	O
above	O
40	O
Artificers	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
Joyners	O
,	O
Watchmakers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
provide	O
for	O
their	O
Shipping	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
their	O
Passage	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
confirmed	O
Knot	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
going	O
aboard	O
and	O
coming	O
ashore	O
again	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Weavers	O
Company	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
how	O
uneasy	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
Apprehensions	O
of	O
the	O
Evil	O
Consequences	O
of	O
such	O
pernicious	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
that	O
Purkes	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Wool-Combs	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
discoursed	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
that	O
Purkes	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
two	O
Weavers	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
make	O
a	O
full	O
Discovery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
provided	O
him	O
two	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
his	O
Son	O
Shields	O
and	O
one	O
Robinson	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
could	O
confide	O
in	O
:	O
That	O
Mills	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
Shipt	O
several	O
before	O
the	O
Act	O
.	O
The	O
Defendant	O
Mills	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
discredit	O
Knot	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Repute	O
,	O
had	O
forfeited	O
3	O
Recognizances	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
safely	O
stay	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
(	O
Mills	O
)	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Ship-Broker	O
,	O
whose	O
Business	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
provide	O
Freight	O
and	O
Passengers	O
for	O
Masters	O
of	O
Ships	O
to	O
all	O
Parts	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
pay	O
their	O
Passage	O
and	O
allow	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
Subsistance	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Councel	O
and	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
To	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
for	O
each	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pays	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Oven	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
for	O
Cursing	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
drinking	O
Health	O
and	O
Prosperity	O
to	O
the	O
Pretender	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
1718	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
two	O
indictments	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonioully	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Tablecloth	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
do	O
by	O
two	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baddiley	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
12	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tallow	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Baddiley	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
Pound	O
of	O
his	O
Tallow	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
Isaac	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tallow	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Tallow	O
of	O
Isaac	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Berriman	O
's	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Berriman	O
deposed	O
that	O
Dennis	O
brought	O
the	O
Tallow	O
and	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
declaring	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Excise	O
Officer	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
enquire	O
among	O
the	O
Trade	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
answer	O
'd	O
both	O
in	O
Weight	O
and	O
Quality	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Tub	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
Matthews	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
not	O
fix	O
'd	O
on	O
Isaac	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Prunelloe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Cassock	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Door	O
cut	O
and	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
His	O
Maid	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Shephard	I-pers
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
boring	O
and	O
cutting	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
lower	O
Bolt	O
with	O
a	O
Rake	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
Downing	O
had	O
been	O
twice	O
condemned	O
and	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
now	O
for	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rudge	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
her	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
shot	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
lauguished	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rudge	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
and	O
himself	O
barbarously	O
used	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
Mrs.	O
Rudge	O
was	O
Murder	O
'd	O
ran	O
down	O
Webb	O
's	O
Rope	O
Walk	O
after	O
3	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
;	O
Two	O
others	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mark	O
Anthony	O
De	O
la	O
Port	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
did	O
exercise	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Function	O
here	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
by	O
Marrying	O
James	B-pers
de	I-pers
Fleury	I-pers
to	O
Barbara	O
de	O
la	O
Gard	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Rites	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
12	O
W.	O
3.	O
for	O
Preventing	O
the	O
Growth	O
of	O
Popery	O
.	O
James	B-pers
de	I-pers
Fleury	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Priest	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Married	O
him	O
to	O
Barbara	O
de	O
La	O
Gard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Certificate	O
signed	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
and	O
witnessed	O
by	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
Reney	O
de	O
la	O
Fontain	O
and	O
Jane	O
de	O
la	O
Fontain	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Present	O
perform	O
the	O
Office	O
and	O
Sign	O
the	O
Certificate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
Witnessed	O
it	O
themselves	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
French	O
nor	O
Latin	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
Marriage	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
joyning	O
of	O
Hands	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
witnessed	O
the	O
Certificate	O
.	O
The	O
Certificate	O
being	O
proved	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asserts	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Roman	O
Priest	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Rites	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
mentions	O
what	O
Romish	O
Bishop	O
he	O
received	O
Orders	O
from	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Perpetual	O
Imprisonment	O
in	O
such	O
Place	O
or	O
Places	O
within	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
as	O
his	O
Majesty	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
his	O
Privy	O
Council	O
shall	O
appoint	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wooldridge	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ferril	I-pers
.	O
Mary	O
Ferril	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Door	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
Wooldridge	O
threw	O
her	O
on	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
forced	O
her	O
,	O
Wooldridge	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
Body	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
Nichols	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
what	O
resistance	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
Nichols	O
say	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
what	O
Mischief	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
then	O
afraid	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Brocket	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Rude	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
very	O
civil	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
bragg	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
Woman	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Mary	O
Ferril	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
Nichols	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
Ravish	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Nichols	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
Swear	O
against	O
Ferril	O
.	O
Wooldridge	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
Warrant	O
for	O
abusing	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
themselves	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
miserable	O
Creature	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Boards	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
this	O
against	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
out	O
without	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pickering	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
several	O
Men	O
besides	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
got	O
50	O
l.	O
by	O
doing	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
might	O
not	O
she	O
.	O
D.	O
James	O
and	O
R.	O
Gough	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
not	O
Talkt	O
of	O
it	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
appear	O
'd	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
she	O
Beat	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
Swear	O
40	O
false	O
Oaths	O
but	O
she	O
'd	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
40	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Fool	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
Stroke	O
without	O
telling	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Brooksby	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
said	O
she	O
expected	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
No	O
Marks	O
of	O
Force	O
or	O
Violence	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
:	O
Honora	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
28	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Pindar	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
4	O
Muflin	O
Aprons	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
7	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Proudfoot	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
8	O
dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
4	O
dozen	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Growt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
about	O
9	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Growt	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
lockt	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
;	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
next	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
she	O
had	O
lockt	O
,	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Papers	O
of	O
new	O
Gloves	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rowland	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
had	O
Admittance	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
sleep	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
produc	O
'd	O
before	O
he	O
waked	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rowland	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
to	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
in	O
before	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Martha	O
Doe	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
arrested	O
her	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
Married	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
or	O
a	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
release	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
carryed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Prison-Room	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
rip	O
her	O
Guts	O
out	O
if	O
she	O
refused	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Husband	O
whom	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
abuse	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Husband	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
his	O
Heart	O
out	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Ball	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
wind	O
your	O
Guts	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
Penknife	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
again	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
she	O
was	O
let	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
with	O
Bruises	O
she	O
received	O
in	O
striving	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
Husband	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
February	O
Philadelphia	B-pers
Luttour	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
Marks	O
on	O
her	O
Thighs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
very	O
large	O
black	O
Spots	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Eastwood	O
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
visited	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
sore	O
in	O
the	O
Private	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Weakness	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
arrested	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Maiden	O
Name	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Married	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
overtook	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
with	O
a	O
Footman	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Bills	O
the	O
Officer	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
Arrested	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
Bills	O
carried	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
but	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
hot	O
Ale	O
and	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Note	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bills	I-pers
confirmed	O
his	O
Arresting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
bringing	O
her	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
their	O
having	O
Ale	O
and	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
of	O
two	O
Pints	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
upon	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
setting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
below	O
Stairs	O
in	O
good	O
Humour	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bills	O
confirmed	O
the	O
carrying	O
the	O
Ale	O
and	O
Gin	O
,	O
3	O
pints	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
the	O
Company	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
Company	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
talking	O
jocularly	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Dobson	O
's	O
a	O
merry	O
Fellow	O
,	O
sure	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
dabling	O
with	O
you	O
too	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Me	O
!	O
No	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
discharg	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
Debt	O
and	O
Fees	O
too	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bonnet	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
discharged	O
her	O
last	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Humour	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
a	O
Soldier	O
had	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Huntridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Arkeen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
Basket	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	B-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
followed	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
dropt	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-Pot	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeaared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scullery	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Chancery	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Burglary	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Lorley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Katharine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
30	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
Neckcloths	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
1717	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Delforce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
1717	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Upcott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Callimancoe	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
o	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
3	O
Pecks	O
of	O
Beans	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pecks	O
of	O
Peas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
load	O
Carts	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
by	O
J	O
.	O
Keen	O
junior	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
Stockings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
which	O
she	O
dislik	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
openly	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
took	O
one	O
pair	O
privately	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
agreeing	O
upon	O
the	O
Price	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fetcht	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Stockings	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
more	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stretch	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
toss	O
the	O
Stockings	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	B-place
of	I-place
Norton	I-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Humble	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Year	O
,	O
sent	O
his	O
Son	O
Home	O
,	O
who	O
lost	O
his	O
Coat	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
some	O
Birds	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Son	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
Coat	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rowleys	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Liberty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
School	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Birds	O
that	O
would	O
sing	O
finely	O
;	O
so	O
got	O
his	O
Clothes	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Indictment	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Bowls	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Radnol	B-pers
Strongitharms	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Eward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lighthaser	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
1717	O
.	O
And	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
11.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Chew	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
3.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Honora	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
27.	O
William	B-pers
Witherell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bourke	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Evans	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dely	I-pers
alias	O
Deling	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingham	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fann	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pindar	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Upcott	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
I	O
sabella	O
,	O
Huntridge	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wrenn	I-pers
.	O
Mark	O
Anthony	O
De	O
la	O
Port	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Misdemeanor	O
was	O
adjudged	O
to	O
Perpetual	O
Imprisonment	O
in	O
such	O
Place	O
or	O
Places	O
within	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
as	O
his	O
Majesty	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
his	O
Privy	O
Council	O
shall	O
appoint	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
for	O
his	O
3	O
Misdemeanours	O
is	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
for	O
each	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pays	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
