TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
21st	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Took	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Halford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hammilton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bezar	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Guiney	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Job	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Huddlestone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Smithhurst	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
80	O
Ells	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
56	O
Ells	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
40	O
Ells	O
of	O
Bag	O
Holland	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Pomroy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plummer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
Horses	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
his	O
Ware-House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
,	O
which	O
be	O
confest	O
(	O
when	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Persons	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eudal	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
26	O
Ells	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Plummer	O
's	O
Stable	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
also	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clendon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whiten	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
James	O
Green	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
(	O
Clendon	O
's	O
)	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
Poverty	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
Mr.	O
Whiten	O
's	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Hamborough	O
Linnen	O
Yarn	O
value	O
48s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
workt	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
a	O
Thread	O
Throwster	O
)	O
took	O
Mr	O
,	O
Cham	O
's	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Yarn	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pincock	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Parcels	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
which	O
being	O
of	O
several	O
sorts	O
he	O
examined	O
her	O
how	O
the	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Crow-Alley	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Cham	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
Linnen	O
Yarn	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
described	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Yarn	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Young	O
Woman	O
who	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Tally	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
in	O
Consideration	O
thereof	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
9	O
Months	O
ago	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Short	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reach	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
7	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
made	O
bold	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
perceiving	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
about	O
3	O
Doors	O
,	O
then	O
had	O
her	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Breast	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Beef	O
off	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Gitters	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
in	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Scarfs	O
and	O
4	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Batholomew	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
by	O
London-Bridge	B-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
800	O
Pound	O
of	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
400	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
Nails	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1717	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Super	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Fleet	B-place
Prison	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Head	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
Charity	O
of	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
added	O
another	O
Lock	O
to	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
on	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Locks	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Broomstick	O
or	O
Mopstick	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
fixt	O
to	O
a	O
main	O
Post	O
in	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
had	O
put	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
Box	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Rolls	O
for	O
Charity	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
stood	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
the	O
Charity	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
but	O
get	O
Money	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Law	O
with	O
the	O
Warden	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Barlin	I-pers
(	O
Turnkey	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
40	O
s.	O
told	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
(	O
besides	O
what	O
other	O
Money	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
(	O
Steward	O
of	O
the	O
Charity	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
Money	O
among	O
those	O
swore	O
on	O
upon	O
the	O
Charity	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Sum	O
,	O
sometimes	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
Christmas	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
just	O
before	O
)	O
askt	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Dividend	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Week	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
kick	O
on	O
the	O
Arse	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
distributed	O
any	O
Charity	O
Money	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
Weeks	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
troublesom	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
associated	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Owlers	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
great	O
Disturbances	O
in	O
the	O
prison	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
afraid	O
of	O
his	O
setting	O
it	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
Which	O
Character	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fitch	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Transportation	O
Act	O
,	O
for	O
receving	O
20	O
Guineas	O
for	O
helping	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
his	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Letter	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
Which	O
were	O
privately	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Apprehending	O
,	O
Prosecuting	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Felon	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
is	O
enacted	O
that	O
all	O
Person	O
so	O
offending	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Felon	O
's	O
place	O
and	O
undergo	O
such	O
Punishment	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
hath	O
appointed	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
fell	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
is	O
Watch	O
,	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
Letter	O
Case	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
privately	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
having	O
found	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
he	O
perceived	O
he	O
had	O
fallen	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
the	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
him	O
some	O
service	O
in	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
askt	O
30	O
Guineas	O
for	O
such	O
service	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Boys	O
busy	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
disturbed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Pick-pockets	O
and	O
Idle	O
People	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Trouble	O
about	O
his	O
Affair	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Prison	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
great	O
Expences	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
contribute	O
something	O
to	O
his	O
Charges	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
offered	O
him	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complaining	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
little	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
Five	O
Guineas	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Katharine	B-pers
Lunn	I-pers
had	O
swore	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
would	O
be	O
security	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
if	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
handsom	O
Sum	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
caused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
no	O
known	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
4	O
Guineas	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a-piece	O
to	O
two	O
Men	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
his	O
Letter-Case	O
in	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
his	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Wastcoat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
down	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Thompson	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
White	B-place
Fryers	I-place
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Beadle	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
seeming	O
to	O
quarrel	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
pretending	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lockt	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Women	O
Washing	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
:	O
Thompson	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
borrowed	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
redeem	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
held	O
chinking	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
his	O
Watch	O
before	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatcht	O
the	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
by	O
Force	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
since	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dentworth	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
in	O
distress	O
with	O
one	O
Foot	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
more	O
for	O
flauging	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
fetcht	O
the	O
Watch	O
down	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
snatcht	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
till	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Richard	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
his	O
being	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Parrot	O
in	O
Green-Arbor-Court	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
faultering	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
in	O
A	O
Fit	O
or	O
Agony	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
in	I-place
Crooked-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Duroy	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buck-Skin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
2	O
Razors	O
,	O
4	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
,	O
11	O
Bath-mettle	O
Belt-Buckles	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4l	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Billingsley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bilingsley	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
remove	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Country	O
Journey	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
having	O
Rid	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Miles	O
amongst	O
his	O
Country	O
Chaps	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
much	O
wore	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Boars-Head	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Eastcheap	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
Account	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breaches	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stocking	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
dozen	O
of	O
Oiled	O
Sheep	O
Skins	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Fesse	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Kitchen	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
2	O
Skins	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
over	O
Night	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
for	O
the	O
Full	O
value	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Excuse	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Kick	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
by	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
since	O
which	O
he	O
oftentimes	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Linnen	O
Clouts	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Tablecloth	O
,	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
2	O
d.	O
1	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiet	O
1	O
d.	O
1	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
bundled	O
up	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
did	O
indeed	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kissin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Klissin	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Dukes	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Woollen	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joannah	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Case	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
set	O
down	O
and	O
warm	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Galloon	O
,	O
and	O
76	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ferret	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sturges	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Galloon	O
for	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
difficult	O
in	O
matching	O
the	O
Colour	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
another	O
Servant	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
Galloon	O
and	O
Ferret	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
1	O
yard	O
,	O
went	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
bought	O
another	O
yard	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
4	O
Pieces	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
then	O
fetcht	O
her	O
back	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Dining-Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
match	O
some	O
Colours	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
hetching	O
in	O
her	O
Clothes	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
fell	O
into	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
pinn	O
'd	O
up	O
)	O
and	O
others	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
again	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
any	O
had	O
fell	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
14	O
some	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
4	O
several	O
Misdemeanours	O
in	O
enticing	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godding	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
David	B-pers
Dunkhill	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
to	O
go	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
to	O
follow	O
their	O
several	O
Occupations	O
there	O
,	O
contary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Trinity	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Wool	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bangoss	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
House	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
hang	O
down	O
,	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
telling	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisner	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Jacob	B-pers
Swane	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wooldridge	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Orley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
,	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lewry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
from	O
about	O
8	O
till	O
10	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
into	O
Black-Horse-Alley	B-place
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Fob	O
to	O
secure	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
deluded	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
snatcht	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
Landladay	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
who	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
Evening	O
till	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
works	O
plain	O
Work	O
for	O
him	O
(	O
a	O
Wholesale	O
Milliner	O
)	O
is	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hugglestone	I-pers
alias	O
James	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
Ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
J.	O
Painter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
his	O
Door	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
,	O
one	O
Chickley	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Purse	O
of	O
Money	O
as	O
they	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Bedside	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
Rhodes	O
and	O
Brown	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
his	O
Purse	O
of	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
forced	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
Brown	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Purse	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Salt-Box	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
lewd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
Chickley	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
another	O
Quartern	O
,	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
till	O
Chickley	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Annis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
with	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Weavers	O
Shuttles	O
,	O
2	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Rules	O
,	O
16	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Bengal	O
Silk	O
,	O
12	O
scanes	O
of	O
Incle	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Plush	O
Coach-Seats	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
setting	O
forth	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
defraud	O
John	B-pers
Huxley	I-pers
of	O
4	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
by	O
forging	O
an	O
Impression	O
upon	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Blacklock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
1	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
1	O
Shirt	O
,	O
1	O
Hood	O
,	O
1	O
Stomacher	O
and	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
bundled	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
packt	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
Sand	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
move	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Cart	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brilliers	I-pers
and	O
Prudence	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Moidor	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clough	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allcock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jodderel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Jodderel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Wig	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Maxey	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Seal	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
empty	O
Box	O
but	O
no	O
Wig	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maxey	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jodderel	O
's	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Clerk	O
who	O
was	O
Writing	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
bid	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
judging	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
7	O
l.	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
her	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Daily	O
Courant	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Wig	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
I	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
2	O
Irons	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
off	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
Three	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
behind	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
Bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Randolph	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Wig	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
staggering	O
Home	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Carrec	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Clemson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
;	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Augres	O
,	O
a	O
Mallet	O
and	O
10	O
Planes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
immediately	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
Watchman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
making	O
diligent	O
enquiry	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
Produced	O
:	O
That	O
Reading	O
(	O
a	O
Soldier	O
)	O
said	O
Smith	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
lent	O
him	O
40	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Reading	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
And	O
Smith	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
seized	O
her	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
Headclothes	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
Headcloathes	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Martha	O
Smith	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
lodged	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
)	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
set	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Wife	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
one	O
Shirt	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Shirt	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
the	O
Wig	O
and	O
Shirt	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
himself	O
having	O
quarrelled	O
and	O
fought	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
up	O
drinking	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Fine	O
Ale	O
from	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
one	O
Night	O
till	O
the	O
same	O
Hour	O
the	O
next	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
and	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
very	O
impudent	O
Fellow	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Wife	O
,	O
was	O
more	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
)	O
than	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
unlockt	O
his	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Clothes	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Wife	O
's	O
Clothes	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
by	O
force	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
gone	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
washt	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
owed	O
her	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Washing	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Clothes	O
into	O
her	O
Drawer	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Dust	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
a	O
Security	O
for	O
her	O
Debt	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
before	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mackwell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
an	O
ill	O
Humour	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Clothes	O
about	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
he	O
would	O
burn	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
his	O
Wife	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stacy	B-pers
Smytham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
Church-Lane	B-place
,	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Three	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
from	O
Bristol	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
he	O
brought	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Viscount	I-pers
Lisbon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
coming	B-place
from	I-place
Hampstead	I-place
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Foot	O
Pads	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
but	O
two	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Silver	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
12s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
from	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
Dickinson	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Lord	O
ran	O
his	O
Cane	O
at	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Breast	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
12s	O
.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
from	O
my	O
Lady	O
;	O
that	O
my	O
Lord	O
pray	O
'd	O
us	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
promised	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
Dickinson	O
sold	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Hilt	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Transported	O
6	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
lately	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
England	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
because	O
the	O
Captain	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
then	O
,	O
was	O
now	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Baltick	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Then	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Reading	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
John	O
Grimes	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
one	O
Shaw	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
10	O
Guineas	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
John	O
Grimes	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Reading	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
clear	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Reading	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
Grimes	O
was	O
just	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
their	O
Gang	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
told	O
Grimes	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
best	O
Friend	O
in	O
preventing	O
his	O
Ruine	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
Shaw	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
up	O
another	O
Shaw	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
whom	O
he	O
knowing	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
without	O
any	O
Reward	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
confirmed	O
what	O
Reading	O
said	O
relating	O
to	O
Shaw	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Excuse	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
Drunk	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
by	O
false	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
sevetimes	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
M	O
Oldridge	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Horn-Church	O
in	O
Essex	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Keys	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Money	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
Senior	O
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
Foot	O
upon	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
encouraging	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
,	O
his	O
Sons	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
in	O
committing	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Giles	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
North	O
End	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Sons	O
came	O
in	O
playing	O
on	O
a	O
Violin	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
a	O
Game	O
Cock	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hit	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Fiddlestick	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
it	O
patiently	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
Giles	O
Millet	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
Millet	O
)	O
would	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Case	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
down	O
his	O
Fiddle	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Millet	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Poker	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Mills	O
got	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Millet	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Sons	O
(	O
Thomas	O
stript	O
)	O
went	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lie	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sons	O
also	O
beat	O
and	O
kick	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
heard	O
their	O
Father	O
say	O
,	O
Fight	O
,	O
Boys	O
,	O
Fight	O
;	O
Kill'em	O
,	O
kill'em	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
the	O
Deceased	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Chair	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Millet	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
kicking	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wondered	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
Company	O
with	O
Holden	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
and	O
had	O
Sett	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
to	O
be	O
Arrested	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
decoy	O
them	O
all	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
carried	O
down	O
Stairs	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
afterwards	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
only	O
that	O
ugly	O
Blow	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
actually	O
kick	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
did	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Holden	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Widow	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
always	O
languish	O
'd	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
Weeks	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
Vincent	O
had	O
kickt	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
hurt	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Vincents	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bathed	O
his	O
Side	O
with	O
Brandy	O
over	O
some	O
Coals	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
spit	O
up	O
some	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Married	O
to	O
him	O
12	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Fever	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
sick	O
since	O
till	O
then	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
that	O
Young	O
Vincent	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Four	O
others	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Rogues	O
the	O
Vincents	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
side	O
Black	O
and	O
Blue	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Thorax	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pleura	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
Settled	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
hasten	O
'd	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Adam	O
's	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
20	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
spare	O
times	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
Musick	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
to	O
help	O
maintain	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
with	O
Gillet	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
2	O
Teeth	O
bear	O
out	O
,	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Eyes	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
Cut	O
to	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
Deceased	O
any	O
Hurt	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
And	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
scuffle	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
Gillet	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Barnaby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
drest	O
him	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Evidences	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
abroad	O
very	O
well	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
that	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
when	O
asked	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
Mrs	O
Nut	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
walking	O
cross	O
the	O
Field	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Burden	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Sweetingham	I-pers
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
planting	O
Beans	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
;	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
off	O
,	O
who	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
well	O
enough	O
with	O
Young	O
Tom	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
Young	O
Dick	O
.	O
and	O
jumpt	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
Cartway	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
some	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
others	O
,	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gardener	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Pains	O
to	O
maintain	O
his	O
large	O
Family	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
Quiet	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
62	O
Guineas	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Philippa	B-pers
Dorrel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
40	O
Guineas	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
from	O
another	O
Place	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
That	O
missing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
Charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
last	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
62	O
Guineas	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
39	O
where	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
40.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
begun	O
on	O
Bartholonew-Day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dorrel	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
)	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
owning	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Guineas	O
by	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
62	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
spent	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
gave	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Nickson	I-pers
alias	O
Hickson	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Nickson	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
Short	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Watch	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
Brandy	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
deposed	O
they	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Watch	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
John	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hixon	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Margaret	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
privately	O
stole	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
and	O
20	O
pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	O
Company	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
New	I-pers
River	I-pers
Water	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Hillary	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
.	O
1	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Shifts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
Pipe	O
Moulds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jone	O
's	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Moulds	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Misdel	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
and	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Misdel	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sands	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
wanted	O
any	O
mending	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Moulds	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Linnen	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Moulds	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shaftoe	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
them	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sanger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
5s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
matter	O
home	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
a	O
Set	O
of	O
Brass	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
several	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Facts	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Faires	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessory	O
to	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crags	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessories	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
Flying	O
to	O
Woobourn	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
only	O
could	O
be	O
tried	O
that	O
Sessions	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
stopt	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
said	O
Boxes	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
Rate	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
upon	O
both	O
which	O
Trials	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
sent	O
their	O
own	O
Three	O
Children	O
abroad	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
steal	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
4	O
other	O
Children	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
further	O
particulars	O
whereof	O
we	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Trials	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-Pot	O
,	O
2	O
Copper	O
Plaister	O
Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Contusion-pot	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Meacham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Kinsman	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
4	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Pall	B-place
Mall	I-place
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
the	O
Night	O
a	O
foresaid	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
and	O
lost	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
said	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
John	O
Unwin	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tull	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Unwin	O
knock	O
down	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Sight	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
that	O
Unwin	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
his	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
of	O
Edminton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
4	O
Aprons	O
,	O
1	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
miss	O
his	O
things	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Headclothes	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleaner	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
falsely	O
,	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
who	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
6	O
Mens	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
Transport	O
one	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
considering	O
the	O
Heinousness	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
ordered	O
Eleanor	O
Lock	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sift	O
closely	O
into	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Roger	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
(	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
Old	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver-lact	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
Senior	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Child	O
was	O
missing	O
about	O
5	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
found	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
Jones	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Field	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
Field	O
the	O
Coat	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
Jones	O
the	O
Hat	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
Their	O
confessions	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Crippligate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Iron	O
Bolts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
his	O
confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
some	O
Years	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Bars	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Turney	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
Jones	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
Rogers	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bradbear	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
steeling	O
two	O
Planes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Iron	O
Streaks	O
.	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foulker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
Streaks	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Pettit	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
(	O
Coach	O
maker	O
)	O
and	O
Millard	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Foulker	O
who	O
makes	O
Wheels	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Newtonners	B-place
Lane	I-place
with	O
the	O
Prisner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
the	O
Minute	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisner	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
felt	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
clap	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Rings	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
she	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
1	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
.	O
5	O
Linnen	O
Pellowbears	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Flannel	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
GERTRUDE	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
;	O
and	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Israel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wine	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
kicking	O
a	O
Foot-Ball	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
Thames	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
along	O
hastily	O
with	O
his	O
Cart	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
;	O
Whipt	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
over	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
stopt	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wine	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Son	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
who	O
was	O
about	O
13	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
with	O
Death	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
over	O
going	O
after	O
the	O
Foot-Ball	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Carman	O
might	O
have	O
saved	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
cut	O
his	O
Horses	O
and	O
drove	O
over	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Back-bone	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
about	O
24	O
Hours	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
.	O
-	O
Doncaster	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Carman	O
might	O
have	O
saved	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rainbow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ball	O
was	O
kickt	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
jumping	O
at	O
the	O
Cops	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
and	O
was	O
run	O
over	O
in	O
an	O
Instant	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Cart	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Duckworth	I-pers
,	O
Dennis	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
confirmed	O
Mr.	O
Rainbow	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
heard	O
no	O
Body	O
call	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fall	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Carman	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
heard	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
believed	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
his	O
Cart	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randolph	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
some	O
charge	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
would	O
contribute	O
some	O
Money	O
for	O
burying	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
paying	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Gentle	O
and	O
Peaceable	O
Temper	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Browne	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Buckley	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bowyer	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bromley	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bartue	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brooks	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bruce	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Butler	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bartey	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
Marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Hannah	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
Marriages	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
he	O
had	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
Wives	O
now	O
living	O
,	O
5	O
of	O
which	O
appeared	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
taking	O
into	O
Considerations	O
the	O
Heinousness	O
of	O
his	O
Crimes	O
,	O
gave	O
leave	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
whom	O
he	O
has	O
Cheated	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
to	O
Charge	O
him	O
with	O
Actions	O
for	O
all	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
had	O
and	O
received	O
by	O
such	O
fraudulent	O
Practices	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gronas	I-pers
and	O
Bladwell	B-pers
Peyton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
did	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Bladwell	O
Peyton	O
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
mist	O
Goods	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Information	O
of	O
his	O
Servant	O
Hawes	O
's	O
frequently	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
Phillips	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
Goods	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
refused	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
produced	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
several	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
)	O
things	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
not	O
prosecute	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
that	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
which	O
cost	O
him	O
6	O
l.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Hawes	O
;	O
though	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mohair	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
lost	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
within	O
3	O
Weeks	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Peyton	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeping	O
idle	O
Company	O
and	O
wanting	O
Money	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
few	O
Remnants	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
always	O
had	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
or	O
into	O
a	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
speak	O
softly	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
might	O
not	O
hear	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
sold	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mohair	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
cost	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Camblet	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
which	O
cost	O
6	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
encouraged	O
him	O
by	O
bidding	O
him	O
bring	O
what	O
Goods	O
he	O
would	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Masters	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wargen	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
Hawes	O
came	O
.	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Master	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
examine	O
Hawes	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
always	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
She	O
named	O
the	O
several	O
Particulars	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
bought	O
of	O
Hawes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
search	O
she	O
heard	O
Mr	O
Peyton	O
say	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
freely	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
voluntarily	O
deliver	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
equivocated	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
examine	O
Hawes	O
whether	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
buy	O
any	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
examine	O
Hawes	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transpor	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
6	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burditt	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
alias	O
Niale	O
,	O
who	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
then	O
not	O
Agreeing	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
were	O
Respited	O
till	O
this	O
Sessions	O
)	O
were	O
called	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
William	B-pers
John	I-pers
Thompson	I-pers
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Elizabeth	O
Hand	O
.	O
4.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
alias	O
,	O
Isreal	O
Green	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Robert	B-pers
Super	I-pers
,	O
,	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	O
,	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allcock	I-pers
,	O
John	O
,	O
John	O
.	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hixon	I-pers
alias	O
Nixon	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Hillary	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5	O
Katharine	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
W	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
William	B-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burditt	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
alias	O
Niale	O
,	O
who	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
then	O
not	O
Agreeing	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
were	O
Respited	O
till	O
this	O
Sessions	O
)	O
were	O
called	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
fro	O
Eman	O
.	O
Matthews	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Back-Gate	O
in	O
Gilt-Spur-Street	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
