TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
:	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
15th	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
1721.	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
,	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honoura	O
ble	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
Alexander	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Turbat	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winsmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burdett	I-pers
James	B-pers
Mackall	I-pers
,	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edden	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Bar	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grevit	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Grevit	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Grevit	O
's	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
whole	O
Lanthorn	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
for	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
off	O
his	O
Ring	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
his	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
drop	O
'd	O
his	O
Ring	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Computer	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryers	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Will	O
.	O
Price	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
William	O
Price	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
having	O
landed	O
at	O
Black	O
Friers	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
New	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Jackson	O
)	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
Chair	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
stopt	O
her	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
soon	O
after	O
told	O
she	O
was	O
Crazy	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
accepted	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
in	O
New	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
one	O
Pint	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jackson	O
said	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
Pint	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
emptied	O
that	O
,	O
Jackson	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Chair	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
being	O
both	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
but	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
easy	O
;	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
Sharp	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Wine	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Wine	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
he	O
drank	O
one	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
about	O
4	O
hours	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
Jackson	O
about	O
11	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Jackson	O
deliver	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
going	O
to	O
Jackson	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
there	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Rings	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Jackson	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
meeting	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
their	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
carry	O
the	O
Chair	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
vomited	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
'd	O
lie	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
stript	O
himself	O
,	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
for	O
Jackson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
with	O
her	O
Hair	O
loose	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
three	O
times	O
confin	O
'd	O
in	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
broke	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
Chain	O
about	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
now	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
`	O
em	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
at	O
all	O
which	O
affected	O
Mary	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
`	O
em	O
both	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Beddow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Firkin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
(	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
leaving	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Dray	O
near	O
the	O
Monument	B-place
,	O
whilst	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Drink	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
he	O
mist	O
a	O
Firkin	O
off	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Cask	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Father	O
with	O
Drink	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
7	O
Years	O
ago	O
be	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
Drink	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
past	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
new	O
Brewhouse	O
.	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
serve	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
since	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
Ale	O
to	O
`	O
em	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
times	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Ale	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
brew	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
old	O
Firkins	O
of	O
a	O
Cooper	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
might	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Ale	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Manner	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Kenneday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
,	O
1	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
Rebeccah	O
Johnstone	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
several	O
Years	O
before	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
her	O
Goods	O
seiz	O
'd	O
on	O
;	O
withal	O
begging	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
entertain	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Service	O
.	O
She	O
accordingly	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
finding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
under	O
great	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
return	O
`	O
em	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freckleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Dukes	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Th.	O
,	O
Marshal	O
,	O
a	O
Buck-skin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Washleather	O
Skin	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Skins	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
;	O
when	O
an	O
Embroideeer	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
employ	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buck	O
Skin	O
embroider	O
'd	O
Breeches	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
`	O
em	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
`	O
em	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
bring	O
`	O
em	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
'd	O
fetch	O
`	O
em	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
wanting	O
Money	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
then	O
run	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Skins	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
missing	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
down	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
for	O
payment	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
Sittingbourn	O
and	O
Maidstone	O
Fairs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
some	O
extraordinary	O
Expences	O
on	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
enjoyn	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
send	O
down	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
he	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
Master	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
at	O
the	O
Fairs	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
was	O
angry	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
allow	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
extraordinary	O
Expence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
not	O
withstanding	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
his	O
Contract	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
)	O
paid	O
his	O
Master	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Skin	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Jugular	I-pers
alias	O
Jugal	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Fink	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edith	B-pers
Barwell	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
9	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
31	O
s.	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edith	B-pers
Barwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Edith	O
Barwell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Lodger	O
about	O
6	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
one	O
Saturday	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
her	O
Debt	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
arrested	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Spunging	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
taking	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
his	O
own	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
hers	O
,	O
to	O
withdraw	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Bedcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Turnover	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
owning	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
let	O
in	O
both	O
their	O
Friends	O
,	O
paid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Receipt	O
in	O
full	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Friend	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
have	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Serjeant	O
and	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had'em	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
no	O
necessity	O
of	O
Robbing	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
lent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
this	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
drop	O
an	O
Action	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Scaddin	I-pers
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
since	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Spunging	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
on	O
another	O
Account	O
)	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
yet	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
Fact	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Spunging	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Books	O
and	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
any	O
Difference	O
had	O
happened	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
Service	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
quart	O
Bottles	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
Bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
Brandy	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
pint	O
Bottles	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
6	O
Months	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
as	O
last	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonah	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fluck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
60	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Fluck	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
6	O
Weeks	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
intimation	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Billinsgate	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Watermen	O
,	O
desired'em	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
Darkhouse	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Waterman	O
plying	O
him	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
,	O
the	O
Waterman	O
(	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
answer	O
Mr.	O
Fluck	O
's	O
Description	O
)	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
in	O
Darkhouse	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fluck	O
's	O
Kinswoman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
afterward	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confused	O
by	O
two	O
Waterman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
up	O
Stairs	O
(	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Flucks	O
)	O
for	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
to	O
light	O
some	O
Company	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
was	O
read	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Colthouse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
(	O
on	O
Hounslow	B-place
Health	I-place
)	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
riding	O
on	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
Rings	O
off	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
ride	O
up	O
to	O
3	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
apply	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Colthouse	O
and	O
Sinnament	O
that	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
Wild	O
's	O
Information	O
they	O
soon	O
took	O
Sinnament	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
Sometime	O
afterwards	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sanderson	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
of	O
Pockets	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plater	O
,	O
his	O
Friend	O
in	O
Oxford	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
examine	O
and	O
enquire	O
if	O
Sanderson	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
:	O
Of	O
which	O
being	O
satisfied	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Plater	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harle	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Metcalf	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Squib	O
,	O
riding	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Metcalf	O
,	O
on	O
Hounslow	O
Health	O
,	O
outrid	O
Mr.	O
Squib	O
;	O
that	O
near	O
Butchers	O
Grove	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Chaise	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
Horseback	O
;	O
and	O
thinking	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Chaise	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
turning	O
his	O
Horse	O
aside	O
to	O
give	O
`	O
em	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Bridle	O
and	O
clapping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
rob	O
ye	O
altogether	O
-	O
be	O
expeditious	O
;	O
then	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Bridle	O
,	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Chaise	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Metcalf	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Squib	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
left	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Harle	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Metcalf	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
17	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
dismount	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
Squib	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
wont	O
trust	O
ye	O
,	O
exchange	O
is	O
no	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cut	O
his	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
exchang	O
'd	O
Horses	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Caeser	O
(	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Metcalf	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
dismounted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
change	O
Horses	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Squib	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
Men	O
committed	O
the	O
Robberies	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
(	O
Sinnament	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
)	O
had	O
already	O
been	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
That	O
his	O
Brother	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
so	O
much	O
alike	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
hardly	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
and	O
Sinnament	O
were	O
seen	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
lame	O
of	O
the	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
abroad	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Robin	O
Hood	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
,	O
saw	O
Sinnament	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
come	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
with	O
`	O
em	O
a	O
Saddle	O
and	O
2	O
Swords	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Coppen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
or	O
.	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
so	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
his	O
Chamber	O
for	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
so	O
nearly	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
sent	O
him	O
in	O
ren	O
Chaldron	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
12	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
blind	O
Receit	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
himself	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
view	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
it	O
bore	O
Date	O
May	O
7.	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
sworn	O
to	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
He	O
likewife	O
called	O
two	O
other	O
Wirnesses	O
,	O
who	O
testified	O
nothing	O
material	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
80	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
John	O
Groves	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June.in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
but	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
teach	O
him	O
how	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Sum	O
double	O
;	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
Nicholas	O
,	O
who	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Chymical	O
Preparation	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Writing	O
out	O
of	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Paper	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
what	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
rais	O
'd	O
11	O
l.	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Sugar	O
Loaf	O
within	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Bill	O
for	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Groves	O
;	O
which	O
Name	O
Nicholas	O
wrote	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Porter	O
brought	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
more	O
private	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	O
writing	O
with	O
his	O
Preparation	O
over	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
Eleven	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Witness	O
write	O
in	O
Eighty	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Hand	O
shaking	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
desiring	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Receipt	O
how	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
Liquid	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Note	O
off	O
.	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Rotterdam	O
,	O
where	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
accept	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
written	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
returned	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
where	O
Ward	O
,	O
fearing	O
the	O
Consequence	O
,	O
advis	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
deface	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
11	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
lock	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
sell	O
it	O
)	O
tomorrow	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
be	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Chymist	O
's	O
on	O
Snow	O
hill	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Preparation	O
wherewith	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Letters	O
in	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
.	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
for	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
11	O
l	O
and	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
11	O
l.	O
was	O
given	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Groves	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
80	O
l.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
insisted	O
,	O
that	O
Ward	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
chief	O
Actor	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drawn	O
him	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
4	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Bird	O
Cage	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
with	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
won	O
5	O
l.	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Jacob	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Isle	O
in	O
Cripplegate	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
the	O
People	O
crowding	O
thick	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
go	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Watkins	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Hungate	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hungate	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hungate	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
between	O
Highgate	B-place
and	I-place
Kentish	I-place
Town	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
at	O
Norton	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Norton	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
loose	O
in	O
Tothill	O
Fields	O
.	O
That	O
Norton	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
Inn	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
Lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
on	O
Saturday	O
to	O
the	O
Boar	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Kingstreet	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
whence	O
he	O
and	O
Shaw	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
Shaw	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
Pistol	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Masque	O
,	O
a	O
Flint	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
loose	O
Powder	O
.	O
Norton	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
by	O
Shaw	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Inns	O
.	O
Shaw	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Norton	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Norton	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Shaw	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
Shaw	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Philip	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Eye	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Staff	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
be	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Corcner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
committed	O
that	O
Robbery	O
near	O
the	O
Tile	O
Kilns	O
at	O
Pancras	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
soon	O
got	O
him	O
under	O
'em	O
and	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Reading	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
Shaw	O
likewise	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
Staff	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
bleed	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Peter	O
Green	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
off	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
led	O
him	O
along	O
to	O
Battle	O
Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
my	O
Soul	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Pritchard	O
then	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Pindar	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Decea	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Contusion	O
(	O
from	O
a	O
blow	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Robberies	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
with	O
Drew	O
and	O
Reading	O
,	O
but	O
others	O
;	O
yet	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
committed	O
violence	O
on	O
any	O
that	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
Drew	O
had	O
been	O
prov	O
'd	O
perjur	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
now	O
be	O
swore	O
his	O
Life	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
140	O
l.	O
Reward	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Butler	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
J.	O
Gunn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Chicester	O
Coach	O
,	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bir	O
'd	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Norris	O
,	O
at	O
Finsbury	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
rode	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lupton	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Huntington	O
Coach	O
at	O
Mount-Mill	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Horses	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
London	O
Wall	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
telling	O
him	O
his	O
Mare	O
was	O
known	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Porringer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
early	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Goswel	O
street	O
,	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Norris	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
being	O
hir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
being	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
Lupton	O
those	O
Particulars	O
of	O
Hawkins	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
Night	O
House	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
your	O
Friend	O
Hawkin	O
's	O
doings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Hawkins	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
going	O
,	O
Hawkins	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bore	O
him	O
a	O
grudge	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Several	O
creditable	O
Tradesmen	O
and	O
Housekeepers	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Perow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
.	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	O
Whitaker	O
,	O
3	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
2	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
18	O
Diaper	O
Clouts	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
laid	O
to	O
her	O
charge	O
.	O
She	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Bar	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
4	O
Children	O
ready	O
to	O
perub	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
purely	O
to	O
relieve	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	O
Hewit	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
back	O
Shop	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropt	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
coming	O
up	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
Drunk	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
croud	O
of	O
People	O
running	O
and	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
so	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Croud	O
the	O
Goods	O
might	O
be	O
dropt	O
and	O
found	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wiggans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
8	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Bowler	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
near	O
Charing	B-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
(	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
perceiving	O
held	O
her	O
Hand	O
fast	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
Husband	O
then	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Hand	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Womans	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
seized	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bully	O
again	O
came	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
People	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
convey	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
brought	O
him	O
4	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
rest	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
take	O
that	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
by	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Grudge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
Thatcher	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
wickedly	O
and	O
maliciously	O
pronounce	O
these	O
Words	O
:	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
King	O
George	O
and	O
his	O
Laws	O
too	O
!	O
we	O
shall	O
never	O
have	O
any	O
good	O
Trade	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crumpler	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
the	B-place
Magpye	I-place
(	I-place
or	I-place
Hat	I-place
)	I-place
Ale	I-place
house	I-place
,	O
in	O
Poppings	I-place
Ally	I-place
Fleet-Street	I-place
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sannear	I-pers
,	O
Journeymen	O
Weavers	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Words	O
arising	O
concerning	O
the	O
deadness	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
a	O
Stranger	O
who	O
sat	O
near	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
make	O
such	O
Complaints	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
and	O
incouragement	O
of	O
your	O
Trade	O
,	O
has	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Act	O
for	O
prohibiting	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Callicoes	O
.	O
In	O
return	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
King	O
George	O
and	O
his	O
Laws	O
too	O
!	O
we	O
shall	O
never	O
have	O
any	O
Good	O
Trade	O
while	O
he	O
's	O
alive	O
.	O
That	O
from	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
afterward	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
12	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
broke	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
Samuel	B-pers
Crumpler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
a	O
bed	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Boyse	I-pers
;	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
Master	O
Thatcher	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Crumpler	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Boyse	I-pers
,	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
this	O
Story	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Crumpler	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
(	O
on	O
cross	O
examining	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
)	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Crampler	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
Samuel	O
had	O
been	O
Journeymen	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
Samuel	O
for	O
some	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
discharg	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Service	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Crumpler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
very	O
Day	O
on	O
which	O
they	O
laid	O
this	O
Charge	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
John	O
thereupon	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
a	O
Chub	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
'd	O
make	O
a	O
Chub	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
Samuel	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Bride	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
agreed	O
that	O
since	O
their	O
Master	O
was	O
a	O
Chub	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
get	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sannear	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
dusk	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Crumpler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
when	O
John	B-pers
Crumpler	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
discourse	O
about	O
their	O
being	O
turn	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
John	O
Crumpler	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
question	O
but	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
hence	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
but	O
Samuel	O
Crumpler	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Hat	O
(	O
or	O
Magpye	O
)	O
in	O
Poppings	O
Ally	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
2	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Company	O
till	O
they	O
all	O
parted	O
.	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
such	O
Words	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
far	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
Words	O
had	O
been	O
spoken	O
.	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers	O
he	O
askt	O
Samuel	O
Crumpler	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
summon	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
for	O
turning	O
him	O
off	O
without	O
the	O
usual	O
warning	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Brothers	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Company	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
(	O
or	O
Hat	O
)	O
in	O
Poppings	O
Ally	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
nothing	O
like	O
the	O
words	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Valentine	O
Henny	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Henny	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
's	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Trial	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Lawn	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Langdale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Stafford	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Langdale	O
to	O
be	O
clearstarch	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Fortune	O
teller	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
he	O
gave	O
,	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
confess	O
they	O
'd	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sawcult	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Bathmetal	O
gilt	O
Equipage	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
rob	O
'd	O
between	O
Mile	B-place
end	I-place
and	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
an	O
Equipage	O
from	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
's	O
Side	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
told	O
3	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
came	O
riding	O
by	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Equipage	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
very	O
exactly	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
'd	O
give	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
at	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Maddy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
7	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
Haws	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
's	O
Equipage	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
Haws	O
's	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
2	O
Horses	O
fixt	O
to	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
said	O
Joan	O
Cornish	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
she	O
received	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquistion	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
in	O
feloniously	O
killing	O
the	O
said	O
Joan	O
Cornish	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
crossing	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
the	O
Nags-head	B-place
between	O
Shoreditch	B-place
and	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Yoak	O
and	O
two	O
Milk-pails	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drove	O
his	O
Horses	O
fiercely	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
trampled	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
the	O
fore	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
over	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
her	O
Death	O
Bed	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
forward	O
,	O
he	O
whipt	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
over	O
her	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Alvear	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
Moses	O
Alvear	O
,	O
being	O
sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
Moses	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
hot	O
headed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stopt	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
the	O
People	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
descending	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
his	O
Horses	O
such	O
a	O
sudden	O
check	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
.	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hanwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Murden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
wooden	O
Draw	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	O
Murden	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Murden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Demar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
on	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
Indictments	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
South	B-place
Mims	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Ostler	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Bezaleel	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
in	O
Hartfordshire	O
,	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Hunt	O
had	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Sole	O
Leather	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Last	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
having	O
got	O
a	O
new	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Four	O
on	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Journeymen	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
Leather	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
them	O
for	O
making	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Last	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
was	O
last	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Duston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
some	O
Shoes	O
made	O
among	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Workmen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Leather	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
making	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
sold	O
Leather	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Several	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
by	O
discharging	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaden	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Bullets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hearing	O
that	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
kept	O
Company	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
marry	O
'd	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
married	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Lynn	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
Sarah	O
Thomson	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
a	O
surly	O
Answer	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
among	O
those	O
that	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Will	O
.	O
Thomson	O
,	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
hir	O
'd	O
James	B-pers
Gush	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Trunk	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
Gush	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
an	O
Entry	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
carrying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
latching	O
the	O
Entry	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Gush	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Trunk	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Lock	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mary	O
Freeman	O
,	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
without	O
coming	O
to	O
Account	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
Share	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Malcolm	B-pers
Gillis	I-pers
,	O
Twenty	O
Yard	O
,	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Malcolm	B-pers
Gillis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Gush	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
seeing	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
as	O
they	O
past	O
by	O
,	O
Vaughan	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
at	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
a	O
each	O
,	O
but	O
Mary	O
Freeman	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Skill	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomson	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Earpicker	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Toothpicker	O
,	O
2	O
d	O
a	O
Lancet	O
,	O
2	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Mary	O
Wells	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
found	O
her	O
Scrutore	O
broke	O
,	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Lodgers	O
gone	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
3	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
Thomson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
that	O
he	O
borrowed	O
the	O
three	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jean	B-pers
Widgen	I-pers
alias	O
Jiles	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Ghenting	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
,	O
Pinner	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
often	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Felony	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
James	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
six	O
Years	O
ago	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
what	O
Sum	O
,	O
only	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Heatly	O
,	O
alias	O
Agnal	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Jackson	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Draw	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Evidence	O
contradicting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
certain	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Gold	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Heatly	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
lying	O
for	O
Transportation	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
Convication	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Oak	O
knees	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Wainscot	O
Boards	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
at	O
Execution	O
Dock	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
by	O
Water	O
to	O
Paul	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Royton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Edlin	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edlin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
kept	O
a	O
Booksellers	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Draw	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
likewise	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cranky	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
loft	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
for	O
45	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Upon	O
search	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
near	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gibb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sweetapple	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
Harding	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
:	O
that	O
Harding	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Middle	O
Row	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
that	O
Young	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Crow	O
,	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
Crow	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Leaky	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
4	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Derothy	O
East	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
with	O
a	O
Nail	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Widow	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hitchman	B-pers
,	O
Spinster	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
Widow	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bouch	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Bouch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
borrow	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Landlady	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
for	O
2	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
owing	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
for	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lory	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chadwell	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Charwoman	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Lory	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
Mary	B-pers
Chadwell	I-pers
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dorton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
a	O
party	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
deliver	O
himself	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
granted	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
following	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Molinere	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Alton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Noguiere	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Turbat	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Du	I-pers
Vimm	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mackall	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Daubez	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomeiure	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Truchard	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
dark	O
Corner	O
,	O
near	O
Deans	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
breast	O
with	O
his	O
Elbow	O
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
his	O
other	O
to	O
her	O
Neck	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
crying	O
you	O
Bitch	O
give	O
me	O
them	O
Rings	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
wear	O
Rings	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Friend	O
(	O
who	O
just	O
parted	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
)	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
began	O
to	O
gather	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
going	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
drag	O
'd	O
her	O
along	O
the	O
Ground	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Yards	O
,	O
without	O
once	O
letting	O
her	O
Hand	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Rings	O
off	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
then	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
.	O
Botfield	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
just	O
parted	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
Lamp	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
afterwards	O
rise	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Lamp	O
dazling	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
full	O
against	O
this	O
Evidence	O
who	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
Wig	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Woman	O
crying	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
toward	O
the	O
Croud	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
Botfield	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
3d	O
person	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
rescue	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Botfield	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
before	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
Rings	O
off	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
in	O
hast	O
he	O
out	O
walk	O
'd	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Lamp	O
dazling	O
his	O
Eyes	O
)	O
he	O
ran	O
accidentally	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Botfield	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Collard	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
struggled	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
again	O
,	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Mob	O
was	O
soon	O
gather	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
accused	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
with	O
robbing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
Friend	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Hankerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Two	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
Rings	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
2	O
Boys	O
found	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
play	O
in	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
6	O
pence	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
askt	O
her	O
how	O
the	O
Boys	O
knew	O
the	O
Rings	O
were	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
her	O
Name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
were	O
wrote	O
in	O
the	O
Rings	O
for	O
Posies	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
flew	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
but	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
never	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
.	O
So	O
many	O
palpable	O
Contradictions	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
on	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Extraordinary	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Boarden	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
linnen	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	O
Boarden	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
King	B-place
street	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
she	O
felt	O
something	O
very	O
unaccountable	O
about	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
then	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
whom	O
she	O
kept	O
in	O
her	O
Eye	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Woman	O
has	O
the	O
fall	O
hurt	O
you	O
?	O
that	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
asking	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
self	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
Robbing	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
pastry	O
Cooks	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Masons	O
)	O
where	O
they	O
stript	O
him	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
.	O
value	O
14	O
s	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
off	O
a	O
Line	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
Charles	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
(	O
a	O
Shoe	O
cleaner	O
and	O
Link	O
Boy	O
)	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Page	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Shirt	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Holms	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Page	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
James	O
Harvy	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Saddle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
since	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
(	O
a	O
Saddlers	O
Shop	O
)	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
.	O
Darby	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
Contradiction	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Cholmley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
,	O
by	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
John	B-pers
Hemlichen	I-pers
,	O
who	O
with	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Brass	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Musquet	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
Bowes	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Belly	O
,	O
1	O
Inch	O
broad	O
and	O
6	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
5	O
o	O
'	O
th	O
'	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Hartshorn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Playhouse	B-place
Passage	I-place
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
sudden	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
about	O
20	O
Men	O
with	O
long	O
Sticks	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
beat	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Cholmley	O
and	O
Vaughan	O
we	O
have	O
them	O
all	O
fast	O
;	O
others	O
,	O
Break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
Knock	O
'em	O
down	O
.	O
That	O
Cholmley	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n'em	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have'em	O
or	O
fire	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shut	O
again	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
and	O
lighted	O
Links	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
lighted	O
Links	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
Soldier	O
then	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
several	O
People	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
flash	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
heard	O
it	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
wounded	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Meal	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
's	O
Shop	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Mob	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Vanderman	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
Cholmley	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Guards	O
then	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
Window-shutter	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
(	O
which	O
had	O
Hinges	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
fasten	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
with	O
a	O
Pin	O
or	O
Button	O
)	O
one	O
Soldier	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
whilst	O
two	O
enter	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
then	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
within	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
Colonel	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
away	O
.	O
Brickbats	O
were	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Soldier	O
enter	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Vintner	O
joining	O
to	O
Vanderman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
knocking	O
their	O
Links	O
against	O
Vanderman	O
's	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
Cholmley	O
bidding	O
'em	O
fire	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
those	O
within	O
making	O
no	O
other	O
resistance	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
beating	O
back	O
the	O
Links	O
with	O
their	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
thrust	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
say	O
,	O
Read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
-	O
Come	O
out	O
ye	O
Dogs	O
and	O
surrender	O
,	O
or	O
ye	O
shall	O
all	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
wounded	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
opposite	O
to	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Mob	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
Passage	O
with	O
long	O
Sticks	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
at	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Open	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Name	O
!	O
those	O
within	O
answer	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
then	O
beat	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
till	O
it	O
flew	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n'em	O
we	O
have'em	O
all	O
safe	O
-	O
more	O
Lights	O
here	O
:	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
then	O
shut	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
.	O
Those	O
within	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
ye	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
us	O
?	O
the	O
others	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Lay	O
your	O
Swords	O
down	O
then	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
then	O
set	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
lighting	O
a	O
Link	O
from	O
one	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
flaming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
Those	O
within	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
without	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
murder	O
ye	O
all	O
!	O
Will	O
ye	O
surrender	O
ye	O
Rogues	O
?	O
The	O
Soldiers	O
then	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Corporal	O
asking	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
House	O
is	O
full	O
of	O
Rogues	O
and	O
Whores	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
want	O
to	O
get'em	O
out	O
.	O
One	O
then	O
helpt	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Those	O
without	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
go	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
'll	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
went	O
in	O
with'em	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after'em	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
what	O
People	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
down	O
with'em	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
Open	O
the	O
Door	O
you	O
Rascals	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
your	O
Officer	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
from	O
within	O
putting	O
the	O
Muzzle	O
of	O
his	O
Piece	O
thro	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
flasht	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
heard	O
one	O
within	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n'em	O
,	O
fire	O
among'em	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
then	O
opened	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
fired	O
down	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
wounded	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
saw	O
Vaughan	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
tho	O
before	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
Chomley	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
James	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
looking	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Wicket	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
(	O
after	O
the	O
Soldier	O
had	O
flasht	O
his	O
piece	O
)	O
he	O
saw	O
Vaughan	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
black	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Soldier	O
if	O
his	O
Piece	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
?	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
then	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
Vaughan	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
Fire	O
among'em	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
indemnify	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
Soldier	O
fir	O
'd	O
slanting	O
towards	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fall	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Denman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Eating-house	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Mob	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
say	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
disperse	O
ye	O
Dogs	O
?	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
else	O
to	O
morrow	O
.	O
-	O
All	O
you	O
that	O
are	O
Prisoners	O
here	O
,	O
surrender	O
on	O
pain	O
of	O
death	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
Brickbats	O
were	O
thrown	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Soldier	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
do	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Fire	O
,	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
indemnify	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
fir	O
'd	O
(	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'th	O
'	O
Clock	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fall	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
into	O
an	O
Eating-house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
happened	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
standing	O
quietly	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Arms	O
folded	O
in	O
his	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
One	O
Woodcock	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Vaughan	O
beat	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
fly	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Fire	O
the	O
House	O
!	O
He	O
then	O
saw	O
Links	O
set	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Brickbats	O
thrown	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
Vaughan	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spike	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
o	O
n't	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
run	O
the	O
Stick	O
through	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
frighted	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
these	O
Evidences	O
swore	O
that	O
Vaughan	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
grey	O
Coat	O
with	O
Brass	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wounds	O
the	O
Deceased	O
then	O
receiv	O
'd	O
were	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
far	O
from	O
intending	O
any	O
harm	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
Ten	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
Gaming	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
disorderly	O
Houses	O
,	O
they	O
accordingly	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
noted	O
Gaming	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
outward	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hatch	O
with	O
Spikes	O
,	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
steps	O
within	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
both	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Gaming	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
about	O
20	O
sitting	O
round	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
seeing	O
them	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
Constables	O
Staves	B-pers
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
taken	O
!	O
Put	O
the	O
Candles	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
your	O
Swords	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
stepping	O
back	O
,	O
his	O
Coat	O
hung	O
by	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
within	O
made	O
passes	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
more	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
aid	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
by	O
tearing	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Gamesters	O
follow'd'em	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
increased	O
,	O
and	O
Oaths	O
,	O
Curses	O
,	O
and	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
were	O
continually	O
flying	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Proclamation	O
against	O
Riots	O
was	O
then	O
read	O
;	O
and	O
telling	O
them	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
askt	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
surrender	O
,	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
have	O
our	O
Swords	O
in	O
your	O
Guts	O
.	O
The	O
Gamesters	O
then	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
within	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
flung	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
Drinking	O
Pots	O
,	O
Piss-pots	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
then	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
one	O
of'em	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
which	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
then	O
without	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Now	O
we	O
have'em	O
all	O
safe	O
together	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
in	O
the	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
threw	O
out	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Solidier	O
then	O
flasht	O
through	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
any	O
Orders	O
to	O
fire	O
.	O
Cholmley	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
being	O
commanded	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Burt	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cartwright	O
to	O
assist'em	O
in	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
2	O
Warrants	O
,	O
obey	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
their	O
Duty	O
in	O
aiding	O
proper	O
Officers	O
at	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
wanting	O
more	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Lives	O
being	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
military	O
Force	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
additional	O
strength	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
without	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
Burden	O
and	O
Ringrose	O
assuming	O
themselves	O
to	O
be	O
Colonels	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
drew	O
off	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
then	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
The	O
Colonel	O
's	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
are	O
going	O
,	O
now	O
let	O
us	O
murder	O
the	O
Dogs	O
!	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Gun	O
fir	O
'd	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
for	O
searching	O
Gaming	O
and	O
other	O
disorderly	O
Houses	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
Ten	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
several	O
other	O
Constables	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Warrant	O
was	O
openly	O
read	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
commanded	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
to	O
Aid	O
and	O
Assist	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
lewd	O
Houses	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
took	O
divers	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
came	O
to	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Play-house	O
Passage	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
stept	O
up	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
thrusting	O
their	O
Staves	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Jamb	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
before	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
shut	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Hatch	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Lights	O
,	O
came	O
with	O
their	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Hatch	O
being	O
pretty	O
high	O
with	O
Spikes	O
at	O
top	O
,	O
he	O
couch	O
'd	O
down	O
so	O
close	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Swords	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
crawl	O
'd	O
away	O
on	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
engag	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
long	O
Staff	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
within	O
quickly	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
longest	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
poising	O
down	O
hard	O
upon	O
the	O
Hatch	O
to	O
wrench	O
it	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
likewise	O
bearing	O
down	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Staff	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
consulted	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
agreed	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Somerset-	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
Guards	O
.	O
Those	O
within	O
then	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
threw	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
drinking	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chamber	O
Pot	O
full	O
of	O
Piss	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
then	O
fasten	O
'd	O
the	O
Window	O
shutter	O
(	O
which	O
hung	O
by	O
hinges	O
at	O
top	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
within	O
force	O
'd	O
it	O
open	O
again	O
.	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
The	O
Guards	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
my	O
self	O
will	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
Search	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
Gamesters	O
who	O
had	O
hid	O
themselves	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
Some	O
under	O
the	O
Beds	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
Closets	O
and	O
other	O
Holes	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
employ	O
'd	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
call	O
from	O
below	O
.	O
Cartwright	O
,	O
Cartwright	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
be	O
Murder	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Gaming	O
Room	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
all	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
below	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Burden	O
and	O
Ringrose	O
had	O
rescu	O
'd	O
a	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Coming	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
those	O
without	O
cry	O
Now	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
informing	O
Dogs	O
!	O
Murder	O
them	O
,	O
Murder	O
them	O
!	O
Ringrose	O
seeing	O
this	O
Evidence	O
through	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
ye	O
Dog	O
!	O
I	O
'll	O
Murder	O
you	O
to	O
chuse	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
flasht	O
through	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
without	O
cry	O
'd	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
Dogs	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
think	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
bugbear	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Powder	O
?	O
That	O
if	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Soldier	O
had	O
not	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
their	O
own	O
lives	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
danger	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Vaughan	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
once	O
bid	O
the	O
Solider	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Cholmley	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirme	O
'd	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
another	O
Constable	O
.	O
Jeffery	O
Nash	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Recorder	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
Richard	B-pers
Mytton	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Walmsley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
charged	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
above	O
600	O
Pounds	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Wyche-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
in	O
conjuction	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cartwright	O
,	O
commanded	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
others	O
present	O
,	O
to	O
Aid	O
and	O
Assist	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
further	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
Cartwright	O
and	O
Burt	O
had	O
already	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Another	O
Constable	O
John	B-pers
Bouch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
in	O
Cartwright	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
cry	O
out	O
D	O
-	O
the	O
Rogues	O
,	O
now	O
's	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
kill	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
