TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
:	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1722	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracey	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Efq	O
:	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heywood	I-pers
,	O
Benoni	B-pers
Pistor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Heydon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Beddle	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pashly	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Arnott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Broadhead	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Mugg	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stop	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
one	O
Kirby	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rodin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
unnatural	O
and	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
,	O
at	O
Peter	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
3	B-place
Shoes	I-place
in	O
Long	B-place
Alley	I-place
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
;	O
that	O
sometime	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
day	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
accidentally	O
came	O
thither	O
to	O
Lodge	O
;	O
at	O
night	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
stranger	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Moonlight	O
night	O
:	O
the	O
stranger	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acted	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
in	O
Cohabiting	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
more	O
pleasure	O
in	O
lying	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
than	O
with	O
the	O
finest	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
being	O
askt	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
sooner	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
his	O
Landlady	O
Wright	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
l.	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
clear	O
'd	O
that	O
Account	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
indicted	O
his	O
Landlady	O
at	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
for	O
a	O
Bawd	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
moved	O
with	O
a	O
Certiorari	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
prefer	O
'd	O
the	O
Bill	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Clayton	O
was	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Villain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
honest	O
ignorant	O
industrious	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
business	O
commonly	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
by	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
sat	O
up	O
so	O
late	O
as	O
Clayton	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Clayton	O
had	O
spitefully	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
Indicted	O
Angelica	B-pers
Lathom	I-pers
,	O
who	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
Clayton	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Husbands	O
beside	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
together	O
above	O
a	O
12	O
Month	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Craft	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dace	I-pers
3	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Dace	I-pers
being	O
Drunk	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
o	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
observing	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Buttons	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Buttons	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Murden	I-pers
,	O
3	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
:	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
another	O
Woman	O
inticed	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Feather	O
Beds	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Bromly	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
l.	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Barge	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
for	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
saw	O
,	O
4	O
men	O
upon	O
the	O
Barge	O
door	O
who	O
perceiving	O
him	O
went	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
;	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Barge	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
lying	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Hoops	O
stript	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cake	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
parted	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
looking	O
further	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leaning	O
on	O
another	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Wharsinger	O
at	O
the	O
Key	O
where	O
the	O
Barge	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
stow	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Barge	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
:	O
who	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
he	O
believed	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mattison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Suttle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
George	O
Suttle	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
he	O
marked	O
several	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpences	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
afterward	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
being	O
Examined	O
,	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mawston	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mawston	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
under	O
Ludgate	B-place
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Mr.Wyser	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
searching	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyser	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Alston	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
between	O
the	O
fine	O
Pleats	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
out	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Williams	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
Williams	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Williams	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
Alston	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wedgwood	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hinton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brushed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
trod	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Swail	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
3	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
7	O
s.	O
3	O
Smocks	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Head	O
cloths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Swail	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hewit	O
,	O
confest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jasper	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonionsly	O
stealing	O
47	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Broome	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Broome	O
to	O
Trim	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
yard	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
.	O
Huckle	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Stockings	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Debt	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
all	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
Night	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wise	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Stranger	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
pair	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
Hosier	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Stranger	O
agreed	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
Answer	O
;	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
story	O
contradicting	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
himself	O
said	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turbat	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
the	O
following	O
wicked	O
and	O
seditious	O
Words	O
;	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
George	O
!	O
Who	O
made	O
him	O
King	O
?	O
The	O
Devil	O
:	O
for	O
he	O
's	O
his	O
Uncle	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
Bow-lane	B-place
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
crying	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
horrid	O
barbarous	O
and	O
bloody	O
Plot	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
(	O
crying	O
another	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
)	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Plot	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
George	O
?	O
D	O
-	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
him	O
King	O
?	O
The	O
Devil	O
:	O
For	O
he	O
's	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Prow	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
several	O
other	O
vile	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Expressions	O
against	O
His	O
Majesty	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
repeated	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
her	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Spight	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
Men	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
Questions	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phelp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Rumbal	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Cane-Hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rumbal	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
towards	O
Holloway	B-place
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
they	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
they	O
enquir	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
directed	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
bye	O
Way	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Seven	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
over	O
took	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Apron	O
.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
Mary	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
bear	O
his	O
Charges	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
him	O
back	O
6d	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Field	O
Lane	O
Holborn	O
,	O
was	O
Sick	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
past	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
several	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Michael	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Laced-Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Horse-Guards	O
and	O
Admiralty	B-place
Office	I-place
,	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
somebody	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
several	O
others	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Sedgwick	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Hat	O
at	O
the	O
Guard-House	O
which	O
she	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Sedgwick	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
knockt	O
Paxton	O
down	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Devil	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Drunk	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
disproved	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
replyed	O
,	O
he	O
wonder	O
'd	O
how	O
they	O
could	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
be	O
led	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
thither	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blacklock	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wigg	I-pers
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boddice	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Clogs	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
(	O
Sisters	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
their	O
Trunks	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Trunks	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
several	O
things	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
scattered	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wigg	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
an	O
opposite	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
down	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
a	O
Char	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
haste	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
crouded	O
by	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
and	O
another	O
(	O
not	O
William	O
Jones	O
)	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
back	O
Window	O
,	O
one	O
Story	O
high	O
,	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
upon	O
Williams	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
.	O
Williams	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
jumpt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
Holland	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
that	O
Window	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
sight	O
of	O
Holland	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Williams	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Molton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Holloway	O
's	O
Window	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
escap	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
Boys	O
pursuing	O
him	O
to	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
among	O
the	O
Logs	O
of	O
Timber	O
,	O
from	O
Whence	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Williams	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Holloway	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
conducted	O
up	O
Stairs	O
backwards	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
Williams	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
Oxendon-Street	B-place
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
(	O
having	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
and	O
ruin	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
seem	O
'd	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Rogue	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
discredit	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
Parish	O
in	O
New	O
Sarum	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Church	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
of	O
February	O
1706.	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
:	O
whom	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
alive	O
within	O
these	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Edward	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
first	O
Wife	O
ask	O
'd	O
this	O
Evidence	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
married	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
her	O
Aunt	O
dy	O
'd	O
last	O
Lady-Day	O
.	O
O	O
!	O
says	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
Molly	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
He	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Parish	O
Register	O
to	O
confirm	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
(	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
co-habited	O
with	O
him	O
three	O
Nights	O
,	O
when	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cliftons	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Swan	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
by	O
Licence	O
from	O
the	O
Archbishop	O
's	O
Court	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
)	O
he	O
married	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
at	O
St.	O
Peter	O
's	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Far	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Salisbury	O
for	O
a	O
Certificate	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
with	O
Three	O
Children	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
by	O
several	O
Letters	O
that	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
and	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
second	O
Wife	O
(	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
Salisbury	O
14	O
Years	O
ago	O
)	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
set	O
her	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
expected	O
she	O
'd	O
leave	O
him	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
when	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
Clifton	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Wife	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Farr	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Barclay	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Mills	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Morning	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Apron	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Apron	O
was	O
after	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lane	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Weaver	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
invited	O
to	O
a	O
Christening	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
for	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
empty	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
met	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
not	O
being	O
present	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Frances	O
Norris	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
her	O
Chairwoman	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
beg	O
for	O
a	O
Nights	O
Lodging	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mashalsea	O
;	O
she	O
entertain	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
leaving	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Dumolin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
Peter	O
Dumolin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
which	O
the	O
Parish	O
pays	O
the	O
Rent	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
either	O
the	O
Day	O
or	O
the	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
set	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Carrick	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
alias	O
Newcomb	O
(	O
both	O
executed	O
)	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Sturges	O
,	O
Newcomb	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
Dumolin	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
French	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
had	O
50	O
l.	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
prevented	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
their	O
first	O
Purpose	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
off	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
shut	O
into	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
coming	O
their	O
Rounds	O
hindered	O
their	O
Entrance	O
,	O
they	O
set	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
board	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
their	O
Pistols	O
:	O
The	O
Watch	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
ventured	O
down	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
disturbed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
this	O
Evidence	O
then	O
got	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Candle	O
at	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
short	O
burnt	O
his	O
Fingers	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
felt	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
round	O
again	O
occasioned	O
them	O
to	O
retire	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
their	O
present	O
adventure	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Celler	O
door	O
after	O
much	O
search	O
being	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
Dumolin	O
was	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gang	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
intire	O
retreat	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
Lock	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Clementia	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Breast	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
in	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Clementia	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
(	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
)	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bolton	O
(	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Husband	O
.	O
)	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
off	O
his	O
own	O
in	O
Stretton	B-place
Grounds	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Bolton	O
's	O
Dog	O
flew	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Dog	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
passion	O
,	O
swore	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
ye	O
Dog	O
do	O
you	O
assault	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
Bolton	O
himself	O
began	O
to	O
strip	O
to	O
Fight	O
Thornton	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Evidence	O
held	O
him	O
.	O
Thornton	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
again	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
Ill	O
Names	O
:	O
the	O
Deceased	O
then	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
heed	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Steps	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
bid	O
the	O
deceased	O
go	O
off	O
her	O
ground	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
not	O
regarding	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
at	O
her	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
She	O
fell	O
backwards	O
and	O
dyed	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Thornton	O
,	O
Go	O
ye	O
Dog	O
,	O
lye	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Bitch	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
Sprinkle	O
Water	O
on	O
ye	O
both	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chub	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
Thornton	O
at	O
the	O
Rails	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Rails	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
her	O
Parish	O
Clem	O
!	O
several	O
times	O
bid	O
her	O
begone	O
,	O
and	O
pusht	O
at	O
her	O
with	O
both	O
hands	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
reach	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Shirly	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
punch	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
their	O
Quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Dog	O
flew	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
calling	O
him	O
off	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
(	O
the	O
deceased	O
)	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
punch	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
persuaded	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
Breast	O
.	O
He	O
going	O
by	O
Bolton	O
's	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Dog	O
,	O
Rougue	O
,	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
ill	O
Names	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
her	O
Parish	O
Clem	O
!	O
and	O
running	O
at	O
her	O
with	O
both	O
hands	O
,	O
pusht	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
:	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seeing	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
See	O
how	O
she	O
Bitch	O
Shams	O
it	O
?	O
Go	O
ye	O
Dog	O
,	O
lye	O
down	O
by	O
your	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
sprinkle	O
ye	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Small	I-pers
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
opening	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
after	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
that	O
could	O
strictly	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
Mortal	O
;	O
the	O
right	O
lobe	O
of	O
her	O
Lungs	O
adher	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Pluera	O
,	O
her	O
Liver	O
was	O
diseas	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
blood	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
her	O
Heart	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
whole	O
Mass	O
rais	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
superiour	O
parts	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
possible	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
strangled	O
purely	O
by	O
the	O
violent	O
Emotion	O
of	O
the	O
Wind	O
in	O
Scolding	O
;	O
though	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
when	O
the	O
Passions	O
were	O
so	O
extravagantly	O
raised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
put	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
ferment	O
in	O
a	O
body	O
so	O
weak	O
,	O
a	O
sudden	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
might	O
very	O
much	O
contribute	O
to	O
her	O
death	O
:	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
doubt	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
determine	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
severe	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
which	O
yet	O
had	O
not	O
occasion	O
'd	O
any	O
Extravasated	O
blood	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Eruption	O
of	O
the	O
Vessels	O
;	O
the	O
right	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
adher	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Pleura	O
;	O
the	O
Blood	O
was	O
hurried	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
little	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
.	O
The	O
Intestines	O
were	O
so	O
inflamed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
blown	O
up	O
artificially	O
,	O
and	O
compress	O
'd	O
the	O
Diapbragma	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Lungs	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
blood	O
left	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
blow	O
was	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
time	O
to	O
recover	O
themselves	O
and	O
breath	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
injur	O
'd	O
a	O
stronger	O
Person	O
in	O
other	O
circumstances	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Norwood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
push	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
who	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
;	O
Take	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
stick	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
ye	O
nasty	O
white	O
Liver	O
'd	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
may	O
lye	O
down	O
by	O
that	O
Bitch	O
your	O
Wife	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
laid	O
her	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
Rails	O
before	O
the	O
prisoners	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
off	O
of	O
her	O
Ground	O
,	O
run	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
punch	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
with	O
both	O
hands	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
stagger	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
d	O
'ye	O
see	O
!	O
she	O
struck	O
me	O
twice	O
.	O
Bear	O
Witness	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
spoke	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
her	O
Husband	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
the	O
Dog	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
bid	O
Thornton	O
take	O
the	O
Dog	O
and	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Dog	O
your	O
Husband	O
,	O
your	O
Boy	O
,	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
?	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
my	O
Husband	O
sha	O
n't	O
fight	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
her	O
own	O
Husband	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
and	O
likewise	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Thornton	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
in	O
struggling	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
threw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Children	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
and	O
persuaded	O
Thornton	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
ugly	O
Coarse	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
followed	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
poor	O
beggarly	O
Bitch	O
,	O
nasty	O
draggle	O
tail	O
'd	O
toad	O
,	O
ugly	O
Puss	O
,	O
and	O
stinking	O
Punk	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
wash	O
her	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
such	O
language	O
till	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
touching	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Quainton	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lucretia	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
blows	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
behalf	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
peaceable	O
civil	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
addicted	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
and	O
disturb	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
Paul	B-pers
Crony	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Asser	I-pers
,	O
by	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
(	O
since	O
Executed	O
,	O
)	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
gave	O
the	O
said	O
Nathaniel	O
Asser	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29	O
of	O
June	O
1718	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Nathaniel	O
Asser	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Purse	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Nathaniel	O
Asser	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
going	O
from	O
Stepney	B-place
to	O
Hackney	B-place
was	O
Assaulted	O
,	O
Murder	O
'd	O
and	O
rob	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
bye	O
Field	O
;	O
that	O
3	O
Persons	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
Emery	O
,	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
Audly	O
,	O
had	O
already	O
been	O
Convicted	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
Oliver	B-pers
Fen	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Fact	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
had	O
likewise	O
impeach	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
fled	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
crime	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
already	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
Murder	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Bruise	O
on	O
his	O
Temples	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brag	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
absconded	O
when	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
impeach	O
'd	O
by	O
Oliver	B-pers
Fen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
coming	O
accidentally	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
James	O
Oldage	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
Baltick	O
,	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Tork	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Ships	O
Crew	O
often	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
Rouge	O
,	O
and	O
twit	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
Murder	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
clear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
ye	O
suffer	O
the	O
Law	O
for	O
the	O
Scandal	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
courted	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
lodged	O
at	O
his	O
Mothers	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
impeach	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
uneasie	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
rest	O
till	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
got	O
him	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Deal	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
bare	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
left	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Ship	O
for	O
the	O
Baltick	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
his	O
Mothers	O
fire	O
side	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
wonder	O
's	O
how	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Action	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Fields	O
off	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
afraid	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
'd	O
murder	O
any	O
Man	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
Father	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
Spoke	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Emery	O
,	O
Brown	O
,	O
or	O
Audly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
upon	O
Pens	O
impeachment	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prest	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rivet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
workt	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Brick-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
persons	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Cair	I-pers
Weaver	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Cradle	O
in	O
Brick	O
Lane	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
prest	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
on	O
Board	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Dorsetshire	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
Buck	I-pers
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rose-Mason	I-pers
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
;	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
the	O
Boy	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
usually	O
did	O
lookt	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
bed	O
side	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
leaving	O
it	O
there	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
about	O
7	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
teach	O
French	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Rosemasen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
side	O
,	O
staid	O
till	O
8	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
they	O
find	O
him	O
at	O
Noon	O
at	O
a	O
Cooks	O
,	O
where	O
till	O
then	O
he	O
constantly	O
din	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
,	O
they	O
askt	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
yesterday	O
,	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
long	O
you	O
staid	O
at	O
each	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
satisfied	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
satisfy	O
him	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
gone	O
first	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
mistaken	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Door	O
's	O
lockt	O
.	O
Well	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
10	O
l.	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abel	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Jame	O
Barber	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
Execution	O
day	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
standing	O
in	O
Princes	B-place
Street	I-place
Leicester	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
to	O
hear	O
4	O
Boys	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
Violin	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
prisoners	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
which	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
keeping	O
his	O
hold	O
)	O
pulled	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twitch	O
'd	O
it	O
through	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Masons	O
Chissels	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nevison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
4	O
Chissels	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rockhead	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nevison	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bingley	O
's	O
they	O
left	O
their	O
Tools	O
there	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
27	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Smiths	O
,	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
batter	O
his	O
tools	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
knowing	O
his	O
Mark	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
private	O
Mark	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Family	O
in	O
Scotland	O
for	O
many	O
Generations	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
Method	O
of	O
marking	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
esteem	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
had	O
partly	O
wrought	O
the	O
Tools	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Marks	O
being	O
pretty	O
deep	O
were	O
not	O
quite	O
hammer	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Rockhead	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Tools	O
at	O
an	O
old	O
Iron	O
Shop	O
among	O
other	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
as	O
is	O
common	O
when	O
they	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
useful	O
)	O
hammer'd'em	O
over	O
again	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
appear	O
better	O
for	O
Sale	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
several	O
Smiths	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
usual	O
to	O
buy	O
such	O
things	O
among	O
Old	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
them	O
over	O
again	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
buy	O
Tools	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Iron	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Salver	O
5	O
l.	O
54	O
l.	O
of	O
Bolonia	O
Thrown	O
Silk	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Folwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Darbieau	I-pers
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
held	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Trantum	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
Mary	O
D'arbieau	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Folwell	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
(	O
his	O
Son	O
Nathaniel	O
being	O
then	O
present	O
and	O
assisting	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
scrupulous	O
of	O
dealing	O
with	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
Trantum	O
)	O
did	O
not	O
yet	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
thorow	O
faced	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
satisfied	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
Villian	O
,	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
trusted	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Ducking-Pond	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Spaw	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Qualifications	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
:	O
which	O
Trantum	O
did	O
;	O
by	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
lately	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nay	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
if	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Safe	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
is	O
well	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
for	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Weights	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
heaviest	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
70	O
l.	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
a	O
Guinea	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
The	O
Plate	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
O	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
safely	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Crown	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
Leonard	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Grey	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Watchhouse	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
cross	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Buyer	O
of	O
Stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Cooper	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Beddow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rotheram	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
near	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
ado	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
notorious	O
for	O
buying	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
instead	O
of	O
clearing	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
serv	O
'd	O
only	O
to	O
confirm	O
what	O
was	O
already	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gayre	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gayre	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Boy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lefevre	I-pers
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
Door	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
Frank	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
according	O
to	O
their	O
Officer	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
)	O
Command	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
,	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
cast	O
his	O
Eye	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Black	O
.	O
The	O
Sight	O
struck	O
him	O
Speechless	O
,	O
his	O
Hair	O
stood	O
an	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Heart	O
sunk	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
be	O
any	O
thing	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
Devil	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
this	O
Consternation	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Comrade	O
slipt	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Mercy	O
on	O
me	O
Frank	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
now	O
recovered	O
his	O
Speech	O
)	O
there	O
's	O
something	O
past	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
What	O
shall	O
we	O
do	O
?	O
The	O
Boy	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
they	O
at	O
length	O
took	O
heart	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
easily	O
have	O
escap	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
as	O
great	O
fear	O
as	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
before	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
out	O
through	O
the	O
Cieling	O
and	O
escap	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
Sleep	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holster	O
Leather	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
while	O
John	B-pers
Furnival	I-pers
was	O
asleep	O
upon	O
the	O
Quilts	O
at	O
the	O
Guard	O
at	O
White-hall	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Caps	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
Boy	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
Furnival	O
awaked	O
,	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Caps	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Caps	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Furnival	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
charg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
Matth.ew	O
Dowling	O
.	O
All	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Recceiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
4.	O
William	B-pers
Marr	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Molson	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
5.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mattison	I-pers
,	O
Jalper	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Two	O
first	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
Matth.ew	O
Dowling	O
.	O
All	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
13.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Craft	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blacklock	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Barclay	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glinister	I-pers
Lewis	B-pers
Furges	I-pers
,	O
Abel	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
he	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wedgwood	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turbat	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Boe-lane	O
end	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bristom	I-pers
to	O
suffer	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
will	O
suffer	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
S.	O
,	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
KING	O
:	O
THE	O
Rights	O
of	O
Sovereign	O
,	O
and	O
Subjects	O
.	O
By	O
Father	O
PAUL	O
the	O
Venetian	O
.	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Council	O
of	O
Trent	O
.	O
Transcrib	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Italian	O
.	O
and	O
compar	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
French	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
from	O
Felgentius	O
,	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
writings	O
and	O
his	O
Character	O
by	O
several	O
eminent	O
Prelates	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
foreign	O
Divines	O
of	O
the	O
reform	O
'd	O
Church	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
by	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
and	O
Sir	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wak	I-pers
,	O
Kts	O
who	O
were	O
Ambassadors	O
from	O
King	O
James	O
I.	O
to	O
Venice	O
and	O
Turin	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Appendix	O
.	O
shewing	O
the	O
Father	O
's	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
Power	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
so	O
much	O
controverted	O
Text	O
,	O
My	O
Kingdom	O
is	O
not	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Graves	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
W.	O
Meadows	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
J	O
Hocke	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
N	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
world	O
is	O
obliged	O
for	O
the	O
Publication	O
of	O
this	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
the	O
Authors	O
particular	O
desire	O
,	O
was	O
preserv	O
'd	O
in	O
M	O
S.	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
of	O
the	O
Senate	O
of	O
Venice	O
;	O
to	O
an	O
illustrious	O
Nobleman	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
much	O
difficulty	O
obtain	O
'd	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
lately	O
Printed	O
at	O
the	O
Hague	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Second	O
Edition	O
of	O
THE	O
Life	O
an	O
Actions	O
of	O
LEWIS	B-pers
DOMINIQUE	I-pers
CARTOUCHE	I-pers
,	O
the	O
famous	O
French	O
Robber	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
broken	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
education	O
in	O
the	O
College	O
of	O
Jesuits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pranks	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
robberies	O
he	O
committed	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
turning	O
Thief	O
taker	O
;	O
how	O
after	O
several	O
and	O
various	O
escapes	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
which	O
defy	O
'd	O
the	O
publick	O
Justice	O
of	O
France	O
above	O
Seven	O
Years	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
relation	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
.	O
Also	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
bold	O
and	O
undaunted	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Confinement	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Scaffold	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
a	O
Series	O
of	O
Adventures	O
and	O
Incidents	O
,	O
remarkable	O
,	O
entertaining	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
variety	O
.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
just	O
arriv	O
'd	O
from	O
France	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Watwick-Lane	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
CARTOUCHE	O
or	O
the	O
ROBBERS	O
,	O
a	O
Comedy	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
Acted	O
many	O
Times	O
with	O
great	O
Applause	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
By	O
Monsieur	O
Le	O
Grand	O
.	O
Comedian	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
French	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
B	O
O	O
O	O
K	O
S	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
at	O
the	O
R	O
O	O
S	O
E	O
in	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Tables	O
(	O
commonly	O
called	O
Sir	O
Isaac	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
's	O
)	O
for	O
Renewing	O
and	O
Purchasing	O
of	O
the	O
Leates	O
of	O
Cathedral	O
Churches	O
and	O
Colleges	O
,	O
the	O
.II	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
D.D	O
,	O
containing	O
an	O
Exposition	O
on	O
the	O
Commandments	O
and	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
servants	O
in	O
Folio	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Edition	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
D.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Edwards	I-pers
'	O
,	O
Body	O
of	O
Divinity	O
,	O
2.Vol.Folio	O
IV.M.Newcombs	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	O
I	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
useful	O
Clerk	O
like	O
Contradictions	O
of	O
Words	O
,	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
,	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
,	O
how	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
Elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
office	O
.	O
II.Acquittances	O
and	O
Prorriffory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
Revl	O
.	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
parcels	O
;	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
,	O
several	O
orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant	O
like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
,	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	B-pers
,	O
A	B-pers
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
,	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
Common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetic	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
,	O
by	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-Master	O
in	O
Soho	O
Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
With	O
whom	O
Youth	O
may	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
fitted	O
for	O
business	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Popes-Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
.	O
Without	O
necessity	O
of	O
purging	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
Price	O
l	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
told	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
Johns	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hick's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
session	O
of	O
Scurvy	O
Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Resale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
A	O
useful	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
Persons	O
who	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
misfortune	O
of	O
losing	O
any	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
Sword	O
Blade	O
Notes	O
,	O
Goldsmiths	O
or	O
other	O
Notes	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Dia	O
monds	O
,	O
Jewels	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
Watches	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
UPON	O
Application	O
to	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
Company	O
at	O
Goldsmiths	O
Hall	O
in	O
Foster	O
Lane	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
Warnings	O
printed	O
and	O
delivered	O
,	O
in	O
three	O
Hours	O
time	O
,	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
Jewellers	O
,	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
Watchmakers	O
Shops	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
Bills	O
of	O
Mortality	O
;	O
to	O
prevent	O
and	O
forbid	O
the	O
taking	O
such	O
Notes	O
in	O
payment	O
;	O
and	O
desiring	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
and	O
detain	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Printer	O
and	O
Messengers	O
always	O
attending	O
to	O
dispatch	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Charge	O
thereof	O
if	O
delivered	O
to	O
Gold	O
.	O
Smiths	O
only	O
is	O
11	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
if	O
to	O
Jewellers	O
,	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
Watchmakers	O
is	O
1	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
It	O
having	O
been	O
found	O
by	O
long	O
Experience	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
readiest	O
method	O
for	O
recovering	O
Notes	O
or	O
Goods	O
lost	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
That	O
all	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
Watchmakers	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
are	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
enter	O
their	O
Names	O
and	O
places	O
of	O
abode	O
in	O
the	O
Assay	O
Office	O
at	O
Goldsmiths	O
Hall	O
;	O
whereby	O
the	O
Beadle	O
and	O
Messengers	O
of	O
that	O
Company	O
and	O
no	O
others	O
can	O
give	O
so	O
speedy	O
notice	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
British	O
Recluse	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Secret	O
History	O
of	O
Cicoma	O
,	O
supposed	O
dead	O
.	O
A	O
Novel	O
.	O
Women	O
are	O
Govern	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
stubborn	O
Fate	O
,	O
Their	O
Loves	O
insuperable	O
as	O
their	O
Hate	O
,	O
No	O
Merit	O
their	O
Aversion	O
can	O
remove	O
.	O
Nor	O
it	O
requital	O
can	O
efface	O
their	O
Love	O
.	O
Waller	O
.	O
By	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
,	O
Author	O
of	O
Love	O
in	O
Excess	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
The	O
Fatal	O
Enquiry	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
s.	O
II	O
.	O
LOVE	O
in	O
Excess	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
The	O
Fatal	O
Enquiry	O
.	O
A	O
NOVEL	O
.	O
By	O
Mrs.	O
Haywood	O
.	O
In	O
three	O
Parts	O
in	O
.	O
Price	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
Roman	B-pers
Actor	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Tragedy	O
Written	O
originally	O
by	O
Philip	B-pers
Massenger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
since	O
reviv	O
'd	O
with	O
Alterations	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Spartan	O
Dame	O
.	O
A	O
Tragedy	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Southern	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
All	O
Printed	O
for	O
D.	O
Browne	O
Jun	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Swan	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
An	O
intire	O
System	O
of	O
Arithmetic	O
:	O
or	O
Arithmetic	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Parts	O
.	O
Containing	O
Vulgar	O
,	O
Decimal	O
,	O
Duodecimal	O
,	O
Sexagesimal	O
,	O
Political	O
,	O
Loggarithmetical	O
,	O
Lineal	O
,	O
Instrumental	O
,	O
Algebraical	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Arithmetic	O
of	O
Negatives	O
,	O
and	O
Approximation	O
,	O
or	O
Converging	O
Series	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
Rules	O
New	O
,	O
curious	O
and	O
useful	O
mostly	O
accounted	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
Preface	O
.	O
The	O
Algebraic	O
part	O
is	O
rendered	O
more	O
plain	O
and	O
easie	O
than	O
hath	O
been	O
done	O
,	O
by	O
Instructive	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
,	O
Literally	O
and	O
Numerically	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
method	O
new	O
solving	O
Equations	O
,	O
Simple	O
,	O
Quadratic	O
,	O
Cuti	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
several	O
ways	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
proper	O
Place	O
of	O
this	O
Work	O
are	O
an	O
accurate	O
Table	O
of	O
Logarithms	O
and	O
natural	O
Numbers	O
to	O
such	O
Logarithms	O
with	O
the	O
full	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
in	O
Multiplication.Division	O
,	O
Involution	O
,	O
Evolution	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Solution	O
of	O
all	O
Cases	O
of	O
Compound	O
Interest	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
are	O
24	O
large	O
and	O
Exquisite	O
Tables	O
,	O
done	O
for	O
the	O
valuation	O
of	O
Church	O
or	O
Collage	O
Leases	O
of	O
Land	O
)	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
those	O
of	O
Simple	O
Interest	O
and	O
Discount	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
method	O
of	O
finding	O
the	O
Latter	O
and	O
the	O
present	O
worth	O
of	O
Money	O
for	O
Days	O
,	O
also	O
ample	O
definitions	O
and	O
Explanations	O
of	O
Numbers	O
,	O
Quantities	O
,	O
and	O
Terms	O
used	O
in	O
all	O
Parts	O
of	O
Arithmetic	O
in	O
Alphabetical	O
Order	O
,	O
rendering	O
the	O
whole	O
more	O
intelligible	O
and	O
the	O
easier	O
learned	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Appendix	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
mensuration	O
and	O
Method	O
,	O
far	O
exceeding	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
Arithmetic	O
exam	O
.	O
Necessary	O
for	O
all	O
who	O
would	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
little	O
study	O
,	O
acquire	O
a	O
compleat	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Numbers	O
and	O
Species	O
,	O
or	O
would	O
make	O
any	O
considerable	O
Progress	O
in	O
the	O
mathmatiks	O
,	O
By	O
Edward	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
Genr	I-pers
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Veneral	O
disease.With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
,	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
,	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
short	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
old	O
Gleers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
some	O
hints	O
on	O
the	O
PRACTICAL	O
SCHEME	O
,	O
the	O
Method	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
expos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CAM	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	O
D.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
mears	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
F	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
author	O
at	O
the	O
golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1s	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
The	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hurly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Moughoa	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Clare	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
on	O
Two	O
several	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
for	O
perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
falsely	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Twelve	O
Hundred	O
and	O
One	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
to	O
Cheat	O
the	O
Popish	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Clare	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
,	O
by	O
Colour	O
of	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
Entitled	O
an	O
Act	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
suppressing	O
Tories	O
,	O
Robbers	O
,	O
Rapparies	O
etc	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
1s	O
,	O
6d	O
.	O
)	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
BENJ	O
,	O
MOTTE	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
,	O
(	O
Price	O
3d	O
)	O
.	O
