TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
:	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1722.	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Ramshaw	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Prew	I-pers
,	O
Samnel	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Handy	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
Clande	B-pers
Viet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crouder	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Josiah	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
James	B-pers
Gwinny	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Samnel	B-pers
Worrel	I-pers
,	O
Samnel	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
1	O
Gross	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
where	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Gross	O
of	O
Buttons	O
were	O
pil	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Gross	O
of	O
Buttons	O
in	O
her	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
her	O
Basket	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
thrown	O
into	O
it	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
alias	O
John	O
Hawkins	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmond	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
Thirty	O
three	O
Moidores	O
,	O
value	O
27s	O
.	O
each	O
;	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16s	O
.	O
a	O
half	O
Pistole	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
40s	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
;	O
and	O
eight	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
value	O
23s	O
.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
Guineas	O
and	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Branch	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
Sword	B-place
Blade	I-place
Coffee-House	I-place
in	O
Birchin	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
June	O
3.	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
76	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
Bags	O
.	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee	O
Room	O
.	O
Upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
about	O
60	O
l.	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Swan	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
Coach	O
for	O
York	O
;	O
he	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
Welling	O
in	O
Herfordshire	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Frances	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Drawer	O
with	O
a	O
Cale	O
Knife	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Jennings	O
's	O
who	O
made	O
him	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
3	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Wigs	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Customers	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
left	O
61	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
with	O
Jennings	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Bill	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Spike	O
,	O
at	O
York	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Sum	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
paid	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Jennings	O
another	O
Guineas	O
which	O
he	O
requir	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
trouble	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
excited	O
to	O
this	O
Robbery	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
clean	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Maybell	B-pers
Weyman	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
l.s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
inveigled	O
his	O
Daughter	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Cup	O
to	O
Mott	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold-Smith	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
Things	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
Isabel	O
Bowers	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Isabel	O
complaining	O
of	O
the	O
Severity	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
take	O
her	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
which	O
her	O
Father	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Cup	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Bowers	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter-in-Law	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	O
Boswell	O
,	O
2	O
Sattin	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isabel	B-pers
Banbroft	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Banbroft	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Burlow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
Af	O
ternoon	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
A	O
Child	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
Elizabesh	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
afterwards	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Isabel	B-pers
Banbroft	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Greenland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
feloniously	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Partington	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
immediately	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Bed	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
fall	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Partington	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
latch	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
but	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
before	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Farward	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
be	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turnning	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
without	O
asking	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lenox	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
on	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Bow	O
street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Charwoman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Plane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
James	O
Crow	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Plane	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
who	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Alborough	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Alberoni	B-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Jew	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hapsly	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
giving	O
notice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheet	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
mist	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
it	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
;	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Essex	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Sand	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
Sand	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
hiding	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Sand-bag	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Mug	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Norman	B-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
value	O
55	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
(	O
Carpenter	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
abruptly	O
,	O
without	O
taking	O
either	O
his	O
Tools	O
or	O
his	O
Wages	O
.	O
The	O
Mug	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
Edward	O
Chase	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
.	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Mug	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
might	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
3	O
Days	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
's	O
Work	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
hung	O
the	O
Cloths	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
she	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
)	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cloths	O
off	O
the	O
Line	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw'em	O
lying	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took'em	O
up	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
advertize'em	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
disappointed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Child	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
sent	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
without	O
his	O
Cap	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Cap	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Smock	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
their	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
l	O
weight	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Congreve	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Hemyns	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
looking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Charter-House	O
)	O
and	O
snatch	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Comrades	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Bull	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
who	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
14	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Daughter	O
gave'em	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelberg	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
4	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
being	O
often	O
mist	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Green	O
Goose	O
Fair	O
she	O
met	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
an	O
old	O
Playfellow	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Long	O
Alley	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
:	O
This	O
Brown	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Picklock	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
promised	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Necessity	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pan	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Pan	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
a	O
Carman	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Chap	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Carman	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Boy	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Groat	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lavinia	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elisha	B-pers
Coysh	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Princes-street	B-place
near	O
Cornnill	B-place
,	O
Mr.	O
Coysh	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Rings	O
was	O
afterward	O
found	O
at	O
Mott	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
's	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
White	O
Chapple	O
:	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Betty	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
(	O
since	O
gone	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
)	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
being	O
found	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Silver	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Albright	I-pers
,	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
Albright	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tearl	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Cheapen	O
Rings	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Albright	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
for	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
might	O
be	O
laid	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
call	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Albright	O
mist	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sometime	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Ring	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Morphew	I-pers
and	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrase	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
6	O
Lemons	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
ounces	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
13	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	O
Dennis	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	O
Dennis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Totenham	B-place
Court	I-place
and	I-place
Hampstead	I-place
,	O
having	O
a	O
basket	O
with	O
Lemons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
whose	O
name	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
learned	O
,	O
is	O
Neal	B-pers
O	I-pers
Brian	I-pers
)	O
came	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Speak	O
one	O
Word	O
and	O
I'le	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
drag	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
stript	O
him	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
taking	O
his	O
Basket	O
of	O
Lemons	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
cut	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
With	O
much	O
strugling	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
meeting	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
O	O
Brian	O
made	O
him	O
Escape	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
finished	O
his	O
deposition	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
confest	O
they	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
whilst	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arnot	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
accused	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Elizabeth	O
Arnot	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Crown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
had	O
so	O
little	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
of	O
Dishonesty	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
rest	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wainscot	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
on	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Branbow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
Women	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
17	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Glass	O
afterwards	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
not	O
appearing	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Trial	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Broad	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Henly	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Selby	O
's	O
Recognizince	O
was	O
Estreated	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
them	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kerr	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Prat	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
Bar	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
:	O
in	O
a	O
Tryal	O
relating	O
to	O
a	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Caruthers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
the	O
Spiritual	O
Court	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hutchenson	I-pers
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Cheseldine	I-pers
proved	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Oath	O
,	O
which	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
Swore	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
the	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Court	O
,	O
before	O
Lockwood	O
Rushworth	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hutchenson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
deposition	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
disprov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Witness	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Jennison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Prat	O
,	O
at	O
Guild	B-place
Hall	I-place
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Archiba	O
'd	O
Turner	O
being	O
arrested	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
Debt	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
Turner	O
hir	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Swear	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
(	O
37	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
)	O
paid	O
to	O
Constable	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
1718	O
.	O
A	O
Memorandum	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
Nicholson	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
forg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
Chimny	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
old	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Trial	O
came	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
other	O
particulars	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
Nicholson	O
instead	O
of	O
Confirming	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Management	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
falsify	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Rushfield	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Hogs	O
Bristles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Pitham	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
escap	O
'd	O
,	O
)	O
intic	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
to	O
procure	O
him	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Bristles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
Shop	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Jackman	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
half	O
the	O
real	O
price	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
feloniously	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Suet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Basket	O
Woman	O
in	O
Leaden	O
Hall	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
commonly	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
sell	O
Suet	O
at	O
Tallow	O
Chandler	O
's	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
privately	O
Stuck	O
some	O
ends	O
of	O
Scewers	O
in	O
the	O
Suet	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Tallow	O
Chandler	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Suet	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Scewers	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
accordingly	O
detected	O
.	O
The	O
Suet	O
and	O
Scewers	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Forty	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
46	O
Yards	O
of	O
Long	O
Ells	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
Seamens	O
Jackets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gapper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Infusion	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Crookshank	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
late	O
Fire	O
happened	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Crutched	O
Friers	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Francon	I-pers
's	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Jew	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of'em	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Place	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
found	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Redmane	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Crookshanks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pondesby	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
;	O
and	O
beginning	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Fellow	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
stopt	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
:	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
one	O
Night	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dawson	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hudson	B-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
alias	O
Hudson	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Katherine	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Cross	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
over	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
she	O
stood	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Door	O
to	O
let	O
a	O
Cart	O
go	O
by	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
gave	O
her	O
back	O
the	O
Queen	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Gunnel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
for	O
abusing	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
.	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crib	I-pers
,	O
now	O
at	O
large	O
)	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Latouche	I-pers
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Casements	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crib	I-pers
now	O
at	O
large	O
)	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Casements	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Casements	O
were	O
fast	O
shut	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Glazier	O
)	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Crib	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
2	O
Casements	O
,	O
but	O
Crib	O
none	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
s	O
Clock	O
the	O
Watch	O
saw	O
them	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
each	O
of'em	O
a	O
Casement	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
home	O
to	O
Webb	O
's	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
their	O
Rounds	O
,	O
they	O
mist	O
the	O
Casements	O
off	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Casements	O
behind	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
confest	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Airy	O
,	O
unhook	O
'd	O
the	O
Casements	O
,	O
and	O
gave'em	O
up	O
to	O
Crib	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
try	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Huddle	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
often	O
mist	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawer	O
,	O
she	O
one	O
Night	O
put	O
just	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
it	O
:	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
4	O
Guineas	O
wanting	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
taxing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
fellow	O
Prentice	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Key	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
)	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
but	O
once	O
his	O
fellow	O
Prentice	O
came	O
back	O
unexpectedly	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
gave	O
him	O
11	O
s.	O
more	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kilmane	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
Gaming	O
Table	O
;	O
these	O
particulars	O
this	O
Evidence	O
wrote	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
thing	O
with	O
his	O
Mistress	O
to	O
tax	O
her	O
Servants	O
with	O
Theft	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
she	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
only	O
Apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Maid	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Master	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
)	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
marry	O
'd	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
Father	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
both	O
Mr.	O
Huddle	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
accuse	O
his	O
Son	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Kilmane	O
could	O
lay	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bugby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Barge	O
to	O
Watch	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Sculler	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Deals	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
row	O
to	O
Puddle	O
Dock	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Adams	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mattison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
several	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
which	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
was	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Peacock	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Journey	O
Man	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Gelliman	O
another	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
at	O
Supper	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Books	O
in	O
Quires	O
.	O
Gelliman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
agreement	O
,	O
he	O
by	O
Peacocks	O
persuasions	O
and	O
assistance	O
took	O
several	O
Books	O
,	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bowyer	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
where	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Stall	O
;	O
that	O
for	O
4	O
Books	O
entitled	O
Leges	O
Ang	O
.	O
Sax	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
7	O
of	O
Bed	O
.	O
Eccl	O
.	O
Hist	O
.	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
for	O
1	O
of	O
Bulli	O
Opera	O
Omnia	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
he	O
received	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
That	O
in	O
Bedes	O
History	O
,	O
the	O
Sheet	O
L	O
was	O
wanting	O
.	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
traffick	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
be	O
discourag	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
let	O
the	O
Quantity	O
or	O
Quality	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
be	O
ever	O
to	O
great	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
mean	O
Appearance	O
yet	O
he	O
had	O
great	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
dispose	O
them	O
,	O
naming	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
bought	O
Books	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
his	O
very	O
good	O
Customers	O
;	O
this	O
Evidence	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
bring	O
any	O
more	O
openly	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
were	O
stopt	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
be	O
frighted	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
enquired	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
give	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
wrong	O
Person	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
Bede	O
's	O
History	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Sheet	O
L	O
was	O
wanting	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
to	O
by	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
the	O
Printer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Blake	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
Bedes	O
History	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jonah	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
the	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
he	O
thereupon	O
making	O
search	O
among	O
his	O
Books	O
,	O
mist	O
several	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Janoh	O
Bowyer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Blake	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
intimating	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
he	O
should	O
again	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
at	O
present	O
under	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
afford	O
for	O
Leges	O
Ang	O
.	O
Sax	O
.	O
which	O
his	O
Servant	O
brought	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bowyer	O
bought	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
being	O
in	O
discourse	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Giles	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Innys	O
they	O
both	O
produced	O
Letters	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
hand	O
Writing	O
.	O
This	O
giving	O
him	O
some	O
suspicion	O
,	O
when	O
Blake	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
Bedes	O
Ecc	O
.	O
Hist	O
.	O
he	O
Apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Books	O
of	O
a	O
Journey	O
man	O
Printer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
quickly	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
Assistance	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Books	O
and	O
Letters	O
to	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
direction	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
bred	O
up	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Worth	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Peacock	O
what	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
;	O
adding	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowyer	O
promised	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
return	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowyers	O
Son	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Receipt	O
to	O
discharge	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Creditable	O
Witnesses	O
from	O
Deptford	O
where	O
he	O
formerly	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
general	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
and	O
Industrious	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wayland	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
alias	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wayland	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Wayland	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Body	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
40	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
near	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Body	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
by	O
Persons	O
who	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
Starlings	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
Back	O
window	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
distributed	O
Advertisements	O
among	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
.	O
Mott	O
Lane	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Dyer	O
and	O
Wayland	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
old	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coral	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting'em	O
,	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Body	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Dyer	O
brought	O
three	O
Rings	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
(	O
Wilmots	O
)	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
remarkable	O
old	O
Ring	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Body	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Conaway	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Dyer	O
and	O
Pool	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
and	O
a	O
Necklace	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Wayland	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
old	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Necklace	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
Pool	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Body	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Wayland	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Ring	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tailworth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
March	O
29.	O
she	O
met	O
Wayland	O
in	O
Red-Lyon-street	O
,	O
South-Wark	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
very	O
wet	O
and	O
draggled	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
fair	O
Morning	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
Wayland	O
and	O
Pool	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Ring	O
:	O
Pool	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
Wayland	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
.	O
She	O
lent'em	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Dyer	O
and	O
Pool	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
.	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Wayland	O
.	O
Wayland	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Rings	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
(	O
Pool	O
)	O
and	O
Sister	O
(	O
Dyer	O
)	O
the	O
2	O
other	O
prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
intirely	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
'em	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
That	O
1	O
Shirt	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
-	O
Selby	O
,	O
in	O
Field	O
Lane	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
Susan	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Goswel	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
several	O
Smocks	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
drunken	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Cartwright	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Cartwright	O
Richardson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
on	O
Whitsunday	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
deposing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
very	O
malicious	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Liar	O
,	O
given	O
to	O
pilfering	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
scruple	O
to	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	O
Hodges	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Grace	B-pers
Halseys	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rising	B-place
Sun	I-place
in	O
Peters	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
near	O
Hicks	B-place
's	I-place
Hall	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
join	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Cyder	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ripping	O
her	O
Gown	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Camp	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
home	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Soldier	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
saw	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
body	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
chang	O
'd	O
Gowns	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
2	O
s	O
to	O
boot	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Hannah	O
Hodges	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
entertain	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Nights	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
chang	O
'd	O
Cloths	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
and	O
driving	O
away	O
2	O
Hogs	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
2	O
Hogs	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Gray	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
driving	O
2	O
Hogs	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Hogs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Molony	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
repeating	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
Chrystal	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
L	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
42	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
from	O
the	O
Bedford	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
Southampton	O
street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
turning	O
into	O
Little	B-place
Queenstreet	I-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
3	O
Men	O
coming	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Chairman	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
into	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
haste	O
;	O
his	O
Hand	O
trembling	O
as	O
he	O
spoke	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
11	O
s.	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
trifle	O
?	O
Another	O
putting	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
de	O
ye	O
?	O
the	O
former	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Chrystal	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
his	O
Purse	O
with	O
Forty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bid	O
the	O
Chairmen	O
go	O
on	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
Chairmen	O
carried	O
him	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Molony	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
Carrick	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
were	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
tye	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
really	O
believ	O
'd	O
Carrick	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
was	O
no	O
less	O
like	O
Molony	O
;	O
having	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
his	O
Wig	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grindal	I-pers
,	O
Chairman	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Molony	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
under	O
the	O
Arch	O
'd	O
Passage	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
getting	O
loose	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
sent	O
his	O
Dog	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
(	O
says	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
like	O
a	O
Hare	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
first	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Hound	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
Chairman	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Brounker	I-pers
,	O
Sales-man	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
street	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
Carrick	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
Whiggington	O
(	O
Brounker	O
's	O
Man	O
)	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
look	O
some	O
suits	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
Whiggington	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
Carrick	O
,	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
others	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Slop	O
Shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
's	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Purse	O
,	O
with	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
.	O
Carrick	O
call	O
'd	O
Katherine	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
by	O
Carrol	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Evidence	O
was	O
intirely	O
unintelligible	O
.	O
Monday	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Carrick	O
and	O
Carrol	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Chair	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to'em	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
intirely	O
ignorant	O
of	O
their	O
Design	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
great	O
protestations	O
of	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found'em	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Griffith	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
of	O
drew	O
Cresner	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
having	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
a	O
Bodice-maker	O
,	O
carried	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
whole	O
possession	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crib	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
already	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Latouche	I-pers
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
two	O
Casements	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
(	O
with	O
T.	O
Web	O
)	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Casements	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Web	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
(	O
Hain	O
's	O
a	O
Joiner	O
)	O
Door	O
,	O
Tom	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbouring	O
Glazier	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
home	O
some	O
Casements	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
neglected	O
it	O
,	O
prithee	O
go	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
went	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Casements	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
took	O
one	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Web	O
's	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Esmond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bringing	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Saw	O
was	O
lost	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Seaser	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
spiteful	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
being	O
invalidated	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boat	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bott	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Hillington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Suit	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
2	O
Riding	O
Coats	O
,	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Burly	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hanwel	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
Seventy	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslim	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Starky	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
aged	O
10	O
.	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hoxly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
Charity	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Girl	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
for	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
Liquors	O
,	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Julian	I-pers
,	O
at	O
his	O
Tent	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smart	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tinsty	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Montford	I-pers
,	O
now	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathanial	B-pers
Hamand	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
the	O
from	O
thence	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
the	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pick	O
Axe	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Trowel	O
,	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hiller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
Laid	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Hiller	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
last	O
not	O
being	O
his	O
,	O
But	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mascal	B-pers
Brockelsby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
printed	O
Books	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Innys	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Innys	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
hir	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
10	O
l	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Under-Servant	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
on	O
Errands	O
;	O
That	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
Books	O
stolen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bowyer	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
a	O
watch	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
few	O
Days	O
found	O
he	O
sold	O
Books	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
accompt	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
searched	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
wrote	O
in	O
Cyphers	O
,	O
which	O
contain	O
'd	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
selling	O
Books	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Masters	O
chiefly	O
dealt	O
in	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
Account	O
,	O
at	O
Prices	O
below	O
the	O
prime	O
cost	O
.	O
The	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
allow	O
'd	O
as	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Nisbett	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sell	O
to	O
Mr.	O
MacEuen	O
,	O
Bookseller	O
of	O
Edinburgh	O
,	O
Drake	O
's	O
Anatomy	O
at	O
6	O
s.	O
Prideaux	O
's	O
Connection	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
s.	O
Spectators	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Books	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
in	O
small	O
Parcels	O
at	O
Mr.	O
MacEuen	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
long	O
traded	O
in	O
Books	O
,	O
having	O
liberty	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Noon	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Innys	O
,	O
who	O
hired	O
him	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Noon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wilkin	I-pers
,	O
Peruke-Maker	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Matte	O
's	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
the	O
Philof	O
.	O
Transact	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Books	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
exchanged	O
Books	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Noon	O
,	O
Bookbinder	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
liberty	O
to	O
Trade	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hatham	O
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
had	O
infor	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Innys	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
liberty	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Innys	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
liberty	O
to	O
Trade	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Indentity	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Abington	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
the	O
Decea	O
'd	O
in	O
Bridges	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
swore	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
a	O
rude	O
Answer	O
,	O
and	O
plac	O
'd	O
himself	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
She	O
persuaded	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
mind	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
'em	O
;	O
the	O
Decease	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
prisoner	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
Some	O
other	O
Word	O
past	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
they	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
collar	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
his	O
sword	O
into	O
his	O
Belly	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Roles	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
Russel	O
street	O
:	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
take	O
Coach	O
:	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
set	O
you	O
home	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
going	O
forward	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
He	O
past	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
met	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
Standing	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Jones	O
shriek	O
out	O
:	O
then	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
holding	O
the	O
Deceased	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sparkam	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
enter	O
'd	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
above	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
and	O
past	O
obliquely	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
settled	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
judged	O
the	O
Vena	O
Parts	O
to	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
Bridges	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Women	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
holding	O
by	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
by	O
your	O
leave	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
held	O
up	O
her	O
Elbow	O
to	O
hinder	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
coming	O
round	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Decess	O
'd	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
affront	O
the	O
Lady	O
for	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
:	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
teach	O
you	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
perceiving	O
,	O
fell	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
cut	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Finger	O
at	O
the	O
1st	O
Pass	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
2d	O
cut	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
they	O
parry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
defending	O
himself	O
,	O
unfortunately	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Colthers	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Fore-finger	O
of	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
drest	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
triangular	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Sword	O
Robert	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
.	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
his	O
Finger	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Pheasant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
'em	O
to	O
-	O
Williams	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oldbury	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
as	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mattison	I-pers
abovemention	O
'd	O
,	O
Peacock	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
Books	O
to	O
Geliman	O
.	O
Geliman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Books	O
to	O
Sale	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
being	O
surprised	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nay	O
it	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
are	O
under	O
some	O
surprise	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
'll	O
ask	O
you	O
no	O
more	O
Questions	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
2	O
of	O
Bedes	O
History	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
Leslys	O
Works	O
value	O
3	O
L	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
1	O
of	O
Saxon	O
Laws	O
and	O
2	O
of	O
Bulls	O
Works	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
Guineas	O
each	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Giles	O
a	O
Book-seller	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
Bedes	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
4	O
5	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
disturbance	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
any	O
Books	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
Bode	O
in	O
Quires	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
bound	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stopt	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
.	O
Morris	O
the	O
Bookseller	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
Bedes	O
Histories	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
of	O
Bulls	O
Works	O
.	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
bound	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
common	O
for	O
Books	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
at	O
a	O
less	O
price	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
subscribed	O
for	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Impression	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
Leigh	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
Lancashire	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Quires	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
Subscribed	O
to	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
That	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
subscrib	O
'd	O
for	O
6	O
Books	O
,	O
had	O
one	O
Gratis	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
had	O
2	O
.	O
Salter	O
a	O
Book-seller	O
and	O
Wistal	O
a	O
Beadle	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
detect	O
Several	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
offer	O
'd	O
stoln	O
Books	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butlock	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Futlock	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Butloyn	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Furloine	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
72	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Claude	B-pers
Langly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
Claude	O
Langly	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
coming	O
from	O
Church	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Goods	O
and	O
Servant	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Chester	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Landy	O
Post	O
Master	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
64	O
Guineas	O
,	O
4	O
Lewisdors	O
,	O
9	O
Livres	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mr.	O
D'arcy	O
,	O
a	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
from	O
France	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Rib	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
on	O
his	O
Duty	O
in	O
Hyde	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
Company	O
coming	O
forward	O
and	O
Challeng	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
Friends	O
;	O
presently	O
after	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
called	O
the	O
other	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
clashing	O
like	O
Whips	O
or	O
Swords	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
then	O
unto	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Morning	O
light	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
2	O
thrusts	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
then	O
retreating	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
back	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
turn	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
neither	O
Stick	O
nor	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Blood	O
nor	O
Wound	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
him	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
John	B-pers
Barrat	I-pers
Serjeant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
rear	O
of	O
his	O
Tent	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
murmuring	O
noise	O
and	O
2	O
blows	O
given	O
like	O
the	O
flashing	O
of	O
Whips	O
;	O
advancing	O
to	O
the	O
Front	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
2	O
thrusts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
resetlement	O
retreated	O
about	O
to	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
other	O
company	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
Wounded	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
'm	O
afraid	O
Mortally	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
have	O
no	O
Sword	O
nor	O
Stick	O
,	O
but	O
Serjeant	O
Summers	O
afteraught	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
cut	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
retreat	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
is	O
no	O
posture	O
of	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
hanging	O
on	O
his	O
wrist	O
,	O
looking	O
back	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
reel	O
'd	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
advancing	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
home	O
thrust	O
and	O
retreated	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Yards	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
Mortally	O
Wounded	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
to	O
be	O
thus	O
hurt	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
upon	O
his	O
Duty	O
he	O
saw	O
4	O
Men	O
,	O
he	O
Challeng	O
'd	O
them	O
they	O
answered	O
,	O
and	O
past	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
about	O
15	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
answered	O
,	O
Use	O
me	O
with	O
good	O
manners	O
Sir	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
Ill	O
manners	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seemed	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Clashing	O
but	O
whethere	O
of	O
2	O
Swords	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
Cane	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
;	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Guard	O
was	O
called	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
Serjeant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Colonel	O
Murry	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Deceased	O
under	O
the	O
Arm	O
.	O
Colonmel	O
Ridley	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Tent	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
disturbance	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
heard	O
Col.	O
Marry	B-pers
demand	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
Sword	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
till	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Sir	O
says	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
had	O
fair	O
play	O
for	O
your	O
Life	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
I	O
mean	O
Sir	O
,	O
continued	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
Wounded	O
;	O
The	O
Deceaed	O
answer	O
'd	O
anser	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Inhumanly	O
Murder	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
sunk	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Col.	O
Darbys	B-pers
Tent	I-pers
.	O
Colonel	O
Wolf	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
followed	O
Colonel	O
Murray	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Tent	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
somewhat	O
before	O
Col.	O
Ridly	B-pers
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
2	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
bleeding	O
and	O
leaning	O
upon	O
his	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
Wound	O
before	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
from	O
the	O
knowledge	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
capable	O
of	O
being	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
base	O
and	O
Action	O
,	O
Several	O
other	O
's	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
asking	O
them	O
the	O
Question	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Sword	O
and	O
Cloths	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
cuts	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Sleeve	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
,	O
2	O
holes	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
thrusts	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
hilt	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Blade	O
.	O
Stephens	O
and	O
Westbrook	O
,	O
Surgeons	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
several	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
entering	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
including	O
upwards	O
went	O
throught	O
the	O
Liver	O
was	O
Mortal	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Cut	O
cross	O
the	O
little	O
Finger	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Blood	O
might	O
run	O
down	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Colonel	O
Meyrick	B-pers
's	O
house	O
at	O
Twittenham	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shirly	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nepheur	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Colonels	O
Tent	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
freely	O
and	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
disagreement	O
.	O
All	O
except	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
they	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
walk	O
along	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
Nepheur	O
,	O
Shirly	O
,	O
and	O
Meyrick	O
,	O
went	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
staying	O
behind	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
into	O
discourses	O
of	O
Gallantry	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
Fat	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
30	O
and	O
40	O
began	O
to	O
brag	O
of	O
his	O
Exploits	O
among	O
the	O
Fair	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
how	O
you	O
can	O
talk	O
so	O
Extravagantly	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Ladies	O
look	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Fumbler	O
as	O
an	O
Old	O
Fellow	O
of	O
Three	O
score	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
damn	O
'd	O
Impertinent	O
fellow	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
pray	O
Sir	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
use	O
me	O
with	O
good	O
manners	O
.	O
You	O
've	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
struck	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
provoked	O
retired	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
they	O
closed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
unhappily	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Meyrick	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Twitnam	O
2	O
days	O
before	O
in	O
other	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
designing	O
to	O
walk	O
it	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Sword	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
lighter	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
cutting	O
Sword	O
.	O
Which	O
he	O
left	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
his	O
Tent	O
,	O
and	O
When	O
they	O
broke	O
up	O
he	O
,	O
Nepheur	O
,	O
and	O
Shirly	O
,	O
went	O
forward	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
Centinel	O
on	O
his	O
Post	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Challenged	O
by	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
the	O
Words	O
Impertinent	O
Fellow	O
;	O
stept	O
back	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
in	O
and	O
close	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Finger	O
cut	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
see	O
any	O
Sword	O
or	O
any	O
stroke	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Moon	O
was	O
behind	O
a	O
Cloud	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
called	O
the	O
Centry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Centry	O
called	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Guard	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
want	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
nearer	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leaning	O
upon	O
his	O
this	O
(	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
cutting	O
Sword	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
at	O
Twitenham	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
till	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
any	O
Sword	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirly	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Words	O
Impertinent	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
blows	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
saw	O
Col.	O
Meyrick	B-pers
parting	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
Challenged	O
by	O
the	O
Centry	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
My	O
G	O
-	O
Nichols	O
you	O
are	O
damn	O
'd	O
Impertinent	O
;	O
blows	O
ensued	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Meyrick	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Shirly	O
assisting	O
:	O
Meyrick	O
went	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Centry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Centry	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Guard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Sword	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sheath	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
abusive	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
up	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Starr	I-pers
Constable	O
and	O
Corporal	O
Glyn	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Forehead	O
and	O
Arm	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
to	O
appearance	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
Westbrook	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
drest	O
the	O
Wound	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
left	O
Arm	O
:	O
that	O
if	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
2	O
Weeks	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
cured	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Rencounter	O
.	O
Col.	O
Richbell	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
leaning	O
upon	O
his	O
Cane	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
somebody	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Tent	O
.	O
Captain	O
Euns	B-pers
swore	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
parted'em	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
beaten	O
the	O
Deceased	O
heartily	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
grosly	O
affronted	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Officers	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
peaceable	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gaffy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
was	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
She	O
found	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Padington	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
43	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
13	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morphew	I-pers
,	O
Natbaniel	O
Jackson	B-pers
John	I-pers
Molony	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
rick	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butlock	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Butloin	O
,	O
alias	O
Futlock	O
,	O
alias	O
Futloin	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
5.	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Winwright	I-pers
,	O
Haunah	O
Blake	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
All	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
35.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Greenland	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilshire	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Forty	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dawson	O
,	O
alias	O
Hudson	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wayland	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Chadwick	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mattison	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Redmane	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bate	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Starky	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Norman	O
,	O
alias	O
Smart	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Quire	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pbesant	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gaffy	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
5	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Lavinia	O
Anderson	O
Fin	O
'd	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
within	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Jennison	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
King	O
street	O
end	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Desters	O
Commons	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
.	O
Fin	O
'd	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
each	O
.	O
A	O
D	O
V	O
E	O
R	O
T	O
I	O
S	O
E	O
M	O
E	O
N	O
T	O
All	O
MELANCHOLY	O
HISTERICAL	O
and	O
HYPOCHONDRIACK	O
Distempers	O
which	O
variously	O
effect	O
the	O
mind	O
with	O
strange	O
fears	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
Fendings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
hurries	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
,	O
and	O
disquietments	O
,	O
(	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
and	O
seldom	O
cur	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
means	O
)	O
also	O
pains	O
and	O
giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
sick	O
fitts	O
,	O
tremblings	O
,	O
and	O
oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
,	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
Gods	O
Blessing	O
,	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physisian	O
who	O
is	O
no	O
vain	O
Pretender	O
:	O
but	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
most	O
doubtful	O
Person	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
great	O
Success	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
