TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	B-pers
CONYERS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
James	B-pers
Hibbart	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cockman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Trowell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Goate	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eggleton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hurn	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Thale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fen	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beetcliff	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Magnus	B-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
70	O
Pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Cook	O
at	O
the	O
Swan-Tavern	B-place
on	O
Fishstreet-hill	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
offering	O
the	O
Plates	O
to	O
change	O
to	O
a	O
Pewterer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
cleaning	O
out	O
a	O
Back-Kitchen	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
clean	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
found	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
this	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Frances	I-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Orgars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
Water	O
at	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Swan	I-place
,	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Crowd	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
Wager	O
to	O
be	O
row	O
'd	O
for	O
;	O
and	O
standing	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Snuff-box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
her	O
they	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
James	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
stoop	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
something	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Snuff-box	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Snuff-box	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
an	O
Old	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Cinnamon	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Box	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Strettam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
Servant	O
s	O
to	O
beat	O
the	O
Thread	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Getting	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Getting	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Ring	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
Money	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
counted	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
our	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
Tenderness	O
for	O
him	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
often	O
collaring	O
him	O
and	O
beating	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
irreclaimable	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
in	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waltham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bruan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marvin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Scowerer	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Coats	O
to	O
scower	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
Dinner	O
the	O
Coats	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fester	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Coats	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
Coat	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
Both	O
these	O
Coats	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Coats	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Coats	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
in	O
Genborn	O
Alley	O
,	O
near	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
1	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
put	O
about	O
6	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
,	O
lock	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
earlier	O
than	O
he	O
usually	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
5	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Fees	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
one	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
about	O
3	O
1.	O
in	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
clothing	O
him	O
from	O
Head	O
to	O
Foot	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
this	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
:	O
And	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Comrade	O
drinking	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
Billingsgate	O
very	O
extravagantly	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
examined	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Cousin	O
at	O
Stratford	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
17	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Summerfield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
put	O
40	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
abate	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Wages	O
:	O
And	O
she	O
still	O
kept	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Promise	O
of	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
But	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
43	O
Guineas	O
into	O
her	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
3	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
into	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Bow	B-place
Churchyard	I-place
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
desiring	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
having	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Night-Walker	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
before	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
that	O
Night	O
)	O
he	O
acquainted	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
procure	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Thomas	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Barbara	O
Ingram	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
Transportation	O
:	O
But	O
acquitted	O
Thomas	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
let	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
also	O
two	O
Cornelian	O
Seals	O
set	O
in	O
Bath	O
Mettal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
two	O
Cornelian	O
Seals	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Silver	O
one	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
for	O
more	O
Seals	O
,	O
he	O
counted	O
thirteen	O
which	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
eleven	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
two	O
Seals	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Seals	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Seals	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
License	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Hawker	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
such	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
two	O
Full	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
apprehended	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Wynns	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hector	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
committed	O
,	O
fell	O
a	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
bound	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
would	O
have	O
sought	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
overpower	O
'd	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
his	O
Tankard	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
direct	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
this	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
did	O
light	O
of	O
Gibbons	O
in	O
the	O
Mins	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Gibbons	O
did	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Thomas	O
bid	O
Wynne	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
Gibbons	O
)	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Mr.	O
Toney	O
's	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
should	O
all	O
he	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
Wynne	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
let	O
him	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
William	O
Davis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Gibbons	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
Half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
present	O
Wynn	O
.	O
:	O
That	O
Wynne	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
they	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
cry	O
'd	O
to	O
Wynne	O
,	O
show	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
show	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
Wynne	O
wringing	O
off	O
the	O
Handle	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saying	O
,	O
Where	O
have	O
you	O
stolen	O
it	O
?	O
they	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereaten	O
'd	O
to	O
beat	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Get	O
you	O
gone	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
employ	O
'd	O
one	O
Harry	B-pers
Salier	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
Stairs	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Falcon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wynne	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Davis	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Trahern	I-pers
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
great	O
Knocking	O
and	O
Hammering	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
,	O
saw	O
them	O
beating	O
of	O
a	O
Tankard	O
to	O
Pieces	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
very	O
plentifully	O
,	O
spent	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Cyder	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sent	O
one	O
Salter	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
That	O
Gibbons	O
ask	O
'd	O
Salter	O
what	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
Gibbons	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
That	O
Salter	O
paid	O
the	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
Gibbons	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
Wynne	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Wynne	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
Tankard	O
till	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
any	O
more	O
with	O
them	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
plain	O
then	O
against	O
Gibbons	O
and	O
Wynne	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
sent	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Lassons	I-pers
;	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Keyne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
his	O
Lighter	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Barge	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
3	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Oats	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Barge	O
into	O
the	O
Lighter	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
getting	O
into	O
a	O
Wherry	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Oats	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wigg	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stulker	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
left	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Sister	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
John	O
Dyer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
good	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Wigg	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
said	O
,	O
Her	O
general	O
Character	O
was	O
a	O
Receiver	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
indeed	O
kept	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hollanpriest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mannus	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Try	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
Fruit	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	B-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
offering	O
the	O
Pot	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
Basket	O
of	O
Fruit	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
tolerable	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Grates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Grates	O
as	O
they	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
Victuals	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Laney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Susannah	I-pers
Laney	I-pers
,	O
by	O
wounding	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baracle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Waldoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
near	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
something	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
thought	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
attempting	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Box	O
a	O
shove	O
under	O
some	O
Rails	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bassam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spinner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Saws	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Saws	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Tools	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Westerman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tools	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
Chests	O
,	O
were	O
stolen	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Newport	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lily	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
drinking	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
take	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stoop	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
was	O
siez	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jenureta	B-pers
Spride	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
abroad	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
far	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
lodging	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
accepted	O
the	O
Motion	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
awake	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
:	O
He	O
found	O
his	O
Watch	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Frock	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
won	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
Cards	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
at	O
all	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
a	O
stray	O
'd	O
Sheep	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquiteed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gwynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
about	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
2	O
Pound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Ticket	O
Porter	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gatlick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-Time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
two	O
Men	O
sculking	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
from	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
siez	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
enquiring	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Necessary-house	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
by	O
a	O
Hem	O
gave	O
Notice	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Comrades	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
examining	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
it	O
was	O
unbolted	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
bolted	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
examining	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
be	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
West	O
End	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Fin	O
'd	O
1	O
Mark	O
.	O
and	O
2	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Paschal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
George	O
Paschal	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
or	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Hostler	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
fell	O
2	O
odd	O
Spurs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
or	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
Spurs	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Bar	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
several	O
Times	O
lost	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
at	O
two	O
a-clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
did	O
pull	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Paschal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
this	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
rose	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
to	O
get	O
ready	O
the	O
Horses	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Owndle	O
Coach	O
,	O
or	O
Waggon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
Morning	O
at	O
four	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Rustling	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
suspected	O
some	O
Thief	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
pull	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fowston	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whelbone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Edgington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Bermudas	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Hats	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
one	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
six	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
first	O
Hat	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
sold	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Golding	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Golding	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Moreton	O
and	O
Edgington	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Golding	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spittle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
set	O
down	O
his	O
Basket	O
on	O
a	O
Stall	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Loaf	O
in	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
his	O
Basket	O
and	O
Bread	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Basket	O
and	O
Bread	O
.	O
His	O
Defence	O
being	O
but	O
trifling	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trowel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
having	O
sometimes	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
tho	O
she	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
Entrance	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
upon	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
21	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Purley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Standen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Souton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
cock	O
and	O
6	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Cook	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cock	O
and	O
6	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Fowls	O
roosted	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fowls	O
carried	O
and	O
laid	O
under	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
hand	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Casks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Brandy	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
at	O
Cox's-Key	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Bread-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Revett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mechlin	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
Lace	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
having	O
apply	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
bid	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
tell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Drop	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Colegrave	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Shoe	B-place
Lane	I-place
:	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
hang	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
upon	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
taxed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
produc	O
'd	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
as	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
order	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
Money	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
so	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
deluded	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
having	O
sworn	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Substance	O
,	O
had	O
200	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
80	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
had	O
deluded	O
his	O
Daughter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
set	O
his	O
Daughter	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
Company	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
being	O
now	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
,	O
had	O
prosecuted	O
his	O
Daughter	O
for	O
stealing	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
de	I-pers
Puis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Simon	B-pers
Ganeroon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Brass	O
and	O
Pewter	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
not	O
only	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
several	O
other	O
Robberies	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Shard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Kaffety	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Honour	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gown	O
having	O
been	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
Water	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
carry	O
something	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
dropping	O
wet	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackdonnel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Patience	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
four	O
Days	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
finding	O
her	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
her	O
eleven	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
having	O
bought	O
Clothes	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
but	O
15	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Dearing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Abbison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
by	O
selling	O
him	O
30	O
Ounces	O
of	O
burnt	O
Silver	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
Tin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
instead	O
of	O
good	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
burnt	O
Silver	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
putting	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Essay	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
2	O
s.	O
worse	O
than	O
good	O
Silver	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
also	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
essay	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
selling	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
Tin	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
sometimes	O
by	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
by	O
Alice	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
like	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
selling	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
30	O
Ounces	O
of	O
burnt	O
Silver	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
Tin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
good	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
sold	O
him	O
burnt	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
per	O
Ounce	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
essay	O
'd	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
21	O
d.	O
worse	O
than	O
new	O
Sterlings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
adulterated	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
fin	O
'd	O
her	O
10	O
l.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
by	O
one	O
Forster	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Bail	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
traverse	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
one	O
Forster	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
traverse	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ravishing	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
's	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
with	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
:	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
she	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
shift	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
such	O
Tokens	O
on	O
her	O
Linnen	O
that	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Body	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
had	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Running	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
Child	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
Benjamin	O
Hullock	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
laid	O
himself	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
her	O
sadly	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
she	O
apply	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
two	O
surgeons	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kellaway	O
.	O
Those	O
Gentlemen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
very	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
and	O
injur	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Privy	O
Parts	O
were	O
much	O
dilacerated	O
,	O
and	O
extended	O
beyond	O
their	O
natural	O
Dimensions	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
committing	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Declaration	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
taking	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
to	O
David	B-pers
Carty	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Tushingham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
where	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
Home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Carty	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
her	O
very	O
impudently	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
opprobrious	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
her	O
Husband	O
stripp	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
advise	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Carty	O
to	O
be	O
peaceable	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
disgrace	O
the	O
Cloth	O
(	O
they	O
being	O
Soldier	O
s	O
)	O
.	O
That	O
without	O
any	O
more	O
Provocation	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
box	O
?	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
Daniel	O
Carthy	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
snatching	O
a	O
Sword	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Arm	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Wife	O
,	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
attack	O
'd	O
Carty	O
,	O
made	O
some	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
Carty	O
had	O
stabb	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
attack	O
'd	O
Carty	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirm	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
Design	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Carty	O
without	O
being	O
encourag	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
about	O
nine	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
backwards	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
Cane	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gotten	O
up	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
wounding	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
crack	O
'd	O
his	O
Skull	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
Allen	O
that	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Kirk	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Cane	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
Murder	O
being	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Kirk	O
threw	O
the	O
Cane	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
a	O
triangular	O
Confusion	O
upon	O
the	O
Coronal	O
Surure	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Scull	O
was	O
bare	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
covered	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
Whether	O
he	O
lost	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
demanded	O
any	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
neither	O
had	O
he	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Brick-maker	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
from	O
his	O
Day-Labour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
jostled	O
them	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Bull-Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Hanover	O
to	O
sow	O
Turnips	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Appearance	O
of	O
their	O
having	O
any	O
Design	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Benning	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Benning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Benning	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Beinning	I-pers
,	O
Son	O
and	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Henry	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Benning	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1000	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gravel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ground	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Husband	O
and	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
:	O
That	O
having	O
cut	O
the	O
Hay	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
off	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Hay	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
not	O
feloniously	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Dispute	O
concerning	O
the	O
Legality	O
of	O
the	O
Title	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
it	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
them	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Borrett	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
174	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Packer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barrett	O
,	O
a	O
Master	O
in	O
Chancery	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Borrett	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
his	O
Accounts	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Chambers	O
in	O
Symond	O
's	O
Iwn	O
upon	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Borrott	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Borrett	O
being	O
then	O
busy	O
,	O
defer	O
'd	O
the	O
Receiving	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Scrutoure	O
in	O
the	O
Study	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
the	O
Study	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Chamber-Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Messenger	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
set	O
scattering	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Next	O
of	O
Drawers	O
a	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
South-Sea	O
Bond	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
which	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Drawers	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
afterwards	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
keeping	O
one	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Laundress	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
get	O
the	O
Laundress	O
's	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
setching	O
a	O
Letter	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
;	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Post-Night	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Occasional	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
Chambers	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Hammer	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chambers	O
.	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
Keys	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
afterwards	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
but	O
single	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
to	O
she	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Study	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Hinges	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
lying	O
scattered	O
about	O
.	O
Here	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
if	O
these	O
Keys	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
lye	O
publickly	O
among	O
other	O
Keys	O
in	O
a	O
Bunch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
Office	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
not	O
withstanding	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
but	O
reputable	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
used	O
these	O
Keys	O
but	O
she	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Master	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
fast	O
barred	O
,	O
only	O
2	O
Nails	O
drawn	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Hinges	O
of	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Hammer	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Desk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Laundress	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
he	O
see	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
unskrew	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
inner	O
Door	O
lying	O
all	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
standing	O
in	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Packer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
missed	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Jams	O
Spires	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Steps	O
from	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Chambers	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
back	O
Way	O
towards	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
or	O
Bond	O
's	O
Stables	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Essex	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
after	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
none	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
also	O
2	O
Hammers	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
borrowed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Peed	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
by	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
Maid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peed	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
instead	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peed	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Hammer	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
his	O
Hammer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Servant	O
was	O
more	O
positive	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
P	O
cut	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
Maid	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Peed	O
's	O
Hammer	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
Notice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hammer	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
Maid	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Peed	O
's	O
Hammer	O
,	O
differing	O
in	O
the	O
Handle	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
P	O
burnt	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
tampering	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Hammer	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
very	O
pressingly	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
that	O
Hammer	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
saying	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
that	O
Hammer	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
to	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
they	O
would	O
like	O
that	O
Hammer	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Martin	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
City	O
Marshal	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
to	O
Muzzle-Hill	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
between	O
Highgate	B-place
and	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
about	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Foot	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Hats	O
slapping	O
,	O
in	O
browaish	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
Posture	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
they	O
were	O
Foot-pads	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Thoughts	O
of	O
turning	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
resolving	O
to	O
venture	O
,	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
flew	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Dyer	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
voluntarily	O
alight	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
almost	O
Slung	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
clapping	O
Pistols	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
large	O
Pistols	O
with	O
Brass	O
Caps	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
Dyer	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
that	O
Dyer	O
kneel	O
'd	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
broke	O
off	O
the	O
Button	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
16	O
or	O
17	O
Shillings	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
forgotten	O
in	O
the	O
Hurry	O
,	O
they	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
for	O
telling	O
them	O
a	O
Lye	O
,	O
and	O
rattled	O
their	O
Pistols	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
having	O
consented	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
Dyer	O
was	O
for	O
cutting	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Lane	O
being	O
dirty	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewen	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
Anger	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
his	O
Tryal	O
desired	O
that	O
Dyer	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
varying	O
in	O
no	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
whereas	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
Dyer	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
Anger	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Anger	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
shot	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
not	O
giving	O
them	O
the	O
Silver	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
having	O
done	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Lenen	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Hedge	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
noisy	O
,	O
and	O
too	O
outrageous	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
over	O
shot	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
strenuously	O
to	O
affirm	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
Dyer	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
that	O
Robbery	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
both	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
another	O
Robbery	O
:	O
To	O
clear	O
up	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Jayl	O
of	O
Newgate	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
apprehended	O
together	O
,	O
was	O
near	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1711	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
the	O
Waggoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
Knights-Bridge	B-place
and	O
Hyde-Park	B-place
Corner	I-place
,	O
two	O
Men	O
called	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Sibley	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
they	O
commanded	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Morning	O
:	O
Here	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Mistake	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
indeed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Mistake	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
punctual	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
entred	O
down	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Robberies	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
:	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
Design	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
Journal	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Perusal	O
of	O
his	O
Robberies	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
the	O
more	O
particularly	O
repent	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Safety	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
more	O
exact	O
when	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
by	O
becoming	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
robbing	O
John	O
Sibley	O
,	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Manner	O
the	O
Carrier	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Black	O
Heath	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
having	O
committed	O
another	O
Robbery	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shot	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
deny	O
'd	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
wishing	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
no	O
Mercy	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
Ways	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Person	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Allstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Five	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Six	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hollanpriest	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Standen	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Two	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
Rebeckah	O
Webb	O
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Thirty	O
Seven	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Strettam	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Barbara	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watkin	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Allstone	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Turvey	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baracle	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Newport	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spittle	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackdonnel	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Dearing	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
one	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
10	O
l.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Veneveal	O
Disease	O
,	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleeta	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
,	O
the	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
jointly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
coren	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Mears	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humonr	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
A	O
Full	O
and	O
Compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
Murders	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Highwaymen	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
William	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1722.	O
beginning	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
and	O
Little	O
John	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Falstass	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hind	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Nevison	O
,	O
Whitney	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
more	O
:	O
also	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
Account	O
than	O
any	O
yet	O
published	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
executed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
;	O
concluding	O
with	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Cartouche	O
in	O
France	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Robberies	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Action	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Malhoni	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
faithfully	O
collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Histories	O
,	O
Records	O
,	O
Trials	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
Mannscripts	O
,	O
and	O
written	O
regularly	O
as	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
By	O
J.W	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
bound	O
in	O
Ship	O
.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
most	O
Surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Robinson	B-pers
Crusoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
Mariner	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
done	O
into	O
One	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Coutractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
,	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Unders	O
standing	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Anthentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Trassick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplisy	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-Master	O
in	O
Soho	O
Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
E.	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
THE	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainments	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
1001	O
Stories	O
,	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Sultaness	O
of	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Sultan	O
from	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
a	O
bloody	O
Vow	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
,	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Lady	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
In	O
eight	O
Vols	O
.	O
Price	O
11	O
s.	O
II	O
.	O
The	O
Adventures	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Clermont	O
and	O
Madam	O
de	O
Ravezan	O
.	O
A	O
Novel	O
.	O
In	O
four	O
Parts	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
new	O
Atalantis	O
.	O
In	O
four	O
Vols	O
.	O
Prices	O
10	O
s.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
amorous	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Lucinda	O
,	O
an	O
English	O
Lady	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
V.	O
The	O
Strange	O
Adventures	O
of	O
the	O
Count	O
Vinouel	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
whist	O
they	O
resided	O
at	O
Constantinople	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VI	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
Madam	O
de	O
Beaumont	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Cave	O
in	O
Wales	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
undiscovered	O
,	O
being	O
forced	O
to	O
fly	O
France	O
for	O
her	O
Religion	O
.	O
By	O
Mrs.	O
Aubin	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VII	O
.	O
Aminadab	O
's	O
Courtship	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Quaker	O
's	O
Wedding	O
.	O
A	O
Poem	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Way	O
of	O
Courtship	O
,	O
Method	O
of	O
Marrying	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
VIII	O
.	O
The	O
High	O
German	O
Doctor	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Vols	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
explanatory	O
Index	O
.	O
IX	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Holy	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Patriarchs	O
.	O
A	O
Book	O
proper	O
for	O
Children	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
X	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
.	O
A	O
Treatise	O
proper	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
Publick	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
XI	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
's	O
Rhetorick	O
.	O
Containing	O
Rules	O
for	O
speaking	O
and	O
writing	O
elegantly	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
XII	O
.	O
Moral	O
Reflections	O
and	O
Maxims	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Duke	O
de	O
la	O
Rochesoucault	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XIII	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
Muly	O
Ishmael	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	O
Morocco	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
cruel	O
Usage	O
to	O
the	O
Christian	B-pers
Slaves	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XIV	O
.	O
A	O
general	O
History	O
of	O
Dreams	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XV	O
.	O
Lydall	O
's	O
Table	O
of	O
Interest	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XVI	O
.	O
A	O
Help	O
to	O
Prayer	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Knags	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
BOOKS	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
CArtouche	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
The	O
Robbers	O
,	O
A	O
Comedy	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
acted	O
many	O
Times	O
with	O
great	O
Applause	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
By	O
Mons	O
,	O
le	O
Grand	O
,	O
Comedian	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Actions	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Dominique	I-pers
Cartouch	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
broke	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
N.S	O
.	O
relating	O
at	O
large	O
his	O
remarkable	O
Adventures	O
,	O
desperate	O
Enterprizes	O
,	O
and	O
various	O
Escapes	O
.	O
