TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	B-pers
CONYERS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Montangue	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
Aland	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
Several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Hinchman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bumstead	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Girle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Ramshire	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chattel	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Town	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Prew	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Guinea	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Worrel	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Tames	I-pers
,	O
Job	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
Peter's-Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
4	O
Pistol	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
Pound-piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Drawer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
having	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Things	O
only	O
in	O
Jest	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bravado	O
show	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taxed	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
readily	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine's-Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	O
Sparrow	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
familiar	O
than	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Mony	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
upon	O
parting	O
with	O
her	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
apprehended	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
privately	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Many	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
and	O
stolen	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
commited	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Dirty	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
Pail	O
she	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
before	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
Search	O
being	O
made	O
for	O
Run-goods	O
,	O
a	O
Hamper	O
of	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
desired	O
Mrs.	O
Spicer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Friend	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
it	O
was	O
Pewter	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
preserve	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
an	O
ill	O
Husband	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Pots	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Hamper	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
also	O
many	O
other	O
Pots	O
found	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Dung-hill	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
about	O
50	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Pots	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
that	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hamper	O
;	O
she	O
having	O
before	O
kept	O
a	O
Cook's-shop	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Pots	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
publick	O
Vault	O
that	O
any	O
Body	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
at	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Mokes	I-pers
was	O
by	O
due	O
Course	O
of	O
Law	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Capp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
buy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Robert	O
Mokes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
Robert	O
Mokes	O
;	O
one	O
Time	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
lent	O
Mony	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
Robert	O
Mokes	O
having	O
before	O
us	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
pleading	O
Necessity	O
,	O
be	O
lent	O
him	O
30	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
Kindness	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
Mokes	O
's	O
Master	O
,	O
that	O
Mokes	O
had	O
bought	O
Stockings	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
Years	O
since	O
upon	O
Mokes	O
's	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
Mokes	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dustan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
some	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
raise	O
Mony	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cowley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
enquir	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
Calender	O
a	O
Calamanco	O
Gown	O
for	O
her	O
without	O
ripping	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Silk	O
;	O
that	O
making	O
enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
dog	O
'd	O
and	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Hound	O
and	O
Hare	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
and	O
shift	O
her	O
Gown	O
there	O
;	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
or	O
pawning	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Shoe	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
in	O
a	O
Door-way	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Shoe	O
,	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
Mony	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Shoe	O
and	O
Buckle	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
not	O
the	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Coral	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Draw	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
Service	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick-house	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Draw	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Sum	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Twine	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
bringing	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Guinis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Silver	O
handled	O
Knives	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Knives	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Daisey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Brace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Sergeant	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
some	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Maid	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
who	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Porters	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
she	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
Commitment	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
privately	O
convey	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
promising	O
never	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
2	O
Penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Pins	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
so	O
drunk	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
hardly	O
tell	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Shirt	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
at	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Pound	O
of	O
Unwrought	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Graham	O
employ	O
'd	O
Oliver	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
to	O
dig	O
in	O
the	O
Ruins	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Fire	O
in	O
Billiter	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
that	O
finding	O
a	O
Bale	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
conceal	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
as	O
their	O
own	O
Goods	O
.	O
Oliver	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Graham	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
conceal	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Country	O
Fellow	O
,	O
but	O
newly	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
he	O
impos	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Ignorance	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
concealing	O
and	O
selling	O
it	O
.	O
Graham	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
had	O
contracted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Foxly	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
certain	O
Sum	O
of	O
Mony	O
for	O
what	O
Yarn	O
of	O
his	O
they	O
could	O
dig	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
entirely	O
burnt	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
damag	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Oliver	O
in	O
digging	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Bale	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
did	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidences	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
Oliver	O
's	O
Poverty	O
and	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
his	O
being	O
drawn	O
into	O
it	O
by	O
Graham	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
commuted	O
his	O
Transportation	O
into	O
Burning	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Micklewright	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Gresham	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black	I-place
Friers	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
hung	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Balcony	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
forgotten	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
,	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
entring	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
himself	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
standing	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
espy	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Balcony	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Balcony	O
to	O
lye	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Edward	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Kendrick	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Bed	O
Ticks	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
the	O
last	O
April	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
since	O
transported	O
,	O
did	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Waterman	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
Shore	O
by	O
John	O
Michael	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Stealing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Guire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vanderhelm	I-pers
,	O
and	O
12	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
them	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kern	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
then	O
warm	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Fowls	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Weminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kern	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Pet	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Pot	O
in	O
change	O
for	O
Earthen	O
Ware	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
Pater-Noster	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Devon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
19	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Stone	O
in	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
keep	O
her	O
Distance	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
Sleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
by	O
his	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
Mony	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
some	O
Body	O
else	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
it	O
as	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
Mony	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Whitehurst	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Garraway	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
since	O
been	O
transported	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
did	O
discover	O
that	O
Garraway	O
,	O
Sly	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
that	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
Stephen	O
Gardiner	O
being	O
now	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Chamber-Door	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Drawer	O
of	O
his	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Drawer	O
thrown	O
behind	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
being	O
then	O
a	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
opening	O
she	O
did	O
step	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
having	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
his	O
Linnen	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
many	O
credible	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bunworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Turkey	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Chickens	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
and	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Fowls	O
and	O
Linnen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Trinity	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
through	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Dun	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Dun	O
before	O
,	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drunk	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Dun	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
likewise	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
the	O
Punch	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
drinking	O
in	O
Dun	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Dun	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
drank	O
the	O
Punch	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Standard	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
Half	O
a	O
Pint	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
treat	O
her	O
with	O
Half	O
a	O
Pint	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Half-Pints	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
buy	O
Hay	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
taxing	O
Dun	O
with	O
treating	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
for	O
bringing	O
a	O
Person	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
Dun	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Leaky	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twice	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
both	O
Times	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
another	O
Woman	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
recover	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
having	O
join	O
'd	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dun	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
there	O
drinking	O
Punch	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
invited	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Standard	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
three	O
Half-Pints	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
would	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
18	O
d.	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Watch	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
being	O
paid	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
lying	O
behind	O
the	O
Bottles	O
:	O
That	O
it	O
raining	O
,	O
she	O
stay	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
Nan	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
arrested	O
Mr.	O
Dun	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
an	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
arrested	O
Dun	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
engag	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Watch	O
forth	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
Dun	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
And	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
a	O
Broad-Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
II	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
near	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
conducted	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
ply	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
Drams	O
very	O
plentifully	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
awak	O
'd	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
them	O
positively	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Valentine	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Grey	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Rhodes	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Cart	O
between	O
Paddington	B-place
and	O
Tyburn	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
verily	O
believes	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
with	O
a	O
Broom-Stick	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Copses	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Fob	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
defended	O
himself	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Blows	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
stick	O
the	O
Knife	O
into	O
his	O
Elbow	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
off	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
he	O
whipping	O
his	O
Horse	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
also	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
two	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Paddington	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
three	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
undress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
differ	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pyeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
th	O
of	O
Yarn	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Saunderson	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
William	O
Pyeman	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Monk	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Sister	O
was	O
then	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Monk	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
frequently	O
coming	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
seeing	O
his	O
Sister-in-Law	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Being	O
suspected	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
James	O
Saunderson	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Saunderson	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Pyeman	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
on	O
Pyeman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Saunderson	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
Stomach	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
Whit-Monday	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
Quarrelling	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Frances	O
Coats	O
holding	O
Dorothy	O
Fennel	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
or	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
beating	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Stomach	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
Dorothy	O
Fennel	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
my	O
Stomach	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Elizabeth	O
Richardson	O
held	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Get	O
up	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Witness	O
,	O
believes	O
,	O
that	O
Richardson	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Frances	O
Coat	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
is	O
blind	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Fennel	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Country-Woman	O
,	O
they	O
tear	O
me	O
Limb	O
from	O
Limb	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
gotten	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
groaned	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Whit-Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Deceased	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Frances	O
Coats	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
Dorothy	O
Fennel	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
almost	O
throttle	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Hand	O
beating	O
her	O
violently	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
Stomach	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
Dorothy	O
Fennel	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
caught	O
up	O
her	O
Crutch	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
Dorothy	O
Fennel	O
a	O
violent	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
Fennel	O
complain	O
'd	O
grievously	O
of	O
her	O
Stomach	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
she	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Complaint	O
to	O
the	O
Overseers	O
for	O
the	O
Poor	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
new	O
Lodging	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
lie	O
there	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
almost	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
6	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
new	O
Lodging	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Richardson	O
,	O
had	O
held	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
while	O
Frances	O
Coats	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
so	O
violently	O
that	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
her	O
go	O
Home	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Care	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
about	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Overseers	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
new	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
to	O
her	O
old	O
Lodging	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
complain	O
'd	O
mightily	O
of	O
her	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Water	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
got	O
her	O
some	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Contusion	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
come	O
by	O
some	O
violent	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Frances	O
Coats	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
began	O
with	O
her	O
first	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
Bitches	O
and	O
Whores	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
before	O
she	O
struck	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Frances	O
Coats	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
she	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
:	O
But	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Elizabeth	O
Richardson	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Duce	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Steel	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
James	O
Butler	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
:	O
But	O
William	O
Duce	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
plead	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
requir	O
'd	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
privately	O
:	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
making	O
Discoveries	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
admitting	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
5th	O
Field	O
between	B-place
London	I-place
and	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
four	O
Men	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
behaving	O
himself	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
did	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
John	O
Dier	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
all	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Dier	I-pers
,	O
who	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
gone	O
some	O
Distance	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
excused	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
from	O
Necessity	O
.	O
John	O
Dier	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
James	O
Butler	O
,	O
William	O
Duce	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
since	O
shot	O
by	O
the	O
Patrole	O
Guard	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
rob	O
Colonel	O
Chudleigh	O
's	O
Lady	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
)	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Chelsea-fields	O
,	O
that	O
Butler	O
and	O
Duce	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
that	O
Butler	O
rifled	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
Duce	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
Rice	O
was	O
hardly	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Papers	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
Duce	O
and	O
Butler	O
sold	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
Butler	O
had	O
the	O
Seal	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
:	O
That	O
Duce	O
had	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Guinea	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
Butler	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Attempt	O
made	O
upon	O
Colonel	O
Chudleigh	O
's	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Persons	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
before	O
apprehended	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Auger	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Sister	O
to	O
William	O
Duce	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
found	O
William	O
Duce	O
and	O
John	O
Dier	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thinks	O
was	O
Dier	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Blackabee	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Justice	O
Blackabee	O
's	O
,	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
John	O
Dier	O
to	O
be	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
Pumps	O
on	O
their	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Same	O
Make	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
them	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Williams	O
Duce	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Duce	O
's	O
Mother	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
Son	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
the	O
greatest	O
Discovery	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Duce	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
confess	O
to	O
him	O
Facts	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
John	O
Dier	O
having	O
been	O
before	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
discover	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
least	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
William	O
Duce	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
any	O
Robbery	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
Concerns	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
John	O
Dier	O
,	O
or	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
William	O
Duce	O
and	O
James	O
Butler	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
:	O
James	O
Butler	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	O
Monk	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Bridge	O
between	O
Tottenham-Court	B-place
and	O
the	O
Turn-Pike	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
three	O
Men	O
coming	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
answer	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
,	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
enough	O
to	O
hang	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
Horse	O
Bridle	O
was	O
John	O
Dier	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
satisfying	O
them	O
,	O
2	O
others	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
for	O
it	O
all	O
Day	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
only	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
John	O
Dier	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
324	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
drive	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
toward	O
Hampstead	O
Road	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
all	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	O
Dier	O
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
half	O
Crown	O
was	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Coachman	O
by	O
William	O
Duce	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Duce	O
's	O
Sister	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Bed	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
bought	O
Pistols	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Duce	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
noisy	O
,	O
and	O
rav	O
'd	O
against	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	O
Dier	O
,	O
Saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Man	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
twice	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
the	O
first	O
Assertion	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
any	O
Crime	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Affection	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
requir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
Statute	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
such	O
Statute	O
;	O
he	O
reflected	O
on	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
urging	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
's	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
first	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
finding	O
any	O
Inconsistency	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
.	O
He	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Justification	O
requir	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
ask	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
James	O
Butler	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
William	O
Duce	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Roberies	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
yet	O
William	O
Duce	O
was	O
not	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
either	O
;	O
altho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
(	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
Duce	O
was	O
an	O
Actor	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
which	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
more	O
Friendship	O
for	O
Duce	O
,	O
that	O
Prudence	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Nor	O
was	O
this	O
Denial	O
of	O
any	O
Service	O
to	O
Duce	O
.	O
Whether	O
Duce	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
natural	O
Temper	O
,	O
or	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
determine	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
his	O
violent	O
raving	O
the	O
proceeded	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
demand	O
a	O
Question	O
to	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
of	O
John	O
Dier	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
which	O
conduc	O
'd	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
Party	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
.	O
The	O
Question	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
kiss	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Holmess	O
Hand	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
John	O
Dier	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
parting	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
either	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
a	O
private	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
omitted	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
mentioned	O
by	O
either	O
Holmes	O
or	O
Dier	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
carried	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
Presumption	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
that	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopcroft	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
saw	O
the	O
Coat	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Coat	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
not	O
ever	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
soft	O
pated	O
Fellow	O
,	O
but	O
supporting	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
Wit	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
between	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
other	O
Peoples	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kately	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunham	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Two	O
.	O
William	O
Duce	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Butler	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Eight	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Edwards	O
,	O
alias	O
Hurst	O
,	O
Frances	O
Coats	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kately	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunham	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Five	O
last	O
convicted	O
the	O
preceeding	O
Sessions	O
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Seventeen	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neves	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pyeman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Guinis	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Sergeant	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Devon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Three	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Guyre	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	O
Bunworth	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
.	O
With	O
Observation	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Core	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
many	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Schemes	O
,	O
the	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justify	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Mears	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A.Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithsield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
Is	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
A	O
Full	O
and	O
Compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
Murders	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Highwaymen	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
William	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1722.	O
beginning	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
and	O
Little	O
John	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Falstaff	I-pers
,	O
Capt.Hind	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Nevison	O
,	O
Whitney	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
more	O
:	O
also	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
Account	O
than	O
any	O
yet	O
published	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
executed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
;	O
concluding	O
with	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Cartouche	O
in	O
France	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Robberies	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Actions	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Malhoni	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
faithfully	O
collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Histories	O
,	O
Records	O
,	O
Trials	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
and	O
written	O
regularly	O
as	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
By	O
J.W	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
bound	O
in	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
most	O
Surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Robinson	B-pers
Crusoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
Mariner	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
done	O
into	O
One	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Price	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
,	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
Several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-Master	O
in	O
Soho	O
Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
E.	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
THE	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainments	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
1001	O
Stories	O
,	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Sultaness	O
of	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Sultan	O
from	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
a	O
bloody	O
Vow	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
,	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Lady	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
In	O
eight	O
Vols	O
.	O
Price	O
11	O
s.	O
II	O
.	O
The	O
Adventures	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Clermont	O
and	O
Madam	O
de	O
Ravezan	O
.	O
A	O
Novel	O
.	O
In	O
four	O
Parts	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
new	O
Atalantis	O
.	O
In	O
four	O
Vols	O
.	O
Price	O
10	O
s.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
amorous	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Lucinda	O
,	O
an	O
English	O
Lady	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
V.	O
The	O
strange	O
Adventures	O
of	O
the	O
Count	O
Vinouel	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
whilst	O
they	O
resided	O
at	O
Conttantinople	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VI	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
Madam	O
de	O
Beaumont	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Cave	O
in	O
Wales	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
undiscovered	O
,	O
being	O
forced	O
to	O
fly	O
France	O
for	O
her	O
Religion	O
.	O
By	O
Mrs.	O
Aubin	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VII	O
.	O
Aminadab	O
's	O
Courtship	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Quaker	O
's	O
Wedding	O
.	O
A	O
Poem	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Way	O
of	O
Courtship	O
,	O
Method	O
of	O
Marrying	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
VIII	O
.	O
The	O
High	O
German	O
Doctor	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Vols	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
explanatory	O
Index	O
.	O
IX	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Holy	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Patriarchs	O
.	O
A	O
Book	O
proper	O
for	O
Children	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
X	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
.	O
A	O
Treatise	O
proper	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
Publick	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
XI	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
's	O
Rhetorick	O
.	O
Containing	O
Rules	O
for	O
speaking	O
and	O
writing	O
elegantly	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
XII	O
.	O
Moral	O
Reflections	O
and	O
Maxims	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Duke	O
de	O
la	O
Rochefoncault	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XIII	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
Muly	O
Ishmuel	O
King	O
of	O
Morocco	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
cruel	O
Usage	O
to	O
the	O
Christian	B-pers
Slaves	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XIV	O
.	O
A	O
general	O
History	O
of	O
Dreams	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XVI	O
.	O
A	O
Lydall	O
's	O
Table	O
of	O
Interest	O
.	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
XVI	O
.	O
A	O
Help	O
to	O
Prayer	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Knags	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
BOOKS	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Cartouche	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Robbers	O
,	O
A	O
Comedy	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
acted	O
many	O
Times	O
with	O
great	O
Applause	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
By	O
Mons	O
.	O
le	O
Grand	O
,	O
Comedian	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Actions	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Dominique	I-pers
Cartouche	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
broke	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
N.S	O
.	O
relating	O
at	O
large	O
his	O
remarkable	O
Adventures	O
,	O
desperate	O
Enterprizes	O
,	O
and	O
various	O
Escapes	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Sentence	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Scaffold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Trial	O
at	O
large	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hurly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Perjury	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
learned	O
Arguments	O
of	O
the	O
Council	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Humfreys	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
E.	O
Symon	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
:	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
,	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
1723	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
Price	O
Three	O
Pence	O
.	O
