TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
Of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
During	O
,	O
the	O
MAYOR	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
Deline	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1724	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Humphreys	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Snee	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forfeit	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiteing	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Whitehurst	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ashman	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Katlin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Letitia	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Letice	I-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gunnis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
meeting	O
no	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Which	O
Pretence	O
not	O
agreeing	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Bathey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ansloe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murther	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Company	O
were	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
near	O
King-street	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
That	O
Thomas	O
Ansloe	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
standing	O
as	O
they	O
supposed	O
,	O
making	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Soldier	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Devil	O
like	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
Colonel	O
Scot	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
cut	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
thrown	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Kennel	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
help	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
also	O
toward	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
cut	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
three	O
Times	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
cut	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bidding	O
them	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
mortally	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
threatened	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
would	O
shoot	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Speaker	O
's	O
Coachman	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Finding	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
wash	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
with	O
Brandy	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
after	O
very	O
restless	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
about	O
Forty	O
five	O
Hours	O
after	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Friborn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Watch-house	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
and	O
outragious	O
.	O
Two	O
Watchmen	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
the	O
Watch	O
called	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
his	O
Breeches	O
either	O
were	O
by	O
him	O
let	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
broke	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
desiring	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
his	O
Hands	O
at	O
liberty	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
presently	O
secured	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
slight	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
above	O
the	O
Groin	O
;	O
against	O
the	O
Hip-bone	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
half	O
deep	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
restless	O
all	O
Night	O
and	O
uneasy	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
being	O
sent	O
by	O
Colonel	O
Scot	B-pers
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Glister	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
through	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceived	O
some	O
Tokens	O
of	O
Convulsions	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Privy	O
Garden	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Richmond	O
'd	O
House	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
a	O
fighting	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
them	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
making	O
Passes	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Passes	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
?	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
seeming	O
willing	O
to	O
desist	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
let	O
alone	O
to	O
fight	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
getting	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
from	O
doing	O
Mischief	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
his	O
Sword	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
himself	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Mischief	O
came	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
forc	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wellbeloved	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Passing	O
through	O
the	O
Privy	O
Garden	O
,	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
a	O
fighting	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stand	O
leaning	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Sword	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
him	O
some	O
Mischief	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
return	O
him	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
great	O
Caution	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Box	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
Mischief	O
came	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
forgave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
gone	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
Yards	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
dressed	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
had	O
penetrated	O
below	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
about	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Liver	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
to	O
the	O
Diaphragma	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
28	O
Hours	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
They	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
pack	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
challeng	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
draw	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
,	O
peaceable	O
Person	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
Killed	O
two	O
Men	O
:	O
and	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Facts	O
had	O
been	O
tried	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Gratian	B-pers
Misson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ransey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Clothes	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
ran	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Hoxton	O
Market-House	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirmed	O
their	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Out-cry	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
Material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Banner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
He	O
kept	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
Errands	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Till	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Knees	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
in	O
a	O
Green	O
Purse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
bits	O
of	O
Sticks	O
,	O
Wax	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
such	O
sticking	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
but	O
pretended	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
being	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Glade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Dickinson	O
were	O
sculking	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
short	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Nesby	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
-	O
Nesby	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Locket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scoffin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
before	O
changed	O
Things	O
for	O
Earthen	O
Ware	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
to	O
change	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
her	O
Chain	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
call	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
down	O
the	O
Things	O
she	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
make	O
towards	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
the	O
Chain	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
thrust	O
something	O
down	O
in	O
her	O
Stocking	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Thought	O
of	O
her	O
Chain	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
another	O
Bargain	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
came	O
again	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Word	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Chain	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
when	O
she	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
Mother	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
nor	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
Chain	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Chain	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
changing	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
been	O
that	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Waymouth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
sick	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
kept	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
all	O
that	O
Week	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
ever	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
chang	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Curtains	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
Acknowledgement	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Huzzy	O
,	O
dont	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
more	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Evidence	O
had	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
from	O
Monday	O
till	O
Friday	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Friday	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
Committed	O
.	O
This	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Thursday	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
commited	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
Week	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Whitehorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Penitent	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
between	O
wet	O
and	O
dry	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
,	O
they	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
cry	O
'd	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
stumbled	O
over	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gadbury	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Mantle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ann	O
Gadbury	O
had	O
nurs	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
discharg	O
'd	O
and	O
paid	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
And	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
their	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
on	O
each	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
Gadbury	O
own	O
'd	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
affect	O
Mary	O
Griffith	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Ann	O
Gadbury	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillenden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Forster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Henry	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Forther	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
very	O
rudely	O
,	O
thrust	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
roll	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
Rolph	O
took	O
a	O
red	O
hot	O
Poker	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
burn	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Cheek	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
him	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
Hot	O
Pots	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
unpaid	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Man	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
otherwise	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
she	O
delay	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
Man	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
taking	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
told	O
out	O
Silver	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
when	O
Henry	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Silver	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
yet	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Change	O
of	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
near	O
5	O
l.	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
thrown	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
holding	O
by	O
the	O
Posts	O
kept	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
being	O
thrown	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
Henry	O
Man	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
Rudeness	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
never	O
appear	O
'd	O
since	O
so	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Rolph	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Saddle	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
,	O
in	O
Gratification	O
for	O
a	O
Buck	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Saddle	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Common	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hand-Saw	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Saw	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Buildings	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
9	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Coney	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
and	I-pers
Alice	I-pers
Nut	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Out-House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
roosted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Fowls	O
all	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
these	O
Fowls	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
Sauce-Pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
Kennedy	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
getting	O
what	O
Things	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Goods	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
any	O
Way	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Kennedy	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hattam	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lace	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Apartment	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
Difference	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
depos	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
murder	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
asleep	O
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
when	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Trunk	O
by	O
her	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
Pence	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
pretended	O
to	O
lose	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
them	O
pay	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
which	O
occasioning	O
some	O
difference	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
and	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Chair	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
some	O
Money	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
hair	O
Coal	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Irenonger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Bum-boat-Man	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sacks	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
craz	O
'd	O
Man	O
.	O
Upon	O
Consideration	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
accounted	O
non	O
Compos	O
Mentis	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
could	O
not	O
in	O
Law	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farquhar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
getting	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Clothes	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Tune	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Purse	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
The	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
further	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Purse	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
under	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Clothes	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
weekly	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Remainder	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Little-John	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
enquiring	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
dishonest	O
Person	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ellar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
sell	O
Oysters	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Men	O
being	O
drinking	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Her	O
Examination	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Man	O
a	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Man	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
further	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
and	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
her	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queen	B-place
Hithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	O
Partridge	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1722	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
once	O
came	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Ring	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
redeemed	O
it	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Her	O
Husband	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
Bundles	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
worth	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Cup	O
for	O
an	O
antient	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
showing	O
her	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Milliner	O
,	O
kept	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Bow-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
Cup	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
presently	O
missed	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
again	O
examined	O
the	O
Bundles	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
nothing	O
but	O
Rags	O
made	O
up	O
artificially	O
,	O
with	O
Tickets	O
with	O
Strings	O
like	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
lately	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
Cup	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Debt	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
intending	O
to	O
defraud	O
Robert	B-pers
Vokins	I-pers
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
containing	O
35	O
Yards	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
by	O
leaving	O
in	O
pawn	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Rags	O
of	O
no	O
Value	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Customers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
Crape	O
for	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Funeral	O
for	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
a	O
Brother	O
who	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Bundles	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Ends	O
of	O
some	O
Cloth	O
in	O
the	O
Bundles	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
Callimanco	O
upon	O
her	O
own	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
upon	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Coat-Makers	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
Coats	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
faint	O
of	O
pulling	O
a	O
Canvass	O
Bag	O
half	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
would	O
leave	O
the	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
it	O
while	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspected	O
nothing	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
reason	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
Notice	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
Shop-lifter	O
,	O
seeing	O
her	O
making	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Great	B-place
Stanmore	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
a	O
Barn	O
of	O
Hezekiah	B-pers
Burr	I-pers
,	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Hay	O
,	O
Corn	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Barn	O
was	O
burned	O
,	O
with	O
Hay	O
,	O
Corn	O
,	O
Peas	O
,	O
and	O
Beans	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
five	O
Horses	O
were	O
destroyed	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
in	O
the	O
Evenings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Watch	O
Light	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Match	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
where	O
the	O
Barn	O
stood	O
adjoining	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Barn	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
blaze	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
no	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
seeing	O
the	O
Fire	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
open	O
the	O
Gates	O
,	O
the	O
Barn	O
is	O
on	O
Fire	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Gates	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
broken	O
open	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
not	O
opening	O
the	O
Gate	O
.	O
tho'he	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
,	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
perceived	O
a	O
Hole	O
new	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Barn	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
smoking	O
a	O
Pipe	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
when	O
the	O
Barn	O
was	O
burning	O
.	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
And	O
three	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
unconcerned	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
help	O
,	O
he	O
walked	O
away	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
Words	O
between	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
his	O
staying	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
too	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Shilling	O
too	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
sav	O
'd	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
fetching	O
the	O
Candle	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Copper	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
fetchings	O
the	O
Match	O
,	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
that	O
because	O
the	O
Candle	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
Difference	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bar	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Barn	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
so	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
never	O
agree	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chapple	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
that	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
pretended	O
Husband	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
laid	O
up	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Children	O
)	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
19	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
wanting	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
losing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
cunning	O
Man	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
brown	O
Woman	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
she	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Cunning	O
Man	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
farther	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
;	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Lambeth	B-place
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
:	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
she	O
directing	O
the	O
officer	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
under	O
some	O
Necessity	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
from	O
coming	O
into	O
Trouble	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
that	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
charitably	O
reliev	O
'd	O
with	O
Victuals	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lent	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
making	O
this	O
appear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
14	O
Board	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
26	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wi	O
fe	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Interim	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
some	O
Mischief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
while	O
we	O
are	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Rogue	O
your	O
Husband	O
does	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wise	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
deserv	O
'd	O
Hanging	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
escap	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
so	O
near	O
home	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
her	O
Things	O
broken	O
and	O
thrown	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
for	O
all	O
their	O
Life	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
,	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
's	O
Daughter	O
said	O
,	O
an	O
Awl	O
and	O
some	O
Things	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Room	O
,	O
were	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
absconded	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Two	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
,	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Goose	O
in	O
Bunhill	O
Fields	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
come	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
easy	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
next	O
Day	O
by	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
it	O
falling	O
over	O
Board	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Awl	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
on	O
Board	O
of	O
Ship	O
.	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Sheath	O
of	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Ship	O
Mates	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Graves	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
about	O
his	O
Landlord	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
having	O
made	O
two	O
Trips	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
them	O
40	O
l.	O
at	O
two	O
Payments	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Grey	O
Hound	O
Ale-House	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Things	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
Danbury	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
helping	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
him	O
yet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Faggots	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perkinson	I-pers
,	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produc	O
'd	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
saw	O
one	O
stoop	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipping	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Willan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Hart-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Half	O
Peck	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Baker	O
's	O
Man	O
Set	O
down	O
his	O
Basket	O
in	O
Mark	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Bread	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Loaves	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
the	O
Loaves	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Mag-pie	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black	I-place
Friers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Castor	O
Hats	O
.	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Hats	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Ann	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
by	O
Pretence	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
Guinea	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
kept	O
it	O
.	O
John	O
Hopkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
sent	O
out	O
by	O
his	O
Mistress	O
Ann	O
Salt	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Bell	O
Yard	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
let	O
her	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
it	O
again	O
upon	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
the	O
Boy	O
John	O
Hopkins	O
came	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
hugging	O
and	O
kissing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
3	O
Pence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
bit	O
him	O
a	O
Dash	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stayes	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
45	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wetherly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bulmore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
whip	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maycock	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
9	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
longest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morehen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Leek	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
visit	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
desired	O
Mrs.	O
Leek	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Friend	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
grew	O
worse	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
accordingly	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
her	O
Couzin	O
Mrs.	O
Leek	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Burleigh	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
,	O
at	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
clasp	O
'd	O
their	O
Arms	O
round	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
go	O
a	O
long	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
seeing	O
them	O
stop	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
we	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
swore	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
know	O
who	O
we	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
was	O
disputing	O
with	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
desiring	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
Business	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
looking	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
Captain	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
requiring	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
thank	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Occasion	O
,	O
since	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
was	O
there	O
himself	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
being	O
resolute	O
,	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
about	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
presently	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
going	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
adding	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
Language	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
French	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
did	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
seemingly	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Unwillingness	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
go	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
a	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
Way	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
thank	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
Civility	O
in	O
waiting	O
upon	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
disswade	O
him	O
from	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
Conveniency	O
for	O
his	O
staying	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
standing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Milk	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
boil	O
for	O
her	O
Supper	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Milk	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Leek	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Leek	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
murder	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
her	O
Milk	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
,	O
asking	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
nothing	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
cross	O
her	O
Break	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Innocence	O
imaginable	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
dear	O
Mrs.	O
Morehen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
flourishing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
Swearing	O
,	O
that	O
whatever	O
Man	O
or	O
Woman	O
entered	O
the	O
Room	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
Way	O
,	O
entreating	O
both	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
directing	O
the	O
Sword	O
to	O
her	O
Breast	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
permit	O
some	O
Help	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
Injury	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
might	O
be	O
repair	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
enter	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
slipping	O
by	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
attempting	O
to	O
disarm	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
suffer	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
submitted	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
John	O
Stanley	O
:	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
ran	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Snowd	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
'd	O
himself	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
Hannah	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Snowd	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
Captain	O
Stanley	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
never	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
these	O
Tricks	O
?	O
And	O
viewing	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
cut	O
her	O
Lace	O
,	O
Strings	O
of	O
her	O
Cloathes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
upon	O
God	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
half	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Morehen	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
walk	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
along	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
set	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
stand	O
leaning	O
near	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
talking	O
together	O
friendly	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
set	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
standing	O
upon	O
a	O
Parry	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
one	O
that	O
entered	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
come	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
wou	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Morehen	O
being	O
kneeling	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
him	O
without	O
going	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Broom-sticks	O
,	O
designing	O
first	O
to	O
throw	O
in	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
Disorder	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
rush	O
in	O
and	O
knock	O
down	O
his	O
Sword	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Women	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
quietly	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
Things	O
afterwards	O
were	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Morehen	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hammond	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
,	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Leek	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Leek	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
faint	O
Shriek	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
lame	O
,	O
made	O
what	O
Haste	O
she	O
could	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
slipp	O
'd	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Addesey	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
wounded	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
be	O
not	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
lay	O
down	O
across	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Dear	O
Hannah	O
,	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Hannah	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
damn	O
'd	O
Bitch	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
looking	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
,	O
be	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
Word	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
her	O
Business	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
by	O
her	O
that	O
was	O
three	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Maycock	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
as	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Addesey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Hammond	O
and	O
she	O
coming	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Out	O
cry	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
slipping	O
in	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
for	O
what	O
follow	O
'd	O
after	O
was	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Snowd	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
Captain	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
never	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
these	O
Tricks	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
mortal	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
put	O
to	O
Bed	O
yet	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
though	O
,	O
for	O
Decency	O
sake	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
dress	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
outragiously	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
dead	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
in	O
Palliation	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
now	O
three	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upbraiding	O
her	O
with	O
Unnaturalness	O
,	O
in	O
not	O
taking	O
care	O
to	O
make	O
and	O
provide	O
some	O
Clothes	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
his	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
)	O
was	O
provok	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
where	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
known	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
rais	O
'd	O
his	O
Passion	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
perswaded	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
lunatick	O
.	O
But	O
these	O
Evidences	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
Point	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
or	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
After	O
having	O
received	O
Sentence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Death	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
treated	O
so	O
unkindly	O
by	O
his	O
Relations	O
or	O
Friends	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Scrivel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidences	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
by	O
them	O
at	O
Ingerstone	B-place
Fair	I-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Why	O
not	O
Beat	O
Dragon	O
,	O
near	O
Mile	O
End	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
and	O
Ann	O
Scrivel	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Theodorick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Towse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Milk	O
Pails	O
,	O
a	O
Yoke	O
,	O
Milk	O
Pot	O
and	O
Strainer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
James	O
Hussey	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
Field	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Jane	O
Towse	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Herringshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
solliciting	O
,	O
and	O
suborning	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	O
Munday	O
,	O
made	O
an	O
Offer	O
and	O
Tender	O
of	O
Payment	O
of	O
52	O
s.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1722	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
of	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
,	O
William	O
Munday	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Condition	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
forbear	O
proceeding	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Munday	O
and	O
his	O
Bail	O
.	O
He	O
not	O
paying	O
the	O
said	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
does	O
proceed	O
against	O
she	O
said	O
Munday	O
and	O
his	O
Bail	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
Producing	O
the	O
said	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
Edward	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
and	O
tender	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Clark	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Day	O
ordered	O
,	O
the	O
Judgments	O
obtained	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
against	O
Will	O
:	O
Munday	O
and	O
his	O
Bail	O
,	O
were	O
set	O
aside	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
afterwards	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Davis	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
that	O
Affidavit	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
and	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Munday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
any	O
such	O
Offer	O
or	O
Tender	O
of	O
the	O
52	O
s.	O
to	O
Clark	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
wilful	O
Perjury	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Notice	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
accepted	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
52	O
s.	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
two	O
Notes	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
52	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
each	O
Offence	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lant	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
500	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1723	O
.	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
riotously	O
,	O
and	O
tumultuously	O
,	O
assemble	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
continued	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
manag	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Attorney	O
General	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
supported	O
their	O
Charge	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
Hollowing	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
about	O
20	O
Men	O
with	O
great	O
Sticks	O
and	O
Clubs	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
hissing	O
,	O
and	O
shaking	O
and	O
rattling	O
of	O
their	O
Clubs	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Manner	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
and	O
Crown	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
marching	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
they	O
made	O
two	O
Bonfires	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Fires	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
burnt	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Club	O
thrown	O
from	O
among	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
which	O
hit	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
throwed	O
Stones	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Lamps	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
retreated	O
to	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
.	O
Then	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
as	O
near	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
as	O
they	O
durst	O
to	O
venture	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
quiet	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
some	O
Hundreds	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
Clubs	O
and	O
Staves	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
retired	O
to	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
broke	O
his	O
Windows	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-Room	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Persons	O
reading	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
frightened	O
at	O
their	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
in	O
Stones	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
bolt	O
the	O
Back-door	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
burst	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
,	O
broke	O
his	O
Sconce	O
which	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
heat	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
was	O
struck	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
broke	O
the	O
Bone	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
They	O
having	O
continued	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Provocation	O
given	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
afterwards	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
battened	O
and	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
to	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
render	O
'd	O
insensible	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Noise	O
of	O
hissing	O
and	O
following	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
greater	O
Number	O
,	O
hissing	O
and	O
hollowing	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
our	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
upon	O
Exercise	O
with	O
Captain	O
Saunders	O
in	O
the	O
Artillery	O
Ground	O
,	O
whose	O
Company	O
had	O
mustered	O
there	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
be	O
himself	O
also	O
being	O
Major	O
of	O
the	O
White	O
Regiment	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Danger	O
he	O
apprehended	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
need	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Mob	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
broke	O
all	O
his	O
Lamps	O
,	O
his	O
Lanthorns	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
almost	O
half	O
way	O
in	O
his	O
Passage	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
sent	O
up	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
being	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
having	O
marched	O
that	O
Day	O
as	O
Voluntiers	O
with	O
Captain	O
Saunders	O
,	O
were	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Muster	O
,	O
invited	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
Sup	O
at	O
Major	O
Adams	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
near	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
.	O
That	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Mob	O
were	O
pulling	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
a	O
Door	O
or	O
two	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
heard	O
several	O
Noises	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Messengers	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
at	O
Times	O
,	O
from	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
bringing	O
News	O
of	O
Injuries	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
another	O
Messengers	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
broken	O
Major	O
Adams	O
's	O
Lamps	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
People	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Sticks	O
had	O
been	O
flung	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
several	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
were	O
driven	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
attempting	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Firelock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
knock	O
any	O
Body	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fire	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
having	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
to	O
defend	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
the	O
Gates	O
were	O
shut	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Constable	O
put	O
through	O
his	O
Staff	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
his	O
Authority	O
,	O
and	O
commanded	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Gates	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Posterns	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
shut	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
round	O
through	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
Cripplegate	O
they	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
among	O
the	O
Mob	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
no	O
Hannoverian	O
Proclamation	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Person	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
particularly	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
but	O
Williams	O
for	O
over	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pursuing	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Lant	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Oaken	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
Ambler	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Supper	O
at	O
Major	O
Adams	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
Said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
William	O
's	O
Mob	O
is	O
out	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Lot	O
them	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
here	O
will	O
stir	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
stay	O
'd	O
some	O
Time	O
longer	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Entry	O
full	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lamps	O
and	O
Windows	O
had	O
been	O
dash	O
'd	O
in	O
pieces	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
seeming	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
rallying	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
them	O
read	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
disperse	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
help	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
they	O
throw	O
'd	O
Firebrands	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
rallying	O
again	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
my	O
House	O
will	O
be	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Lant	O
came	O
and	O
jostled	O
him	O
.	O
One	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
Lant	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
heading	O
them	O
all	O
this	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
Captain	O
Lamb	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
last	O
they	O
wrested	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Mob	O
cry	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Militia	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Mob	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
unruly	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
his	O
long	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
among	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
short	O
one	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
borrow	O
him	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
the	O
Mob	O
began	O
to	O
halloo	O
,	O
and	O
gather	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
another	O
Constable	O
present	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
Staff	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
growing	O
more	O
unruly	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
Bonfire	O
and	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
shall	O
abuse	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
meddle	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
Aldermen	O
have	O
done	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
shall	O
obstruct	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
Rejoycing	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Constable	O
had	O
likewise	O
a	O
Staff	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
they	O
grew	O
very	O
unruly	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Lanthorns	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
there	O
saw	O
Lant	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Stick	O
,	O
flourishing	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
grew	O
more	O
violent	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
Sticks	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Passage	O
,	O
were	O
for	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
disswaded	O
them	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
give	O
no	O
occasion	O
or	O
pretence	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
the	O
Aggressors	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Staff	O
cross	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
Persons	O
advised	O
the	O
Reading	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
push	O
'd	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
about	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
more	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
murthered	O
,	O
to	O
withdraw	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Head	O
broken	O
going	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
pursed	O
them	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
reading	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
Sticks	O
and	O
Firebrands	O
in	O
very	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
great	O
Lanthorn	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
pressed	O
so	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
attempting	O
to	O
shut	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
could	O
not	O
shut	O
it	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
but	O
they	O
forced	O
their	O
way	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
wounded	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
being	O
driven	O
out	O
they	O
retired	O
to	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gates	O
were	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Staff	O
partly	O
in	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
show	O
his	O
Authority	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
round	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Kits	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
a	O
Fool	O
and	O
a	O
Blockhead	O
,	O
for	O
reading	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Cry	O
was	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Williams	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
see	O
a	O
more	O
unprovok	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
barbarous	O
Abuse	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
that	O
gave	O
them	O
no	O
Provocation	O
in	O
Word	O
or	O
Deed	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
Members	O
of	O
the	O
Artillery	O
Ground	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
at	O
their	O
Tuesday	O
's	O
Exercise	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
News	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
broken	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
might	O
be	O
read	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
replying	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
there	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
in	O
writing	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
ill	O
Effect	O
of	O
their	O
violent	O
Proceedings	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Notice	O
by	O
their	O
Watches	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
10	O
Minutes	O
after	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
terrible	O
Racket	O
about	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
getting	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
forgetting	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
Watches	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Lamps	O
and	O
Windows	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
several	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
very	O
civilly	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
retire	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
very	O
Severe	O
Blows	O
,	O
Stones	O
and	O
Sticks	O
being	O
flung	O
in	O
as	O
thick	O
as	O
Hail	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
retire	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Lant	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
assaulted	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
Men	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
Swords	O
,	O
Muskets	O
,	O
and	O
Bayonets	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
went	O
with	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
with	O
Muskets	O
,	O
to	O
defend	O
