TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	B-pers
CONYERS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracey	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Peed	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lukin	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Futril	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamston	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Chorley	I-pers
,	O
Barthol	B-pers
Wimberly	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sams	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sibbs	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Collison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmund	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Loan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Friend	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Lombard	B-place
Street	I-place
into	O
George	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
clapping	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
his	O
Pocket	O
missed	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
one	O
under	O
each	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
his	O
own	O
was	O
found	O
dropp	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
several	O
Yards	O
farther	O
than	O
he	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
wash	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Quilt	I-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Saggs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
where	O
the	O
Ticking	O
was	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Ticking	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
Ticking	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
Piece	O
from	O
her	O
Side	O
.	O
Another	O
Person	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Dropping	O
of	O
the	O
Ticking	O
from	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Ticking	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
she	O
supposed	O
did	O
drop	O
the	O
Ticking	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
Stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
has	O
since	O
absconded	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
calling	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
over	O
against	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Grove	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediatley	O
clapp	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Horse-Coarser	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
unpin	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
take	O
off	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Childs	O
Coat	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
Than	O
asking	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
stripp	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mother	O
had	O
bid	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Child	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
's	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
coming	O
Home	O
at	O
Five	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Word	O
brought	O
about	O
Six	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
the	O
Child	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
Pin	O
prick	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
only	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
to	O
ease	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Evidences	O
came	O
and	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
another	O
Woman	O
Servant	O
being	O
left	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Servant	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
and	O
Linnen	O
.	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
strong	O
made	O
Box	O
,	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
taking	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Box	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
all	O
her	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Clothes	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
found	O
the	O
Hinges	O
had	O
been	O
wrenched	O
open	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hinges	O
wrench	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
was	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
often	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
his	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
several	O
Times	O
found	O
his	O
Landlady	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Landlady	O
;	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
while	O
they	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
he	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
Time	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
that	O
her	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Glade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Clear	O
Starcher	O
was	O
Ironing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Person	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Another	O
,	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
the	O
Clothes	O
in	O
a	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
off	O
in	O
great	O
Haste	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
Hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
too	O
strong	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
dropp	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
laid	O
Hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
Pan	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
over	O
the	O
Pan	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Griffith	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candle-sticks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
run	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Candle	O
sticks	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
Nicholas	O
Lambert	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Landis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Judge	I-pers
;	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Judge	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Slayden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaving	O
himself	O
irregularly	O
and	O
Things	O
having	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
sound	O
also	O
a	O
Key	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
:	O
And	O
upon	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
many	O
contradictions	O
Accounts	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
Key	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
confes	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
Times	O
taken	O
out	O
divers	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
wrote	O
down	O
the	O
particular	O
Some	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Mother	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
using	O
Many	O
Menaces	O
,	O
threatned	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
terrified	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
about	O
27	O
s.	O
but	O
his	O
Master	O
still	O
threatning	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
his	O
former	O
Confession	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
Direction	O
of	O
those	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
write	O
upon	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
although	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
so	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
that	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
credible	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
their	O
terrifying	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
in	O
finding	O
the	O
Key	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
Villain	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
this	O
Key	O
will	O
bring	O
you	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
considering	O
the	O
good	O
Character	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Wallbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	O
de	O
la	O
Fountain	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Noerey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Counting-House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
their	O
Servant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Capacity	O
of	O
a	O
Footman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
their	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
return	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apperhended	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
so	O
suddenly	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
had	O
told	O
his	O
Master	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
foul	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Certificate	O
from	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Distemper	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
own	O
'd	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
Talk	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
resolv	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
him	O
away	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
The	O
Reason	O
he	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
upon	O
confessing	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
would	O
have	O
forgiven	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Martha	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
House	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
hide	O
herself	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
far	O
distant	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gorgin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Colfield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Colfield	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
forewarn	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
10	O
Guineas	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
he	O
missed	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
would	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
forbid	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Stibs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Paper	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
miss	O
'd	O
Things	O
,	O
Suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Pepper-Box	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
her	O
none	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
38	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
miss	O
'd	O
Callimanco	O
by	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
divers	O
Times	O
cut	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Smock	O
was	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wore	O
it	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Private	O
Whipping	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
the	O
Deals	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
Deals	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Jobb	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
undertaken	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
Account	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
his	O
Servant	O
Orders	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
cutting	O
the	O
Deals	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Deals	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
Jobb	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Master	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
the	O
Owner	O
being	O
at	O
Work	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Highfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dayton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Grates	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Grates	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stall	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Shoes	O
on	O
to	O
wear	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
Stall	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Soams	I-pers
and	O
Quilt	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Forster	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
one	O
Night	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
afterwards	O
by	O
Daniel	O
Soams	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
Quilt	O
Arnold	O
took	O
his	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
by	O
what	O
Authority	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Arnold	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
Authority	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
forg	O
'd	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
9	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
that	O
their	O
Authority	O
was	O
such	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
tampered	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
for	O
the	O
Smith	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
Key	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Soams	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
Bellamy	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
forg	O
'd	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
9	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shoes	O
standing	O
there	O
,	O
Arnold	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
also	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Buckles	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Arnold	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
be	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Soams	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
had	O
forg	O
'd	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
9	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
going	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Soams	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
informing	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Bellany	O
,	O
who	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
had	O
forg	O
'd	O
a	O
Receipt	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
resolving	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
apprehended	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Soams	O
came	O
and	O
undertook	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Arnold	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
no	O
Order	O
for	O
the	O
Searching	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
their	O
having	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
rashly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
justify	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Arnold	O
had	O
been	O
assisting	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
apprehending	O
One	O
Hundred	O
and	O
Fifty	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
greater	O
Number	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
prosecuted	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Houses	O
of	O
Persons	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
Things	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Soams	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
him	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Teggs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
taking	O
120	O
Carp	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Colebrook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	O
Packer	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
120	O
Carp	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pond	O
of	O
James	O
Colebrook	O
,	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1723.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1723	O
.	O
did	O
wilfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
break	O
and	O
cut	O
down	O
the	O
Head	O
or	O
Mound	O
of	O
a	O
Pond	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
James	O
Colebrook	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Carp	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
them	O
did	O
destroy	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
and	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Packer	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Fence	O
into	O
a	O
Ground	O
where	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Colebrook	O
's	O
Pond	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Packer	O
went	O
both	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
broke	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Sluice	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Sluice	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
out	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Packer	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
take	O
out	O
about	O
60	O
Brace	O
of	O
Carps	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
Teggs	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
St.	O
John	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
set	O
up	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Teggs	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Fish	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Pond	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Fish	O
out	O
of	O
was	O
a	O
square	O
Pond	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
a	O
Stove	O
Pond	O
,	O
about	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
guesses	O
,	O
15	O
Foot	O
Square	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Church	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Pond	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
Foot	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Foot	O
over	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Fall	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
let	O
all	O
the	O
Water	O
out	O
in	O
two	O
Hours	O
Time	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
about	O
60	O
Brace	O
of	O
Carp	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sluice	O
belonging	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Breaking	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Sluice	O
on	O
Thomas	O
Packer	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
on	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Penalty	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
Indictment	O
,	O
founded	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Determination	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
Whether	O
the	O
Crime	O
be	O
allowed	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Body	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Servant	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hinchley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
then	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Bar	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Mattox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
South	B-place
Mims	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Four	O
Ducks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
Baronet	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lodg	O
'd	O
one	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Stomachers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Weston	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coal	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Flexly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
Esquire	O
Bulstrode	O
's	O
Coach	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
immediately	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
besides	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
Notes	O
for	O
above	O
20	O
l.	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Garter	B-pers
Stanbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Roebuck	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hurgrove	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Porridge	O
Pots	O
,	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Benford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Ducks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Amy	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Monk	O
Savil	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Boy	O
that	O
clean	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
want	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cup	O
being	O
lost	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
Muslin	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Edmund	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Ram	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
like	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
perceiving	O
something	O
of	O
Linnen	O
hang	O
below	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sheets	O
gone	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
detain	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheet	O
was	O
drop	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
the	O
Ram	O
Inn	O
to	O
sup	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
resolving	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
her	O
Friend	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Servant	O
demanding	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
Child	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
doing	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
transport	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
that	O
another	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
enough	O
already	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sheet	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
sheet	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bollard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
and	I-pers
William	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
James	O
Charnock	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
far	O
about	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
David	O
Davis	O
had	O
been	O
also	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
that	O
Sugar	O
house	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
discharg	O
'd	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
That	O
David	O
Davis	O
had	O
been	O
let	O
in	O
two	O
Mornings	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
three	O
o-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mawson	O
,	O
the	O
Clerk	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
Information	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
Sugar	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
unreasonable	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
the	O
next	O
Time	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
acquaint	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
about	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
Davis	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Brandy	O
to	O
treat	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Clerk	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
saw	O
Charnock	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Lumps	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
weighing	O
40	O
Pound	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Charnock	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
Sack	O
with	O
the	O
Sugar	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
warm	O
,	O
just	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stove	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Charnock	O
had	O
lighted	O
him	O
down	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
David	O
Davis	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
his	O
Foot	O
against	O
a	O
Sack	O
in	O
the	O
Scale	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
lift	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
immediately	O
Mr.	O
Mawson	O
started	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
wash	O
his	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.Mawson	O
push	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
brush	O
'd	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
Davis	O
's	O
having	O
any	O
Sugar	O
.	O
Nor	O
had	O
he	O
ever	O
given	O
away	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
's	O
Sugar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitburn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishophgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
Franklin	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
others	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Magpye	I-place
,	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
drank	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
to	O
order	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Goety	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
were	O
going	O
through	O
Broadstreet	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
wish	O
'd	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
their	O
Light	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
he	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
there	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
another	O
Tankard	O
fill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
-	O
Franklin	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Towels	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ridler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
being	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
after	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Duke	I-place
's	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Her	O
Examination	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
That	O
whereas	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Micajah	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
February	O
Sessions	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
172	O
1/2	O
and	O
thereupon	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
was	O
transported	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Plantations	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Term	O
of	O
Seven	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
England	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
a	O
second	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Coach	O
Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathan	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
1	O
Coach	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
both	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Confession	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Watts	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
Tucker	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1722	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winstanley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Wallbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Rakestraw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
o-Clock	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Plough	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
at	I-place
Stocks-Market	I-place
.	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
he	O
examined	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Sleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saying	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
putting	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
into	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Drawer	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
one	O
Night	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Fork	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Fork	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Table-Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
assoon	O
as	O
she	O
rose	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Fork	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Week	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
lost	O
two	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	O
Magdelen	O
du	O
Feue	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
45	O
Yards	O
of	O
Hair	O
Camlet	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pyen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Work	O
was	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Loom	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
the	O
Camblet	O
was	O
found	O
cut	O
in	O
five	O
Pieces	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Straw	O
Bed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Straw-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
opening	O
it	O
found	O
46	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
in	O
her	O
Straw-Bed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Spicer	O
's	O
Street	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Camblet	O
that	O
was	O
so	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
suited	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Loom	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
out	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Camblet	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
knowing	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Camblet	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Prison	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
before	O
the	O
Camblet	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
about	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
out	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
particular	O
Place	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Her	O
Landlady	O
gave	O
her	O
Leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Sheet	O
and	O
Blankets	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
5	O
s.	O
that	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
nurs	O
'd	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrought	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Iron	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
;	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
carried	O
a	O
Fare	O
,	O
had	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Ladies	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
drawn	O
the	O
Coat	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Centry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
thrown	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
came	O
by	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
take	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lillo	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gown	O
having	O
been	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
hung	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
excused	O
himself	O
as	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
designing	O
no	O
Harm	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owning	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdmeneanor	O
,	O
in	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
James	O
Noble	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
stepped	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Maid	O
holding	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
beset	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
and	O
behind	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
finding	O
himself	O
lock	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
beset	O
,	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
backwards	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Glass	O
broken	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
he	O
was	O
beset	O
that	O
way	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
which	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
her	O
Master	O
being	O
gone	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Apartment	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Candle	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
starting	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
just	O
turning	O
to	O
go	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
wanted	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
strange	O
Name	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
pulled	O
it	O
hard	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
Spring	O
Lock	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
till	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Help	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
thus	O
caught	O
in	O
a	O
Trap	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
no	O
ways	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
opened	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Thorough-fare	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
a	O
lusty	O
young	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
advised	O
him	O
,	O
Voluntarily	O
to	O
chuse	O
Transporatation	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
Fine	O
and	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
following	O
their	O
Advice	O
,	O
was	O
sentenced	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
One	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
GERARD	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonas	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
for	O
ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
Ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
Gerard	O
Bourn	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Fact	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
are	O
Prisoners	O
for	O
Debt	O
in	O
the	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
's	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
self	O
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
Debt	O
in	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
the	O
Child	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
in	O
going	O
of	O
Errands	O
,	O
fetching	O
her	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
a	O
Half	O
Penny	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
that	O
were	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Had	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
broken	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Child	O
said	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Gerard	O
Bourn	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
rallied	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
before	O
observed	O
him	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
toying	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
threatened	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Goal	O
ring	O
if	O
he	O
persisted	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
Rogue	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
afraid	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
droop	O
,	O
fall	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
Stomach	O
,	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
stir	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
disordered	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
showing	O
her	O
to	O
some	O
Women	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
pox	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Bourn	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
Three	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
Penn	O
once	O
,	O
who	O
stopped	O
her	O
Mouth	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
accusing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
examined	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
abus	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
degree	O
,	O
the	O
Parts	O
being	O
violently	O
lacerated	O
,	O
contus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
inflam	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pox	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
being	O
called	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
not	O
giving	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Answer	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
permitted	O
to	O
swear	O
:	O
And	O
so	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
Lawer	O
requires	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Matter	O
appearing	O
so	O
clear	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
till	O
they	O
do	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Tott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Keysar	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Hoops	O
were	O
Ann	O
Keysar	O
's	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Beadle	O
and	O
Headborough	O
;	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Hoops	O
;	O
that	O
examining	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Cooper	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Mary	O
,	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
hoop	O
some	O
Casks	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
to	O
sail	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
but	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
detain	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mordant	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Seal	O
Skin	O
Pouch	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
Seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
Merchant	O
Forward	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Voyage	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Half-way	O
House	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
Penny	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Half-way-House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
far	O
down	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
and	O
Pint	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
taking	O
out	O
his	O
Pouch	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
were	O
both	O
his	O
Tobacco	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
fill	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
fill	O
'd	O
his	O
Pipe	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Pouch	O
again	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
having	O
other	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
was	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
towards	O
Stepney	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
Time	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Pouch	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
back	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
had	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
never	O
light	O
on	O
her	O
till	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
take	O
his	O
Pouch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Person	O
in	O
this	O
Company	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Familiarity	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
Talk	O
and	O
Drinking	O
together	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Charity	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
kiss	O
her	O
Lips	O
,	O
nor	O
feel	O
her	O
any	O
where	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
suppose	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Pouch	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
rising	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Back	O
Lane	O
from	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Oysters	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
her	O
hold	O
by	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
whom	O
he	O
Courted	O
seven	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
gone	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
no	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
still	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
two	O
Shillings	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
her	O
Basket	O
of	O
Oysters	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
Names	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Bitch	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
he	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
the	O
Robbery	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
all	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Oysters	O
or	O
Basket	O
either	O
.	O
She	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
Proof	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
call	O
any	O
one	O
Person	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Pindar	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
,	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Daughter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
Money	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Landlady	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Daughter	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Daughter	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
look	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
self	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
in	O
stead	O
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Pork	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Things	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
t	O
Compting	O
:	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Scot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Reeves	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
borrowed	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
Kent	O
.	O
Their	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
they	O
both	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Compting	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
not	O
being	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
Back-door	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
left	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wastcoats	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
8d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
calling	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiteing	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Magie	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Pot	O
,	O
Cup	O
,	O
Candle-sticks	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
two	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
within	O
a	O
Door	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Mr.Saunderson	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
Whiteing	O
came	O
running	O
in	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
What	O
need	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
Masters	O
than	O
Parish	O
Churches	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Time	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
he	O
came	O
off	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Whiteing	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Leather	O
to	O
mend	O
his	O
Shoes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
500	O
l.	O
if	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
meaning	O
Mackey	O
,	O
would	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
much	O
Money	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
very	O
easily	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
all	O
being	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
they	O
consulted	O
about	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
That	O
Whiting	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
young	O
Mr.	O
Saunderson	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
300	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Method	O
proposed	O
by	O
Whiteing	O
for	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
.	O
Mackey	O
being	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
appointed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
blind	O
and	O
gag	O
Mr.	O
Saunderson	O
,	O
his	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
vest	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
except	O
Whiteing	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
room	O
this	O
Blood	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
and	O
trampled	O
about	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Show	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
murthered	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
then	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
Mackey	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
binding	O
and	O
gagging	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
asked	O
Whiteing	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
got	O
this	O
Booty	O
.	O
How	O
they	O
must	O
dispose	O
of	O
themselves	O
and	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Whiteing	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
New	O
England	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
way	O
thither	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
into	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
melt	O
down	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Consultations	O
,	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
resolved	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
Whiteing	O
appointed	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
about	O
twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
mistake	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
Chalk	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Mackey	O
,	O
did	O
about	O
twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
Mackey	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Mackey	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
That	O
Whiteing	O
the	O
Footman	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
Plate	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
that	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Saunderson	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
also	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
Occasion	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
into	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
seeing	O
Mackey	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
calling	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
Break	O
of	O
Day	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
opened	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
seen	O
whit	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
Way	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lake	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
Mackey	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Gripe	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the-next	O
Day	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
talked	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
buying	O
Silver	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
an	O
Ounce	O
?	O
And	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
most	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
Form	O
,	O
or	O
melted	O
down	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
asking	O
several	O
impertinent	O
Questions	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
that	O
Morning	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Saunderson	O
's	O
Robbery	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
enquired	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
that	O
Ship	O
which	O
had	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
resolutions	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Plunder	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mackey	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Harman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
who	O
examining	O
him	O
,	O
finding	O
his	O
Account	O
was	O
inconsistant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
some	O
Expression	O
,	O
of	O
having	O
another	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
buying	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Hints	O
whereabout	O
,	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Landlady	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
always	O
kept	O
their	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
permit	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
strengthened	O
their	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
demanded	O
Entrance	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
showing	O
them	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
;	O
the	O
Landlady	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
they	O
searched	O
all	O
about	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
,	O
till	O
examining	O
an	O
old	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
so	O
heavy	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
that	O
without	O
Difficulty	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
at	O
last	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Plates	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Winchester	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
Notice	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
The	O
Plate	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Whiting	O
the	O
Footman	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
doing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Solicitations	O
of	O
Wilkinson	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Mackey	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
Mackey	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
consenting	O
nor	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
only	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
and	O
walking	O
with	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
fields	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
stepp	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
nor	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
along	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Miles	O
off	O
.	O
Whiting	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
both	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
after	O
them	O
Apprehending	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Shadrach	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Annis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Charles	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Baltimore	I-pers
.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Dugard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Zachary	I-pers
.	O
The	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Four	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiteing	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
alias	O
Magie	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitburn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
six	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Landis	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Turvey	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Maze	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neeves	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Four	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Forty	O
Two	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hurgrove	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Glade	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stibs	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
Shadrach	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Highfield	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Annis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Dugard	I-pers
,	O
Garter	B-pers
Stambury	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Tott	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Six	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convicts	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
Gerard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonas	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
Seven	O
years	O
Charles	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
and	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Teggs	I-pers
,	O
left	O
to	O
the	O
Determination	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
published	O
,	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venerual	O
Disease	O
.	O
with	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admouitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Authur	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
,	O
the	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justify	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specifies	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
How	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Means	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
J	O
.	O
Backer	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hick's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
A	O
Full	O
and	O
Compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
Murders	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Highwaymen	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
William	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1722.	O
beginning	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
and	O
Little	O
John	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Flalstaff	I-pers
,	O
Capt.Hind	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Nevison	O
,	O
Whitney	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
more	O
:	O
also	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
Account	O
than	O
any	O
yet	O
published	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
executed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
;	O
concluding	O
with	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Cartouche	O
in	O
France	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Robberies	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Actions	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Malhoni	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
faithfully	O
collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Histories	O
,	O
Records	O
,	O
Trials	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
and	O
written	O
regularly	O
as	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
By	O
J.W	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
bound	O
in	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
most	O
Surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Robinson	B-pers
Crosoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
Mariner	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
done	O
into	O
One	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
,	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Vanety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Courle	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplisy	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.Ayre	O
's	O
Effect	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-Master	O
in	O
Soho	O
Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
