TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	O
CONYERS	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Kistel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
Drew	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Betsworth	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wrenn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Castor	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Rubber	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Workhouse	O
at	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Hats	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
given	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Hats	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
The	O
Hats	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
or	O
borrow	O
Money	O
upon	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
producing	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
East-cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mug	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Harris	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Two	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
Mug	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
the	O
Drawer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carrying	O
off	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
what	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Mug	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
there	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
hungry	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
Milk	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Mug	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Milk	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
privately	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
Milk	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
Pots	O
:	O
That	O
beings	O
a	O
Cobler	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Stall	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
design	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Mug	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wardent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
walking	O
near	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shore-ditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brain	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Lock	O
;	O
that	O
taxing	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
that	O
Lock	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
divers	O
Times	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
however	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
and	O
another	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Bushnel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Kingstreet	B-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Hats	O
off	O
the	O
Rails	O
of	O
the	O
Stair-Case	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Hats	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
Strand	O
Bridge	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
House	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
and	O
waited	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
:	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
waited	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
meeting	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
Business	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
near	O
the	O
Horns	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
his	O
Money	O
?	O
You	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Deptford	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
Matters	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
make	O
Matters	O
worse	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
'till	O
to	O
Morrow	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
Execution	B-place
Dock	I-place
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
Weaver	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
Morris	O
his	O
Money	O
?	O
't	O
is	O
like	O
your	O
Irish	O
Tricks	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
them	O
both	O
over-board	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
leaning	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Boat	O
from	O
over-turning	O
:	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
kill	O
them	O
all	O
Three	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
the	O
Man	O
mad	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
Passes	O
at	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Morris	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
saw	O
Eleanor	O
Clark	O
learning	O
over	O
the	O
Bootside	O
,	O
and	O
bleeding	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
the	O
Boat	O
ashore	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Waterman	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Price	B-pers
Sturgil	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Waterman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
near	O
New	O
Crane	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
brandishing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
overturn	O
'd	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
the	O
Waterman	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
at	O
Morris	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
some	O
Business	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
would	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
secure	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
hire	O
a	O
Boat	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
accidentally	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
Business	O
with	O
one	O
Jane	O
-	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Demand	O
upon	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
down	O
for	O
James	O
-	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
Day	O
treated	O
him	O
very	O
handsomely	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
curs	O
'd	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
made	O
Passes	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
wounded	O
;	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
the	O
Waterman	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
examining	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
pierced	O
through	O
the	O
Intercostal	O
Muscles	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
both	O
Lobes	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
the	O
Sword	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
his	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Sword	O
and	O
Cloths	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
sword	O
again	O
,	O
before	O
or	O
at	O
their	O
coming	O
from	O
Deptford	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
Three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.Ethelburg	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
Linen	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
40lb	O
of	O
Lead	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Lead	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
carrying	O
away	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lead	O
that	O
fitted	O
the	O
Place	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stripp	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Lead	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
called	O
Origenis	O
contra	O
Celsum	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stall	O
in	O
White	B-place
Friars	I-place
Gate	I-place
Way	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Dog-Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Dog	O
Kennel	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Pearce	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pennyal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
Cows	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Lambeth	B-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
the	O
8th	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
And	O
Will	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
ordered	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
must	O
pay	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
a	O
Stranger	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
but	O
half-witted	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elisabeth	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hely	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Hely	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Smith	O
for	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Abetting	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Corner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Will	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Journey-Man	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
some	O
Stove-Grates	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Smith	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
they	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
talking	O
lewd	O
Discourse	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
lewdly	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
not	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
Rogue	O
and	O
Whore	O
.	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
Elis	O
.	O
Hely	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
beating	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
with	O
her	O
Fist	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Smith	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
cut	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Hely	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
deceased	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
Secure	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
murther	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hawk	O
's	O
Son	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Difference	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
Elis	O
.	O
Hely	O
falling	O
upon	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
not	O
abuse	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
swore	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
Were	O
she	O
not	O
a	O
Woman	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
should	O
Match	O
him	O
,	O
meaning	O
William	O
smith	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Smith	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
Fall	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
deceased	O
violently	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
or	O
Cane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
deceased	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
murthered	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Skull	O
lay	O
bare	O
for	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
shrunk	O
down	O
towards	O
his	O
Ear	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Fracture	O
nor	O
Depression	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
made	O
with	O
.	O
That	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fair	O
Way	O
of	O
Recovery	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
about	O
five	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Fever	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
opened	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
extravasted	O
Blood	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
Fracture	O
or	O
Depression	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
habitation	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
might	O
be	O
prejudicial	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
that	O
apperenhended	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Elisabeth	O
Hely	O
,	O
while	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
laid	O
on	O
him	O
very	O
heartily	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Elis	O
.	O
Hely	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hely	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
William	O
Smith	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
Some	O
Money	O
for	O
Work	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
bid	O
her	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
overtaken	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
Hawks	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
who	O
saying	O
,	O
There	O
goes	O
a	O
Rogue	O
and	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidences	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
to	O
depose	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
William	O
Smith	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-Slaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Polfrey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chamber	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
her	O
chest	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
her	O
Bag	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
entering	O
the	O
Chamber	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beesely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
7	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
having	O
gone	O
out	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
and	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
apprehended	O
and	O
six	O
Pounds	O
odd	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
owned	O
was	O
his	O
Money	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
who	O
committed	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
Beesely	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
Rose	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
shared	O
it	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gust	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
30	O
Shillings	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Boys	O
that	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
fifteen	O
Times	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
lift	O
up	O
a	O
sash	O
Window	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
two	O
Boys	O
being	O
young	O
the	O
one	O
being	O
but	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
but	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
Nine	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
admit	O
them	O
as	O
Evidences	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
deficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burton	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Hammer	O
Heads	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jevins	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	O
Jevins	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crady	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dustan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
Three	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
28th	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Job	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
entertaining	O
him	O
well	O
with	O
victuals	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Hungry	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
himself	O
,	O
might	O
eat	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
Crady	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Cup	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cousin	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Spoons	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Cup	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Turnkey	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
by	O
Job	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Joiner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennet	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Deals	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bugby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
taken	O
another	O
Person	O
's	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Deals	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Boat	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
laden	O
with	O
Deals	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bugby	O
's	O
Wharf	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fryer	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
their	O
Trials	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Being	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
drunk	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
Boat	O
a-drift	O
with	O
the	O
Deals	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
their	O
confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fryer	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
say	O
then	O
what	O
the	O
Clark	O
bid	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Market	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Joint	O
of	O
Meat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
Katherine	O
Clark	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
beat	O
the	O
Meat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
at	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
Francis	O
Haydon	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Katherine	O
Clark	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Clark	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Three	O
Pence	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolp	I-place
's	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Raisins	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Longuet	I-pers
and	O
Mark	B-pers
Weyland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Basket	O
from	O
a	O
Heap	O
that	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Wharf	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
Iron	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Jevins	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
Sugar	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Emerson	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
,	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
(	B-pers
commonly	I-pers
call	I-pers
'd	I-pers
Callico	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
convicted	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
privately	O
stolen	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hoe	I-pers
for	O
which	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
January	O
14th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Years	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
did	O
return	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
without	O
License	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
Excuse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
serviceable	O
in	O
his	O
Voyage	O
,	O
having	O
his	O
Liberty	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
keeping	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Felons	O
transported	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
mutiny	O
'd	O
in	O
their	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Master	O
and	O
Ship	O
's	O
Crew	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Sea	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
prevented	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saved	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
Crew	O
and	O
Cargoe	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
Merchant	O
Forward	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
but	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
appointed	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Liberty	O
on	O
Board	O
of	O
Ship	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
the	O
Felons	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
preventing	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
Ship	O
's	O
crew	O
and	O
Cargo	O
,	O
the	O
Ship	O
not	O
being	O
yet	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Nevis	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
landed	O
there	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wykes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cheese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whiteside	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Windmill-Inn	B-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Sheets	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Pinloe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Snelling	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bibb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
by	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
sweeping	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
any	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Oakey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Levee	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Junks	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Matth.ew	O
Flood	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
Flood	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
along	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
with	O
Colonel	O
Cope	O
,	O
near	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
the	O
Chariot	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
held	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
another	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
Seals	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
such	O
Sort	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
us	O
'd	O
them	O
civilly	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Levee	O
and	O
Flood	O
,	O
were	O
together	O
robbing	O
in	O
Hampstead	O
Road	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
lay	O
hold	O
:	O
That	O
Flood	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Levee	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Chariot	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
receive	O
from	O
Levee	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
,	O
Seals	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
Chains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
taken	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
and	O
Colonel	O
Cape	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
no	O
Hurt	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
a	O
Couple	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
2	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
,	O
Chains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
hold	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gratrix	O
,	O
in	O
Southwark	O
for	O
14	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
shared	O
among	O
them	O
Three	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
1	O
s.	O
for	O
their	O
Parts	O
of	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
Ring	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Persons	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
)	O
either	O
from	O
Colonel	O
Cope	O
or	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
they	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
rob	O
about	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
Levee	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
rather	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
threatned	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
He	O
inquiring	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Head	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
that	O
would	O
discover	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
intice	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Robbing	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
promise	O
her	O
Husband	O
should	O
come	O
and	O
go	O
safe	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
Intelligence	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
cleaning	O
their	O
Pistols	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
Levee	O
and	O
Blake	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
Flood	O
was	O
that	O
Day	O
apprehended	O
for	O
some	O
Fact	O
in	O
Southwark	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
Intelligence	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Levee	O
and	O
Blake	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Rings	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
lent	O
him	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
Rings	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
depos	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Ring	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Blake	O
and	O
Flood	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
Brandy	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
Robbing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
Information	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
stopp	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Levee	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Ring	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
Blake	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Ring	O
that	O
Esquire	O
Young	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
inveigh	O
'd	O
bitterly	O
against	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
opprobirous	O
Names	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Colonel	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
22	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
Flood	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Indictment	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Simeon	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Turnover	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Link	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
another	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
spoke	O
one	O
Word	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
Fig	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
near	O
Pancras	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
it	O
quite	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Levee	I-pers
acknowledged	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
affirm	O
'd	O
that	O
Oakey	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
Lordship	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Levee	O
and	O
Oakey	O
,	O
were	O
standing	O
in	O
Fig	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
along	O
.	O
That	O
himself	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
Levee	O
took	O
his	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
some	O
Resistance	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
:	O
That	O
Oakey	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rich	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
of	O
but	O
one	O
Guinea	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Cooks	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Goose	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Oakey	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
or	O
Levee	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
committed	O
any	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
this	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
transported	O
another	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Matthew	O
Flood	O
and	O
John	O
Levee	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
Fourth	O
Time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Forey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
James	O
Forey	O
depos	O
'd	O
He	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Burden	O
from	O
the	O
Hitchin	O
Coach	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
burden	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Goods	O
among	O
them	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
the	O
Porter	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
to	O
rob	O
in	O
Hamstead	O
Road	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Bundle	O
on	O
a	O
Bulk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
Tallow	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
making	O
Inquiry	O
.	O
John	O
Levee	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
corroborating	O
Evidence	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
James	O
Blake	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
Flood	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Curtain	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Foulk	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jobber	I-pers
Esquire	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whippp	O
'd	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Key	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
Thirty	O
six	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
two	O
Beds	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
opened	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
25	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hewit	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Plough	O
Coulter	O
and	O
Hook	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Plough	O
Coulter	O
and	O
Tuck	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Rigdon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
The	O
facts	O
were	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Render	I-pers
,	O
Carpenters	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ragdel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
he	O
saw	O
John	O
Smith	O
take	O
the	O
Boards	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Work-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
about	O
600	O
yards	O
,	O
into	O
another	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
Render	O
was	O
one	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
Trust	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Foreman	O
.	O
John	O
Smith	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
Occasion	O
for	O
two	O
Boards	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Robert	O
Render	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
two	O
Boards	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
charge	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
Accompt	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
also	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
accompt	O
depending	O
of	O
about	O
40	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
call	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
clandestine	O
taking	O
the	O
Boards	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
Job	O
of	O
Work	O
in	O
Hand	O
near	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Deals	O
falling	O
short	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Deals	O
on	O
Accompt	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Way	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	O
Render	O
a	O
Person	O
whom	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
his	O
Foreman	O
,	O
and	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Disposing	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
Smith	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Isaac	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Nell	B-pers
Harrel	I-pers
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
little	O
Boys	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
one	O
Gust	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
shared	O
it	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
and	O
Roger	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Boys	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Gust	I-pers
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
fetch	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
Notice	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
James	O
Gust	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
planted	O
there	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
by	O
Whistling	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
any	O
Body	O
coming	O
that	O
was	O
likely	O
to	O
disturb	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Boys	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
a	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
about	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
tip	O
him	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
Suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
this	O
Way	O
,	O
by	O
swearing	O
falsely	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
Day	O
of	O
last	O
December	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
themselves	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
in	O
Little	O
Windmill-Street	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
all	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Landlord	O
refus	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
being	O
Merry	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
trying	O
their	O
Strength	O
by	O
Wrestling	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
thrown	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Fire	O
Grate	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
push	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Provocation	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
Two	O
Surgeons	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
or	O
wounded	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
above	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
Six	O
or	O
seven	O
Inches	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Skull	O
lay	O
bare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Skin	O
and	O
Flesh	O
hung	O
over	O
his	O
Ear	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Depresssion	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
visible	O
outwardly	O
,	O
yet	O
opening	O
the	O
Head	O
after	O
his	O
decease	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Fractures	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Temple	O
Bone	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
upon	O
the	O
Bregma	O
,	O
several	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
with	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pressure	O
upon	O
the	O
Meninges	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wounds	O
were	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
did	O
charge	O
his	O
Death	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
He	O
was	O
murthered	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
those	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
this	O
Difference	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
among	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
their	O
Wrestling	O
and	O
Throwing	O
one	O
another	O
down	O
,	O
seem	O
'd	O
rather	O
in	O
earnest	O
than	O
jest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
thrown	O
under	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
undermost	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
)	O
The	O
Landlord	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
their	O
Quarrelling	O
they	O
had	O
broken	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
a	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
refusing	O
to	O
pay	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
thereupon	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beesely	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
she	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
ran	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
They	O
would	O
beat	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Watchman	O
's	O
staff	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
wrest	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
's	O
Hit	O
and	O
Wig	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
probably	O
fall	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
that	O
Bench	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
fallen	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Clothes	O
torn	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Macarty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
Committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Fires	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Captain	O
Kerby	O
at	O
Blackwall	B-place
,	O
a	O
Person	O
desiring	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Person	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Rooms	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Girl	O
between	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
suspicious	O
posture	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
his	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
's	O
entering	O
the	O
Room	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Girl	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
that	O
going	O
afterwards	O
through	O
three	O
Rooms	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Girl	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Closet	O
together	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Damage	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Pressure	O
of	O
the	O
Parts	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Opinion	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
lain	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
interrogated	O
,	O
Whether	O
she	O
understood	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Answer	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
smothering	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
Same	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Reader	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Countenance	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
struck	O
with	O
Death	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Sack	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fainted	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
recover	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
she	O
suspecting	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
,	O
had	O
tax	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
wondred	O
she	O
had	O
such	O
hard	O
Thoughts	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
Warning	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
her	O
Delivery	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
Katherine	O
Reader	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
examined	O
her	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
nothing	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
thought	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
only	O
a	O
Miscarriage	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Child	O
born	O
,	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
it	O
very	O
home	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sims	O
the	O
Midwife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
,	O
did	O
examine	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Child	O
born	O
,	O
urged	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
having	O
directed	O
to	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Places	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
aside	O
the	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
pretty	O
fast	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
call	O
for	O
help	O
so	O
loud	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
the	O
Rattling	O
of	O
the	O
Coaches	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Crying	O
of	O
Two	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Nursery	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
needs	O
have	O
been	O
heard	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
offered	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
2	O
Specks	O
on	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
believed	O
happened	O
by	O
its	O
falling	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
hir	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
.	O
A	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
before	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
her	O
away	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
troublesome	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
owned	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Rogue	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
other	O
Wives	O
.	O
This	O
last	O
Evidence	O
exempting	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Statute	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
founded	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Female	O
Infant	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dickson	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
,	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
Back	O
by	O
lifting	O
a	O
Washing-Tub	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
something	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
something	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
complain	O
'd	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Lad	O
up	O
to	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
down	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Steward	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
for	O
something	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Steward	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
did	O
think	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Miscarriage	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
owning	O
any	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Child	O
born	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber-Pot	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Jaw-Bone	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Check	O
torn	O
:	O
That	O
having	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
warm	O
Water	O
,	O
it	O
bled	O
at	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
Hair	O
and	O
Nails	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
small	O
and	O
lean	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Steward	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
former	O
Witnesses	O
had	O
deposed	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
bidding	O
the	O
Boy	O
bid	O
his	O
Mistress	O
come	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
inquiring	O
of	O
her	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Landing-Place	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
,	O
did	O
suspect	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
several	O
Things	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
when	O
found	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
nothing	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber-Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife-deposed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
rather	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
usual	O
)	O
because	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
Stool	O
after	O
it	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
generally	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Jawbone	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
might	O
be	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
received	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
falling	O
on	O
or	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
no	O
other	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
but	O
those	O
.	O
The	O
Mistress	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
silly	O
Creature	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
natural	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
so	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Aunt	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
herself	O
was	O
born	O
without	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
Grandmother	O
,	O
in	O
like	O
Manner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knock	O
'd	O
for	O
Help	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
murder	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Case	O
being	O
evidently	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
for	O
Bastard	O
Children	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Susannah	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
10	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
without	O
her	O
Consent	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Mitchel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Back	O
Yard	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Dust-Cart	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
Clothes	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
hurt	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
consenting	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
threatned	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
any	O
Body	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Tongue	O
out	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Girl	O
's	O
Linnen	O
not	O
as	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Girl	O
what	O
ailed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
acquainted	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
and	O
damaged	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
sore	O
and	O
raw	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Running	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
That	O
threatning	O
to	O
whip	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
examined	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
injur	O
'd	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
lain	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Body	O
penetrated	O
.	O
Two	O
surgeons	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
both	O
agreed	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Girl	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
injured	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Inflammation	O
of	O
the	O
Parts	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
infected	O
,	O
yet	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
That	O
Endeavours	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
force	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Girl	O
's	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
entered	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
But	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
Mistake	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
upon	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Evidence	O
were	O
all	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
a	O
new	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Slates	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Chipp	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Middleton	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mariner	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Poppin	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Poppin	I-pers
,	O
Barbara	B-pers
Poppin	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Poppin	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Poppin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Maddor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
to	O
defraud	O
James	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
of	O
several	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
by	O
cancelling	O
a	O
Deed	O
made	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Poppins	O
before	O
mentioned	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
Margaret	B-pers
Poppin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Stubs	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Grey	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Deed	O
,	O
as	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
the	O
Defendants	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
By	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
,	O
Foulk	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wykes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Seven	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Wells	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Oakey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Levee	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Junks	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Seven	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Joiner	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hely	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hutcheson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Two	O
last	O
convicted	O
the	O
preceding	O
Sessions	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Nineteen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dier	I-pers
,	O
Soloman	O
Hargrave	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crady	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beesely	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Lydia	B-pers
Pinloe	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Wanklin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
fined	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Bates	O
,	O
alias	O
Chip	O
,	O
alias	O
Middleton	O
,	O
fined	O
twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Wells	O
,	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Calicoe	O
Sarah	O
,	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanneled	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
By	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
,	O
Foulk	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wykes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
A	O
Full	O
and	O
Compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
Murders	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Highwaymen	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
William	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1722.	O
beginning	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
and	O
Little	O
John	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Falstaff	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hind	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Nevison	O
,	O
Whitney	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
more	O
:	O
also	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
Account	O
than	O
any	O
yet	O
published	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
executed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
;	O
concluding	O
with	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Cartouche	O
in	O
France	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Robberies	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Actions	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Malhoni	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
faithfully	O
collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Histories	O
,	O
Records	O
,	O
Trials	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
and	O
written	O
regularly	O
as	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
W.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
bound	O
in	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
most	O
Surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Robinson	B-pers
Crusoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
Mariner	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
done	O
into	O
One	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
Printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Just	O
published	O
(	O
neatly	O
printed	O
in	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Volume	O
)	O
the	O
7th	O
Edition	O
,	O
corrected	O
and	O
enlarged	O
to	O
almost	O
as	O
much	O
again	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
sold	O
near	O
10,000	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Edition	O
)	O
of	O
ONANIA	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
The	O
heinous	O
Sin	O
of	O
Self	O
pollution	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
its	O
frightful	O
Consequences	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
considered	O
with	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Physical	O
Advice	O
to	O
those	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
already	O
injur	O
'd	O
themselves	O
by	O
this	O
abominable	O
Practice	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
divers	O
remarkable	O
Letters	O
from	O
such	O
Offenders	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
lamenting	O
their	O
Impotencies	O
and	O
Diseases	O
thereby	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
Letters	O
from	O
eminent	O
Divines	O
,	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Conscience	O
relating	O
thereto	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Lady	O
(	O
very	O
curious	O
)	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
a	O
married	O
Man	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Answers	O
,	O
manifesting	O
(	O
from	O
Scripture	O
)	O
that	O
a	O
married	O
Couple	O
may	O
commit	O
Whoredom	O
between	O
themselves	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
his	O
Answers	O
,	O
as	O
promised	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Edition	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Letters	O
of	O
C.T	O
.	O
and	O
Philalethes	O
,	O
urging	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Self	O
pollution	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
surprizing	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
young	O
married	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
this	O
detestable	O
Practice	O
,	O
became	O
barren	O
and	O
diseased	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
astonishing	O
Cases	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
had	O
so	O
abused	O
themselves	O
thereby	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
three	O
curious	O
Casoistical	O
Letters	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
,	O
since	O
,	O
one	O
signed	O
Will	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
N.	O
Pedigogus	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Answers	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
subscribed	O
Dives	O
,	O
concerning	O
his	O
Son	O
's	O
Fornication	O
,	O
and	O
Adultery	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Impotency	O
,	O
by	O
Self	O
pollution	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Barrenness	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
strange	O
Effects	O
of	O
that	O
Practice	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
hardly	O
ever	O
till	O
now	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
;	O
with	O
seasonable	O
Adimonitions	O
to	O
the	O
Youth	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
(	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
)	O
and	O
those	O
whose	O
Tuition	O
they	O
are	O
under	O
,	O
whether	O
Parents	O
,	O
Guardians	O
,	O
Masters	O
,	O
or	O
Mistresses	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
grave	O
and	O
learned	O
Divine	O
and	O
Physician	O
,	O
having	O
perused	O
this	O
Edition	O
before	O
it	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Opinion	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
This	O
little	O
Book	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
by	O
all	O
Sorts	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
,	O
Degree	O
,	O
Profession	O
,	O
or	O
Condition	O
soever	O
,	O
Guilty	O
or	O
not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Sin	O
declaimed	O
against	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
near	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
Note	O
,	O
No	O
more	O
Additions	O
will	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
this	O
Book	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
.	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Schemes	O
,	O
the	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cans	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Stpahen	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Mears	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
agains	O
t	O
Harron-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	O
I	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
,	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Ecxchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
,	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
,	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
Common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School	O
Master	O
in	O
Soho	O
Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
E.	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
THE	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainments	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
1001	O
Stories	O
,	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Sultaness	O
of	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Sultan	O
from	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
a	O
bloody	O
Vow	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
,	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Lady	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
In	O
eight	O
Vols	O
.	O
Price	O
11	O
s.	O
II	O
.	O
The	O
Adventures	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Clermont	O
and	O
Madam	O
de	O
Ravezan	O
.	O
A	O
Novel	O
.	O
In	O
four	O
Parts	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
Attalantis	O
.	O
In	O
four	O
Vols	O
.	O
Price	O
10	O
s.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
armorous	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Lucinday	O
,	O
an	O
English	O
Lady	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
V.	O
The	O
strange	O
Adventures	O
of	O
the	O
Count	O
Vinouel	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
whilst	O
they	O
resided	O
at	O
Constantinople	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VI	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
Madam	O
de	O
Beamnount	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Cave	O
in	O
Wales	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
undiscover	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
forced	O
to	O
fly	O
France	O
for	O
her	O
Religion	O
.	O
By	O
Mrs.	O
Aubin	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VII	O
.	O
Aminadab	O
's	O
Courtship	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
Quaker	O
's	O
Wedding	O
.	O
A	O
Poem	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Way	O
of	O
Courtship	O
,	O
Method	O
of	O
Marrying	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
VIII	O
.	O
The	O
High	O
German	O
Doctor	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
Vols	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
explanatory	O
Index	O
.	O
IX	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Holy	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Patriarchs	O
.	O
A	O
Book	O
proper	O
for	O
Children	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
X	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
.	O
A	O
Treatise	O
proper	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
Publick	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
XI	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
's	O
Rhetorick	O
.	O
Containing	O
Rules	O
for	O
speaking	O
and	O
writing	O
Elegantly	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
XII	O
.	O
Moral	O
Reflexions	O
and	O
Maxims	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Duke	O
De	O
la	O
Rochesoucault	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XIII	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
Muly	O
Ishmael	O
,	O
King	O
of	O
Moroco	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
cruel	O
Usage	O
to	O
the	O
Christian	B-pers
Slaves	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XIV	O
.	O
A	O
general	O
History	O
of	O
Dreams	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
Parts	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XV	O
.	O
Lydall	O
's	O
Table	O
of	O
Interest	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
XVI	O
.	O
A	O
Help	O
to	O
Prayer	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Knogs	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
BOOKS	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Cartouche	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Robbers	O
,	O
A	O
Comedy	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
acted	O
many	O
Times	O
with	O
great	O
Applause	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
By	O
Mons	O
.	O
le	O
Grand	O
,	O
Comedian	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Actions	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Dominique	I-pers
Cartouche	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
broke	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
N.	O
S.	O
relating	O
at	O
large	O
his	O
remarkable	O
Adventures	O
,	O
desperate	O
Enterprizes	O
,	O
and	O
various	O
Escapes	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Sentence	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Scaffold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Trial	O
at	O
large	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hurly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Perjury	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
learned	O
Arguments	O
of	O
the	O
Council	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Brotherton	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
Present	O
State	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
in	O
three	O
Parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
of	O
South	O
,	O
the	O
Second	O
of	O
North	O
Britain	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Containing	O
,	O
An	O
Accurate	O
and	O
Impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
these	O
famous	O
Islands	O
:	O
Of	O
their	O
several	O
Counties	O
and	O
Inhabitants	O
;	O
the	O
Advantages	O
and	O
Disadvantages	O
of	O
Both	O
,	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
Foreign	O
Countries	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
Curiosities	O
of	O
Nature	O
and	O
Art	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
vast	O
,	O
populous	O
and	O
opulent	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Metropolis	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
celebrated	O
Universities	O
,	O
Oxford	O
and	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Britons	O
Original	O
,	O
Language	O
,	O
Temper	O
,	O
Genius	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
Morals	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Their	O
Nobility	O
,	O
Gentry	O
,	O
Clergy	O
,	O
and	O
Commonalty	O
.	O
Their	O
Laws	O
and	O
Government	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
succinct	O
History	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
English	O
Monarchs	O
to	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
With	O
Lists	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Officers	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
both	O
Houses	O
of	O
Parliament	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
Present	O
State	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Dominions	O
in	O
Germany	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
corrected	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Sedley	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
In	O
Prose	O
and	O
Verse	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Volumes	O
.	O
Containing	O
his	O
Poems	O
,	O
Plays	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
eminent	O
Hand	O
.	O
And	O
his	O
Picture	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
from	O
an	O
Original	O
Painting	O
.	O
The	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
and	O
Behaviour	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
State	O
Prisoners	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
executed	O
the	O
last	O
300	O
Years	O
.	O
With	O
their	O
several	O
Characters	O
,	O
from	O
Cambden	O
,	O
Spotswood	O
,	O
Clarendon	O
,	O
Sprat	O
,	O
Burner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
shewing	O
how	O
the	O
respective	O
Sentences	O
were	O
Executed	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
Mitigated	O
,	O
or	O
Pardon	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
proper	O
Supplement	O
to	O
the	O
State-Trials	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Serious	O
and	O
Comical	O
,	O
in	O
Prose	O
and	O
Verse	O
.	O
In	O
Four	O
Volumes	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
corrected	O
from	O
the	O
Errors	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Impressions	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Character	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
all	O
his	O
Writings	O
.	O
Adom	O
'd	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
A	O
complete	O
Collection	O
of	O
remarkable	O
Trials	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Year	O
1706	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
1720.	O
for	O
the	O
Crimes	O
following	O
:	O
Murders	O
,	O
Highway-Robbing	O
,	O
Piracy	O
,	O
House-breaking	O
,	O
Foot	O
padding	O
,	O
Rapes	O
,	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
Polygamy	O
,	O
Fortune-stealing	O
,	O
Trespassing	O
,	O
Shop-lifting	O
,	O
Callicoe-tearing	O
,	O
Mohocking	O
,	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
Dying-Speeches	O
.	O
Faithfully	O
collected	O
from	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
Trials	O
,	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Authentick	O
Narratives	O
.	O
In	O
four	O
Volumes	O
.	O
Written	O
from	O
the	O
own	O
Memorandums	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
,	O
corrected	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Hamfreys	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
E.	O
Symon	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
:	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
,	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
1722	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
Price	O
Three	O
Pence	O
.	O
