TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Jail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
James	B-pers
Boyte	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Breach	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dagger	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duffin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Freelove	I-pers
,	I-pers
John	B-pers
Filmore	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
Nicolas	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gering	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Clitherow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mealin	I-pers
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wilgus	I-pers
a	O
Watch	O
val	O
:	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Chamberlain	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mealin	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
(	O
Mealin	O
having	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Tapster	O
let	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lay	O
asleep	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Tapster	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
awaked	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Calcot	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
Mealin	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Catcot	O
being	O
afterwards	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
stoln	O
,	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confes	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mealin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
high	O
Fever	O
,	O
his	O
Tryal	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
deferr	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
Since	O
dead	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Aldermanbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
three	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
Clouts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Washer-Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
tax	O
'd	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
restor	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Half-Guineas	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Tester	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bays	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
observing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
stept	O
in	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Half-Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
of	O
South	B-place
Mims	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
,	O
by	O
wilfully	O
strangling	O
the	O
said	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
up	O
a	O
Bullock	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Hog	O
on	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Arms	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
eaten	O
off	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shorrard	I-pers
,	O
Farmer	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
Wallis	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
that	O
the	O
Hog	O
had	O
partly	O
devour	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
that	O
Child	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
still-born	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bury	O
'd	O
both	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
After-birth	O
in	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Judgment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
her	O
full	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Toe	O
Nails	O
of	O
the	O
Infant	O
were	O
not	O
perfect	O
.	O
Justice	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
produced	O
some	O
Child	O
bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
in	O
her	O
Service	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lerigo	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lerigo	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
betwixt	O
drunk	O
and	O
sober	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Alehouse	O
so	O
shun	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
one	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
still	O
keep	O
him	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
walked	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Rope-Walk	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
busy	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
your	O
Money	O
or	O
your	O
Watch	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
seizing	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
she	O
pluck	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
with	O
t'other	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
catch	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
let	O
go	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
this	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
her	O
Word	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Bustle	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Moon-light	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
close	O
Engagement	O
.	O
Get	O
ye	O
gone	O
from	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
cool	O
your	O
Courage	O
with	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
presently	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Help	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
Blow	O
as	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
remember	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
Struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
:	O
At	O
which	O
time	O
John	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
both	O
tugging	O
for	O
the	O
Chain	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Caterwauling	O
Lovers	O
were	O
taking	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
clear	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gaskin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
3	O
Aprons	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
four	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
missed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
38	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carcass	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dameron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Sheep	O
into	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
Mutton	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
Carass	O
?	O
says	O
one	O
in	O
Company	O
.	O
You	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
Word	O
I	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
l	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Carcass	O
,	O
presently	O
knew	O
who	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
forthwith	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leaden	O
14	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
7	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Hanwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Giles	O
Hanwell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
backwards	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
forwards	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Thrusting	O
the	O
fourteen	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
down	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
perceived	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Jest	O
.	O
How	O
easily	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
could	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
this	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Thief	O
?	O
He	O
thought	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Earnest	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
seems	O
she	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
left	O
too	O
far	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Seven	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
under	O
her	O
Armpit	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wilsden	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ox	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cuxon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Feburary	O
.	O
William	O
Cuxon	O
,	O
Grasier	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Ox	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
at	O
Kilborn	B-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
seized	O
by	O
-	O
Neal	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
in	O
Clare	O
Market	O
.	O
-	O
Neal	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nichols	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
An	O
Ox	O
to	O
the	O
Slaughter-House	O
,	O
and	O
asks	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
came	O
and	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ox	O
.	O
Have	O
a	O
care	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
Nichols	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
Cuxon	O
's	O
Bullock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
stoln	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
says	O
Nichols	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
quickly	O
bring	O
your	O
to	O
Will	O
.	O
Fell	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
but	O
at	O
that	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
sharp	O
Examination	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
Kilborn	O
,	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
your	O
Heart	O
ake	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
Tyburn	O
?	O
says	O
Neal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
faith	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
Fell	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
very	O
Ox	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
several	O
Stops	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Mind	O
to	O
drive	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Devil	O
was	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
forward	O
.	O
No	O
Proof	O
appearing	O
against	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Fell	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
)	O
did	O
assault	O
Richard	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Richard	O
Cade	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
London-Spaw	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
attend	O
Mr.	O
Starky	O
to	O
Grays-lnn-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
about	O
13	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
near	O
the	O
Ducking	O
Pound	O
,	O
between	O
Sir	B-place
John	I-place
Oldcastle	I-place
's	I-place
and	O
the	O
London	B-place
Spaw	I-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Brother	O
to	O
Page	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
Session	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Watch	O
Maker	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Jack	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
)	O
They	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Three	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
home	O
with	O
.	O
L	O
-	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
Kemp	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
Three	O
Half-pence	O
:	O
Let	O
us	O
take	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Deponent	O
)	O
stopt	O
Page	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
next	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
after	O
Kemp	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
it	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
comply	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
near	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
Jo	B-pers
Watmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
their	O
Way	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
Direction	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Turning	O
to	O
Brook	O
's	O
Market	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
knockt	O
Lloyd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
Jones	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
.	O
Loyd	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
followed	O
with	O
a	O
Cry	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
by	O
John	O
Pitman	O
an	O
Excise	O
Officer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
Duty	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
escaped	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
confessed	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
He	O
promised	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Wig	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Penny	O
Post	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
following	O
Note	O
:	O
Sir	O
,	O
enclosed	O
is	O
Richard	O
's	O
Wig	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
desired	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
forthwith	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
Servant	O
unknown	O
,	O
A	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
Watmore	O
and	O
Pitman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Page	O
accidentally	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
ill	O
Courses	O
)	O
they	O
resolved	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
unluckily	O
happen	O
'd	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
two	O
old	O
Friends	O
should	O
part	O
with	O
dry	O
Lips	O
,	O
Page	O
very	O
generously	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
for	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
spend	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Spaw	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lived	O
.	O
Here	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
Lloyd	O
and	O
Kemp	O
,	O
the	O
Latter	O
of	O
whom	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
Home	O
together	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Maidenhead	O
at	O
Windmill-Hill	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Kemp	O
to	O
the	O
London-Spaw	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
a	O
Service	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Spaw	O
he	O
and	O
Jones	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
heard	O
Page	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
)	O
say	O
,	O
Honestly	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pot	O
?	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
answered	O
,	O
Not	O
so	O
much	O
Honesty	O
as	O
you	O
think	O
for	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Discourse	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
when	O
Kemp	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
take	O
his	O
Wig	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
But	O
Kemp	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Reply	O
,	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
proposed	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Suit	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
;	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
and	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Clark	O
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Candle	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
an	O
Entry	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
She	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
you	O
be	O
contented	O
with	O
one	O
Suit	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
like	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fare	O
accordingly	O
for	O
all	O
covet	O
,	O
all	O
lose	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bavan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
;	O
val	O
:	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pots	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
both	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
absconding	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Ring	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
her	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
and	O
all	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
kind	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
mainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fleetwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Piper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
is	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stocking	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ear	O
Rings	O
5	O
s.	O
:	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Hood	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
,	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carried	O
'em	O
to	O
her	O
new	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
privately	O
stealing	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
val	O
34	O
s.	O
33	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
and	O
Holland	O
woven	O
together	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
,	O
19	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Lindsey	O
Woolsey	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Beauchamp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	O
Beauchamp	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Beauchamp	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Kitchen	O
in	O
Goswell-street	B-place
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
Carthusian-street	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
But	O
more	O
Company	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Charterhouse-Square	O
.	O
Rich	O
.	O
Evans	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Rob	O
Lodqe	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Botloph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Baker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Wig	O
comb	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
Wig	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
Branch	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
powder	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
new	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
looked	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
lame	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Broadbank	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
;	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
Half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
Fourteen	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Drawer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	O
in	O
Brentford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
,	O
Col.	O
Emely	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Percival	O
,	O
Lieutenant	O
Shipton	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
About	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
but	O
the	O
2	O
last	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
gave	O
Orders	O
for	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
very	O
pleasant	O
and	O
friendly	O
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
Dice	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
5	O
Minutes	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
'	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
;	O
the	O
tormer	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
within	O
half	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
retreat	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
Posture	O
this	O
Evidence	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
call	O
up	O
his	O
Fellow-Servants	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
fallen	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
undermost	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
his	O
Dear	O
Merrick	O
.	O
And	O
turning	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
run	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
immediately	O
;	O
but	O
returning	O
without	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
staid	O
to	O
prepare	O
some	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
Impatience	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
bled	O
pretty	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
had	O
taken	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
Drawer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
Dear	O
Cook	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
Dear	O
Merrick	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
freely	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
But	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
your	O
seeking	O
?	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
afterwards	O
laid	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
Evidence	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
Very	O
well	O
!	O
How	O
does	O
Cook	O
do	O
?	O
Cook	O
had	O
2	O
Wounds	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bethune	I-pers
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
being	O
called	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
standing	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
Manner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Drawer	O
standing	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
friend	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
tho'in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fainted	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
would	O
suffer	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Wounds	O
,	O
till	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
dress	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
had	O
lost	O
about	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Blood	O
by	O
his	O
Wounds	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Condition	O
appearing	O
dangerous	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
necessary	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
-	O
Hollaway	O
was	O
send	O
for	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
together	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
another	O
Posture	O
,	O
perceived	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
quite	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
He	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
says	O
Merrick	O
,	O
you	O
Know	O
't	O
was	O
your	O
own	O
Fault	O
?	O
But	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
former	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
forgive	O
him	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
had	O
perforated	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
the	O
Guts	O
in	O
two	O
Places	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
about	O
11	O
'	O
o	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
that	O
that	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sate	O
next	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
round	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
stepping	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
forced	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Necessity	O
of	O
using	O
his	O
Sword	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
happened	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
no	O
Signs	O
of	O
ill	O
Will	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
their	O
Leave	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Shipman	O
to	O
stay	O
longer	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
Sign	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Intention	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
The	O
Duke	O
of	O
Richmond	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Montague	O
,	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Essex	O
:	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mansfield	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Albemarle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Walgrave	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
Disposition	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
subject	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
were	O
present	O
and	O
ready	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
.	O
The	O
Verdict	O
was	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
Worster	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Tothill	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
feloniously	O
staying	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tothill	I-pers
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
drinking	O
l'unch	O
together	O
at	O
Sturges	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
S	O
Martin's-Court	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Deponent	O
)	O
lived	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
Wilson	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
affronted	O
:	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
lose	O
my	O
Life	O
first	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Tothill	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
sure	O
you	O
are	O
but	O
in	O
Jest	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
a	O
n't	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Well	O
but	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
our	O
Punch	O
out	O
before	O
we	O
quarrel	O
.	O
-	O
Come	O
-	O
to	O
your	O
Health	O
!	O
-	O
Do	O
you	O
drink	O
it	O
with	O
all	O
your	O
Heart	O
?	O
says	O
Tothill	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
to	O
your	O
Health	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
emptied	O
the	O
Bowl	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
lighted	O
them	O
into	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
affront	O
me	O
so	O
for	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
He	O
snew	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
New	O
Sherry	O
;	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
They	O
drank	O
a	O
Boat	O
apiece	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
withdrew	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
five	O
Minutes	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Stairs-Head	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
then	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Tothill	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
?	O
But	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
at	O
whole	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Next	O
time	O
I	O
'll	O
fight	O
you	O
with	O
Pistols	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smalman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Boy	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
kindle	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
those	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
Fire	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
die	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Fault	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilky	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
supporting	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
would	O
all	O
take	O
Notice	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Fault	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
offering	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
then	O
received	O
was	O
mortal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
twenty	O
Hours	O
after	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Larouche	O
in	O
Round-Court	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lodged	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Midnight	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
dangerously	O
wounded	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
sober	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
together	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
sober	O
when	O
we	O
first	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
;	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
fight	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
Fault	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
drew	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
nobody	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
drank	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Hell	O
.	O
He	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
stumbled	O
over	O
some	O
Faggots	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Necessity	O
of	O
using	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hains	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Brigadier	O
Wilson	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Room	O
at	O
Sturges	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Rum	O
made	O
into	O
Punch	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
Stair	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
together	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
sate	O
below	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
come	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
pray	O
stay	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
repeating	O
his	O
Entreaties	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
and	O
peaceable	O
even	O
in	O
his	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
quarrelsome	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
remarkably	O
diligent	O
in	O
reconciling	O
Differences	O
among	O
others	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Die	O
or	O
Live	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Fault	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
first	O
and	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Brigadier	O
drew	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
all	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
wrote	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
present	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Subscribers	O
.	O
Major	O
Wright	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Batson	O
,	O
Capt	O
Moreton	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Parker	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
an	O
even	O
Temper	O
,	O
never	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
passionate	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
contary-wise	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsome	O
in	O
his	O
Drink	O
.	O
Many	O
others	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
needless	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Currants	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
9d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Men	O
were	O
fighting	O
in	O
Jewin-street	B-place
near	I-place
Crowder's-Well-Alley	I-place
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
knockt	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
former	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Castile	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Gabriel	I-place
Fenchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Forward	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
miss	O
'd	O
Tobacco	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
.	O
Others	O
,	O
that	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
Tobacco	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
concealed	O
it	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
were	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
That	O
Forward	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Liter	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
abused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
called	O
him	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
without	O
any	O
Cause	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Rogue	O
as	O
any	O
breathing	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
honester	O
Man	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lemmon	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Shovel	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Scales	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Canes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Chamberlen	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Horse	O
Whip	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head-Inn	O
in	O
Smith-field	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Grasier	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
early	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Doors	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
staying	O
to	O
shut	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Night-House	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
where	O
offering	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Canes	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Levee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
steal	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	B-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
Sake	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
still	O
holding	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
slipt	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
in	O
Hopes	O
of	O
escaping	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
observing	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Coat	O
drop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
fresh	O
Hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
gathering	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
quite	O
lost	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
l.	O
William	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Gracechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ken	I-pers
;	O
and	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvass	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rob	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handcherchief	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
Waring	B-pers
Seaman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellitt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Spelter	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Henrietta-street	O
;	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
discover	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Spoon	O
into	O
three	O
Pieces	O
,	O
threw	O
one	O
Piece	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
middle	O
Piece	O
(	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Owner	O
's	O
Name	O
upon	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
gave	O
Betty	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Throll	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
16s	O
.	O
a	O
Smock	O
3s	O
.	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cottons	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
1s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Fenly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
and	I-pers
Comp	I-pers
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	O
.	O
Richard	O
,	O
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Bars	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
Old	O
Graves-Lane	O
,	O
who	O
bade	O
him	O
be	O
careful	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
each	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shirts	O
val	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Horses	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Coach	O
val	O
.	O
20l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Etoff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Driver	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Etoff	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Coach	O
upon	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
lived	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
to	O
beg	O
off	O
a	O
Summons	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
upon	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Complaint	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
prevail	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
his	O
Coach	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Roebuck	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Herbert	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
water	O
his	O
Horses	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
dined	O
together	O
that	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
Herbert	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
a	O
fare	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
drove	O
along	O
.	O
Away	O
went	O
Herbert	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
some	O
Ladies	O
hir	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
Herbert	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Herbert	O
,	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
the	O
Horses	O
the	O
remaining	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
Care	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Herbert	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4s	O
4d	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carmichel	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ias	O
Acton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Santa-Cruse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cable	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Dupar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
Transport	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
9	O
Pair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Drawer	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
47s	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
crept	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
a	O
way	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
observed	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quickly	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Duce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Half-Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Holford	O
being	O
apprehended	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
each	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
(	O
Transp	O
.	O
)	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
The	O
Men	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
a	O
Frock	O
;	O
the	O
Women	O
help	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
to	O
try	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
in	O
accidentally	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Grayer	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Weaver	O
)	O
who	O
there	O
paid	O
me	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
10	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
drank	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Discourse	O
passing	O
between	O
them	O
and	O
me	O
about	O
Kicking	O
and	O
Jumping	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
?	O
And	O
my	O
Wife	O
answered	O
jestingly	O
,	O
Perhaps	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Running-Footman	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Munday	O
,	O
went	O
soon	O
after	O
Eleven	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
little	O
Difference	O
arising	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
first	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
in	O
Baker's-Row	B-place
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
went	O
homewards	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Greyhound	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Father-in-Law	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
Two	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Key	O
being	O
usually	O
left	O
for	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
Grayer	O
)	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Running-Footman	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
,	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
him	O
,	O
says	O
Whitehead	O
to	O
Grayer	O
,	O
Does	O
be	O
bid	O
you	O
stand	O
?	O
Knock	O
the	O
Dog	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
hauled	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
Rogue	O
,	O
Tom	O
.	O
Munday	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
:	O
And	O
Whitehead	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
Grayer	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
which	O
bring	O
Pretty	O
right	O
,	O
the	O
drawing	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
pulled	O
the	O
Lining	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
bursted	O
the	O
Wasteband	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
only	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
Pin	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
Care	O
what	O
ye	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
ye	O
both	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
would	O
frighten	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
worse	O
.	O
And	O
Whitehead	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Murder	O
the	O
Dog	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
Grayer	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
kill	O
me	O
:	O
Do	O
but	O
spare	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
me	O
Where	O
you	O
please	O
;	O
is	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
do	O
ye	O
any	O
Hart	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
damned	O
Lye	O
that	O
I	O
told	O
ye	O
when	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
to	O
Mother	O
Aldridge	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
White-street	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
all	O
that	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
mine	O
that	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
presently	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Mistake	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Sake	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
stay	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
several	O
Places	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
Bruised	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
parting	O
at	O
Greybound-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
(	O
says	O
Whitehead	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robotham	O
,	O
who	O
deals	O
in	O
Manchester	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Grayer	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Customer	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Grayer	O
some	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
where	O
Wright	O
and	O
Munday	O
forced	O
their	O
Discourse	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Running-Footman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
laying	O
Wagers	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Activity	O
.	O
We	O
not	O
liking	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Blind	O
Beggar	O
of	O
Bednal-Green	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-Light-Night	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Greybound-Lane	O
,	O
Wright	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hollowed	O
for	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
who	O
started	O
from	O
behind	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
Wright	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
his	O
Companion	O
threw	O
a	O
Brick-Bat	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Wright	O
why	O
he	O
stopt	O
me	O
?	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
but	O
my	O
Necessity	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
blame	O
me	O
for	O
going	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
is	O
ready	O
to	O
Lie-in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
as	O
myself	O
or	O
her	O
.	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
first	O
know	O
who	O
his	O
Companion	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
to	O
name	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
last	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Munday	O
.	O
Some	O
People	O
who	O
lived	O
there-abouts	O
,	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Windows	O
,	O
heard	O
this	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
bid	O
us	O
search	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Pistols	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Struggle	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pinn	O
'd	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Wim	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
they	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
Men	O
quarreling	O
.	O
Says	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
stop	O
us	O
for	O
?	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
the	O
Rogue	O
that	O
told	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
a	O
Running	O
Footman	O
?	O
Who	O
was	O
your	O
Companion	O
that	O
threw	O
the	O
Brick-Bat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
?	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
they	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
a	O
muttering	O
Voice	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
known	O
by	O
his	O
Tongue	O
.	O
)	O
Well	O
!	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
silly	O
Fellow	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
my	O
Necessity	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
blame	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
called	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
not	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
same	O
muttering	O
Voice	O
,	O
answered	O
.	O
Ay	O
,	O
search	O
me	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
silly	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
who	O
his	O
Companion	O
was	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robotham	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Repute	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted'em	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
and	O
uttering	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
70	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
dated	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
1724.	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
Twenty	O
Pounds	O
was	O
paid	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
a	O
Bill	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
107	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Sam	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Bearer	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
positive	O
that	O
that	O
Person	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Woodburn	O
depos	O
'd	O
thus	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
Tavern	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
)	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
Chicken	O
to	O
be	O
broil	O
'd	O
for	O
Supper	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
eating	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
change	O
him	O
a	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Bank	O
would	O
be	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
Occasion	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
ready	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Bill	O
was	O
Numb	O
.	O
10.	O
dated	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan	O
1724.	O
for	O
70	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Sam	O
.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
or	O
Bearer	O
.	O
Not	O
having	O
so	O
much	O
Cash	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Drawer	O
with	O
the	O
Bill	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
Word	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
changed	O
it	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Heart	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
paid	O
away	O
a	O
large	O
Sum	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
unprovided	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Club	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Bill	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
chang	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
good	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Sam	O
.	O
Brooks	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
new	O
Houses	O
in	O
Chiswel-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
opposite	O
the	O
Tobacco-Roll	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
50	O
l.	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
on	O
Demand	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
10	O
l.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
Drawer	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
50	O
l.	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
since	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
was	O
before	O
Witness	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Trouble	O
of	O
writing	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Remaining	O
10	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
(	O
No	O
370	O
)	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
him	O
to	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
when	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
Jail	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
a	O
Visit	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bill	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
50	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
70	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
readily	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
remaining	O
20	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
received	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Sam	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
opposite	O
the	O
Tobacco-Roll	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hard	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Legross	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
at	O
the	O
Tobacco-Roll	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Places	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nobody	O
that	O
knew	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
even	O
heard	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
Sam	O
.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
or	O
Francis	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
that	O
had	O
ever	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
Parish	O
;	O
and	O
much	O
less	O
been	O
Owner	O
of	O
three	O
new	O
Houses	O
there	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
50	O
l.	O
Bill	O
which	O
Isaac	B-pers
Woodburn	I-pers
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
paid	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
Woodburn	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
mentioned	O
as	O
a	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
knowing	O
the	O
70	O
l.	O
Bill	O
to	O
be	O
alter	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
else	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
sent	O
that	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
a	O
Journey	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
as	O
much	O
hindred	O
in	O
waiting	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
50	O
l.	O
as	O
in	O
waiting	O
to	O
receive	O
70	O
l.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
that	O
Bill	O
was	O
so	O
nicely	O
alter	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mistrusted	O
even	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
examine	O
their	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Bill	O
payable	O
to	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brooks	I-pers
given	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Numb	O
.	O
107	O
The	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
[	O
I	O
]	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
it	O
turned	O
into	O
an	O
[	O
S	O
,	O
]	O
the	O
[	O
W	O
]	O
was	O
changed	O
into	O
[	O
Ev	O
,	O
]	O
and	O
the	O
[	O
7	O
]	O
in	O
the	O
Number	O
taken	O
quite	O
out	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
Drawer	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Gaming	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lost	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
have	O
wm	O
70	O
l.	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
for	O
one	O
presently	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
handsome	O
Amends	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
little	O
Ready	O
Money	O
just	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
change	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Chester	O
Man	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Oddness	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
offering	O
a	O
Gratuity	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
began	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
suspicion	O
in	O
some	O
or	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Bill	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Away	O
the	O
Drawer	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
Discovery	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appeared	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr	O
.	O
Parks	O
(	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
)	O
if	O
his	O
Drawer	O
was	O
honest	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
a	O
Drawer	O
proves	O
a	O
Rogue	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
the	O
Money	O
will	O
be	O
expected	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
still	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
till	O
farther	O
Enquiry	O
could	O
be	O
made	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Pillory	O
,	O
fined	O
20	O
l.	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
security	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Child	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4l	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
(	O
little	O
Boy	O
s	O
)	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coral	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
Collins	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Belcher	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Brooks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Terril	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
Bail	O
Bond	O
.	O
-	O
Pepper	O
,	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
;	O
By	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
Samuel	B-pers
Quessenborough	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Administrator	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
)	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
Tho	B-pers
Pixley	I-pers
,	O
Cheesemonger	O
,	O
10r	O
70l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
execute	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
accordingly	O
arrested	O
Pixley	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Lemon	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Bail-Bond	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Founder	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Farrier	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
Tho	B-pers
Pixley	I-pers
the	O
Defendant	O
,	O
and	O
themselves	O
,	O
as	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Bond	O
into	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
's	O
Office	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Office	O
in	O
Thavies	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
an	O
Assignment	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
these	O
two	O
Bondsmen	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
never	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
afterwards	O
another	O
Writ	O
against	O
Pixley	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
Why	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
run	O
after	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
?	O
They	O
then	O
both	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
such	O
Persons	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
But	O
(	O
says	O
Leman	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
Terril	O
that	O
signed	O
the	O
Bond	O
with	O
those	O
Names	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pepper	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
Terril	O
)	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
this	O
Old	O
Rogue	O
Lemon	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
above	O
all	O
Men	O
ought	O
never	O
to	O
have	O
served	O
you	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
our	O
very	O
good	O
Friend	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
Damn	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
you	O
'll	O
never	O
know	O
your	O
Business	O
;	O
for	O
as	O
Pepper	O
is	O
our	O
Friend	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
do	O
us	O
no	O
Hurt	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
Quessenborough	O
is	O
your	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
fear	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Take	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Rule	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
a	O
Man	O
has	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
his	O
safest	O
way	O
to	O
practice	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Friends	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Quessenborough	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
Bondsmen	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
a	O
Prosecution	O
against	O
Terril	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
and	O
meeting	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Why	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
do	O
you	O
prosecute	O
me	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
expect	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
pay	O
the	O
Debt	O
?	O
You	O
have	O
Reason	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
for	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
secured	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
taken	O
good	O
Bail	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
true	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
false	O
Bond	O
.	O
Lemon	O
's	O
an	O
Old	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
been	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
regard	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Indictment	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
Consideration	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
injured	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
fined	O
them	O
only	O
20	O
Nobles	O
each	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
be	O
was	O
acquitted	O
Mars	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
of	O
Algate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
an	O
Accessary	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dicksey	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Tho	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
18	O
Plates	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
one	O
Kettle	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
Candlesticks	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	O
,	O
Selby	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	B-place
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
two	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
Tho	O
.	O
Hands	O
in	O
Rose-Alley	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Torkington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
three	O
Wigs	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Torkington	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Wigs	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mitchell	O
for	O
abusing	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Wig	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
for	O
10s	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
Bird-in	O
Hand	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Coomes	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
then	O
present	O
.	O
John	O
Coomes	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cheapning	O
a	O
Wig	O
of	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
10s	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
Price	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Lying-in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
hard	O
put	O
to	O
it	O
for	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
the	O
Irishman	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
Witness	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
fairly	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
his	O
Wigs	O
till	O
that	O
same	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Ozwin	I-pers
,	O
19	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
-	O
Wall	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Crab	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
for	O
1	O
s	O
per	O
Bobbin	O
:	O
But	O
Wall	O
and	O
Crab	O
afterwards	O
falling	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
abscounded	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Holden	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hawkinson	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
Rachel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Anna	B-pers
Marin	I-pers
Billing	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
complain	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
such	O
a	O
Kick	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
not	O
Subject	O
to	O
the	O
Tiffick	O
Susan	B-pers
Blanch	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
do	O
n't	O
come-down	O
,	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
break	O
your	O
Neck	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
,	O
year	O
Maid	O
is	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
em	O
,	O
they	O
lye	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
for	O
I	O
only	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Kick	O
on	O
the	O
Arse	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
narrowly	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Belly	O
as	O
she	O
lay	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
;	O
that	O
all	O
appeared	O
fair	O
and	O
White	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
the	O
least	O
Blackness	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
external	O
Signs	O
of	O
a	O
Hurt	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Instrument	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Rupture	O
,	O
s	O
no	O
Confusion	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
could	O
raise	O
the	O
least	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
Death	O
.	O
Her	O
Card	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
wasted	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
common	O
in	O
Persons	O
subject	O
to	O
the	O
Tiffick	O
and	O
Consumption	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Corser	I-pers
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
often	O
ailing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
tender	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
good	O
warm	O
Things	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
her	O
Business	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
often	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
Nan	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
your	O
Work	O
myself	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
bring	O
ye	O
something	O
hot	O
to	O
take	O
inwardly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
often	O
complained	O
of	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
Ailments	O
than	O
the	O
Tiffick	O
and	O
Consumption	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
Ulcer	O
in	O
her	O
Womb	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
again	O
incurable	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whitchurch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roche	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Small	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornesey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Kicking	O
,	O
Beating	O
,	O
Bruising	O
and	O
Pinching	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
Privy	O
Members	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Man	I-place
on	I-place
Muzzle-Hill	I-place
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Ostler	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Wife	O
served	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
old	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
manner	O
,	O
till	O
some	O
Dispute	O
arising	O
about	O
Wrestling	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Cramin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
either	O
throw	O
you	O
or	O
beat	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
had	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
try	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
stript	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
Boxing	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Small	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Rogue	O
;	O
you	O
kicked	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
they	O
shook	O
Hands	O
,	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
Friends	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
deceased	O
afterwards	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
t'other	O
Stroke	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Fighting	O
,	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
evident	O
that	O
the	O
Blows	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
if	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willington	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
10s	O
.	O
2	O
Smock	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheltrum	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
and	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
10d	O
.	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Pot	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoot	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Dames	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
val	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
kept	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
New	B-place
Rag-Fair	I-place
.	O
At	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
parted	O
from	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
only	O
by	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Partition	O
.	O
This	O
Back	O
Shop	O
stood	O
empty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
sometimes	O
by	O
himself	O
and	O
sometimes	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rainy	O
Night	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Shop	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Shop-Window	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
safe	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
betwixt	O
her	O
Shop	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
broken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
above	O
5	O
l.	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Shop	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
.	O
She	O
met	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
Lane	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
from	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
till	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Areton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rudge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rudge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	O
Hughs	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
(	O
depos	O
'd	O
Joseph	O
Walters	O
)	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
-	O
Bains	O
;	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
Business	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
old	O
Things	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
selling	O
some	O
so	O
-	O
s	O
Wheatly	O
,	O
a	O
Salesman	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
street	O
,	O
Bains	O
came	O
thither	O
and	O
desired	O
Wheatly	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
.	O
Wheatly	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
paid	O
9	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
for	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Wheatly	O
,	O
who	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Justices	O
at	O
Button	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
nobody	O
them	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
at	O
Liberty	O
.	O
The	O
Course	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
Smocks	O
;	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ashford	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
New	O
Queen-street	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
former	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
Talk	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
in	O
Russel	O
Court	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
bade	O
me	O
make	O
haste	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
Daughter	O
will	O
rob	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
get	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
Words	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
indeed	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
accidentally	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
others	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Chipping-Norton	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
has	O
since	O
Lain-in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cornwick	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
Cornwick	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tipping	I-pers
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Four	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Clitherow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Five	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cornwick	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
Cornwick	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bavan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
.	O
All	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
were	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Forty	O
three	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gering	I-pers
,	O
Penelope	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gaskin	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Fleetwood	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dison	I-pers
alias	O
Dixon	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Castile	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lemmon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellitt	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Throll	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
