TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
21st	O
,	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
23d	O
,	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1726.	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Sleath	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Martindale	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Shugburgh	I-pers
William	B-pers
Petly	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
William	B-pers
Colthorp	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cooms	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Blundel	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Tent	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Waddel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
William	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Duffen	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
March	O
29	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
.	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Drinis	I-place
Back	I-place
Church	I-place
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Hogs	O
Brisles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Hopford	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Wood	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Mare	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
at	O
Newcastle	B-place
upon	I-place
Tyne	I-place
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
partly	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
lik	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
price	O
should	O
be	O
7	O
Guineas	O
ready	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
6	O
pence	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
as	O
Earnest	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
try	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
bridled	O
and	O
saddled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
mounted	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Ride	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Mile	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
forgot	O
to	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
traced	O
him	O
all	O
over	O
Yorkshire	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
and	O
Advertizing	O
,	O
found	O
out	O
both	O
the	O
Mare	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Holms	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Shoe-Lane	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
clapt	O
one	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
somewhere	O
else	O
-	O
and	O
,	O
How	O
d	O
'ye	O
do	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Breast	O
to	O
shove	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
pull	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
whereof	O
I	O
took	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
there	O
steps	O
up	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
begun	O
to	O
be	O
saucy	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
caned	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Brass	O
,	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
February	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bennet	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
2	O
pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
pound	O
of	O
Pepper	O
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Ratcliff	B-place
;	O
I	O
fastned	O
my	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
understanding	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
Shop	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
remov	O
'd	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Joyns	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Brook-Street	O
with	O
a	O
Burden	O
for	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
William	B-pers
Catesby	I-pers
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
Hy	O
,	O
Hy	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
here	O
,	O
a	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
Step	O
over	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
is	O
and	O
so	O
my	O
Master	O
did	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
extropolus	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
his	O
grest	O
Coat	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Catesby	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Man	O
Ned	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Market	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Asparagus	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
step	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
struggled	O
hard	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
Butter	O
Firkin	O
with	O
Butter	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
standing	O
under	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
without	O
side	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Pepper	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
West	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
large	O
Gimblet	O
,	O
small	O
Saw	O
,	O
Chissel	O
,	O
and	O
little	O
Poker	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Packs	O
of	O
Cards	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
28	O
pound	O
Iron	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
14	O
pound	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Maycock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Marry	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Marriage	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cockshead	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Trigger	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Parishioners	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Cripplegate	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Jeffreys	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Vanwick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Breese	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Topping	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
17	O
pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
6	O
pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Buckles	O
,	O
3	O
Razors	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Breksy	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen's-Head	O
in	O
Pennington-street	O
,	O
Ratcliff	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
last	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Mugs	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
New	O
Row	O
,	O
Tuthill-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
these	O
10	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
and	O
begun	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
that	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
2	O
silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
weigh	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
and	O
Place	O
of	O
abode	O
were	O
engrav	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
by	O
no	O
Means	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Mugs	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
perceive	O
my	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
.	O
Last	O
January	O
was	O
a	O
1	O
s.	O
Month	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Topping	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
notice	O
whenever	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
did	O
.	O
John	O
Topping	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
Gore	I-place
(	I-place
betwixt	I-place
Kensington	I-place
and	I-place
Knights-bridge	I-place
)	I-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
down	O
Gore-lane	O
behind	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Shop-Door	O
and	O
Window	O
both	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cheese	O
,	O
Bacon	O
,	O
Eggs	O
,	O
Candles	O
,	O
2	O
Razors	O
,	O
2	O
Flasks	O
of	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Ha	O
!	O
Ye	O
old	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
tell	O
ye	O
that	O
your	O
House	O
would	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
that	O
Window	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Wife	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
our	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
Tallow	O
sticking	O
to	O
the	O
Stile	O
that	O
led	O
into	O
Gore-lane	O
.	O
She	O
Suppos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
broke	O
there	O
in	O
getting	O
over	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
more	O
Tallow	O
Sticking	O
upon	O
his	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
the	O
Tallow	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
more	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
greasy	O
and	O
that	O
Eggs	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
run	O
thro	O
'	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
strictly	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
back	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
He	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
-	O
But	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
has	O
stole	O
the	O
Mugs	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Macclane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
and	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Treen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bolter	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mansel	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bolter	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sweet	O
.	O
We	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
Clifford	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
call	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
dismounted	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sweet	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
upon	O
my	O
Mare	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Mansel	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Chambers	O
.	O
-	O
Presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
mounted	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
riding	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
-	O
What	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
-	O
why	O
Mr.	O
Millington	O
-	O
Friend	O
you	O
're	O
mistaken	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Millington	O
's	O
Horse	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
again	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Why	O
sure	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Millington	O
's	O
Horse	O
well	O
enough	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Horse	O
a	O
Lick	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
clear	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
prevented	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
this	O
Time	O
Mr.	O
Mansel	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
hard	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Scuffam	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Seven	O
half	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Jewen	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
herself	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Marry	O
my	O
Maid	O
-	O
Yes	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
togive	O
them	O
a	O
wedding	O
Dinner	O
at	O
Easter	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
lent	O
her	O
any	O
Money	O
says	O
he	O
-	O
No	O
-	O
have	O
you	O
mist	O
any	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
Why	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
Money	O
somewhere	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
15	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Bag	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
hearing	O
this	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
24	O
l.	O
We	O
presently	O
tax	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
confestd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
return	O
'd	O
me	O
1	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Shillings	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
bought	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
with	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
3	O
Guineas	O
at	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
Wedding	O
Cloths	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
for	O
her	O
Sweetheart	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
and	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joe	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Simkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gadsby	I-pers
,	O
Novem	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brockhurst	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brookhouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Bromley	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
tame	O
Conies	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Peers	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Townstead	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
kept	O
several	O
tame	O
Conies	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Morning	O
I	O
mist	O
4	O
Does	O
and	O
a	O
Buck	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Does	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Rabbits	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
already	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Hand	O
should	O
be	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Keepers	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Executioner	O
,	O
Come	O
hither	O
Jack	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
The	O
Executioner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mark	O
was	O
visible	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Blocksedge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Books	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Temperance	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Laced	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackricket	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bun	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
lest	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
-	O
Binks	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Drawer	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
Who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Eagle-Court	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
betwixt	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bourn	O
came	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
And	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
standing	O
there	O
(	O
for	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
)	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
Guinea	O
that	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Bear-Garden	O
Fellow	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
nothing	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
was	O
Swearing	O
and	O
Calling	O
Names	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
hussled	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bourn	O
closed	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stab	O
'd	O
the	O
Decease	O
'd	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Bourn	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
flourish	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stand	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Decease	O
'd	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bourn	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
died	O
presently	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
little	O
suddled	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
very	O
well	O
all	O
that	O
pass	O
'd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Poplet	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Fire	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hains	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Sister	O
)	O
heard	O
his	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Mr.	O
Chandler	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
(	O
says	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
)	O
-	O
Dear	O
Dick	O
take	O
another	O
opportunity	O
:	O
He	O
answered	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Time	O
like	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
,	O
Stand	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
looking	O
at	O
his	O
last	O
Breast	O
;	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
pale	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Drawer	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
When	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
Stand	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
Bear-Garden	O
Fellow	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
Boxing	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
ill	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Cook	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
run	O
our	O
great	O
Passion	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
Door	O
so	O
hard	O
after	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
split	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
You	O
owe	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
a	O
Rascal	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
and	O
a	O
Black	O
Guard	O
.	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
three	O
parts	O
of	O
your	O
Regiment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
Stand	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
Bear-Garden	O
Fighter	O
,	O
though	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Drawer	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
an	O
Answer	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
no	O
Knife	O
when	O
he	O
run	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
the	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
-	O
Mrs	O
Bourn	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
his	O
own	O
Finger	O
to	O
be	O
bloody	O
.	O
See	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
by	O
saving	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
ye	O
go	O
after	O
your	O
Friend	O
Chandler	O
?	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Bitch	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Strike	O
her	O
:	O
-	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
will	O
ye	O
strike	O
a	O
Women	O
with	O
Child	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
Mortal	O
,	O
it	O
penetrated	O
to	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
strait	O
downward	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
obliquely	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
Breadth	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
given	O
over	O
another	O
Mans	O
Shoulder	O
:	O
For	O
in	O
Such	O
a	O
Case	O
the	O
Wound	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
wider	O
at	O
the	O
Orifice	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
inwards	O
.	O
Hasting	O
and	O
Mead	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Resistance	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bourn	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
demanded	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
owe	O
you	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Bones	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
kickt	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Fall	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
Skin	O
off	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
:	O
He	O
retreated	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Keep	O
off	O
.	O
Bear-Garden	O
!	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Yards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
still	O
bade	O
him	O
keep	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
back	O
as	O
he	O
spoke	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
continued	O
to	O
push	O
forward	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
ran	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gillingham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
Robert	B-pers
Shirly	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
February	O
21	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
de	I-pers
Comines	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
1725	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
since	O
dead	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
)	O
did	O
send	O
to	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Letter	O
,	O
not	O
signed	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
,	O
demanding	O
20	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirly	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
along	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
Attack	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Jostled	O
my	O
Fore	O
Chairman	O
.	O
and	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
bade	O
him	O
Stand	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Chair	O
Door	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
stirr	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
while	O
his	O
Companion	O
stood	O
over	O
the	O
other	O
Chairman	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
Fore	O
Chairman	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Parents	O
kept	O
a	O
Fruiterers	O
Stall	O
just	O
by	O
White	O
's	O
Chocolate	O
House	O
.	O
Hall	O
the	O
Chairman	O
depos	O
'd	O
thus	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
me	O
Stand	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Rogue	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
Partner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Poles	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
a	O
knock	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Companion	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Chairman	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
Swore	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Chairman	O
acknowledged	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
Swear	O
,	O
only	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
his	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
at	O
some	O
Charges	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Midnight	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
more	O
pickt	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Fighting	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
Indictment	O
Richard	B-pers
Meeks	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
my	O
Master	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Reith	O
a	O
Watch-maker	O
,	O
)	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Wig	O
to	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Pall-mall	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hipp	O
'd	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Letter	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Chocolate	O
Houses	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemans	O
own	O
House	O
in	O
George	O
Street	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Letter	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Fellow	O
threatens	O
to	O
Shoot	O
me	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
meets	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
send	O
him	O
20	O
Guineas	O
by	O
the	O
Bearer	O
.	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
Swore	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
She	O
Swore	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
Swore	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Contents	O
follow	O
.	O
To	O
Mr	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
Great	O
George	O
Street	O
over-against	O
the	O
Church	O
near	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
I	O
Desire	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
20	O
Guineas	O
by	O
the	O
Bearer	O
without	O
letting	O
him	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
Innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Contents	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
my	O
Blood	O
and	O
Soul	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
before	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
:	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
send	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Devil	O
dash	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
Shoot	O
you	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
you	O
stir	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
Or	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
others	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
your	O
Business	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Opportunity	O
.	O
Therefore	O
pray	O
fail	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
G	O
-	O
strike	O
me	O
to	O
instant	O
D	O
--	O
tion	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
3d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Blisset	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
.	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Unnion	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
2Boy	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Pendar	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
5	O
Keys	O
,	O
a	O
Tweezer	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
d.1/2	O
on	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
Dishes	O
,	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Braintry	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
(	O
with	O
John	O
Burrows	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovejoy	I-pers
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
6	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Munn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
their	O
Goods	O
April	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
and	O
Robert	O
Wills	O
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Map	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Benfield	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
8	O
Pair	O
of	O
Hinges	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
16	O
s	O
.	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
William	O
Benfield	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Hamstead	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
bright	O
Night	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Haverstock	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	I-place
which	I-place
is	I-place
between	I-place
the	I-place
Half-way	I-place
House	I-place
and	I-place
Hamstead	I-place
,	O
we	O
were	O
Attack	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
ye	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
in	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
undid	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
-	O
Now	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
lying	O
Son	O
of	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
ne'er	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
String	O
?	O
The	O
other	O
took	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
Things	O
from	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Hinges	O
.	O
Their	O
Pistols	O
had	O
Brass	O
Stocks	O
and	O
bright	O
Barrels	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Carpenter	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
.	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
you	O
no	O
hurt	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
Cast	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
broke	O
cut	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
We	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Hamstead	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
got	O
these	O
Hinges	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
'd	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Blackerby	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
.	O
Quilt	O
Arnold	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
2	O
Pistols	O
upon	O
him	O
You	O
see	O
the	O
Stocks	O
are	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Barrels	O
bright	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fleetwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Rislip	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Sacks	O
and	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Bugby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Sack	O
and	O
4	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Bugby	O
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
Ralph	O
Bugby	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Corn	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
making	O
Search	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Haymow	O
at	O
Hendon	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Wheat	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
broken	O
Farmer	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Waggon	O
at	O
Bear	O
Key	O
,	O
though	O
some	O
Folks	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
there	O
never	O
are	O
any	O
Waggons	O
come	O
to	O
Bear	O
Key	O
with	O
Corn	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Wheat	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Sacks	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
old	O
Sacks	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
Searching	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hollow	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Mow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Fork	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
fetch	O
ye	O
one	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
coming	O
with	O
it	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
-	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
20	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
or	O
40	O
Guineas	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
desire	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
usual	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Room	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
Places	O
in	O
Haymows	O
to	O
put	O
Chaff	O
,	O
or	O
Beans	O
,	O
or	O
Corn	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
10	O
Pounds	O
a	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
Rented	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
Score	O
Pounds	O
a	O
Year	O
more	O
at	O
Hendon	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
in	O
Credit	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
likely	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
turn	O
Thief	O
in	O
his	O
old	O
Age	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Wheat	O
.	O
Abram	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Bear-Key	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
2	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Wheat	O
in	O
Sacks	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Cart	O
.	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
common	O
in	O
my	O
Country	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
Holes	O
in	O
Hay-mows	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
Chaff	O
and	O
Peas	O
in	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neighbours	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
.	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lowder	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Birmingham	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tudor	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
2	O
Razors	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Unnion	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sargeant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
her	O
(	O
Grandmother	O
)	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Right-hand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
made	O
dayly	O
complaints	O
of	O
ill	O
Usage	O
that	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
struck	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
near	O
100	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
my	O
self	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Jumble	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harlock	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
visited	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
Room	O
in	O
Plimpton	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
speechless	O
.	O
Her	O
Hand	O
was	O
mortify	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Wrist	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
had	O
been	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
for	O
great	O
Allowance	O
must	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
old	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
Poorness	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
;	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
old	O
Grandmother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
grown	O
Childish	O
with	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bade	O
me	O
get	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
thus	O
.	O
My	O
Grandmother	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
unsatisfied	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Mischief	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
I	O
never	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
abused	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
want	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
complain	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
growing	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
should	O
loss	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
way	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
aBoy	O
)	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
30	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
.	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
Kings-land	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
'em	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sold	O
Eggs	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
White-Chaple	O
,	O
and	O
thot	O
she	O
encourag	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
likewise	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
died	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Billings	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woods	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
bon	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
the	O
former	O
by	O
striking	O
and	O
bruising	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hays	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Petty	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
being	O
Traiterously	O
present	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Billings	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bromage	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Katherine	O
Hays	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Leonard	B-pers
Myring	I-pers
went	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
here	O
on	O
this	O
Account	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
too	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
cou	O
'd	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
your	O
Head	O
,	O
to	O
commit	O
such	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Murder	O
upon	O
your	O
own	O
husband	O
?	O
Why	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Devil	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
John	O
Hays	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
the	O
Husbands	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
half	O
starved	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
repent	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
in	O
drawing	O
those	O
two	O
poor	O
Man	O
into	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
in	O
importuning	O
'em	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
agreed	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
was	O
made	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Billings	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Taylor	O
)	O
and	O
Wood	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Fore	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Billings	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pole	O
Ax	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Wood	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
while	O
Wood	O
cut	O
his	O
Head	O
quite	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
chop	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
legs	O
and	O
Arms	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
use	O
your	O
Husband	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
inhumane	O
manner	O
.	O
Because	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
Old	O
Chest	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
too	O
big	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
with	O
only	O
cutting	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
Thighs	O
and	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Chest	O
would	O
not	O
hold	O
'em	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Body	O
and	O
Limbs	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
out	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
into	O
a	O
Pond	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
could	O
induce	O
the	O
Men	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Money	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
The	O
Devil	O
was	O
in	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
got	O
drunk	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
for	O
your	O
self	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
before	O
the	O
Judge	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
signify	O
nothing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
long	O
Preamble	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
hold	O
up	O
my	O
Hand	O
and	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Guilty	O
,	O
for	O
nothing	O
can	O
save	O
me	O
,	O
nobody	O
can	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Myring	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Times	O
was	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
're	O
come	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
Murder	O
are	O
taken	O
.	O
and	O
have	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
'em	O
when	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
Stool	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Blow	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
stamp	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
:	O
and	O
after	O
his	O
Head	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
Billing	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
lye	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
dead	O
Body	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
she	O
first	O
Occasion	O
of	O
your	O
contriving	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
came	O
Home	O
drunk	O
one	O
Night	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
says	O
Billings	O
,	O
This	O
fellow	O
deserves	O
to	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
Wood	O
I	O
'd	O
be	O
his	O
Butcher	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
they	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
they	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
'd	O
do	O
it	O
the	O
Night	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
your	O
Husband	O
of	O
this	O
Design	O
to	O
murder	O
him	O
?	O
Because	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
beat	O
me	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Mercer	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
you	O
are	O
Tom	O
Billing	O
's	O
Friend	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
pray	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
vain	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
my	O
Husband	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
both	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Brawns-Head	O
in	O
New-Bond-Street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
that	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
for	O
6	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Mountain	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
put	O
into	O
Bottles	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
Home	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Bottles	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Empty	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
9	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
Men	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
Empty	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
Quart	O
of	O
Wine	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Bottle	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
besides	O
ours	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Springet	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
Committed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
Day	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
My	O
Husband	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
great	O
Merrimaking	O
below	O
,	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
Dancing	O
,	O
and	O
Singing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
tired	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
first	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
their	O
Liquor	O
was	O
almost	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
,	O
be	O
disturbed	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rest	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
tap	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
almost	O
done	O
Drinking	O
;	O
ay	O
,	O
Child	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
not	O
a	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
up	O
I	O
goes	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
O	O
says	O
She	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
a	O
Charge	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Wits	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
Murder	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
may	O
come	O
safe	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
such	O
an	O
Obstinate	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
gets	O
a	O
little	O
Liquor	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
persuading	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
early	O
next	O
Day	O
which	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
Wood	O
and	O
Billings	O
.	O
She	O
again	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
uneasiness	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
some	O
wicked	O
Rogue	O
or	O
other	O
should	O
knock	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
drawling	O
along	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
again	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
those	O
2	O
Men	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Bed	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
brought	O
only	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
I	O
heard	O
another	O
drawling	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
bought	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
What	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Landlords	O
Mark	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
say	O
they	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
She	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
more	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
heard	O
another	O
Bustling	O
below	O
.	O
I	O
begun	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
that	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
smoke	O
half	O
a	O
Pipe	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
While	O
she	O
staid	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Men	O
going	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
Stair-Head	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
uneasy	O
.	O
Truly	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Hays	O
I	O
believe	O
your	O
'	O
r	O
a	O
going	O
to	O
move	O
your	O
Goods	O
by	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
its	O
Shame	O
you	O
should	O
do	O
so	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
Money	O
that	O
lies	O
by	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
indeed	O
,	O
says	O
She	O
its	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
pray	O
Mistress	O
Hays	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
Why	O
nothing	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
self	O
easy	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
which	O
was	O
Thursday	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Wood	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
down	O
Swallow	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
that	O
Bundle	O
was	O
,	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
be	O
borrow	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
in	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Head	O
that	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
at	O
Mill	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pail	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
,	O
in	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Head	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hayns	O
's	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Pail	O
was	O
his	O
Pail	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
fainted	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bows	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Lodge	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
Coat	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Springet	O
Swears	O
was	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
acknowledged	O
,	O
that	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
before	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Design	O
against	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
when	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Hand	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
was	O
clear	O
of	O
his	O
Blood	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Morard	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Margrand	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Abetting	O
John	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
)	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
gave	O
the	O
said	O
Ferguson	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
was	O
Sworn	O
between	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
Patrole	O
in	O
the	O
5	O
Fields	O
between	O
Chelsea	O
and	O
Westminster	O
,	O
we	O
past	O
by	O
the	O
Genoese	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
got	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Yards	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
John	O
Andrews	O
came	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
us	O
King	O
Georges	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
other	O
abusive	O
Language	O
.	O
-	O
Sir	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Andrews	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
dont	O
mend	O
your	O
manners	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
carry	O
you	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Guard	O
.	O
-	O
Will	O
you	O
says	O
he	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
Stick	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
naked	O
Knife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
Collar	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
kickt	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
.	O
My	O
Comrade	O
might	O
then	O
be	O
about	O
2	O
Yards	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Candle	O
was	O
beat	O
out	O
.	O
Andrew	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
my	O
Comrade	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
Candle	O
at	O
the	O
Genoese	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
fallen	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
abused	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
Then	O
looking	O
about	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Andrew	O
a	O
Strugling	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
towards	O
the	O
Genoese	O
Arms	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Andrews	O
ran	O
quite	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Sword	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
Drawn	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Genoese	O
Arms	O
.	O
Captain	O
Steward	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Knife	O
upon	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
Andrews	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
Strugling	O
.	O
Captain	O
Washington	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Drinking	O
with	O
Andrews	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Artichoak	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Andrews	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Snick	O
or	O
Snee	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
grew	O
very	O
Quarrelsome	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
Way	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
Andrews	O
,	O
but	O
Andrews	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hepburn	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Knife	O
had	O
entred	O
the	O
left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
much	O
Blood	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Break	O
,	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
near	O
7	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Mortal	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
sober	O
,	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
,	O
peaceable	O
Man	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brograve	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Branthwait	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
George's-Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Devereux-Court	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Brograve	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
with	O
his	O
Cloak	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
remarkable	O
warm	O
Day	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
very	O
ill.	O
We	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
of	O
indifferent	O
Things	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
sat	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
Here	O
!	O
and	O
presently	O
steps	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
frequented	O
that	O
Coffee-House	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
often	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Pistol	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
any	O
Body	O
out	O
upon	O
a	O
Message	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trout	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
at	O
George	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
whom	O
I	O
never	O
(	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
)	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
our	O
Bar	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Red	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Brograve	O
,	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
Here	O
;	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
the	O
Stranger	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
strange	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
any	O
Body	O
out	O
upon	O
any	O
Message	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
frequents	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sope	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
Air	O
in	O
Hyde-Park	B-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
Scarlet	O
Cloaks	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
pretty	O
fast	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
turn	O
'd	O
off	O
towards	O
some	O
Bushes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
tallest	O
of	O
'em	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
dropt	O
his	O
Cloak	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
immediately	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
each	O
of	O
'em	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
-	O
Says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Fire	O
.	O
No	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
do	O
you	O
fire	O
first	O
-	O
You	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Well	O
then	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
let	O
as	O
fire	O
both	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
mist	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
run	O
toward	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
parry	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
pusht	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
closed	O
,	O
struggled	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
stagger	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
Speak	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Fault	O
?	O
Will	O
ye	O
forgive	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
Pray	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
Weak	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
nor	O
call	O
aloud	O
His	O
Sword	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
crooked	O
.	O
He	O
wiped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
and	O
streighten	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
waved	O
his	O
Hat	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
Hyde-Park	O
Corner	O
.	O
A	O
Coach	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Cloak	O
,	O
his	O
Wig	O
.	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
.	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
Pistols	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
Gentleman	O
standing	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
making	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
beckon	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rand	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
both	O
Ventricles	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
were	O
penetrated	O
.	O
The	O
Entrance	O
was	O
made	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Fourth	O
and	O
Fifth	O
Rib	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
Mortal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
Business	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
concern	O
with	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Coach	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
acted	O
like	O
a	O
Rascal	O
and	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
;	O
In	O
what	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
setting	O
me	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
this	O
pitiful	O
business	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
's	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
employing	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
your	O
Affairs	O
of	O
great	O
Consequence	O
;	O
and	O
beside	O
you	O
have	O
injur	O
'd	O
my	O
Character	O
in	O
another	O
Affair	O
and	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
two	O
Pistols	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
pacify	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
stir	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
Some	O
Notice	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
of	O
my	O
wearing	O
a	O
Cloak	O
on	O
a	O
warm	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
conceal	O
my	O
Pistols	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
favour	O
my	O
Escape	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
only	O
wore	O
it	O
to	O
prevent	O
catching	O
Cold	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
.	O
Nor	O
was	O
my	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
any	O
Assignation	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
frequented	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
might	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
likely	O
Place	O
to	O
find	O
me	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Wasey	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
of	O
his	O
Illness	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
George	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
frequently	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
enquire	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
that	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pennock	I-pers
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
large	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
These	O
Pistols	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mallory	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
among	O
his	O
Papers	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Challenge	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Powder	O
Horn	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Charge	O
lying	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Distinction	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
even	O
Temper	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
inclinable	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsome	O
.	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
and	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Osgood	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pendril	I-pers
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
9	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
aboy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
6	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Friar	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
5	O
Clouts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Judith	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Dowager	I-pers
Dover	I-pers
April	O
6	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
be	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Margaret	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Kenney	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
190	O
Pounds	O
Tobacco	O
Stalks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
.	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Sikes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wigly	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
60	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s	O
.	O
March	O
15	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phillip	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
O'Connor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Shoemakers	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thimas	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Deacons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
.	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bermudas	O
Cane	O
Plat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sylvanus	B-pers
Sutcliff	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
.	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arabella	B-pers
Venus	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wainhouse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brisco	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Shingle	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Par	I-pers
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kooker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Sauce	O
pans	O
,	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Counter-pane	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pollet	I-pers
,	O
April	O
7	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
Lead	O
off	O
Lion's-Inn	B-place
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
Mistake	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Broadbent	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Broadbent	I-pers
a	O
piece	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Frock	O
,	O
3	O
Clouts	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Rags	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cosier	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Phillis	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Broadbent	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
the	O
Rainbow	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mary	O
Broadbent	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
living	O
among	O
ill	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
they	O
seduced	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Stay	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
that	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wipe	O
my	O
Razors	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
them	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Broadbent	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
lost	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
never	O
find	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
2	O
Child	O
's	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Frock	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
Cosier	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
own	O
a	O
thousand	O
Times	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
instructed	O
in	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
;	O
she	O
can	O
say	O
her	O
Catechism	O
in	O
English	O
and	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
answer	O
all	O
lawful	O
Questions	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
drawn	O
aside	O
by	O
wicked	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Mary	O
Harding	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Phillis	O
,	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
charge	O
them	O
with	O
receiving	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
kept	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
their	O
Houses	O
,	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cosier	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
's	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
being	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Chairing	O
at	O
Broadbent	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
When	O
Broadbent	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
odd	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
owned	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
a	O
Quit	O
.	O
Says	O
,	O
Broadbent	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
take	O
this	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
former	O
Wife	O
gave	O
her	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Miller	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Consier	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
4	O
Years	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
mist	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
's	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
ever	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
brought	O
Twenty	O
creditable	O
House-keepers	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hudsen	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Broadbent	O
's	O
own	O
Sister	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
his	O
new	O
Wife	O
have	O
used	O
the	O
child	O
very	O
barbarously	O
.	O
They	O
beat	O
her	O
till	O
they	O
made	O
her	O
confest	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
made	O
her	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
Chintz	O
Gown	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Mother	O
never	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Gown	O
.	O
And	O
since	O
the	O
Child	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
Charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
he	O
himself	O
,	O
gave	O
these	O
very	O
Curtains	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
has	O
met	O
with	O
such	O
cruel	O
Usage	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
run	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
for	O
Succour	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
one	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
upon	O
my	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lain	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
knock	O
at	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
asks	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
use	O
his	O
own	O
Child	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
Have	O
ye	O
a	O
Mind	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
or	O
Transported	O
?	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
but	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Broadbent	O
charged	O
Cosier	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
stay	O
.	O
She	O
readily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
your	O
Wife	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
here	O
are	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pickt	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
Rags	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
brought	O
to	O
dress	O
her	O
Doll	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
thinking	O
it	O
improper	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
live	O
again	O
with	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Step-Mother	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Agreement	O
,	O
to	O
allow	O
his	O
Sister	O
Mrs.	O
Hudson	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Board	O
and	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Fees	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
committing	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
30	O
Years	O
,	O
the	O
heinous	O
and	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Newton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Bavidge	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
-	O
Eccleston	O
(	O
who	O
dy	O
'd	O
last	O
Week	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clap	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
first	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Clap	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Grapes	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
It	O
bore	O
the	O
publick	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Place	O
of	O
Entertainment	O
for	O
Sodomites	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
her	O
Customers	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
Beds	O
in	O
every	O
Room	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
usually	O
had	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
of	O
such	O
Persons	O
there	O
every	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
conducted	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Perswasions	O
of	O
Bavidge	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
)	O
I	O
suffer	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
Crime	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
attempted	O
the	O
same	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
would	O
permit	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
When	O
Mrs.	O
Clap	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
Bail	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
Information	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Information	O
accordingly	O
.	O
-	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Clap	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
notorious	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
Molly-House	O
.	O
-	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
some	O
that	O
frequented	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
of	O
'em	O
together	O
,	O
making	O
Love	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
Manner	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
by	O
Pairs	O
,	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
their	O
return	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
tell	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
marrying	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
Times	O
at	O
Clap	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Rendesvouz	O
for	O
such	O
Persons	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoxan	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
him	O
with	O
Milk	O
these	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Milk	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cow-Keeper	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Oxfordshire	O
Feast	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
have	O
both	O
got	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
Home	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
he	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
married	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
18	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
these	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Girl	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
-	O
Several	O
others	O
deposd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
inclinable	O
to	O
such	O
Practices	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
committing	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
Mark	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Former	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Try	O
'd	O
for	O
this	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Committing	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Newton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
absconded	O
,	O
)	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
for	O
near	O
2	O
Years	O
at	O
Clap	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Act	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Gang	O
at	O
Clap	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Redear	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Regar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Edward	O
Courtney	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Gray	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
Market	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
He	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
Dine	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
away	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
and	O
kist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sollicited	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
Thomas	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
's	O
a	O
Silk-Dyer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
in	O
Crown	O
Court	O
in	O
Knaves	O
Acre	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
entertaining	O
such	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
Drink	O
in	O
private	O
back	O
Rooms	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
often	O
after	O
me	O
to	O
persuade	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Ned	O
Courtney	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
injury	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
handsome	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
pretty	O
younger	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
I'le	O
fetch	O
him	O
fir	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Tom	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
School	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
good	O
.	O
Drink	O
Ned	O
there	O
again	O
solicited	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Privy	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
subsist	O
upon	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
got	O
by	O
doing	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
that	O
course	O
of	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Women	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
Swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
courteous	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
Buggery	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
Jan	O
10	O
1724-	O
5	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Newton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Last	O
January	O
12	O
Month	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Carnal	O
Use	O
of	O
my	O
Body	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Christophers	O
Alley	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Wooll-Comber	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sold	O
a	O
Dram	O
among	O
such	O
Company	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
afterwards	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
Beech	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
kept	O
Rooms	O
for	O
the	O
entertainment	O
of	O
Sodomites	O
.	O
He	O
sold	O
Ale	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
other	O
Ale-houses	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
often	O
fetch	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
oblige	O
Company	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
to	O
one	O
Gregory	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
and	O
-	O
Sellars	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
discovering	O
of	O
the	O
Molly	O
Houses	O
,	O
was	O
chiefly	O
owing	O
to	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
Mark	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
and	O
-	O
Harrington	O
:	O
For	O
upon	O
this	O
Quarrel	O
Partridge	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
Herrington	O
,	O
had	O
blab	O
'd	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
a	O
large	O
Information	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Mollies	O
had	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Discovery	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
far	O
he	O
had	O
proceeded	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
further	O
Designs	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
By	O
his	O
means	O
we	O
were	O
introduced	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
's	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Room	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
playing	O
upon	O
a	O
Fiddle	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
one	O
while	O
dancing	O
in	O
obscene	O
Postures	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
while	O
Singing	O
baudy	O
Songs	O
,	O
and	O
talking	O
leudly	O
,	O
and	O
Acting	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Indecencies	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
a	O
skew	O
upon	O
Mark	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
treacherous	O
,	O
blowing-up	O
Mollying	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
that	O
they	O
'd	O
Massacre	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
betray	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
kist	O
us	O
all	O
at	O
parting	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
indecent	O
manner	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
such	O
report	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
and	O
bred	O
at	O
Newbury	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
esteem	O
'd	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Whytle	I-pers
alias	O
Whittle	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	O
December	O
1	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
,	O
the	O
Royal-Oak	B-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George's-Square	I-place
in	I-place
Pall-Mall	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
for	O
the	O
Mollies	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
betwixt	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
The	O
Chappel	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
there	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
several	O
Husbands	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Day	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Ned	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Country	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
that	O
's	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Wedding	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
pay	O
you	O
very	O
handsomely	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
Mid-Night	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
6	O
Pence	O
.	O
-	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rigs	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
commonly	O
reported	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
a	O
Receptacle	O
for	O
Sodomites	O
.	O
Drake	B-pers
Stoneman	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
For	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Men	O
behave	O
themselves	O
very	O
indecently	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
exposing	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
's	O
sight	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
keep	O
conceal	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
retire	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
first	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
Courtney	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
thrice	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
says	O
Courtney	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
for	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
ye	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
First	O
I	O
it	O
was	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Cardigan's-Head	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
in	O
his	O
Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
abused	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
me	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
Molley	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Master	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
his	O
Goods	O
by	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
saucy	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Time	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
raising	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
about	O
a	O
Mollying	O
Cull	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
proceeded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
unfortunately	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
let	O
a	O
Shop	O
to	O
one	O
Johnson	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
whose	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
scandalous	O
Character	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
her	O
that	O
such	O
Things	O
were	O
reported	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
ever	O
she	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
these	O
2	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
Children	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
visiting	O
another	O
Widow	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
Marriage	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
broke	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
for	O
what	O
Drake	B-pers
Stonemen	I-pers
says	O
,	O
about	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
some	O
young	O
Surgeons	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
their	O
Patients	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
examine	O
their	O
Distempers	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
Applications	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Ned	O
Courtney	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
Butler	O
,	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crowyard	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Bayle	I-pers
Depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Times	O
in	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Lifetime	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
that	O
might	O
give	O
the	O
least	O
Ground	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
inclinable	O
to	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
such	O
Things	O
whisper	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Servant	O
ever	O
since	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Ned	O
Courtney	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
Room	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Encouragement	O
given	O
to	O
any	O
uncivil	O
Persons	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Maid	O
Servants	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
within	O
these	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Vigous	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Shock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Walmsly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Walmsly	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
saturday	O
