TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
The	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1726.	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barsby	I-pers
William	B-pers
Eusden	I-pers
William	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Waterson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
William	B-pers
Proudman	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
Bryan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Asahel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
James	B-pers
Guinny	I-pers
John	B-pers
Witherington	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
May	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
self	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
rest	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
dont	O
remember	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Breeches	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
waked	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
mist	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
truly	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
how	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
safe	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
somebody	O
should	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Guy	O
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Swan-Stairs	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
were	O
pretty	O
well	O
infor't	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
Night	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Folly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
6	O
Guineas	O
.	O
She	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
any	O
Money	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
stript	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
6	O
Guineas	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
only	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
safe	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
fall	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
and	O
lose	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
turn	O
up	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
Folly	O
had	O
been	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
himself	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
swear'em	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
before	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
'em	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
6d	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Matth.ew	O
Fuller	O
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
alias	O
Ely	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Medal	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
-	O
Collinson	O
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
and	O
accus	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Medal	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Shillings	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
Susan	O
Sly	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Stockings	O
I	O
found	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
Medal	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
bound	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
in	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Bound	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
but	O
yet	O
being	O
unwilling	O
to	O
expose	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
thus	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
us	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
by	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Room	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
stept	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
the	B-place
Gun	I-place
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Medal	O
to	O
Filewood	O
,	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
doing	O
as	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Medal	O
to	O
Sly	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Medal	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
meet	O
us	O
there	O
another	O
Night	O
and	O
redeem	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
send	O
for	O
one	O
that	O
should	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Landlord	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
clear	O
'd	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Abigail	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Robert	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Won	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
alias	O
Warnford	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Sheppard	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Walford	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
shew	O
.	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
she	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Loves-Court	B-place
in	O
Shoe-lane	B-place
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
tumbled	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
Sharpless	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
Walford	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
lag	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Child	O
)	O
by	O
driving	O
2	O
Horses	O
drawing	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
those	O
Horses	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Child	O
Joseph	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
ran	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
several	O
Children	O
were	O
playing	O
in	O
Totenham-Court-Road	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
or	O
Copse	O
,	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Horses	O
apace	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Children	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
aloud	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
the	O
fore	O
Horse	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
run	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darbon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Monro	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
17	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Brocaded	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	O
Monro	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Monro	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
suspected	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Necessity	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Directions	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patrick	B-pers
Macdermont	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tudman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
South-Mims	B-place
,	O
where	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Collinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
7	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Collinson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
May	O
26	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
North-hall	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
upon	O
Enfield-Chase	B-place
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
Sticks	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
Robert	O
Smith	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
stopt	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
7	O
d.	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Scot	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
still	O
about	O
ten	O
Yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
Smith	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Potter	O
's	O
Bar	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
told	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
Smith	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
at	O
Lamsted-Mills	O
by	O
Brockets-hall	O
Gate	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
he	O
was	O
traced	O
to	O
Mr.Powel	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Wind-mill	O
upon	O
North-hall	O
Common	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Bed	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
ready	O
charg	O
'd	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
impeach	O
'd	O
Scot	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
thereupon	O
apprehended	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
against	O
Smith	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Scot	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Smith	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rag	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Susan	B-pers
Duncalf	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
John	O
Hills	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Greenhith	B-place
in	O
Kent	B-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
Knight's-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
the	O
Prisoners	O
Brother	O
upon	O
my	O
Geldings	O
Back	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
hir	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
or	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Screen	I-pers
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Sun	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
swearing	O
to	O
a	O
Time	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
contradicting	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Strickland	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Pawley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
lodged	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perswaded	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Wigs	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
after	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
where	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Maurice	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Albertus	B-pers
Burnaby	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Golden-lane	B-place
,	O
Brewer	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
on	O
an	O
Act	O
An	O
.	O
Reg	O
.	O
Geo	O
.	O
R.V	O
.	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Trader	O
,	O
and	O
absenting	O
himself	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
did	O
thereby	O
become	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
afterwards	O
conceal	O
,	O
remove	O
,	O
and	O
convert	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
several	O
Goods	O
and	O
Notes	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Shorter	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	O
at	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Shorter	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Execution	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
me	O
by	O
Two	O
of	O
my	O
Creditors	O
,	O
Allen	O
and	O
Toms	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
Ironmonger-lane	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
'd	O
call	O
a	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Coach	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
Counter	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Bail	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Actions	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Records	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
an	O
Action	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Allin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
for	O
300	O
l.	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Fitch	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
of	O
November	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
surrender	O
'd	O
to	O
discharge	O
his	O
Bail	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marshall	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Clerk	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
.	O
Being	O
cross	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
(	O
by	O
examining	O
his	O
Books	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
than	O
would	O
pay	O
every	O
one	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tates	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
them	O
150	O
l	O
for	O
Goods	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Book	I-pers
keeper	O
at	O
Blossoms	O
Inn	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
A	O
parcel	O
of	O
Manchester	O
Bays	O
,	O
and	O
Penistons	O
worth	O
I	O
believe	O
50	O
l.	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
Inn	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
These	O
Goods	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
who	O
brought	O
this	O
Note	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Name	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
writing	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Carriage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
made	O
evident	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
secreted	O
3	O
Promissory	O
,	O
Notes	O
,	O
2	O
for	O
275	O
Guilders	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Sterling	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Bankruptcy	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Bart	O
,	O
and	O
Com	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
Morgan	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Jones	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
headed	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Moonlight	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Assaulted	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
-	O
more	O
He	O
had	O
dog	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
knocks	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Wig	O
,	O
this	O
Cane	O
and	O
my	O
,	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Money	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
side	O
Pocket	O
he	O
mist	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
beat	O
me	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
sad	O
Martyr	O
of	O
me.-	O
The	O
Wig	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cane	O
found	O
by	O
my	O
Directions	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
quarrelsome	O
,	O
and	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
Knocks	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
Cane	O
and	O
Wig	O
to	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
to	O
fighting	O
;	O
The	O
Mob	O
hurry	O
'd	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
.	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coopers	O
in	O
the	O
Victualing	O
Office	O
.	O
and	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
also	O
seduced	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blakeway	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
Evidences	O
against	O
him	O
)	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
like	O
practices	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
detected	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Leaper	I-pers
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Hoops	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilt	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goswell	I-pers
,	O
September	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Clark	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Strainer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Brogdon	B-pers
Poplet	I-pers
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Vanham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Best	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
a	O
double	O
Cruisado	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Gold	O
in	O
an	O
Ingot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Darmata	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Basil	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gaskin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Russel	B-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
hot	O
Poker	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Kate	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
keeps	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cant	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
Dram	O
there	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
upon	O
last	O
Christmas	O
Eve	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
Moll	O
Beech	O
,	O
and	O
Peg	B-pers
Gaskin	I-pers
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
Mrs.	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
sent	O
us	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
buy	O
Holly	O
and	O
Ivy	O
.	O
18	O
Pence	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
oldest	O
Basket	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
my	O
Girl	O
and	O
Moll	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
,	O
but	O
Moll	O
is	O
dead	O
and	O
buried	O
since	O
then	O
-	O
poor	O
Soul	O
!	O
She	O
'll	O
never	O
cry	O
Holly	O
and	O
Ivy	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
till	O
Moll	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
seems	O
she	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Quartern	O
at	O
another	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
in	O
she	O
comes	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
drunk	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
must	O
send	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
go	O
get	O
drunk	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
begun	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
heard	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
as	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
whereof	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
lean	O
'd	O
against	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pitch	O
'd	O
forward	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Blood	O
,	O
gusht	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
spoke	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Scouring	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
and	O
again	O
it	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
and	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Davis	O
was	O
Pretty	O
well	O
in	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
two	O
fell	O
a	O
Quarreling	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
pusht	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
helpt	O
her	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
far	O
Swearing	O
and	O
Cursing	O
,	O
and	O
ready	O
to	O
forwards	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Nose	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
when	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
right	O
Breast	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
always	O
kind	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Holly	O
and	O
Ivy	O
.	O
Then	O
were	O
both	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
should	O
carry	O
out	O
the	O
Holly	O
and	O
Ivy	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Ye	O
Bitches	O
,	O
shall	O
my	O
Wife	O
send	O
you	O
Money	O
to	O
get	O
Drunk	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
?	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
kept	O
chattering	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
red	O
hot	O
Poker	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
very	O
Poker	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
just	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
-	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
spoke	O
another	O
word	O
-	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
and	O
this	O
Kate	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
came	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
my	O
Mouth	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
hush	O
!	O
hush	O
!	O
She	O
says	O
indeed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fall	O
off	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
but	O
its	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
our	O
Murder	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
she	O
'll	O
Swear	O
any	O
thing	O
a	O
Beast	O
-	O
Nay	O
-	O
pray	O
keep	O
your	O
Hands	O
off	O
me	O
Mrs	O
Bolaface	O
I	O
beseech	O
ye	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
Quarreling	O
with	O
Sarah	O
Davis	O
who	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
again	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
Plates	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lye	O
Kettle	O
with	O
the	O
Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
my	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
against	O
the	O
Poker	O
-	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Davis	O
came	O
drunk	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Sarah	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
live	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
Rogue	O
year	O
Husband	O
hang	O
'd	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
fell	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
dear	O
Mrs.	O
Atkinson	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
putting	O
out	O
her	O
Tongue	O
,	O
See	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
how	O
my	O
Tongue	O
is	O
swell	O
'd	O
for	O
Swearing	O
.	O
Others	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Sarah	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
like	O
a	O
Mad	O
Woman	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Hair	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
Patches	O
upon	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
Bedlam	O
.	O
Several	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Civil	O
good	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabell	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Caldecot	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Haslem	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Quilt	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Ynur	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Ynur	O
Lloyd	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Shoe	B-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
private	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
Business	O
it	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
She	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
confoundedly	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
Course	O
to	O
take	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Watch	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
such	O
a	O
Woman	O
if	O
they	O
met	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Baudy	O
Houses	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
Search	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
-	O
We	O
presently	O
came	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
Person	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
less	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
Warehouse-Man	O
of	O
Bread-Street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Bankruptcy	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
being	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
and	O
Concealing	O
his	O
Effects	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
feloniously	O
break	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Warrant	O
of	O
his	O
Commitment	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
signed	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
present	O
that	O
could	O
prove	O
those	O
Names	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
Writing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sconce	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
black	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
May	O
21	O
and	O
a	O
Prayer-Book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
psalm-Book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pollixsen	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dickenson	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bowler	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hartrey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hartrey	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
last	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Kings-Head	B-place
Court	I-place
.	O
The	O
Bawd	O
's	O
Name	O
that	O
kept	O
it	O
was	O
Alice	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Fuddled	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
we	O
did	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
but	O
however	O
she	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
finding	O
her	O
Hand	O
near	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
mist	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
came	O
her	O
Bullies	O
,	O
and	O
maul	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
hussel	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
among	O
the	O
dark	O
Alleys	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
lamentable	O
Pickle	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
several	O
Pawn-brokers	O
to	O
step	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
I	O
afterwards	O
recover	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
up	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
,	O
by	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
stop	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
put	O
me	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
from	O
one	O
Time	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
tired	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
the	O
Watchman	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Masters	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Barber	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Bale	O
Court	O
,	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
Now	O
its	O
always	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
them	O
safe	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
ever	O
I	O
meet	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
my	O
Rounds	O
:	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
fell	O
out	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
see	O
's	O
my	O
Master	O
Hartrey	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
should	O
be	O
up	O
upon	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
very	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
Madam	O
Blewit	O
,	O
or	O
Dickenson	O
,	O
or	O
Bowler	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
Wife	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
Three	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
First	O
of'em	O
are	O
now	O
a	O
hanging	O
in	O
Chains	O
in	O
St.	O
George's-Fields	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
is	O
neither	O
here	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
presently	O
laid	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
grew	O
woundy	O
loving	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Hussy	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
Saucy	O
Brimstone	O
Toad	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
,	O
have	O
ye	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
call	O
my	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
ye	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
directly	O
,	O
And	O
,	O
Ah	O
Master	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Master	O
,	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
that	O
Hang-in-Chains	O
Bitch	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
call	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
'll	O
certainly	O
pick	O
your	O
Pocket	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
or	O
Serve	O
you	O
a	O
worse	O
Trick	O
.	O
-	O
Come	O
,	O
come	O
do	O
n't	O
expose	O
yourself	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
signify	O
'd	O
nothing	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
for	O
his	O
Fancy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
poor	O
Watchman	O
's	O
Advice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
before	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pally	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Poringer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Viscount	I-pers
Tyrconnel	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jelfs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Mug	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Davis	O
and	O
Jelfs	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Robinson	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Perukes	O
,	O
June	O
24	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Henry	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sheering	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sheering	I-pers
,	O
Eastman	B-pers
Sheering	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Woman	O
)	O
and	O
Prudence	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
upon	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
were	O
alarm	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
,	O
were	O
deny	O
'd	O
Entrance	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
which	O
begun	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
a	O
Hole	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
burning	O
Wood	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Winders	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
were	O
intrusted	O
by	O
their	O
Masters	O
with	O
several	O
Parcels	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
gave	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
was	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
neither	O
Fire	O
nor	O
Candle	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
other	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
remov	O
'd	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
particular	O
Fact	O
on	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dormer	B-pers
Fines	I-pers
,	O
May	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Legee	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Featon	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Frocks	O
,	O
1	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
3	O
Frocks	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
2	O
Shaving	O
Hats	O
,	O
2	O
Bermudas	O
Hats	O
,	O
5	O
Straw	O
Hats	O
,	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bermudas	O
Plot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Etkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Etkins	I-pers
.	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Claxon	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
.	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chalkhill	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
,	O
brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Mare	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Edmonton	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
Stamford	O
Horse	O
Race	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
well	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
Mare	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
Stamford	O
Market	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brakes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hotchinson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
at	O
Horncastle	B-place
in	O
Lincolnsshire	B-place
,	O
advising	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Coats	O
his	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
me	O
to	O
Search	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
Smith-field	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
both	O
the	O
Mares	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brakes	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Coat	O
's	O
Mare	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
Sell	O
for	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
Ale	O
House	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
either	O
of	O
Brakes	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
they	O
Confest	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Two	O
Mares	O
upon	O
Horncastle	O
Common	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Inn	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
;	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
the	O
Mares	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Black	O
Mare	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
The	O
Mares	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Raynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Rains	I-pers
in	O
More	B-place
fields	I-place
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rains	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
1	O
was	O
crossing	O
one	O
of	O
More	O
fields	O
Quarters	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
pull	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
In	O
5	O
Days	O
afterward	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bedlam	O
Wall	O
a	O
tossing	O
up	O
for	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Kelly	O
and	O
Jenkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Coat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
so	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
Berkley	O
's	O
at	O
Cranford	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
received	O
4	O
Guineas	O
of	O
his	O
Steward	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Inn	O
the	O
Rose	O
at	O
Holbourn-bridge	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
being	O
all	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bolt	O
and	O
Tun	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Shoe	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
fell	O
into	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
she	O
led	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
near	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
Liquor	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
spent	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Drams	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
as	O
they	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
were	O
wrapt	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
into	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
mist'em	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Paper	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
wrapt	O
in	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Country	O
Man	O
after	O
her	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
they	O
rais	O
'd	O
a	O
Mob	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
one	O
Guinea	O
fall	O
,	O
another	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
follow	O
me	O
in	O
Doors	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
thrust	O
them	O
down	O
my	O
Bosom	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
struggling	O
together	O
,	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Minute	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
Stairs	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Peircey	I-pers
alias	O
Kelly	B-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
Peircy	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Collar	O
Bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
;	O
and	O
Jones	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquests	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Senior	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Last	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
New	O
Inn	O
Yard	O
by	O
Holywell	B-place
Dunghill	I-place
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
upon	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
People	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
other	O
Soldiers	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Soldier	O
s	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
quarrel	O
with	O
a	O
Baker	O
.	O
The	O
Soldiers	O
took	O
Newsham	O
's	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
People	O
stood	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
fall	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
agree	O
and	O
be	O
Friends	O
;	O
And	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
that	O
advice	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
Bullock	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shall	O
thrash	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Baker	O
and	O
Newsham	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
The	O
Baker	O
was	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
Newsham	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
perceiving	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
help	O
'd	O
up	O
Newsham	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
standing	O
by	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
fair	O
play	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
Son	O
seeing	O
be	O
Collar	O
'd	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
strugling	O
they	O
tumbled	O
one	O
another	O
down	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
the	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Cloths	O
,	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
heap	O
together	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Peircy	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
heap	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Sword	O
or	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Hill	O
after	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Junor	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
and	O
thus	O
added	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
strugling	O
with	O
Jones	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
Peircy	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
did	O
afterwards	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
,	O
for	O
Jones	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
closely	O
engaged	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
Jones	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
young	O
Smith	O
and	O
Jones	O
tumbled	O
down	O
the	O
Hill	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Piercy	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rising	O
again	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Peircy	O
Stab	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
by	O
that	O
Name	O
.	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
shorter	O
and	O
broader	O
than	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Smith	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
.	O
Darby	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
Peircy	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cloths	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
dont	O
very	O
well	O
know	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
besides	O
.	O
He	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
not	O
quite	O
flat	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
within	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
And	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rising	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Arms	O
stretch	O
'd	O
out	O
in	O
this	O
Posture	O
,	O
-	O
Peircy	O
stuck	O
the	O
Bayonet	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Peircy	O
setting	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
waved	O
his	O
Sword	O
(	O
or	O
Bayonet	O
)	O
about	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
People	O
off	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Hand	O
,	O
when	O
Peircy	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
their	O
Arms	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
when	O
the	O
Stab	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
and	O
Smith	O
immediately	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Peircy	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bayonet	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
we	O
wrested	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Jones	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
ten	O
Yards	O
off	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mandit	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
second	O
and	O
third	O
Rib	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
prob	O
'd	O
it	O
5	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
with	O
some	O
such	O
Weapon	O
as	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mortal	O
.	O
Peircy	O
then	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Jones	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
Murder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
Smith	O
and	O
French	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
-	O
Thus	O
Peircy	O
.	O
Then	O
Jones	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
closely	O
engaged	O
with	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
Sword	O
and	O
Stick	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cawary	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Peircy	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
Weapon	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cawdry	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Newsham	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
Brother	O
)	O
was	O
fighting	O
with	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
got	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
their	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
putting	O
on	O
their	O
Cloths	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
Soldier	O
was	O
almost	O
Murder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
towards	O
,	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
brown	O
Cloths	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
now	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Peircy	O
presently	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Weapon	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Col.	O
Rialey	B-pers
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Civil	O
,	O
quite	O
honest	O
Men	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Peircy	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Mackintosh	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sellers	I-pers
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
November	O
12	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sellers	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
carried	O
me	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
several	O
Sodomitical	O
Houses	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
frequented	O
them	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jone	O
's	O
a	O
Tallow-Chandler	O
at	O
the	O
Tobacco	B-place
Roll	I-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
or	O
the	O
3	B-place
Tobacco-Rolls	I-place
know	O
not	O
which	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
(	O
it	O
was	O
since	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
Sodomy	O
)	O
began	O
to	O
scold	O
at	O
Mark	O
Partridge	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
vile	O
Dog	O
,	O
a	O
blowing	O
up	O
Bitch	O
and	O
other	O
ill	O
Names	O
because	O
Partridge	O
had	O
blad	O
'd	O
out	O
something	O
about	O
one	O
Harrington	O
's	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
such	O
Practice	O
.	O
Patridge	O
excus	O
'd	O
himself	O
by	O
telling	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
that	O
Harrington	O
first	O
divulged	O
the	O
Secret	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
well	O
reconcild	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
agreed	O
before	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
pass	O
for	O
Mark	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Husband	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
being	O
too	O
far	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
Oranges	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Maiden	O
Name	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
Orange	O
Deb	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
Lawrence	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
fond	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
hug	O
'd	O
and	O
kissed	O
and	O
employ	O
'd	O
their	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
vile	O
Manner	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
my	O
Breeches	O
thrust	O
his	O
Tongue	O
into	O
my	O
mouth	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
40	O
Mile	O
enjoy	O
me	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
refusing	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sit	O
bare	O
in	O
my	O
Lap	O
upon	O
which	O
Partridge	O
snatch	O
'd	O
a	O
red	O
hot	O
pocker	O
out	O
he	O
Fire	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
arse	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Bed-follows	O
;	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
Child	O
and	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clap	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
procur	O
'd	O
and	O
encourag	O
'd	O
Persons	O
to	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
and	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
in	O
Field-Lane	B-place
,	O
Holbourn	B-place
.	O
I	O
found	O
near	O
Men	O
Fifty	O
there	O
,	O
making	O
Love	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
they	O
'd	O
sit	O
in	O
one	O
anothers	O
Laps	O
,	O
use	O
their	O
Hands	O
indecently	O
Dance	O
and	O
make	O
Curtsies	O
and	O
mimick	O
the	O
Language	O
of	O
Women	O
-	O
O	O
Sir	O
!	O
-	O
Pray	O
Sir	O
!	O
-	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
!	O
Lord	O
how	O
can	O
ye	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
!	O
-	O
Ah	O
ye	O
little	O
dear	O
Toad	O
!	O
Then	O
they	O
'd	O
go	O
by	O
Couples	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
to	O
be	O
marry	O
'd	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
at	O
that	O
Room	O
was	O
kept	O
by	O
-	O
Ecclestone	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
body	O
from	O
balking	O
their	O
Diversions	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
brag	O
in	O
plain	O
Terms	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
Liquors	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
-	O
Griffin	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
since	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
Derwin	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Martins	I-pers
for	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
brag	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
baffled	O
the	O
Link	O
Boy	O
's	O
Evidence	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
boasted	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Derwin	O
's	O
Favour	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Means	O
of	O
bringing	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Sundays	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Practices	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
talk	O
'd	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
and	O
most	O
vile	O
Obscenity	O
in	O
her	O
Presence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
wonderfully	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sellers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
and	O
added	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
there	O
were	O
above	O
40	O
Sodomies	O
commited	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
Darwin	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
considered	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
ever	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
abonsinable	O
Practices	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
and	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patrick	B-pers
Malcolme	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Committing	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Pokins	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
17	O
.	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
has	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Pokins	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
Tokins	O
had	O
committed	O
several	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
being	O
hang	O
'd	O
had	O
provided	O
a	O
Master	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Sea	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
one	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
wheedle	O
Pokins	O
to	O
discover	O
who	O
this	O
Captain	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
prevent	O
his	O
being	O
sent	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
softly	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
Expectation	O
of	O
hearing	O
some	O
Discourse	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
Nature	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Witness	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
several	O
Expressions	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
repeated	O
,	O
which	O
strongly	O
implied	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
committing	O
Sodomy	O
together	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
trembled	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pokins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
Mistress	O
was	O
perjur	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
Foot	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
Side	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
Husband	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
a	O
careful	O
Father	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
pretende	O
'd	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Women	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
-	O
Many	O
of	O
his	O
male	O
bedfellows	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
such	O
incivilities	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Johnson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Macadame	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sows	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bistrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gettings	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Terence	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Principle	O
Witnesses	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Hats	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
Henry	O
Hill	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
an	O
old	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
difficult	O
in	O
his	O
Choice	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
buying	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
mist	O
.	O
-	O
Owen	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
Hats	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
which	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
borough	O
-	O
Penn	O
,	O
a	O
Quaker	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
.	O
-	O
Penn	O
produced	O
three	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Oath	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
Owen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
swore	O
that	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
Hats	O
he	O
lost	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Correl	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmines	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
Mary	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
was	O
convicted	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hartrey	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Emmines	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Gales	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Bawd	O
)	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cosins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
5	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anna	B-pers
Marie	I-pers
Caton	I-pers
June	O
2	O
.	O
Anna	O
Maria	O
Caton	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
lodged	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
made	O
a	O
common	O
Practice	O
of	O
lending	O
Goods	O
to	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Swearing	O
they	O
Stole	O
them	O
.	O
Eleaner	O
Emerson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Ship	O
to	O
Father	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
upon	O
Captain	O
of	O
Wrangham	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
allow	O
her	O
for	O
its	O
Maintenance	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
doing	O
,	O
she	O
flew	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
a	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
Eyes	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
so	O
heartily	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
all	O
over	O
Black	O
and	O
Blue	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
Swear	O
against	O
the	O
Captain	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
another	O
Woman	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
her	O
-	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
Ann	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
Married	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Sweethearts	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
Oath	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
these	O
very	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
now	O
stands	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Swore	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
its	O
well	O
known	O
,	O
she	O
makes	O
no	O
Conscience	O
of	O
Swearing	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
July	O
6	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vanderanker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
June	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kelf	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Mans	O
Apparel	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
came	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
I	O
shoew	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
together	O
upon	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
empty	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
consider	O
'd	O
that	O
my	O
Drawers	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
were	O
unlock	O
'd	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Cloths	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
were	O
gone	O
and	O
my	O
Cloths	O
too	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Bramton	O
Park	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Ale	O
House	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
fell	O
into	O
discourse	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
3	O
been	O
acquainted	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Lodging	O
to	O
let	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
us	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Drawers	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Women	O
her	O
Cloths	O
;	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
it	O
seem	O
the	O
Women	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
indeed	O
call	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Sister	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
Jest	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
Strangers	O
to	O
me	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Ravishing	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
.	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
(	O
his	O
own	O
Daughter	O
,	O
)	O
aged	O
11	O
Years	O
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
Ravish	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Boot	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Nurse	O
Stevens	O
at	O
my	O
Aunts	O
House	O
in	O
Tyburn	B-place
Road	I-place
.	O
My	O
Father	O
took	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
sometimes	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
lockt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
my	O
Nurse	O
,	O
Come	O
Mrs.	O
Best	O
I	O
'll	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
so	O
will	O
I	O
too	O
says	O
my	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
Doors	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
Father	O
came	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
privy	O
Parts	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
much	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Free	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Aunt	O
and	O
my	O
Nurse	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
old-Mistress	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
Weeks	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Childs	O
Mistress	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
was	O
kept	O
upon	O
Charity	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
to	O
learn	O
Needle	O
Work	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
disorder	O
in	O
her	O
Linnen	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gauld	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Nurse	O
Stevens	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
For	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
Examine	O
the	O
matter	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
torn	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
where	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Penetration	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
running	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
be	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
foul	O
Disease	O
.	O
Neither	O
the	O
Aunt	O
,	O
the	O
Nurse	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
appearing	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
light	O
into	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pitchard	I-pers
June	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lucy	B-pers
Dumming	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Riley	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brewers	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
to	O
Miss	O
.	O
Loveday	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Ball	I-place
Ale	I-place
house	I-place
in	O
King	B-place
Street	I-place
St.	I-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
Friday	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
Purse	O
with	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Loveday	O
advis	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Nap	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
Bed	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Purse	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
waked	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
throughly	O
waked	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
out	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
about	O
10	O
l	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
the	O
Indictment	O
but	O
for	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
being	O
willing	O
rather	O
to	O
charge	O
less	O
than	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
for	O
Lucy	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
Lodged	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
came	O
a	O
Charing	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lovedays	O
;	O
So	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
loss	O
that	O
Night	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
fuddled	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
seeing	O
Lucy	O
,	O
I	O
still	O
said	O
nothing	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
People	O
are	O
apt	O
to	O
talk	O
and	O
make	O
things	O
worse	O
than	O
they	O
are	O
-	O
For	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Loveday	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
then	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
Lucy	O
ask	O
'd	O
Charity	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
merry	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Well	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
and	O
then	O
too	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
howsoever	O
I	O
saw	O
Lucy	O
a	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
Mothers	O
Door	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
as	O
fine	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
a	O
Husband	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
hours	O
after	O
my	O
Pocket	O
was	O
Pick	O
'd	O
.	O
Ah	O
Lucy	O
!	O
Lucy	O
!	O
thinks	O
I.	O
that	O
Husband	O
that	O
wedding	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
them	O
new	O
Cloths	O
were	O
all	O
bought	O
with	O
my	O
Mercy	O
ye	O
wicked	O
Jade	O
you	O
'	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
neither	O
-	O
But	O
in	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Loveday	O
,	O
and	O
sits	O
,	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
in	O
comes	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
Lucy	O
yonder	O
has	O
gotten	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hardly	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
the	O
other	O
Day	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
well	O
if	O
she	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Iy	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
e'en	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Loveday	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
fuddled	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Lucy	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
washing	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
Girl	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
'd	O
fain	O
have	O
to	O
hire	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
Aye	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
pay	O
her	O
Wages	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Earnest	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Take	O
the	O
Money	O
Lucy	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
too	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
Sleep	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Lucy	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Well	O
go	O
Girl	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
sit	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
be	O
'll	O
be	O
a	O
sleep	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
may	O
come	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Sider	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
But	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
No	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
is	O
of	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
be	O
borrow	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Security	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Mackgwyer	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Brother	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
drinking	O
plentifully	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
too	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
her	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
:	O
Her	O
Mother	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Lucy	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
small	O
Legacy	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
Brook	O
the	O
Watchman	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mackgwyers	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
the	O
Baker	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
be	O
Married	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
Yes	O
.	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
Married	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Loveday	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
Shilling	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
(	O
with	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lampton	I-pers
)	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
large	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Household	O
Goods	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brown	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
)	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
)	O
.	O
Household	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
John	B-pers
Vanwick	I-pers
was	O
here	O
convicted	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Topping	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
They	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
did	O
receive	O
six	O
pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
(	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
)	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mackever	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackintosh	I-pers
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
Willis	O
and	O
Stevenson	O
the	O
Constables	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Sodomites	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
agreed	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
one	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
'd	O
wait	O
at	O
a	O
proper	O
Distance	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
that	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-home	O
and	O
parts	O
the	O
upper	O
Field	O
from	O
the	O
middle	O
I	O
knew	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Place	O
that	O
Sodomites	O
frequented	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Methods	O
they	O
took	O
in	O
picking	O
one	O
another	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
So	O
I	O
takes	O
a	O
Turn	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
passes	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
looks	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
stands	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
moves	O
higher	O
and	O
higher	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
stood	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
Tis	O
a	O
fine	O
Night	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
Then	O
he	O
takes	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
I	O
shewing	O
no	O
dislike	O
)	O
he	O
guides	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
puts	O
his	O
Privities	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
Companions	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
up	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
-	O
Wright	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
-	O
Willis	O
and	O
Stevenson	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
asked	O
why	O
he	O
made	O
such	O
an	O
Offer	O
to	O
Newton	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Crime	O
in	O
making	O
what	O
use	O
I	O
please	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
across	O
the	O
Fields	O
he	O
stood	O
up	O
only	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
,	O
Newton	O
came	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
on	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
a	O
kind	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
loved	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Women	O
better	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Sex	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Muggleston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
9.	O
Edward	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brakes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Claxon	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
also	O
convicted	O
Capitally	O
,	O
but	O
dy	O
'd	O
before	O
Judgement	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Strickland	B-pers
Beadles	I-pers
William	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
4.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Clark	O
,	O
Isabel	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
36.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
Sarah	B-pers
Darbon	I-pers
Patrick	B-pers
Macdermont	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Phillip	B-pers
Vanham	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
Christian	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Pally	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Masley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vanderanker	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Kelf	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Mackintosh	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
near	O
Bloomsbury	O
Square	O
,	O
pay	O
a	O
fine	O
of	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
one	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
pay	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clap	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
Smith	O
field	O
,	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
two	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Muggleston	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
Palace-Yard	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
suffer	O
one	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
