TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1726	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
.	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Farringdon	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Ballet	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
David	B-pers
Tough	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
William	B-pers
Plimpton	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Huntly	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Arthurs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
William	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Elisha	B-pers
Impy	I-pers
Allen	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Aubrey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
John	B-pers
Row	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Bagwell	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
47	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	O
Milton	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Milton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
22	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
my	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
before	O
Easter	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
7	O
l.	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
keeping	O
it	O
secret	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
the	O
sooner	O
discover	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
how	O
much	O
Money	O
was	O
then	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
mist	O
3	O
Guineas	O
more	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
had	O
for	O
sometime	O
past	O
pretended	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
Sermon	O
Time	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sunday	O
present	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
several	O
Picklock-Keys	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Doors	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Purse	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
10	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
-	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
this	O
Confession	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Agony	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
own	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
hang	O
'd	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
prevented	O
from	O
doing	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
effectually	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
Sweetheart	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
China	O
Bed-Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
belonging	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Pump	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Noe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Custhouse	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-street	I-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
.	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stoln	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
run	O
.	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Hedge-lane	O
,	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
him	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Miriam	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Hashfield	O
,	O
70	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ferret	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
70	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Thousand	O
of	O
Pins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
1	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
4	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Bibs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hashfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hashfield	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
once	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Day	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
)	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
-	O
Now	O
,	O
it	O
so	O
fell	O
out	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Loin	O
of	O
Veal	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
but	O
down	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Wife	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Ring	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Thousand	O
of	O
Pins	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
would	O
open	O
all	O
our	O
Drawers	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ridley	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
near	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Ridley	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
not	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
's	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hitherto	O
born	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	O
Farmer	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	O
Farmer	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Tankard	O
about	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
I	O
procur	O
'd	O
Warnings	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
distributed	O
among	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
I	O
quickly	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Well-Close-Square	B-place
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Tankard	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
my	O
File	O
of	O
Warnings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
exactly	O
described	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
soon	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
Clerk	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
William	O
-	O
and	O
what	O
besides	O
William	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Clerk	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
stood	O
still	O
.	O
-	O
Wherfore	O
the	O
Clerk	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
William	O
Still	O
in	O
the	O
Mutimus	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
yet	O
know	O
his	O
true	O
Name	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
,	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
and	O
positive	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	O
Lovell	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Stuff-Boxes	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
8	O
Silver	O
Medals	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
Gold	O
Toothpick	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
Stone	O
Studs	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
Diamond	O
.	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
Stone	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
8	O
Gold	O
Lockets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
23	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
64	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
2	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
4	O
Strings	O
of	O
Pearl	O
for	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
8	O
Smelling	O
Bottles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
Gold	O
Enamel	O
'd	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
Stone	O
Rings	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Picture	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Head	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
Watch	O
Chains	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
5	O
Silver	O
Seissar-Cases	O
,	O
5	O
Silver	O
Needle-Cases	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spunge-Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye-Tavern	O
,	O
just	O
without	B-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
into	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
Drink	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Show-Glass	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
how	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
carried	O
off	O
undiscover	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
open	O
publick	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
Enquirys	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
sor't	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
drinking	O
along	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Customers	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Nap	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
somebody	O
knocks	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
-	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
-	O
Why	O
its	O
I	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
-	O
What	O
d	O
'ye	O
went	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
-	O
Can	O
ye	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
Hannah	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Rings	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
that	O
this	O
Hannah	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Flows	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
besides	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
Day	O
at	O
Bess	B-pers
Dammeree	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Clare	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
House	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
Mother	O
Dammeree	O
's	O
.	O
Brown	O
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clare	O
(	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Crooked-Billet	O
and	O
Sugar-Loaf	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
)	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
Mother	O
Dammeree	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
Side	O
,	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ticken	O
Breeches	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
2	O
Rings	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
-	O
Bishop	O
another	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
sent	O
Word	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
3	O
Rings	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
lately	O
come	O
,	O
over	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Brother	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Hatter	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
Noon	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
Child	O
,	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
again	O
for	O
Ireland	O
.	O
-	O
From	O
our	O
House	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mother	O
Dammeree	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Next	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
spent	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
and	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
spent	O
8	O
l.	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Rings	O
and	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
my	O
new	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
Weeks	O
Lodging	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
hid	O
behind	O
a	O
Picture	O
.	O
We	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pockets	O
loaded	O
with	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Chains	O
,	O
and	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
-	O
Whereupon	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Kinsman	O
had	O
got	O
so	O
many	O
fine	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
and	O
a	O
Night	O
's	O
Time	O
,	O
Why	O
then	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
nor	O
she	O
Mony	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
ten	O
Pence	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
lets	O
go	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Riches	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
lodges	O
.	O
So	O
up	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
an	O
old	O
Picture	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
hid	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Snuff	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bess	B-pers
Dammeree	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
my	O
Kinsman	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
above	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Kinsman	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Hustling	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suppose	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Mauxes	O
were	O
a	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
slipt	O
on	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
those	O
Breeches	O
we	O
found	O
more	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
round	O
Holywel-Mount	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
near	O
Holywel-Lane	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
standing	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
Posture	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
almost	O
between	O
his	O
Legs	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
imagine	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
laid	O
himself	O
all	O
along	O
upon	O
something	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
off	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
rise	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Box	O
under	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
Manner	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
proffered	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Friend	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
only	O
to	O
watch	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
called	O
another	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
who	O
was	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
empty-handed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
waiting	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Case	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
just	O
now	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
has	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
turned	O
upside	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
afterwards	O
get	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bridget	O
-	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Glass	O
Case	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Cheapned	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bollam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
22	O
Guineas	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
sold	O
an	O
old	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
his	O
Beds	O
Tester	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
own	O
Son	O
)	O
were	O
great	O
Cronies	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
had	O
hid	O
his	O
Treasure	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	O
Walker	O
,	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
bought	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Thing	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
by	O
a	O
Miracle	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Body	O
may	O
say	O
;	O
for	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Floor	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Man	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
some	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
peeps	O
up	O
this	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
over	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
should	O
he	O
see	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
but	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
up	O
he	O
comes	O
,	O
and	O
tells	O
me	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
:	O
We	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
soon	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Kelham	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Susan	O
Kelham	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
from	O
near	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
in	O
Red-Cross-Street	B-place
,	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
her	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
having	O
her	O
Necklace	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
missing	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
was	O
found	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
,	O
without	O
its	O
Necklace	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
Post-Office-Yard	B-place
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
sneaking	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Tortoise	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
William	I-pers
Deards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deards	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
between	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
mistrust	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
Yesterday	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Ring	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Workmen	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
that	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
Information	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
Tortoise-Shell	O
Snuff-Box	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Cane	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sweeping	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
Penknife	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Mistress	O
lent	O
him	O
to	O
cut	O
some	O
Cords	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Cane	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
out	O
to	O
walk	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Heydon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Easter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
my	O
Landlady	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
Landlord	O
Johnson	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
:	O
He	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
Mistrusted	O
Nothing	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
no	O
sooner	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Drawers	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
my	O
Money	O
bag	O
was	O
empty	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Rings	O
and	O
my	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
too	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Beadle	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
some	O
Constables	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Feathers	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
some	O
Women	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Whores	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Snuff-boxes	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Bear-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Tap-house	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
Whores	O
come	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
plunder	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Tap	O
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
my	O
Care	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
still	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
and	O
lye	O
at	O
the	O
Bell-Savage-Inn	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
Charge	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
from	O
Monmouth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
as	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
Charity	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
till	O
the	O
Night	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bureau	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
at	O
the	O
Bear-Inn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
my	O
silver	O
Salt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Snuff-box	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
;	O
besides	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fawdery	I-pers
,	O
60	O
l.	O
of	O
Allom	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fawdery	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
And	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fawdery	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
lurking	O
about	O
my	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
a	O
Man	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
a	O
Lump	O
of	O
Allom	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines-lane	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Cellar	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
it	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
and	O
57	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	O
Ferry	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Perry	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
and	I-place
Magpye	I-place
Ale-house	I-place
,	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Guineas	O
for	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Seat	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
no	O
Lock	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
busy	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
we	O
afterwards	O
found	O
)	O
took	O
that	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
advertiz	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
Post	O
,	O
of	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
April	O
26.	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
I	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Duke-Street	O
,	O
Picadilly	O
;	O
and	O
got	O
between	O
40	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
me	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sarch	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Germain-street	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
Ruffles	O
set	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him-Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
some	O
Scarlet	O
Camblet	O
for	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
.	O
-	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
view	O
my	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Sword	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
indifferent	O
Rigging	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
from	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Which	O
Way	O
,	O
Says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
from	O
Dublin	O
to	O
Cork	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
West-Chester	O
:	O
But	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
without	O
better	O
Apparel	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
I	O
disagreed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
how	O
many	O
Yards	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Suit	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
exactly	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
call	O
down	O
my	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shall	O
take	O
Measure	O
of	O
ye	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
quickly	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Play	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
pray	O
let	O
the	O
Ruffels	O
be	O
set	O
upon	O
my	O
Shirt	O
time	O
enough	O
.	O
-	O
Have	O
ye	O
ne'er	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
or	O
Tavern	O
here-abouts	O
.	O
Yes	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Tavern	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
cameback	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Mountain	O
.	O
-	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
send	O
for	O
none	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
Pint	O
over	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
lye	O
upon	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
fall	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
counting	O
it	O
over	O
before	O
Witness	O
,	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
40	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
my	O
Spark	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
Weekly	O
Journal	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
thinking	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Webster	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
-	O
Well	O
,	O
then	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
will	O
ye	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Webster	O
,	O
he	O
read	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
Pause	O
,	O
he	O
consented	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Webster	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Webster	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
having	O
left	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
the	O
Father	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
advertise	O
for	O
his	O
Son	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
expos	O
'd	O
as	O
little	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
I	O
suppose	O
upon	O
reading	O
this	O
Advertisement	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Sarch	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
right	O
Person	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
suspicious	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
his	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
privately	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Sarch	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
some	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
News	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
Servant	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
's	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
do	O
you	O
pretend	O
to	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
thus	O
he	O
brazen	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
Money	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
since	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
this	O
time	O
12	O
Month	O
,	O
try	O
'd	O
at	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guineas	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Gilburn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Unicorn	O
in	O
Aylsbury	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
likewise	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
In	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Box	O
;	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
were	O
but	O
little	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
wearing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
upon	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
Dennis	O
Foxon	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Foxon	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Clothes	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
dead	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
4	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
7	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
Draper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
2	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Gill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
12	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
again	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Groove	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Shutters	O
was	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Shutters	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sashes	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
which	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Maid	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
added	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Claridge	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
this	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
cut	O
the	O
Groove	O
,	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shutters	O
and	O
the	O
Saines	O
,	O
crept	O
in	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
Blewet	O
and	O
Burnworth	O
were	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
Chains	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Claridge	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cherry	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
Linnen	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Claxton	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Cherry	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Claridge	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
that	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
stoln	O
.	O
Claxton	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Claridge	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
thereabout	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
that	O
requir	O
'd	O
an	O
earnest	O
Concern	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Flusterating	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Laughing	O
and	O
a	O
Talking	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
Claridge	O
was	O
all	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
Rob	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
preparation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
was	O
wrenched	O
open	O
with	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Weapon	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
conversed	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cherry	O
was	O
perfectly	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
after	O
Claridge	O
had	O
made	O
preparation	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Margan	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
Claxton	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
honest	O
Care	O
for	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
Others	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
sold	O
Oranges	O
.	O
Cucumbers	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
.	O
That	O
Cherry	O
lived	O
in	O
Falconers	O
Alley	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
Claxton	O
in	O
Frying	O
Pan	O
Ally	O
Tunmill	O
.	O
Street	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Claridge	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Robbery	O
but	O
Cherry	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
Claxton	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Cherry	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Onion	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ignon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Steel	O
Seals	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
sell	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sometimes	O
a	O
Customer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Daughter	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
hanging	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
behind	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Smoaking	O
a	O
Pipe	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Hoop	O
and	O
my	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
threw	O
in	O
the	O
Cradle	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
leaving	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
yet	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
presently	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
Apron	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
of	O
yours	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cluff	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
5	O
Shirts	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jordon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jordon	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
lye	O
from	O
home	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
advis	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Cunning	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cunning	O
Woman	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
Thief	O
in	O
a	O
Weeks	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
the	O
Cunning	O
Woman	O
had	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
and	O
this	O
gave	O
them	O
such	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
takes	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
begins	O
to	O
carechise	O
her	O
;	O
Hannah	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
Conjururing	O
Woman	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
describ	O
'd	O
you	O
so	O
exactly	O
,	O
that	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
can	O
come	O
nigher	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
you	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
ye	O
will	O
Confess	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
expose	O
you	O
;	O
She	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
Protested	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
signified	O
nothing	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
cunning	O
Woman	O
had	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Confess	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
in	O
Plumb	O
Tree	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Soal	O
Leather	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Customer	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
honestly	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
reduc	O
'd	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
immediately	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
testified	O
that	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
consideration	O
of	O
her	O
extreme	O
Sickness	O
and	O
Poverty	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
immediately	O
corected	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Garlick-hith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Service	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
Scower	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
abroad	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
was	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
within	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
knockt	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
before	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
directly	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
quickly	O
found	O
my	O
Drawers	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
them	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
willfull	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Yard	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
to	O
dry	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Granfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Granfield	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
washt	O
my	O
Gown	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
my	O
Landladys	O
Celler	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
Landlady	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
my	O
Gown	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mattison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
140	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ashmelay	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ashmelay	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Albemarle-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
Rooms	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Villars-Court	B-place
;	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
my	O
Key	O
upon	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Warnings	O
among	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
stopt	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
broken	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Brick-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Hyde-Park-Corner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
more	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Ashmelay	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
finding	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
small	O
Beer	O
for	O
the	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Buckles	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bring'em	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Totemham-High-Cross	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Field	O
at	O
Totemham	B-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
exactly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
him	O
about	O
Five	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
-	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
-	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
meeting	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Wood	O
,	O
I	O
required	O
of	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
Gelding	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
a	O
top	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
pray	O
'	O
e	O
Friend	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
he	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
subscribed	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
of	O
I	O
ghest	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
farther	O
Information	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
know	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
brings	O
Fish	O
from	O
Billinsgate	O
to	O
Totenham	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
sure	O
how	O
matters	O
might	O
fall	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
this	O
Gelding	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Caldecot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
reprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Majesty	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Caldecot	I-pers
;	O
and	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
sign	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
half	O
his	O
Mark	O
;	O
but	O
somebody	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Confess	O
and	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
undone	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Caldecot	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Gelding	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Monoy	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Monmouth-Street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Called	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
no	O
Drams	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
drink	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
well	O
and	O
good	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
comes	O
among	O
with	O
a	O
Puppy	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
an	O
old	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
this	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Soldier	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
the	O
Puppy	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
a	O
Six-Pence	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Fathings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
presently	O
clapt	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
But	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Shilling	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
gain	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
.	O
Harry	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
Month	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Gold	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
-	O
but	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
often	O
enticed	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
would	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
dropt	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mosley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Dumeny	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	O
Dumeny	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
May	O
Michael	B-pers
Dumeny	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Hosiers	O
Shop	O
near	O
the	O
Bear	O
Tavern	O
in	O
York	B-place
Buildings	I-place
.I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
on	O
Sunday	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
Wife	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
-	O
My	O
Maid	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
at	O
some	O
Pawn	O
brokers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hodderds	O
,	O
In	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
accidentally	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
near	O
Northumberland	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
intimate	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
your	O
Servant	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
you	O
lay	O
Felony	O
to	O
my	O
Charge	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
'll	O
secure	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
struggled	O
hard	O
and	O
broke	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Spring	O
Garden	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Web	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
and	O
several	O
pursuing	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
trip	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
in	O
Spring	O
Garden	O
;	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Fit	O
of	O
Jealousie	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Mosely	O
,	O
alias	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
alias	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
alias	O
t'other	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
what	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hoddard	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Maid	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
offer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
bade	O
her	O
tell	O
her	O
Master	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
such	O
Goods	O
already	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Stockings	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
trusted	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dumeny	O
was	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
sold	O
him	O
any	O
Stockings	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
from	O
her	O
upon	O
any	O
Account	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Ellinbarkers	O
a	O
Stay	O
Maker	O
,	O
in	O
Hart	O
Street	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
was	O
Seven-night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dumeny	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Gown	O
and	O
Slippers	O
.	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dumeny	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dumeny	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
bade	O
me	O
give	O
this	O
Service	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
engaged	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
wait	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wondred	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Dumeny	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
-	O
He	O
sent	O
word	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
clean	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dumeny	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dumenys	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Gown	O
and	O
foul	O
Shirt	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dumeny	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Yes	O
Madam	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
-	O
Pray	O
them	O
says	O
she	O
give	O
my	O
Service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
this	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
six	O
Pair	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
flat	O
square	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
writ	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
Scarlet	O
,	O
Grey	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
Mens	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Barrack	O
Master	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Place	O
worth	O
about	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
turn	O
'd	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Dumeny	O
was	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
an	O
Orange	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Play-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eccleton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Dumeny	O
for	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
an	O
Orange	O
Woman	O
,	O
added	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
Drinking	O
a	O
Bottle	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
then	O
Adams	O
.	O
-	O
Several	O
Irish	O
Evidence	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Kenneday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ossend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Camblet	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
Fire	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James's-street	I-place
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
1	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	O
Spencer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
both	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margery	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
3	O
Smocks	O
,	O
4	O
Towels	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kind	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Grimsham	I-pers
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shag	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Punch-Bowl	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Drinking-Glasses	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Byars	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Totemham	B-place
Highcross	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Womens	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
May	O
16th	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
contest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barnel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bryar	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bryar	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Yesterday	O
Morning	O
about	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
Fish-street-hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
follow	O
'd	O
'em	O
.	O
and	O
stood	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
pretty	O
busy	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
presently	O
threw	O
her	O
Apron	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
step	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
East-Cheep	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
the	O
Sword	O
them	O
.	O
However	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Dorfille	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Letar	O
's	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Peter	O
Dorfille	O
,	O
married	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Noye	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
married	O
at	O
the	O
Elephant	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Thomas	O
Bishop	O
.	O
-	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
the	O
Thing	O
was	O
managed	O
very	O
oddly	O
,	O
for	O
upon	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
serv	O
'd	O
a	O
Warrant	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
advis	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
together	O
.	O
Dorfille	O
's	O
Landlord	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
for	O
2	O
Years	O
while	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sometimes	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Commissary	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Receipts	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sometimes	O
would	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
love	O
him	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
weakly	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
rather	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Dorfille	O
's	O
right	O
Name	O
is	O
Brookman	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Dorfille	O
and	O
Defonelle	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
14	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Letart	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
be	O
debauch	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
proving	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
sometimes	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
marry	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
promis	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
be	O
contented	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
maintain	O
her	O
handsomely	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
the	O
least	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
Her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Tool	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
lying	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
Manner	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
away	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
Condition	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Brass-Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Byerly	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Cotton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
Gelding	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
into	O
James	O
Prosser	O
's	O
Grounds	O
,	O
at	O
Highgate	B-place
and	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Thomas	O
Richmonds	O
,	O
at	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
Saddle	O
,	O
a	O
Halter	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Shoos	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stoln	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
Man	O
cheapned	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
for	O
three	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
paid	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Larford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Thorogood	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Fish-pond	O
,	O
a	O
Carp	O
,	O
a	O
Tench	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gudgeon	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7.	O
William	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Horse	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
Judgment	O
was	O
then	O
respited	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
3.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
3.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
23.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
,	O
Miriam	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cluff	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kenneday	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kind	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Landford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
WHereas	O
it	O
was	O
inserted	O
by	O
mistake	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Broadbent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
by	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
certify	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Broadbent	I-pers
was	O
not	O
committed	O
by	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
in	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
of	O
any	O
itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hick's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
purging	O
and	O
plain	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Remedy	O
generally	O
successful	O
in	O
easing	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
of	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Just	O
Published	O
.	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Collection	O
of	O
Remarkable	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
near	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
past	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
and	O
their	O
Speeches	O
.	O
Faithfully	O
collected	O
from	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Tryals	O
,	O
and	O
Papers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wikes	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Locrain	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
of	O
New	O
gate	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
Printing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
Authentick	O
Narratives	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Brotherton	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
over-against	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
.	O
THe	O
Town	O
being	O
still	O
imposed	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
publick	O
Prints	O
daily	O
cramm	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
fulsome	O
Praises	O
of	O
installible	O
Specificks	O
Arcausa	O
's	O
,	O
Italian	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Quack	O
Medicines	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
necessary	O
to	O
cuadios	O
the	O
wary	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
to	O
Danger	O
that	O
she	O
judicious	O
Part	O
of	O
Mankind	O
should	O
be	O
deceived	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Why	O
are	O
these	O
Medicines	O
exposed	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Toys	O
Shops	O
,	O
unless	O
to	O
skreen	O
the	O
Preparets	O
of	O
such	O
notorious	O
Cheats	O
from	O
the	O
Resentment	O
of	O
injured	O
People	O
?	O
Are	O
the	O
best	O
Physicians	O
,	O
or	O
most	O
emineant	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
ashamed	O
of	O
their	O
Prescriptions	O
and	O
Preparations	O
?	O
Must	O
the	O
severe	O
Affiction	O
of	O
an	O
Impostor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
induce	O
Men	O
to	O
ruin	O
their	O
Constitutions	O
?	O
Can	O
we	O
believe	O
that	O
Charity	O
for	O
others	O
deplorable	O
Circumstances	O
will	O
prevail	O
on	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
to	O
publish	O
what	O
he	O
dare	O
not	O
own	O
?	O
Are	O
not	O
the	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Veneral	O
Disease	O
various	O
?	O
Are	O
not	O
Mens	O
Constitutions	O
vastly	O
different	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
ever	O
a	O
Remedy	O
always	O
infalliable	O
?	O
Do	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
agree	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
prove	O
Poison	O
to	O
another	O
?	O
Or	O
are	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Number	O
of	O
able	O
and	O
experienced	O
Physicians	O
and	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
who	O
practice	O
in	O
Publick	O
,	O
and	O
whole	O
Credit	O
depend	O
upon	O
their	O
skill	O
and	O
Success	O
?	O
The	O
most	O
ingenious	O
Prescription	O
may	O
sometimes	O
fail	O
:	O
And	O
will	O
any	O
one	O
depend	O
upon	O
he	O
Apparatus	O
or	O
an	O
unknown	O
Author	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
sees	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
consults	O
your	O
Distemper	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
sufficiently	O
cheated	O
you	O
,	O
will	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
some	O
able	O
Surgeon	O
?	O
Shall	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Mesery	O
incline-him	O
to	O
be	O
tredulous	O
,	O
and	O
prevail	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
more	O
miserable	O
?	O
Or	O
can	O
any	O
one	O
foolishly	O
fear	O
that	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
will	O
expose	O
his	O
Patraent	O
?	O
For	O
your	O
own	O
Sales	O
,	O
therefore	O
apply	O
to	O
some	O
Man	O
of	O
Kills	O
and	O
Probity	O
who	O
appears	O
to	O
justify	O
his	O
Practice	O
,	O
and	O
answer	O
for	O
its	O
Success	O
;	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
invites	O
you	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
Right-hand	O
in	O
Crane-Court	O
near	O
Feter	O
:	O
Lane	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
a	O
Golden	O
Heart	O
and	O
Lamp	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
most	O
.	O
Degree	O
of	O
that	O
unhappy	O
Disease	O
,	O
will	O
receieve	O
you	O
to	O
Health	O
and	O
Vigour	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
securely	O
,	O
without	O
Salivation	O
.	O
Enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
may	O
he	O
advised	O
with	O
any	O
Morning	O
till	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
Three	O
to	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
(	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mistakes	O
)	O
take	O
Notice	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Hand	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
by	O
William	O
.	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Anns	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Four	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
