TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1726.	O
in	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
George	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
John	B-pers
Frate	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
Williams	B-pers
Thame	I-pers
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sams	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrele	I-pers
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rumbale	I-pers
Sarah	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
(	O
a	O
boy	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
two	O
Holland	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
pence	O
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
near	B-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
'd	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
belonging	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Sadly	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
2	O
Holland	O
Doits	O
and	O
18	O
Pence	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
seeing	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
!	O
The	O
Woman	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Holland	O
Pieces	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
18	O
Pence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
calling	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Boy	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
Woman	O
too	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
which	O
of	O
'em	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
spoken	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
accord	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
wicked	O
young	O
Rogue	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
rob	O
'd	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
Copper	O
Pieces	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
cleared	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Club	O
,	O
the	O
Feathers	O
in	O
Watling	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Shift	O
to	O
get	O
drunk	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Club	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
While	O
Page	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
Page	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
no	O
such	O
doings	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
,	O
Says	O
he	O
.	O
Mean	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
ye	O
pick	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
open	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
3	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
persuading	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
borrowed	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rashfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
thus	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Bains	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Bundle	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
on	O
Fish	O
Street-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Sale	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
.	O
These	O
2	O
Parcels	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
at	O
Church-yard	B-place
Stairs	I-place
near	O
the	O
Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
the	O
Boat	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
Return	O
the	O
Boat	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Overies	O
Stairs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
carried	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Rashfield	O
,	O
who	O
delivered	O
'em	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Bines	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
'em	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Field	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
'em	O
3	O
Pounds	O
for	O
what	O
was	O
worth	O
about	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
'em	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
Lock	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
speak	O
with	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Crown	O
,	O
meaning	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
Steal	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
being	O
spread	O
among	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
;	O
and	O
Bines	O
and	O
Rice	O
having	O
pledged	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Growns	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
in	O
Worcester	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
Southwark	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
impeached	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bucknall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
September	O
2	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Hand	O
reach	O
my	O
Hat	O
from	O
a	O
back	O
Seat	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Barefoot	O
followed	O
the	O
Thief	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Barefoot	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
insufficient	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
quitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marjoram	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elias	I-pers
Huggady	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Butchers	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
Shillings	O
and	O
6	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
19	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
more	O
Butchers	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Fellows	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Charter-house-street	O
and	O
followed	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
felt	O
my	O
Apron-strings	O
cut	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Steel	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Yonder	O
goes	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
cut	O
your	O
Apron-string	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
your	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Butchers	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
behind	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apron-string	O
,	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Steel	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
'em	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
to	O
piss	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
my	O
Brother	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Apron-string	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
only	O
playing	O
the	O
Rogue	O
in	O
Jest	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
presently	O
offer	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Blewit	O
and	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
Week	O
out	O
of	O
Goal	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waist-coat	O
value	O
30	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
Shillings	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Collier	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms-Tavern	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
fuddled	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
whither	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
with	O
my	O
self	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
somewhere	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
without	O
either	O
Hat	O
or	O
Wig	O
,	O
or	O
Coat	O
or	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
mortal	O
Dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Sky	O
above	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Amazement	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Where	O
am	O
I	O
?	O
In	O
the	O
World	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
lookt	O
a	O
little	O
lower	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
tops	O
of	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
be	O
thought	O
my	O
self	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
some	O
Town	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
Alley	O
without	O
any	O
Clothes	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
though	O
still	O
I	O
was	O
strangely	O
confounded	O
to	O
think	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
upon	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
quickly	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Street	O
that	O
lookt	O
a	O
little	O
lighter	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
spied	O
a	O
Man	O
making	O
Candles	O
:	O
I	O
inquired	O
of	O
him	O
where	O
about	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
that	O
Pickle	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
other	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Whitney	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Busby	O
in	O
Whitney	O
?	O
Yes	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
and	O
every	O
me	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
that	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
over	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
day-light	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
till	O
we	O
met	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
with	O
my	O
Clothes	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
my	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wig	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Joseph	O
that	O
stands	O
here	O
at	O
the	O
Barr	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
Wastcoat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
its	O
true	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
is	O
a	O
Grey	O
,	O
but	O
its	O
all	O
one	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Man	O
may	O
turn	O
grey	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
may	O
a	O
black	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
over	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
try	O
how	O
his	O
Legs	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
a-clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Ale-House	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
and	O
stript	O
and	O
left	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
We	O
quickly	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
ill	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
particularly	O
directed	O
to	O
Castle-Alley	O
in	O
Mercer	O
's	O
Street	O
near	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hughsly	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Betweed	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
from	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
caus	O
'd	O
the	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cloths	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
and	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
thrust	O
the	O
cane	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
being	O
with	O
me	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Several	O
People	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Collier	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
but	O
few	O
Houses	O
in	O
this	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
some	O
of	O
you	O
will	O
stand	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
another	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
goes	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
may	O
search	O
within	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
we	O
saw	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
come	O
out	O
of	O
Green	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cane	O
and	O
Wig	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
'em	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
Crown-Court	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Country	O
will	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
That	O
Country	O
Will	O
is	O
the	O
greatest	O
Rogue	O
of	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
has	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Quarterns	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
whereof	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Welch	B-pers
Kates	I-pers
in	O
Farr	O
's	O
Ally	O
.	O
Fanny	B-pers
Olifphant	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
Company	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
And	O
so	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Kates	O
Door	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Lodging	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
)	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
six	O
Pence	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
)	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
,	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
upon	O
a	O
Bank	O
over	O
against	O
us	O
;	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
snacks	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
6	O
pence	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
then	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
get	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
murder	O
ye	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Cole	O
my	O
Self	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Ally	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
knock	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
more	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Chalkleys	O
Night-house	O
in	O
Princes-Street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
Smith	O
Confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Country	B-pers
Will	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jenny	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Money	O
and	O
Cloths	O
,	O
when	O
Moll	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
left	O
him	O
at	O
Welsh	O
Kates	O
Door	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
nothing	O
against	O
Anderson	O
,	O
but	O
Smiths	O
Confestion	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
affect	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Smith	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
suffocated	O
,	O
and	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Men	O
coming	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
lay	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
in	O
Farthing	B-place
Fields	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
.	O
I	O
ran	O
thither	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
Cold	O
,	O
her	O
Throat	O
was	O
cut	O
about	O
two	O
Inches	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
Windpipe	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
accidental	O
Scratch	O
,	O
but	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
sharp	O
Instrument	O
.	O
-	O
Mathews	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lodged	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
King	O
Street	O
Stepney	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
got	O
along	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
expose	O
him	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
could	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
him	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Other	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
her	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
the	O
words	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Noon	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
in	O
some	O
rost	O
Pork	O
for	O
Dinner	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
within	O
,	O
but	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Sarah	O
!	O
Sarah	O
!	O
He	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
disturbance	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
with	O
another	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Sailor	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Sailor	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answered	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
under	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
O	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
My	O
poor	O
Sarah	O
is	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
lies	O
in	O
Farthing	O
Fields	O
with	O
her	O
Throat	O
Cut	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
see	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
bear	O
her	O
Husbands	O
usage	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
keep	O
no	O
Woman	O
under	O
her	O
Nose	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
crying	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Face	O
(	O
well	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Headcloths	O
torn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
knocks	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
open	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Bed	O
stood	O
near	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
though	O
a	O
broken	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Curtain	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
a	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
bold	O
Baggage	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
flew	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
'	O
a	O
'	O
scratch	O
'd	O
my	O
Eyes	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Husband	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
parted	O
us	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
Noon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
after	O
Dinner	O
.	O
He	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
resolved	O
never	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
continuing	O
to	O
knock	O
and	O
call	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
herself	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
stand	O
to	O
long	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
what	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
Laugh	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
quietly	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
only	O
deny	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
within	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
Garret	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
with	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
She	O
soon	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
the	O
Pot	O
upon	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
Speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
About	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Our	O
work	O
was	O
in	O
hast	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
except	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Is	O
my	O
Mother	O
dangerously	O
Ill	O
?	O
What	O
ails	O
her	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
-	O
She	O
's	O
dead	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
Cut	O
her	O
own	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
lies	O
in	O
Farthing	O
Fields	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
Mistress	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
that	O
some	O
People	O
would	O
think	O
hard	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
Mothers	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
danger	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
No	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
stay	O
,	O
it	O
with	O
took	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
Innocent	O
.	O
In	O
Church	O
Lane	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
Creature	O
that	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
swore	O
he	O
should	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
King-street	O
in	O
about	O
2	O
hours	O
;	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
meaning	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
that	O
Woman	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Daughter	O
;	O
As	O
we	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
several	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Old	O
Rogue	O
that	O
murder	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
Rateliffe	O
High-way	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Throat	O
was	O
very	O
slight	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
penetrated	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
without	O
dividing	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
large	O
Vessels	O
.	O
One	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
tumify	O
'd	O
which	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
water	O
in	O
her	O
Stomach	O
,	O
which	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Drowned	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
breathed	O
under	O
water	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
her	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Shovel	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
heave	O
Ballast	O
a-broad	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Betty	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
heave	O
Ballast	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
hardly	O
worth	O
while	O
to	O
rise	O
so	O
soon	O
for	O
an	O
Eight-penny	O
Jobb	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lay	O
still	O
till	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
People	O
looking	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
wonder	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
Betty	O
Thomas	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
-	O
Butcher	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
own	O
Throat	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
Jealous	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Privy	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
Suffocated	O
and	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
often	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
one-Day	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
purging	O
and	O
vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Caudie	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Holidays	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
Betty	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
up	O
comes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
And	O
so	O
have	O
I	O
too	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
Chat	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
necessary	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
2	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
talking	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6	O
of	O
September	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
empty	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
laid	O
upon	O
some	O
Straw	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Male	O
Child	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
bruises	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
the	O
Night-man	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
's	O
Vault	O
and	O
this	O
are	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
an	O
Arch	O
that	O
parts	O
then	O
at	O
top	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
empty	O
'd	O
6	O
Tun	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
7th	O
when	O
as	O
I	O
sunk	O
the	O
Soil	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
pop	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Holidays	O
Vault	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
had	O
laid	O
there	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
fair	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
ghess	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
things	O
before	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
Isabel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
sign	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
mistrusted	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
Brown	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
the	O
Midwife	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
came	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
hurt	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
World	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
born	O
alive	O
or	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
Breasts	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
draw	O
her	O
Milk	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
miscarried	O
about	O
5	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
4	O
Months	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
Milk	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Weeks	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
Miscarriage	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Confession	O
was	O
then	O
read	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
owns	O
;	O
That	O
being	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
gone	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Paved	O
Alley	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
herself	O
very	O
much	O
disorder	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Bowchers	O
Vault	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Vault	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
while	O
she	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Seat	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
thither	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Married	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
private	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
displeasing	O
my	O
Friends	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Southwell	O
,	O
to	O
provide	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Midwife	O
and	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
desired	O
the	O
first	O
Witness	O
Isabel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
some	O
Child-Bed-Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Southwell	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
my	O
Room	O
to	O
lye	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
chuse	O
her	O
a	O
Nurse	O
and	O
a	O
Midwife	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
often	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
Child-Bed-Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
could	O
serve	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
reason	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
suspect	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Ferdinand	B-pers
Lanson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
's	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
People	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
Passage	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
modest	O
Woman	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Churchill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Churchill	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bridges-street	B-place
(	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
and	I-pers
Percival	I-pers
Heslem	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
had	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robotham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
scarlet	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
Septemb	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Satterfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Aaron	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
upon	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Pot	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Landlady	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
any	O
Drink	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Looks	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
shew	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
commonly	O
twice	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
her	O
Lying-inn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Griffis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coney-wool	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	O
smith	O
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
Griffis	O
was	O
acquited	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
against	O
a	O
Stone-Pavement	O
;	O
whereby	O
he	O
received	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Scarlet	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
Picadilly	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Gardener	O
's	O
Boy	O
about	O
19	O
Years	O
Old	O
)	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
Dog	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
and	O
ran	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
whipt	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
He	O
collared	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Ear	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Nosle	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
presently	O
reel	O
'd	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
backwards	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Meridith	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
went	O
along	O
smacking	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
whistling	O
and	O
singing	O
like	O
a	O
Nightingale	O
,	O
the	O
Dog	O
ran	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
whipt	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
ye	O
whip	O
the	O
Dog	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
Stagger	O
'd	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gasped	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
fetch	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
yards	O
when	O
the	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Keller	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hamtshire-Hog	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jewit	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
point	O
of	O
Purl	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Beach	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Did	O
ye	O
ever	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
sad	O
Accident	O
?	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
?	O
says	O
1	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
only	O
with	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
look	O
on	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
hurt	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
Mark	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Jewit	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
whipt	O
the	O
Dog	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Whip	O
;	O
they	O
strugled	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Boy	O
once	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Blow	O
given	O
with	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
stroke	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
Stood	O
two	O
pulls	O
for	O
the	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
losing	O
his	O
hold	O
,	O
he	O
reel	O
'd	O
towards	O
the	O
Kennel	O
and	O
fell	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Death-bed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
suffer	O
the	O
Law	O
.	O
Several	O
Surgeons	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
an	O
Apoplectick	O
fit	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
his	O
Head	O
shaved	O
and	O
made	O
and	O
Incision	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Fracture	O
nor	O
any	O
signs	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
being	O
hurt	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
they	O
opened	O
his	O
skull	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
much	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
they	O
suppos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Blow	O
receiv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
occation	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Concussion	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
Vessels	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Scarborough	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Distinction	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
peaceable	O
,	O
and	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Beaver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
13	O
printed	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Anthony	B-pers
Westcomb	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Crafter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Veal	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
3	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Flaningham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
enameld	O
George	O
with	O
a	O
Ruby	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gascoin	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stew-Pan	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Lidget	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Ann	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pennison	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Buford	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
assault	O
Katherine	B-pers
Boyde	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Aug.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Copper-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pally	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Newins	I-pers
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquited	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Braily	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
19	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pinnard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce-Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Skimmer	O
and	O
Plates	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
October	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rose	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicated	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Nordet	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pannel	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
September	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Waltham	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
Horse	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Man	I-place
at	I-place
Waltham	I-place
Abby	I-place
,	O
about	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
was	O
lost	O
before	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
him	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Horse	O
him	O
away	O
for	O
another	O
Horse	O
,	O
with	O
Waltham	O
Abby	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Grass	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
without	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
scrubbed	O
Horse	O
with	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
a	O
Saddle	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
swapping	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
with	O
the	O
Bridle	O
and	O
saddle	O
to	O
my	O
Stable	O
for	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Mugg	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
Pound	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisonersoffering	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
marks	O
and	O
claimed	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Rag	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Shaggreen	O
Pocket	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
and	O
a	O
Chare-woman	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Holbourn-bridge	B-place
.	O
--	O
He	O
mist	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
and	O
several	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket	O
Case	O
upon	O
a	O
Person	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
sweeping	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langstone	I-pers
September	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Langstone	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
about	O
10	O
a-clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
shut	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
within	O
two	O
Doors	O
of	O
my	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
going	O
along	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Langstone	O
asleep	O
,	O
they	O
consulted	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Butler	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wig	O
to	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
was	O
gone	O
aside	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
Hat	O
at	O
Highgate	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
and	O
Wheeler	O
Sold	O
the	O
Wig	O
for	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
very	O
Sober	O
,	O
honest	O
Boys	O
till	O
the	O
Committing	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Coach-Seat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jewson	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Smithfield	B-place
with	O
any	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
happening	O
to	O
turn	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
by	O
the	O
Lamp-light	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Coach-door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
snatch	O
'd	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
seats	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Cow-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
seat	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Sheep-pens	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ram	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Hamper	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
15	O
Moidores	O
,	O
210	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
80	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Robert	O
king	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Page	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
forcibly	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
betwixt	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
Bister	O
Waggon	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
other	O
Waggons	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Pass	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Southwell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Rug-Coat	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
upon	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
plainly	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
Night	O
,	O
He	O
stop	O
'd	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
Mr.	O
King	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
King	O
was	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
ride	O
his	O
Horse	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Sleep	O
.	O
-	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
he	O
came	O
riding	O
up	O
again	O
full	O
speed	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
Shoot	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
King	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
stand	O
by	O
the	O
Horses	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Knife	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Ropes	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
Knife	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Patience	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
untye	O
'em	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
haste	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
own	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
cut	O
'em	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
road	O
was	O
beset	O
with	O
Highwaymen	O
.	O
Some	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
got	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
ordered	O
several	O
Hampers	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
Wondered	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
of	O
any	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
all	O
the	O
Hampers	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
should	O
be	O
shot	O
into	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
brown	O
paper	O
Parcel	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hamper	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Parcel	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
heavy	O
for	O
the	O
bigness	O
.	O
He	O
attended	O
us	O
near	O
two	O
Hours	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
for	O
some	O
Maggotty	O
London	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
got	O
upon	O
a	O
drunken	O
Frolick	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
and	O
Unicorn	O
at	O
West-Wickham	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
so	O
exactly	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
by	O
several	O
Spots	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
-	O
Barret	O
,	O
a	O
Banbury	O
Waggoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
about	O
a	O
Marble-Table	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
see	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
at	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Drury	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
Credit	O
at	O
Wendover	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
Discourse	O
while	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Bank	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Receipt	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
plainly	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Screw	O
Barrel	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
Swore	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
to	O
make	O
resistance	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
20	O
more	O
Highway-men	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
Furlong	O
of	O
Eling	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
King	I-pers
the	O
Waggoner	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
it	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Parcel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
Hamper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
of	O
Bister	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
Thundring	O
and	O
Swearing	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Waggon	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Wheeler	O
was	O
.	O
O	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
Kill	O
him	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Bister	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Swore	O
D-ye	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Shillings	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Having	O
occasion	O
to	O
send	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
15	O
Moidores	O
and	O
250	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
Fan	O
,	O
I	O
Wrapt	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bats	O
;	O
I	O
cover	O
'd	O
these	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Brown	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
ty	O
'd	O
with	O
Pack-thread	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
in	O
to	O
a	O
small	O
Hamper	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bister	O
Waggoner	O
.	O
This	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Fan	O
and	O
brown	O
Paper	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lowes	O
at	O
Wattleton	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Order	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Low	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Wattleton	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
direct	O
him	O
to	O
somebody	O
that	O
would	O
return	O
50	O
l.	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hern	O
,	O
who	O
readily	O
served	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
7	O
Moidores	O
for	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lamdens	I-pers
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Parcel	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
came	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
old	O
Gown	O
and	O
Fan	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Pistols	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
ever	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
was	O
quickly	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
we	O
perceive	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
Parcel	O
sew	O
'd	O
under	O
his	O
Arm-pit	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
ript	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Hern	O
on	O
Perry	O
,	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
another	O
of	O
Burt	O
on	O
Marriot	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Receipt	O
of	O
78	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
paid	O
at	O
reading	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Bills	O
and	O
Receipts	O
,	O
where	O
dated	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ride	O
through	O
Wickham	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Rug	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Laced	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
when	O
Eldridge	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
.	O
Why	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
ride	O
through	O
here	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
last	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
No	O
indeed	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
've	O
mistaken	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
30	O
Miles	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Hawkswell	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Page	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Banbury	O
Waggon	O
,	O
which	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Bister	O
Waggon	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Waggons	O
in	O
Company	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Hannaway	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Bister	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Aylsbury	O
Jail	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
3	O
Gentlemen	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
what	O
place	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
When	O
things	O
were	O
to	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
Then	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Notes	O
and	O
Bills	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
were	O
purchas	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
whole	O
Money	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
not	O
ready	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Hardy	O
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bensted	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bensted	I-pers
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Close	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Peckham	O
and	O
Camberwell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
,	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wrote	O
me	O
Word	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
Wakeman	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
two	O
Brothers	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Larking	I-pers
at	O
Edgworth	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Barns	O
and	O
Larkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
(	O
in	O
Partnership	O
)	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
to	O
Nichols	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Nichols	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Highwood-hill	B-place
.	O
That	O
the	O
Barn	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fowls	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wager	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
bargain	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Toll-book	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
toll	O
'd	O
.	O
Where	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
Vouch	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Indeed	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
live	O
as	O
far	O
off	O
as	O
Hendon	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
there	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Parish	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
named	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
earnest	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Voucher	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lent	O
him	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servants	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
its	O
true	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
ride	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Miles	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
in	O
2	O
hours	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
rod	O
quite	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
time	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Will	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
lets	O
go	O
and	O
steal	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
Fowls	O
.	O
No	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
'twill	O
be	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
said	O
nay	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Nay	O
nay	O
its	O
true	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
wicked	O
Lyar	O
for	O
denying	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
saying	O
,	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
4	O
Hens	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
says	O
;	O
'That	O
Brown	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
ride	O
where	O
'	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Fowls	O
the	O
same	O
'	O
Night	O
.	O
That	O
Brown	O
and	O
Gough	O
afterwards	O
agreed	O
'	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
'	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
Payment	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Horse	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Keatly	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
held	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
Capitally	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Denmark	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mess	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gifford	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ravenel	I-pers
.	O
She	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
Keatly	O
alias	O
Long	O
,	O
did	O
afterwards	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
and	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
common	O
buyer	O
of	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
White	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prudom	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
Persons	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
unknown	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
Executed	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
green	O
Damask	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Gifford	O
and	O
Ravenel	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Theodosia	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
;	O
after	O
which	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
outright	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Fitzpatrick	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
She	O
went	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
part	O
for	O
the	O
green	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
bring	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
more	O
.	O
We	O
redeem	O
'd	O
the	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
Bargain	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bad	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
coarse	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Damask	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Sister	O
to	O
Fitzpatrick	O
alias	O
Boswell	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
By	O
my	O
Sister	O
Fitzpatricks	O
order	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
green	O
Damask	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
my	O
Sister	O
dealt	O
with	O
People	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
White	O
Damask	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
7	O
Stars	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
in	O
Cooks-Court	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
without	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
held	O
the	O
Money	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
6	O
Guineas	O
)	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
softly	O
to	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
Shall	O
I	O
pay	O
ye	O
?	O
and	O
at	O
same	O
time	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
cautious	O
look	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
doubted	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
satisfied	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Piece	O
of	O
white	O
Damask	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hewit	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
business	O
secret	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
for	O
Officers	O
that	O
were	O
searching	O
for	O
Run	O
Goods	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
nothing	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
Swear	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
fled	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
had	O
intelligence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Brook-Street	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
place	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Keatly	O
.	O
Indeed	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
lives	O
here	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
lives	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Long	O
.	O
We	O
concluded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
new	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
discovery	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
us	O
back	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
wait	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
we	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
then	O
brought	O
us	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
mistaken	O
her	O
Message	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
call	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Answer	O
we	O
rusht	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
hearing	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
to	O
hide	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
quickly	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Long	O
and	O
Keatly	O
were	O
but	O
one	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
had	O
once	O
Swore	O
before	O
Col.	O
Ridley	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gown	O
she	O
then	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
was	O
stoln	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
could	O
prove	O
the	O
buying	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Col.	O
Ridley	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
Swore	I-pers
that	O
the	O
Gown	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
was	O
stoln	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
at	O
the	O
Blackmores-head	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moons	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
remember	O
that	O
Burton	O
ever	O
said	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
that	O
very	O
Silk	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
such	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
very	O
easily	O
be	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
common	O
a	O
Silk	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Mercers	O
Shops	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Whitlow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
box	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Austin	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
October	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lemell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
yellow	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wiliam	O
A	O
ate	O
and	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tabby	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arther	B-pers
Eastmead	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
privately	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pimble	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovejoy	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
nobody	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
6	O
Aprons	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
and	O
a	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
receiving	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
which	O
were	O
stoln	O
by	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
She	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Curtains	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Strange	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
But	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Proved	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Turner	O
,	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stole	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Sarcenet	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Dobbins	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Indian	O
Queen	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
we	O
equally	O
divided	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
my	O
share	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
13	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Sarcenet	O
was	O
worth	O
above	O
2	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
Turner	O
and	O
Fitzpatrick	O
to	O
be	O
Shoplifters	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sample	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
stopt	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
Conversation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
delivered	O
her	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
Care	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
Sense	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
wheedle	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
Day-light	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
Eyes	O
were	O
dazzled	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
under	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
refusing	O
both	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
had	O
stoln	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
and	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Mattors	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Job	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Satterfield	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marjoram	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
Pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanelled	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
1.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
1.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Trasportion	O
22.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rashfield	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Ann	O
Lane	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robotham	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beaver	I-pers
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Flaningham	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Braily	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Painard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Weeler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lemell	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
