TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal-Delivery	O
and	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORILITY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1727	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
by	O
J	O
Read	O
for	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1726.	O
in	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.Justice	O
Fortescue	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Carter	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Patrick	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marten	I-pers
Job	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
George	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
John	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Talbot	B-pers
Turbervill	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Oak	B-pers
Bickford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Gown	O
and	O
Slippers	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Man	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
my	O
Gown	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
prevaricating	O
Answers	O
;	O
whereupon	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Gown	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
10	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
wanting	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
from	O
Paul	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Illing	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Illing	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Men	O
upon	O
my	O
Lighters	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
the	O
Coals	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
33	O
Bushels	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
19	O
Bushels	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lighter	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Lighter	O
which	O
lay	O
just	O
by	O
mine	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Boat	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Lighters	O
;	O
When	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
random	O
Account	O
,	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Coals	O
below	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jenks	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
called	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
Coals	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Practice	O
many	O
Years	O
to	O
buy	O
Coals	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
Rate	O
of	O
Lightermens	O
Servants	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
to	O
Paul	B-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
two	O
Lighters	O
took	O
near	O
a	O
Chaldron	O
of	O
Coals	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
interrupted	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
made	O
him	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barsham	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barsham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
3	O
Years	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
300	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
10	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Night	O
's	O
Collection	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Shed	O
under	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
rais	O
'd	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
caus	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
please	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
That	O
-	O
that	O
-	O
Two	O
Pound	O
Ten	O
,	O
is	O
-	O
is	O
50	O
Shillings	O
-	O
and	O
so	O
much	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
about	O
five	O
Months	O
ago	O
for	O
30	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
but	O
about	O
Half	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pachler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Waste	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
Pounds	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barsham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sell	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
for	O
25	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
with	O
John	O
Hills	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
against	O
him	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Hobs	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gasken	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Waste	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Booth	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
Play	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
Shillings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barnfather	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wolford	I-pers
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cully	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
Home	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
.	O
He	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Hanging-Sword	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
Gin	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Crouch	B-place
's	I-place
Alehouse	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Bottom	I-place
of	I-place
Water-Lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
got	O
drunk	O
with	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Ale	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
we	O
sate	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
both	O
thrust	O
their	O
Hands	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
the	O
Button	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Hanging	O
Sword	O
Alley	O
I	O
met	O
Nan	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
so	O
says	O
she	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Will	O
ye	O
spend	O
Three	O
Half-pence	O
?	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
Sir	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
one	O
Word	O
of	O
a	O
Lie	O
,	O
Meredith	O
was	O
pissing	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
-	O
he	O
knows	O
very	O
well	O
-	O
there	O
he	O
stands	O
-	O
let	O
him	O
deny	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Fill	O
of	O
a	O
Farthing	O
-	O
nor	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
-	O
but	O
only	O
what	O
Gentlemen	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
-	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Pint	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
's	O
and	O
sate	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
nor	O
Child	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Neels	B-pers
Oulson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Borsel	I-pers
,	O
Decem	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
Decem	O
4	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Bourn	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
behind	O
Montague	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
talked	O
very	O
Friendly	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
along	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
tore	O
my	O
Breeches	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Hats	O
and	O
Coats	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
the	O
Watchman	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drag	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
along	O
,	O
draw	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
demand	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
Partner	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
away	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
Staff	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stout	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Knocks	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
fetch	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
His	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Maccartney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Felix	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carfeen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Mug	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Kezia	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Brewel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
November	O
21	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smedley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckler	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Biggins	I-pers
,	O
November	O
29	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Foxwell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clap	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
Foxwell	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Arnold	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Oxley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
and	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bengal	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Oct	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
Judith	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
in	O
Butler	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Stuff	O
of	O
Butler	O
upon	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
Constable	O
past	O
her	O
Word	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
her	O
Security	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
her	O
Possession	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
without	O
her	O
leave	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Pillow	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lent	O
it	O
for	O
one	O
Night	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
Constable	O
asking	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
presently	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Maccartney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotten	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
26	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hasey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowry	I-pers
,	O
November	O
26	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowery	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
pretty	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
or	O
somebody	O
else	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
nor	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
mahap	O
never	O
may	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
ne'er	O
the	O
worse	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
argues	O
nothing	O
-	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
shall	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
Pint	O
together	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
much	O
matter	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Hoop	O
in	O
Essex-street	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
Sociable	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
and	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
then	O
or	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
Tun	O
Taverns	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
seems	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Place	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
since	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
much	O
of	O
those	O
Matters	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carcase	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
October	O
24	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
October	O
19	O
.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Bathmetal	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bathmetal	O
.	O
Buckles	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
who	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rodd	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Quarter	O
Leaves	O
of	O
Wainscoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
,	O
November	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Nicorage	O
Wood	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barons	I-pers
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Farmer	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Picart	I-pers
November	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Crommy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
November	O
21	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
Ay	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
she	O
,	O
-	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Chick	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Broth	O
;	O
that	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
thereabout	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
before	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
jostled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
die	O
this	O
Minute	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
Father	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
Loss	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
Jenny	B-pers
Crommy	I-pers
and	O
Black	O
Bess	O
had	O
robbed	O
an	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
a	O
Ginshop	O
in	O
White	O
Horse	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
dividing	O
a	O
Booty	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Green	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
out	O
comes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swearing	O
and	O
jumping	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
mad	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
Shillings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Haslam	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Haslam	O
deposed	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
stept	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Sleeve	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Beeswax	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hackney	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Musling	O
Apron	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bays	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
One	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
cut	O
up	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
takes	O
away	O
the	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
runs	O
about	O
15	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
dropt	O
the	O
Pork	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
stopt	O
and	O
seized	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
several	O
Glass	O
Rubbers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Hereford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
finding	O
several	O
Things	O
missing	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
no	O
Account	O
could	O
be	O
given	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
other	O
Servants	O
Trunks	O
and	O
Boxes	O
have	O
been	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
coming	O
frequently	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
no	O
more	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
John	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
small	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Glass	O
Rubbers	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
John	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
Conference	O
,	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
so	O
stolen	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
the	O
Beadle	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rouse	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Phipps	O
's	O
Direction	O
;	O
which	O
Linnen	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Mason	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Mary	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Roller	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ambros	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ambros	O
Brown	O
,	O
Oct.	O
21	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
tempting	O
and	O
solliciting	O
William	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
to	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Bond	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
deceased	O
,	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
;	O
and	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
said	O
Turner	O
lend	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Forty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
July	O
30	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
:	O
But	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
old	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
five	O
Guineas	O
one	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
Shop	O
?	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
)	O
without	O
side	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
but	O
looking	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
within	O
side	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Draw	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
Draw	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
Search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
advertiz	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
Thatford	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
change	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
who	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Drawer	O
had	O
not	O
Silver	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
Money	O
as	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Chivers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Albert	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vernham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Sailor	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sides	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
in	O
Leadenhall	B-place
Market	I-place
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Flower	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Coming	O
cross	O
the	O
Market	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
Candle	O
I	O
saw	O
Burnham	O
,	O
alias	O
Vernham	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
3	O
Flitches	O
of	O
Bacon	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
Bacon	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
I	O
tumbled	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
getting	O
up	O
again	O
I	O
overtook	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
I	O
run	O
to	O
see	O
Burnham	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
afterwards	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Marsh	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
Shoot	O
me	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Albert	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Chatham	O
,	O
took	O
Water	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tilt-Boat	O
at	O
Billinsgate	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Leadenhall-Market	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
who	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Honest	O
Fellow	O
will	O
you	O
earn	O
6	O
d.	O
Ay	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
if	O
't	O
is	O
any	O
Thing	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
tis	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
3	O
Flitches	O
of	O
Bacon	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
so	O
Sir	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
them	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
asks	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
great	O
Coat	O
crics	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
Dog	O
run	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
his	O
Holy	O
Name	O
.	O
Then	O
Marsh	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
proceeded	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Nasaw	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
withal	O
,	O
I	O
strouled	O
into	O
Leadenhall-Market	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bulks	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
growing	O
a	O
little	O
lighter	O
I	O
gets	O
up	O
and	O
runs	O
against	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
felt	O
some	O
Straw	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
indeed	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Bacon	O
there	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Friend	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
Father	O
nor	O
Mother	O
,	O
Sister	O
or	O
Brother	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Friend	O
else	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
dear	O
Person	O
.	O
Burnham	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
Marsh	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gand	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Odway	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Putland	B-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
18	O
.	O
Putland	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
one	O
white	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Odway	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Drawers	O
lost	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Rooms	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Bed-cloaths	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
and	O
feiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
concealed	O
himself	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
robbing	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
propos	O
'd	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
to	O
bare	O
his	O
Charges	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Odway	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
Entrance	O
by	O
climbing	O
over	O
a	O
high	O
Wall	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Paradice	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Anstis	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Oct.	O
22	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anstis	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
returning	O
from	O
Bath	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
with	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
and	O
some	O
Children	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
come	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
on	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
when	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
on	O
Horseback	O
making	O
towards	O
them	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Stop	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
Mask	O
,	O
caused	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
stop	O
and	O
demanded	O
their	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Anstis	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Bath	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
excepting	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
readily	O
deliver	O
him	O
,	O
provided	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fright	O
the	O
Lady	O
and	O
the	O
Children	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Silver	O
first	O
and	O
the	O
Guinea	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Mask	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Horse	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
.	O
Streaker	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
eight	O
fat	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Bath	O
Coach	O
was	O
just	O
robbed	O
by	O
one	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
let	O
us	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
near	O
south-wall	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
the	O
Bath	O
Coach	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
strongly	O
,	O
and	O
stops	O
short	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hays	O
's	O
Lane	O
and	O
alights	O
and	O
stays	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
we	O
goes	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Glove	O
dropt	O
,	O
a	O
Mask	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
thrown	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
raked	O
out	O
afterwards	O
;	O
whereupon	O
we	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
mighty	O
desirous	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expos	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Perfumer	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
A	O
Bay	O
that	O
rode	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Bath	O
Coach	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Horse	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
upon	O
who	O
robbed	O
the	O
Bath	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Relations	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
above	O
Sixty	O
Miles	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
fail	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
perform	O
his	O
Journey	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
returning	O
to	O
provide	O
himself	O
better	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
reputable	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
spoke	O
loudly	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Marwood	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
200	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Holsey	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Hatch	O
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Marwood	O
sent	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
Whit	O
cross	O
street	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
at	O
half	O
the	O
Value	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ordered	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
if	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Halsey	O
had	O
bought	O
this	O
Bar	O
of	O
Marwood	O
at	O
full	O
Price.-	O
Marwood	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gately	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Potage-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Stew-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
November	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Love	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Gately	O
of	O
Twitenham	B-place
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fitzwater	I-pers
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fitzwater	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
supposed	O
Wife	O
's	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
Cloth	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Spawford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wainscoat	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Medal	O
,	O
3	O
Linen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Crowel	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Girdle	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crowell	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
Bloomsbury	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
Wages	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
(	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
)	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
to	O
my	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
.	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
November	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
William	B-pers
Coreham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
10	O
Silver	O
Tumblers	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Coffee-Pots	O
,	O
13	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
19	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Saucepans	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wrought	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
7	O
or	O
800	O
l.	O
and	O
61	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Isabel	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
37	O
Hats	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
into	O
Richard	O
Hall	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
at	O
Hertford	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Kingstand	O
Road	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
cast	O
my	O
Eye	O
and	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
Hertford	O
Wagon	O
did	O
not	O
pass	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
Word	O
it	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Wagon	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Ropes	O
to	O
be	O
unty	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Boxes	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
then	O
agreed	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Cart	O
and	O
Horse	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
but	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
Bishopsgate	O
Street	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Brick	O
Lane	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
4	O
Boxes	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
contained	O
hard	O
Ware	O
and	O
Plate	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Victualling-house	O
,	O
the	O
Royal-Oak	O
at	O
Rotherhith	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
or	O
fifth	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Waterman	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
soon	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Waterman	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
till	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
through-bridge	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
discharg	O
'd	O
that	O
Waterman	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
another	O
Waterman	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Sevenstep	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Room	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
:	O
But	O
soon	O
after	O
seeing	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
News-Papers	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Waterman	O
which	O
he	O
last	O
employ	O
'd	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
both	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
poor	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fotherby	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cox	O
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
first	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Kennet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Susan	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
this	O
Way	O
?	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Constables	O
are	O
after	O
you	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
only	O
some	O
Money	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
without	O
a	O
Lock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
Hostler	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
Inn	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
my	O
Habitation	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
Folly	O
in	O
going	O
into	O
Gentlemens	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
has	O
fetch	O
'd	O
me	O
three	O
Times	O
of	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
whatever	O
I	O
got	O
he	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Nay	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
he	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hatt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6.	O
d.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Wragg	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Siddon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Alcock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
by	O
striking	O
and	O
kicking	O
the	O
said	O
Alcock	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Feet	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
until	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
My	O
Son	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Sickness	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
recover	O
the	O
Kick	O
that	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sibbon	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
after	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
St.	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
Hospital	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
to	O
play	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Cribbidge	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
Words	O
arising	O
about	O
the	O
Game	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
parted	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Indisposition	O
he	O
laboured	O
under	O
some	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Kick	O
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Westbrooke	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
,	O
Old	O
Alcock	O
's	O
Son	O
and	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
great	O
Croneys	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
Rogue	O
in	O
jesting	O
with	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
look	O
poorly	O
,	O
What	O
a	O
Pox	O
ails	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Pox	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Kick	O
by	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
will	O
be	O
my	O
Death	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
one	O
Night	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
plaid	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Cribbidge	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
ensued	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
lay	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Charge	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
lay	O
no	O
Blame	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
Kick	O
from	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Nurse	O
at	O
the	O
Hospital	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
during	O
his	O
illness	O
there	O
,	O
his	O
Sweetheart	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
that	O
her	O
Unkindness	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
Heart	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
against	O
Tho	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Smathers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
hanged	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
about	O
elven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hanged	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
August	O
1.	O
and	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Company	O
from	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
twelve	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
John	B-pers
Smathers	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
Garret	O
from	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
till	O
eight	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
remain	O
'd	O
'till	O
after	O
eleven	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
till	O
after	O
that	O
Hour	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
for	O
speaking	O
treasonable	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
not	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
.	O
William	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
declare	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
Witness	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sugar-Loaf	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
November	O
8	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
Grate	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Sugar-Loaf	O
,	O
runs	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
still	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Maid	O
went	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
and	O
Tobias	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Peusy	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
a	O
Master	O
in	O
Chancery	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kinsing	O
Stoke	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
November	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Spacill	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Berks	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roff	O
deposed	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
Rowland	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
price	O
vouched	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Prince	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Rowland	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
November	O
8	O
.	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
John	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
absconded	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Linny	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Grove	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calimanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Linly	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Velvet	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
80	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
-	O
9	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Brocade	O
Silk	O
,	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Clogs	O
were	O
wore	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Clogs	O
with	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Silk	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Clog-maker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
were	O
used	O
for	O
Patchwork	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Livermore	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Livermore	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
his	O
Shoes	O
tumble	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Garnham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
3	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
3	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
House	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
first	O
the	O
Street-door	O
and	O
afterwards	O
two	O
Partitions	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
several	O
Bundles	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
carryed	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
laid	O
ready	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
.	O
Parnel	B-pers
Foulks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
She	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
her	O
Father	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
there	O
to	O
hide	O
herself	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Bundles	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
she	O
had	O
carryed	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
in	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Price	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
shoved	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
lodged	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
ever	O
came	O
there	O
again	O
I	O
would	O
kick	O
her	O
A	O
-	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
,	O
The	O
fourth	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Month	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
round	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
Foot	O
high	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
there	O
stood	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stark	O
naked	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
down	O
she	O
dropt	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
-	O
But	O
had	O
she	O
fell	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
sadly	O
frighted	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
open	O
any	O
Door	O
whatsoever	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
here	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
little	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
served	O
since	O
the	O
Former	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
for	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
Service	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
distracted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
got	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
to	O
prescribe	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
that	O
were	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
sometimes	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
wild	O
Actions	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
asked	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
?	O
would	O
answer	O
,	O
Punch	O
bid	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
Consideration	O
of	O
her	O
Lunacy	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sagathy	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
23	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
pleasing	O
me	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
14	O
Days	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
my	O
Servants	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
missed	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
several	O
Things	O
wanting	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
on	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
George	B-pers
Scullard	I-pers
corroborated	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Elton	O
's	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
enticeing	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
foul	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
October	O
16	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Service	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lov	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
and	O
Mother	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
kiss	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Mall	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
against	O
Baron	B-place
Bothmor	I-place
's	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
he	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
tir	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
letting	O
down	O
his	O
Breeches	O
I	O
run	O
away	O
-	O
On	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
Day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
great	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
no	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
street	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
passage	O
,	O
kiss	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
you	O
are	O
deadly	O
cross	O
,	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Pall	O
Mall	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Mountain	O
,	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
Chair	O
close	O
to	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
put	O
mine	O
into	O
his	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Croft	O
deposed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
told	O
me	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Orders	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
should	O
have	O
Liberty	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
left	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
coming	O
amongst	O
the	O
Children	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
ill	O
effect	O
.	O
Silvanus	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
having	O
Liberty	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
through	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
street	O
into	O
a	O
Passage	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rude	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Unicorne	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Chairman	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
fear	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Club	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
what	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Schollars	O
?	O
he	O
laughed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
Molley	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
asked	O
Henry	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
what	O
Acquaintance	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
Treat	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Supper	O
-	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
prevented	O
,	O
he	O
down	O
of	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
Treat	O
us	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Defence	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
lived	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Case	O
Value	O
15	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Chain	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Glass	O
Bottle	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Top	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Smelling	O
Bottle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
from	O
Dagger	O
's	O
Bridewell	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
such	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
had	O
not	O
offered	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Plains	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cowdon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Condron	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
7	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
and	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Oct.	O
29	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Clement	O
's	O
Lane	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
the	O
Sunday	O
was	O
Sev'night	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dunnago	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
22	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
30	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flock-Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Novemb	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
and	O
Fifty	O
three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Keneday	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
3	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Keneday	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
robbed	O
me	O
last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
of	O
four	O
Pounds	O
odd	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
for	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Man	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
returning	O
home	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
Collar	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
another	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pay	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
for	O
rifling	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
scratched	O
my	O
Face	O
;	O
whereupon	O
I	O
gets	O
to	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
cries	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
twisted	O
it	O
so	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
for	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
Purse	O
away	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
10	O
Clock	O
at	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-house	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
taxed	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
they	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
found	O
the	O
Purse	O
with	O
Thirty-five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Coin	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Hanover	O
Piece	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
their	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
use	O
his	O
Pleasure	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
before	O
she	O
see	O
him	O
)	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
and	O
almost	O
strangled	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
in	O
Whitecross-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Middle-Moor	O
fields	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ebenezar	B-pers
Stinton	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
being	O
pursued	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
home	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Hand	O
Alley	O
,	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Pot	O
and	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
several	O
Remnants	O
and	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silks	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Gervis	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mulatto	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Gold	O
Dust	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
Captain	O
Strange	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Last	O
January	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Coast	B-place
of	I-place
Africa	I-place
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Captain	O
Griffis	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
about	O
150	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Dust	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
to	O
buy	O
more	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Gervis	O
Charlton	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
Three	O
Pounds	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
per	O
Ounce	O
.	O
Archihald	B-pers
Kenedy	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Steerage	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Gervis	O
Charlton	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Seals	O
off	O
Capt	O
.	O
Griffes	O
's	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Lump	O
in	O
a	O
Leather	O
Case	O
much	O
like	O
that	O
which	O
we	O
tie	O
up	O
Gold	O
Dust	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Capt	O
.	O
Dart	O
was	O
sick	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Carlton	O
in	O
the	O
Cabin	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Hold	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
see	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
opened	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Charlton	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Deponent	O
as	O
much	O
Gold	O
Dust	O
as	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
42	O
Shillings	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
was	O
not	O
open	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Farnell	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
,	O
Shop	O
with	O
two	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
some	O
small	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
Three	O
Pounds	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
per	O
Ounce	O
for	O
its	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
melt	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
me	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
eight	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Examination	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
affected	O
but	O
by	O
Charlton	O
's	O
Examination	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
of	O
Billiter-Square	B-place
London	I-place
,	O
Merchant	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Publishing	O
certain	O
Writings	O
or	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
;	O
impowering	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
assign	O
,	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
South-Sea	O
Stock	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
Eight	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	O
Heysham	O
of	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Seal	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Heysham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
Forge	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
being	O
an	O
infirm	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
afficted	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
he	O
intrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
negotiate	O
Affairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1725	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Service	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
wrote	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
a	O
very	O
formal	O
Letter	O
,	O
desiring	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
to	O
impower	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Dividends	O
of	O
Stock	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
having	O
some	O
Business	O
near	O
the	O
South-sea	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
wife	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
enquire	O
at	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
House	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Dividends	O
of	O
Stock	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
proper	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clerks	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
Stock	O
in	O
that	O
Company	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
extremely	O
surprised	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
ill	O
at	O
home	O
)	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
accordingly	O
,	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
ruffled	O
,	O
and	O
talking	O
very	O
warmly	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Who	O
insisted	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
his	O
Stock	O
being	O
disposed	O
of	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Mistake	O
of	O
the	O
Clerk	O
's	O
-	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
such	O
Pretence	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
proper	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
assured	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
had	O
no	O
Stock	O
in	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
Company	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
see	O
me	O
so	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
General	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
for	O
transferring	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
denying	O
he	O
that	O
ever	O
gave	O
him	O
any	O
such	O
Authority	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
some	O
Necessities	O
that	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
promised	O
he	O
would	O
reinstate	O
the	O
said	O
Stock	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
.	O
And	O
for	O
his	O
further	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
takes	O
Pen	O
,	O
Ink	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
up	O
and	O
delivered	O
me	O
a	O
promisory	O
Note	O
,	O
to	O
Transfer	O
Four	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
South-Sea	O
Stock	O
;	O
which	O
Note	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
also	O
an	O
Account	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
gives	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
Credit	O
for	O
the	O
Dividends	O
of	O
his	O
South-Sea	O
Stock	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
none	O
was	O
disposed	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
disposed	O
of	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
without	O
his	O
Privity	O
or	O
Knowledge	O
long	O
before	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
made	O
Application	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
by	O
what	O
Authority	O
the	O
said	O
Stock	O
was	O
Transferred	O
and	O
they	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
Powers	O
of	O
Attorney	O
.	O
which	O
Powers	O
I	O
got	O
leave	O
to	O
inspect	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
South-Sea-House	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
whose	O
Care	O
and	O
Custody	O
all	O
such	O
Powers	O
are	O
committed	O
)	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
several	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
impowering	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
assign	O
,	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
South	O
Sea	O
Stock	O
at	O
sundry	O
Times	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Powers	O
or	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Powers	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
greatest	O
Stress	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lance	O
,	O
a	O
Notary	O
Publick	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
execute	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
either	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Heysham	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Billiter-Square	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
appearing	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Lance	O
a	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
an	O
honest	O
punctual	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
attest	O
a	O
Falshood	O
upon	O
any	O
Consideration	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
tried	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
granted	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
only	O
the	O
same	O
Evidence	O
Mr.	O
Lance	O
,	O
but	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bouncher	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Heysham	I-pers
's	O
Barber	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
was	O
Witness	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Powers	O
,	O
Dated	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
1722	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
He	O
see	O
the	O
same	O
executed	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Heysham	I-pers
's	O
Compting-House	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
was	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Powers	O
or	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
were	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
:	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
producing	O
some	O
Draughts	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Heysham	O
's	O
,	O
proved	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cause	O
Tried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
,	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	B-place
in	O
Decemb	O
.	O
1725	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Skinner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Holloway	O
both	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
present	O
in	O
Court	O
at	O
the	O
above	O
mentioned	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Pusey	O
eight	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
during	O
his	O
Service	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
paid	O
his	O
Wages	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Pusey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
received	O
any	O
Wages	O
or	O
Money	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
paid	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
Chariot	O
Expences	O
,	O
as	O
Mops	O
and	O
other	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Pusey	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
April	O
1721	O
,	O
she	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
pay	O
him	O
Seven	O
Pounds	O
odd	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
gave	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
produce	O
that	O
Receipt	O
,	O
she	O
declared	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
produced	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
all	O
the	O
Vouchers	O
were	O
delivered	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
the	O
Accounts	O
were	O
settled	O
and	O
adjusted	O
between	O
Colonel	O
Pusey	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Pusey	O
pay	O
any	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bills	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
enquired	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Pusey	O
,	O
unless	O
when	O
she	O
wanted	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
full	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
material	O
Circumstance	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Receipt	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
Col.	O
Pusey	O
,	O
as	O
John	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
wrote	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
's	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
Signed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
but	O
subscribed	O
John	O
the	O
Coachman	O
;	O
which	O
Receipt	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
no	O
Credit	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gearing	O
's	O
Evidence	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
Reward	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
Dependance	O
on	O
Col.	O
Pusey	B-pers
when	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Deposition	O
before-mentioned	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
of	O
Credit	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Voiture	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Partners	O
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
of	O
Mary	O
Burton	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Pink	O
coloured	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Pink-coloured	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
delivered	O
20	O
Yards	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
her	O
Part	O
,	O
to	O
Ann	O
Green	O
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
What	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
she	O
spoke	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
offer	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
her	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stout	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
confess	O
'd	O
they	O
knew	O
Barton	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Shoplifter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Stopt	O
once	O
with	O
some	O
Tabby	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
4.	O
Jane	B-pers
Crommy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
3.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Liney	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Groves	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
.	O
Transportation	O
32.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
Farmer	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pachlow	I-pers
,	O
Neels	B-pers
Oulson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Carfeen	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Brewell	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bays	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Gervis	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
,	O
Albert	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vernon	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Gand	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Marwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gately	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Spawford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Coreham	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fotherby	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cowdon	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
Green	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
convicted	O
of	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
;	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
Felony	O
.	O
Books	O
printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
COnnection	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Testament	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
and	O
Neighbouring	O
Nations	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Declension	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdoms	O
of	O
Israel	O
and	O
Judah	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Christ	O
.	O
By	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Pridems	I-pers
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
Dean	O
of	O
Norwich	O
,	O
2	O
Vols	O
.	O
Folio	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
and	O
Maps	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Dealers	O
in	O
Stock	O
's	O
Assistant	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Calculation	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
any	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Stock	O
from	O
10000	O
l.	O
to	O
1	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
to	O
200	O
l.	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Ease	O
of	O
the	O
Proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Transferrable	O
Stocks	O
in	O
Buying	O
,	O
Selling	O
,	O
and	O
Calling	O
up	O
Dividends	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Clerks	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
House	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	O
,	O
1st	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
useful	O
Clerk-like	O
Contradictions	O
of	O
Words	O
;	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
2dly	O
,	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promisory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
3dly	O
,	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
and	O
Bills	O
of	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
Manner	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
4thly	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understandin	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
5thly	O
.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law	O
Precedents	O
,	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
6thly	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
rednce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Vyre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
By	O
M.	O
Glare	O
,	O
School-Master	O
in	O
Soho-Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Physical	O
Dictionary	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Causes	O
of	O
Diseases	O
,	O
Chirurgical	O
Instruments	O
,	O
their	O
Use	O
,	O
are	O
accurately	O
described	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Virtues	O
of	O
Medicinal	O
Plants	O
,	O
Minerals	O
,	O
Stones	O
,	O
Gums	O
,	O
Salts	O
,	O
Barths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Method	O
of	O
chusing	O
the	O
best	O
Drugs	O
:	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
Chymistry	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Art	O
:	O
The	O
various	O
Forms	O
of	O
Medicines	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ways	O
of	O
compounding	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
Stephen	B-pers
Blamcard	I-pers
.	O
M.	O
D.	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
at	O
Middleburg	O
in	O
Zealand	O
.	O
The	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
many	O
Thousand	O
Terms	O
of	O
Art	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Explanation	O
(	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
and	O
best	O
Edition	O
of	O
Castellus	O
's	O
Lexicon	O
Medicum	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Authors	O
)	O
more	O
than	O
in	O
any	O
former	O
Impression	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
the	O
Characters	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
Physick	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Latin	O
and	O
English	O
,	O
curiously	O
Engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
.	O
The	O
Annals	O
of	O
King	O
GEORGE	O
,	O
containing	O
not	O
only	O
the	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
Europe	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Introduction	O
in	O
Defence	O
:	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Title	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Descent	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
Royal	O
Families	O
that	O
ever	O
Reign	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Island	O
,	O
in	O
Six	O
Volumes	O
.	O
Jam	O
Nova	O
Progenies	O
,	O
Celo	O
demittitux	O
Alto	O
.	O
Virg	O
Custode	O
Return	O
Caesare	O
,	O
non	O
furor	O
Civilis	O
out	O
Vis	O
eximet	O
Otinm	O
.	O
Hor	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Revolutions	O
that	O
have	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	B-pers
Republick	I-pers
.	O
Written	O
in	O
French	O
by	O
the	O
Abbot	O
de	O
Vertot	O
.	O
Translated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Oxell	O
,	O
2	O
Vols	O
.	O
The	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Farrier	O
,	O
or	O
Farring	O
compleated	O
.	O
Containing	O
every	O
Thing	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
compleat	O
Horseman	O
,	O
Groom	O
,	O
Farrier	O
,	O
or	O
Horse	O
Leach	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Office	O
of	O
the	O
Breeder	O
,	O
Keeper	O
,	O
Rider	O
,	O
Feeder	O
,	O
Buyer	O
and	O
Farrier	O
;	O
shewing	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
Beauty	O
,	O
Goodness	O
,	O
Faults	O
and	O
Interfections	O
of	O
Horses	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
best	O
Method	O
of	O
Buying	O
,	O
Dieting	O
,	O
Shooing	O
,	O
and	O
otherwise	O
Managing	O
Horses	O
for	O
all	O
Uses	O
.	O
4th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
Interest	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
per	O
Cent	O
from	O
One	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
to	O
one	O
Shilling	O
for	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Exactly	O
computed	O
to	O
the	O
Thousandth	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
Also	O
Tables	O
of	O
Compound	O
Interest	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	B-pers
Lydal	I-pers
,	O
Accomptant	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Excise	O
.	O
