TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
:	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1726.	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serj	O
.	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fidman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
James	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Tookey	I-pers
Obadiah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
George	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Eden	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Castledine	I-pers
James	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Gorge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sudbury	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Brounker	I-pers
James	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
5	O
Yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	O
Lewis	O
,	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
(	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Hounds-Ditch	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
my	O
Maid	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Gravel-Lewis	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Val	O
.	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Lasingby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Nap	O
Dragger	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s	O
.	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
coming	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Legg	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Birchin-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
Suspected	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
Fen-Church-Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Answer	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
strugling	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wightman	I-pers
coming	O
by	O
assisted	O
Hawkins	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Legg	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
whose	O
Goods	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Broad-Street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pitches	I-pers
,	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Cook	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pitches	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
.	O
Her	O
Master	O
had	O
mist	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
off	O
'd	O
4	O
Plates	O
to	O
Sale	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Broadburst	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
December	O
9	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Washer	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
accus	O
'd	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phillis	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Box	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Benjamin	O
Gosling	O
,	O
January	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Gosling	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-Horse	O
Alley	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
's	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
well	O
known	O
that	O
I	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
,	O
betwixt	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
a	O
Mortal	O
cold	O
Night	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
have	O
good	O
Cause	O
to	O
remember	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bennets	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
who	O
should	O
I	O
meet	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
How	O
dye	O
do	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
bloody	O
cold	O
Weather	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
Whereof	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
can	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
-	O
what	O
signifies	O
lying	O
-	O
we	O
struck	O
a	O
Bargain	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
do	O
so	O
than	O
wander	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
must	O
needs	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
any	O
Wife	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
that	O
's	O
neither	O
here	O
nor	O
there	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
for't	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
once	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
mind	O
which	O
End	O
goes	O
foremost	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
many	O
a	O
poor	O
Mans	O
Case	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
mine	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
Sir	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Brass	O
Box	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
upon	O
Command	O
for	O
6	O
Pounds	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
Matters	O
.	O
Whereof	O
I	O
takes	O
out	O
this	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Shot	O
.	O
Now	O
whether	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
she	O
mought	O
or	O
she	O
mought	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
howsoever	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
Landlady	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
People	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
Landlady	O
brings	O
me	O
a	O
Groat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Groat	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Phillis	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
Money	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
a	O
cold	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Gosling	O
a	O
drinking	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Bunters	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
fain	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
never	O
caring	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
self	O
familiar	O
with	O
any	O
such	O
Fellows	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
fly	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
ravish	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sells	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mattocks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Halton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
inside	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
outside	O
Seal	O
Case	O
,	O
studded	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Will	O
.	O
Halton	O
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
William	O
Halton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
my	O
Chaise	O
up	O
Kentish	B-place
Town-Hill	I-place
,	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
to	O
Highgate	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
imperfect	O
Sight	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
who	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Mattocks	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichol	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
Chaise	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Sells	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
presented	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
Mattocks	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Chaise	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
Masters	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
Master	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Men	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
great	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dawgs	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
having	O
been	O
many	O
Robberies	O
lately	O
committed	O
about	O
Highgate	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
making	O
Sells	O
's	O
Landlord	O
suspect	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
ill	O
Courses	O
;	O
the	O
Landlord	O
informs	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
I	O
surpris	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
a-bed	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
these	O
Pistols	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
Possession	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
which	O
gives	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Furniture	O
,	O
and	O
Arms	O
of	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
apprehend	O
him	O
.	O
Sells	O
presently	O
impeached	O
Mattocks	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
near	O
Holloway	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Mattocks	O
,	O
deposing	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
formerly	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
there	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Holmes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
Shoe-Makers	O
Shop	O
in	O
Wych-Street	B-place
;	O
his	O
Wife	O
siting	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
inquir	O
'd	O
of	O
Rob	B-pers
Swinny	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
)	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
Shoes	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
They	O
pursued	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Five	O
Bell	O
Tavern	O
into-the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
Shoe	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
is	O
his	O
Lap	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Fowell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Keys	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sattin	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
sixteen	O
Sarsenet	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
lives	O
at	O
Rochester	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
in	O
Goods	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gets	O
done	O
at	O
London	O
.	O
In	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Hamper	O
of	O
Goods	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
Graves-End	O
in	O
the	O
Tilt-boat	O
,	O
she	O
provided	O
as	O
much	O
Beef	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
sufficient	O
for	O
the	O
Voyage	O
,	O
and	O
tying	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Pudding	O
Bag	O
,	O
packt	O
it	O
securely	O
in	O
the	O
Hamper	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Raymond	O
came	O
to	O
Billings-Gate	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
scarce	O
landed	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
ply	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Kings-Bridge	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
He	O
observed	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Hamper	O
in	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
row	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
quickly	O
came	O
to	O
Kings-Bridge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Raymond	O
stept	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Waterman	O
went	O
abast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
bring	O
the	O
Hamper	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
row	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
Mr.	O
Raymond	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
to	O
but	O
little	O
Purpose	O
;	O
for	O
says	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
My	O
Boat	O
was	O
stole	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
Hamper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Rogue	O
too	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
that	O
the	O
Hamper	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
in	O
Ashen-Tree-Court	O
,	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Spur	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
Nurse	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
a	O
Hamper	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Spur	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
packt	O
with	O
Silk	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
prepared	O
for	O
Dying	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
suspect	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
Landlord	O
to	O
enquire	O
among	O
the	O
Callenders	O
and	O
Dyers	O
,	O
if	O
no	O
such	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Raymond	O
's	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
in	O
Black-Fryers	O
;	O
who	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
)	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Callender	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
traced	O
out	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Baptist's-Head	O
,	O
in	O
White-Cross-Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Bag	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Spur	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hains	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
wrapt	O
up	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Beef	O
at	O
Graves-End	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Hamper	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
accidentally	O
met	O
a	O
Stranger	O
that	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
bare	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Parlour	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
crept	O
in	O
on	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
they	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
and	O
so	O
reel	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
against	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
some	O
of	O
'em	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
only	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
'em	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fells	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fellis	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Wooden-Drawer	O
with	O
a	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
4	O
s	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	O
Willey	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
John	O
Willey	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
backwards	O
my	O
Till	O
was	O
stoln	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
Search	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
quickly	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ellwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
washt	O
Linnen	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hung	O
his	O
Shirt	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Yard	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
and	O
stopt	O
,	O
with	O
it	O
by	O
Tho	B-pers
Norgrave	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
scorn	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
honestly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
Sea	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
but	O
loosing	O
his	O
Toes	O
turn	O
'd	O
merry	O
Andrew	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
capacity	O
had	O
served	O
Mr	O
Bullock	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Franks	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradfield	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
he	O
for	O
striking	O
,	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Patrick	O
Clifford	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
and	O
Belly	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
aiding	O
abetting	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
thus	O
.	O
Mary	O
was	O
Wife	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
Bedfellow	O
to	O
William	O
and	O
Patrick	O
both	O
Soldier	O
s	O
:	O
Patrick	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
William	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
so	O
intirely	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Patrick	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
at	O
Williams	O
Quarters	O
in	O
Bedford-bury	B-place
;	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mother	O
Ostler	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
Drams	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
disagreement	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
upon	O
the	O
Score	O
of	O
their	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Patrick	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
and	O
very	O
merry	O
with	O
Bob	B-pers
Sillet	I-pers
and	O
Doll	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Spread-Eagle	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Wills	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
Doll	O
Staid	O
in	O
her	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
below	O
.	O
Bob	O
went	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Moll	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
answered	O
no	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
asked	O
the	O
same	O
Question	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
like	O
Answer	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
Do	O
ye	O
come	O
to	O
Rob	O
me	O
?	O
Bob	O
left	O
'em	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Lion-Ale-House	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
which	O
a	O
little	O
bustle	O
and	O
a	O
trampling	O
of	O
Feet	O
was	O
heard	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
,	O
in	O
comes	O
Moll	O
and	O
goes	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
Will	O
quickly	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
in	O
Mother	O
Ostler	O
's	O
Room	O
that	O
Patrick	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
engaged	O
with	O
their	O
Quartern-pots	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
but	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Moll	O
goes	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
cries	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
alarm	O
'd	O
'em	O
that	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Patrick	O
lying	O
dead	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
without	O
his	O
Shoes	O
:	O
They	O
searched	O
him	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Bruise	O
or	O
any	O
sign	O
of	O
hurt	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
might	O
kill	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
the	O
Breath	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
without	O
leaving	O
any	O
visible	O
Mark	O
of	O
Contusion	O
,	O
or	O
breaking	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Vessels	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
causing	O
the	O
Patient	O
to	O
Vomit	O
Blood	O
:	O
He	O
answered	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
great	O
allowance	O
must	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
weakness	O
of	O
a	O
Mans	O
Constitution	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
being	O
disorder	O
'd	O
with	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
render	O
him	O
more	O
obnoxious	O
to	O
Suffocation	O
,	O
ye	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
likely	O
and	O
indeed	O
hardly	O
possible	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
Patrick	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
Mary	O
's	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
only	O
to	O
bring	O
Company	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
run	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
which	O
none	O
of	O
'em	O
would	O
do	O
before	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
that	O
whoever	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
would	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
if	O
she	O
or	O
William	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
:	O
She	O
added	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
that	O
she	O
loved	O
her	O
Husband	O
too	O
well	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Men	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
Doll	O
Burrows	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
utter	O
rain	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold-lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
she	O
was	O
accus	O
'd	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
'em	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Mold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
David	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cornelian-seal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fernandes	I-pers
Nunes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nunes	O
deposed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
the	O
Constables	O
thus	O
Deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lyne	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Colcot	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Hounds-ditch	B-place
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Person	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Diaper-napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
?	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Napkins	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lambert	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head-Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Pert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Slippers	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Common-prayer	O
Book	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Swan-Inn	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
by	O
the	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
while	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
hid	O
'em	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
and	I-pers
Edith	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Edith	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
210	O
Ells	O
of	O
Culgee	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
136	O
Yards	O
of	O
Slesias	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
33	O
Yards	O
of	O
Britanny	O
,	O
value	O
58	O
s	O
6	O
Ells	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Ells	O
of	O
Canvas	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
deposed	O
Mr.	O
Whitaker	O
received	O
into	O
his	O
Ware-house	O
a	O
Truss	O
of	O
Linnen	O
at	O
the	O
3	B-place
Cranes	I-place
from	O
Messrs	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Atkinsen	O
to	O
be	O
shipt	O
for	O
Newcastle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Christopher	O
had	O
for	O
3	O
Months	O
past	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Whitaker	O
at	O
his	O
Wharf	O
,	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
early	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
enquiry	O
among	O
the	O
Drapers	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
in	O
reallity	O
.	O
Another	O
parcel	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
desir	O
'd	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
Parcel	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Peacok	O
in	O
Pepper	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
left	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4.	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
directing	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
by	O
Law	O
the	O
Wife	O
is	O
under	O
the	O
influence	O
and	O
Power	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
therefore	O
whatever	O
she	O
does	O
in	O
Obedience	O
to	O
him	O
or	O
with	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
imputed	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
Criminal	O
.	O
They	O
acquitted	O
Edith	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
76	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
December	O
24th	O
.	O
Thus	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Brasiers-shop	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
sees	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Boy	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
steps	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
given	O
him	O
Six	O
Pence	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
Tavern	O
;	O
and	O
Child	O
(	O
continues	O
he	O
)	O
you	O
may	O
leave	O
your	O
Linnen	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
.	O
Which	O
the	O
Boy	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
being	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
accordingly	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Management	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
and	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Stocks-Market	O
by	O
Williams	B-pers
Huggens	I-pers
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Brasier	O
's	O
Door	O
who	O
he	O
thought	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
why	O
he	O
run	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pettifer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Pettifer	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
true	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
taken	O
an	O
honest	O
Care	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Bread	O
,	O
but	O
Misfortunes	O
may	O
happen	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Case	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
wicked	O
Baggage	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
For	O
she	O
comes	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
tells	O
me	O
a	O
fine	O
Story	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
Pension	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Loaf	O
of	O
Bread	O
that	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
the	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
quite	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
consenting	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
alias	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
with	O
William	O
Plowman	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Napkin	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Sheet	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
the	O
Prisoners	O
Mother	O
that	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Husband	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
one	O
Day	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
white	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
or	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
which	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
pickt	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
shooting	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
Gun-powder	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
thus	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Cooper	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
drinking	O
In	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
plac	O
'd	O
herself	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
whispering	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
those	O
three	O
Men	O
were	O
Thieves	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
heard	O
the	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
the	O
Words	O
were	O
spoken	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Gardner	O
;	O
he	O
swearing	O
;	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
Yes	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
You	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
three	O
Thieves	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
guilty	O
Conscience	O
needed	O
no	O
Accuser	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
encreasing	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
the	O
Landlord	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stepping	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
she	O
first	O
Man	O
thus	O
opposes	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
however	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Powder	O
slash	O
'd	O
in	O
Hall	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Ball	O
past	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
's	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
the	O
Rognes	O
then	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candles	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
pursued	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
escap	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
quickly	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
2	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Godby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Crow	O
out	O
of	O
Bell-Savage-Yard	B-place
,	I-place
on	I-place
Ludgate-Hill	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
afterwards	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Smith	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
old	O
Brass	O
and	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Crow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rug	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Huddlestone	I-pers
;	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roche	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rug	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Roche	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
early	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Cloths	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Trunk	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
Rudge	I-pers
in	O
Houns-ditch	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
Butler	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Smock	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
her	O
(	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
)	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
there	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Brown	O
in	O
Old-Street	B-place
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
from	O
Brown	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Butler	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
31	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Perring	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Perring	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Perring	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
Places	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Barnaby-Street	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Hands	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
steal	O
from	O
thence	O
9	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
9	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Bed-pan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
8	O
.	O
Copper-pot	O
Lids	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	O
Parker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
following	O
Account	O
.	O
Mary	O
Parker	O
(	O
who	O
sells	O
Coals	O
and	O
Sand	O
in	O
Kings-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
)	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
fast	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
with	O
Buckles	O
in	O
them	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
to	O
prevent	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Watchman	O
's	O
coming	O
his	O
Rounds	O
.	O
The	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Tom	O
.	O
Randal	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
(	O
Jack	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
had	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
been	O
order	O
'd	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
Shelter	O
to	O
his	O
Aunts	O
second	O
Husband	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Love-Court	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-Side	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
He	O
to	O
secure	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
against	O
the	O
Cannon	O
in	O
Cannon-Street	O
,	O
Wapping	O
;	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
Jack	O
Howard	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Pewter	O
and	O
Brass	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Moll	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
presently	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Lammas	O
.	O
Pursuant	O
to	O
which	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
)	O
Jack	O
Howard	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
;	O
and	O
Moll	O
Watkins	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Taylor	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
left	O
Randal	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Robert	O
Lammas	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Pewterers	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Cock	I-place
and	I-place
Wheat-Sheaf	I-place
,	I-place
between	I-place
Harp-Alley	I-place
and	I-place
Stone-Cutter's-Street	I-place
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
six	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
the	O
Pewter	O
;	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
lost	O
.	O
Jack	O
Howard	O
was	O
entrusted	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
all	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
gave	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Mother	O
died	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
good	O
Brass	O
and	O
Pewter	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
these	O
Plates	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Lection	O
of	O
having	O
her	O
other	O
Goods	O
seiz	O
'd	O
for	O
Rent	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
of	O
his	O
old	O
Trade	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
my	O
Husband	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mary	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
to	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
in	O
her	O
Cellar	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Ship	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Sea	O
out	O
of	O
harms	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
merry	O
Making	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
away	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
Jack	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
consented	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
rather	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Owen	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
Dermont	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Frances	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Walter	I-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Walter	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
Chattles	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Walter	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Coach-House	O
of	O
Walter	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
thus	O
appeared	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Footman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
his	O
Mistress	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Mistress	O
was	O
reading	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
swear	O
to	O
keep	O
secret	O
what	O
ever	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
kist	O
the	O
Book	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
Chest	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
swore	O
she	O
must	O
fetch	O
him	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
her	O
immediately	O
.	O
She	O
arose	O
extreamly	O
terrify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
swear	O
again	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
.	O
She	O
kist	O
the	O
Book	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
met	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
by	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
who	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Disorder	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
understanding	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
carry	O
down	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
bounc	O
'd	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
splitted	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
presented	O
the	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
.	O
But	O
yet	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
the	O
Coachman	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
over	O
the	O
Stables	O
.	O
My	O
Breeches	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
Peg	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
because	O
his	O
own	O
was	O
at	O
mending	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
wear	O
them	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
Martin	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
felonious	O
taking	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
contented	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
2	O
Years	O
imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Grenolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hankerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
:	O
A	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Neck	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
;	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
made	O
Oath	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
with	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
with	O
their	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
which	O
Room	O
stood	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
wherein	O
Cook	O
had	O
lockt	O
up	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
When	O
their	O
Liquor	O
was	O
out	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
undress	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
Cook	O
pulling	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
with	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
wrapt	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
by	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
usually	O
lay	O
till	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
pretended	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
plain	O
Work	O
in	O
haste	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Cook	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
her	O
Keys	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
(	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
)	O
helpt	O
her	O
for	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
looked	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Rings	O
were	O
mist	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
's	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Shirt	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
forgot	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
Butcher	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Headborough	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Brattle	I-pers
,	O
being	O
apprehended	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
by	O
him	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
upon	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
who	O
granting	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
committing	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
Jone	O
's	O
Custody	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
wilfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
at	O
large	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brattle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Robert	O
Storth	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
2	O
Pockets	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Storth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Storth	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
from	O
Shackelwell	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
Ponds	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
about	O
2	O
Stones	O
throw	O
of	O
the	O
Cock-Alehouse	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
String	O
that	O
tied	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
took	O
'em	O
both	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
scream	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Minutes	O
time	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
several	O
there	O
of	O
my	O
loss	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
here	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
And	O
whether	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
had	O
a	O
Gun	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
his	O
Hair	O
hung	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
indeed	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
his	O
Hair	O
was	O
put	O
back	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Gun	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Inns	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
up	O
Love-Lane	O
,	O
towards	O
the	B-place
Cock	I-place
at	I-place
Newington	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Bank	O
and	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
2	O
Banks	O
and	O
a	O
Stile	O
just	O
by	O
his	O
Fathers	O
House	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
answer	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Father	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Place	O
behind	O
a	O
Curtain	O
with	O
with	O
a	O
Book	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
Hat	O
below	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
said	O
Jack	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
out	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
no	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
than	O
bad	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
same	O
Hat	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
might	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
run	O
a	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
losing	O
his	O
Gun	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baden	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
her	O
loss	O
;	O
she	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
took	O
.	O
We	O
immediately	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
quickly	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
over	O
3	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Garden	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
upon	O
seeing	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
we	O
should	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Gun	O
;	O
several	O
others	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Field	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Account	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
given	O
,	O
I	O
guess	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
not	O
above	O
20	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
Screaming	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Field	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
'em	O
both	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
have	O
seen	O
if	O
he	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
laid	O
his	O
Gun	O
down	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Trees	O
after	O
a	O
Thrush	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Thrush	O
sing	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Peter	O
Gunner	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Masters	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
'd	O
set	O
the	O
Dog	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Sight	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
Pond	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
says	O
)	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
had	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Grains	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
some	O
Sparrows	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Gun	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
quickly	O
flew	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
spy	O
'd	O
a	O
Thrush	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Field	O
where	O
the	O
Boy	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
Peter	O
Gunner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Father	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
back-way	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
because	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
bear	O
me	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
wore	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Lad	O
has	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
being	O
present	O
clapt	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
shall	O
Swear	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
(	O
among	O
whom	O
were	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
)	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
Character	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magaretes	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trophy	O
Pendant	O
for	O
a	O
Hearse	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
instant	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
Mr.Arnold	O
,	O
I	O
assisted	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Countess	O
of	O
Grandison	O
(	O
General	O
Stewarts	O
Lady	O
)	O
who	O
was	O
interr	O
'd	O
at	O
Westminster-Abby	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
at	O
the	O
Abby-gate	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
warned	O
several	O
(	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
particular	O
)	O
not	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Ornaments	O
of	O
the	O
Hearse	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Felony	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
'em	O
answer	O
'd	O
We	O
know	O
that	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
tis	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
Whipping	O
bout	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Pendant	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Deposed	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
snatch	O
the	O
Pendant	O
from	O
the	O
Hearse	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
call	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sanson	I-pers
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Hearse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
right	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
Shenkin	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
.	O
No	O
inteet	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
hur	O
was	O
not	O
mettle	O
with	O
'em	O
for	O
the	O
Farld	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
spoke	O
,	O
2	O
Men	O
reached	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Pendant	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
were	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cordingly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
Porridge	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Cordingly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
John	O
Cordingly	O
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lemon-Street	B-place
Goodmans-fields	I-place
,	O
our	O
Kitchin	O
is	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Windows	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
Pallisades	O
before	O
'em	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Window	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Flap	O
that	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
let	O
down	O
lies	O
aslope	O
over	O
the	O
little	O
Airey	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
the	O
Weather	O
.	O
The	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
all	O
made	O
fast	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
taken	O
off	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
Ally	O
opposite	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
Sir	O
Tho	B-pers
Master	I-pers
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Edgehill	I-pers
a	O
Watch-man	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Hearing	O
somebody	O
cry	O
Watch	O
and	O
Thieves	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Men	O
pulling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
the	O
Pallisades	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
what	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
,	O
will	O
ye	O
tear	O
my	O
cloths	O
to	O
pieces	O
?	O
And	O
afterwards	O
searching	O
behind	O
the	O
Pallisades	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
without	O
side	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Old	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
half	O
in	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Plates	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
rais	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Caryl	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Lemon-Street	O
;	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Persons	O
standing	O
together	O
and	O
whispering	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
to	O
listen	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
yonder	O
stands	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
betray	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
watcht	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
Goods	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
off	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
Mr.	O
Old	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
her	O
we	O
found	O
8	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Pot-lid	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pallisades	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
over	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
ravish	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Standard	I-pers
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Betts	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
Boy	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fern	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
for	O
another	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
stopt	O
by	O
Tho	B-pers
Port	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Half	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ward	O
and	O
Prat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
half	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
behind	O
a	O
Puncheon	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
walking	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
observed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wrapt	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Paneir-Alley	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
Alias	I-pers
Cuningham	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cuningham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	O
Green	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
Instant	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Person	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
-	O
Lane	O
,	O
of	O
Tower-Street	B-place
,	O
Victualler	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
willful	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
injure	O
James	B-pers
Ashly	I-pers
,	O
by	O
making	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
,	O
in	O
Nov.	O
last	O
;	O
1	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Ashly	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Tipstaff	O
,	O
arrested	O
her	O
at	O
an	O
unreasonable	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
at	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
Bail	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
carried	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wattle	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
no-body	O
could	O
take	O
bail	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Judge	O
who	O
granted	O
the	O
Warrant	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
kept	O
her	O
there	O
a	O
Day	O
and	O
a	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Demanded	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
Guineas	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
Expences	O
and	O
Civility	O
;	O
when	O
,	O
in	O
Truth	O
,	O
every	O
Particular	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
false	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Words	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
exactly	O
agreeing	O
with	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Knowls	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sturgis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
;	O
2	O
Riding	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Stable-Keeper	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
stoln	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
forewarn	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Stables	O
:	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
'em	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Saddle	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
Hog	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
stitch	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
)	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
at	O
Rag-Fair	B-place
;	O
where	O
he	O
also	O
sold	O
one	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	B-place
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
Loose	O
all	O
Night	O
o	O
'	O
Christmas	O
Eve	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
needs	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
Sorts	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Spring-Gardens	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Dear	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
Fancy	O
for	O
going	O
home	O
so	O
soon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Night-Cellar	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
,	O
by	O
our	O
selves	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
my	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
of	O
my	O
Neck	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
drowsy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
knowhowish	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
mist	O
'em	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereof	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
searched	O
her	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Fellow	O
in	O
Spring-Garden	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
shun	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Night-House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Purl	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
my	O
Purl	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
bold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
alias	I-pers
William	I-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Makeness	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Nov	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Gin-Shop	O
in	O
Broad	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Ames	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
were	O
drinking	O
likewise	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Jarvis	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Ames	I-pers
after	O
them	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Ames	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
holding	O
the	O
Wig	O
betwixt	O
'em	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
Anne	O
Jarvis	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Jury	O
likewise	O
acquitted	O
these	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
was	O
Landlord	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
in	O
Old-Street	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Low	O
was	O
his	O
Tenant	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
Default	O
of	O
paying	O
Rent	O
,	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
Tyler	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
in	O
Rotten-Row	O
,	O
Douglass	O
and	O
-	O
Low	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Son	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Low	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
common	O
Discourse	O
,	O
Low	O
told	O
Tyler	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mothers	O
Landlord	O
would	O
seize	O
her	O
Goods	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
moved	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
desir	O
'd	O
Tyler	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Tyler	O
went	O
with	O
'em	O
.	O
Between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bruce	O
coming	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
within	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Light	O
and	O
Assistance	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
Goods	O
bundled	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
higher	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
.	O
But	O
Low	O
was	O
already	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
Tyler	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
'em	O
both	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Torrois-Shell	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Viscount	I-pers
Nutterville	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Follard	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Sir	O
John	O
Follard	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Lion	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
14	O
Shillings	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Ring	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
for	O
three	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Nutterville	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Ring	O
in	O
pledge	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Ring	O
again	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Gore	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Nutterville	O
,	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Queen-Street	I-place
,	I-place
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	I-place
,	O
she	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
Ring	O
away	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Seal	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Follard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Lord	O
gave	O
'em	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Present	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
brought	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
overcame	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
proved	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
sent	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
Guineas	O
more	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Lord	O
's	O
Gentleman	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Reflection	O
might	O
be	O
cast	O
upon	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
common	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
paid	O
me	O
weekly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
Chariot	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
High-Cross	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Hinges	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Sibborn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ript	O
the	O
Hinges	O
off	O
some	O
Doors	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
)	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Price	I-pers
wash	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
a	O
Distiller	O
,	O
in	O
White-Chappel	B-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
some	O
Questions	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
just	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Seagar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Tench	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Eels	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
60	O
Flounders	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Anchor	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
's	O
Barge	O
at	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Boat	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
,	O
he	O
row	O
'd	O
to	O
Strand	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Green	I-place
,	O
betwixt	O
Chiswick	O
and	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
the	O
Fish	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Well	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
's	O
Boat	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Ratty	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Amos	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
entring	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Absalom	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hatch	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
bolted	O
by	O
Anne	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
backward	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Customer	O
calling	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Hatch	O
unbolted	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
laid	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
some	O
Tricks	O
with	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
therefore	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
prevent	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
imprison	O
'd	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whoran	I-pers
,	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pinard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
2.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sells	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mattocks	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
I.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whoran	I-pers
,	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5.	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Mold	I-pers
,	O
Jenkin	O
Evans	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pinard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
24.	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
Phillis	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Fowell	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fells	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellwood	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Pert	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sturges	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Moore	O
alias	O
Murphey	O
,	O
find	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
2	O
Years	O
imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
alias	O
Owen	B-pers
Man	I-pers
Dement	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
2	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Amas	O
Stokes	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
I	O
Years	O
imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
