TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Four	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Paschal	B-pers
Fennant	I-pers
,	O
Bryan	B-pers
Marriatt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Byram	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Marmad	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
Randall	B-pers
Randalls	I-pers
,	O
Nebemiah	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tett	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Bronker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gloucestershire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
pursuing	O
her	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
Fellow	O
Servants	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Bow-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
)	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patience	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulcher	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Stennet	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Stennet	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
going	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
accidentally	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Harms	O
way	O
)	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
this	O
good	O
Company	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Feet	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stennet	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
he	O
charged	O
it	O
upon	O
Goodman	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
positively	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
not	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perrine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Matthew	I-place
Friday-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pint	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Enoch	B-pers
Steeple	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Steeple	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
least	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
but	O
receiving	O
a	O
Letter	O
that	O
Night	O
from	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Tankard	O
bearing	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breaches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Hempson	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Taylor	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Breeches	O
to	O
repair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
from	O
his	O
Stall	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Goose	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
they	O
was	O
whipt	O
away	O
before	O
a	O
Man	O
could	O
well	O
have	O
swallowed	O
a	O
pickle	O
Cucumber	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Grubb	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
something	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
stopt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
own	O
Breeches	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Coombs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
White	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cuff	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
there	O
confess	O
'd	O
her	O
taking	O
and	O
pawning	O
them	O
at	O
one	O
Stone	O
's	O
in	O
Barbakin	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
was	O
found	O
:	O
Her	O
Defence	O
being	O
weak	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Shelly	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
before	O
a	O
Chair	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Boy	O
cross	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
open	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fearing	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
Mischief	O
in	O
design	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
more	O
Occasion	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
himself	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
following	O
him	O
hard	O
,	O
saw	O
another	O
join	O
and	O
run	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
latter	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
affirm	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Wellkin	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shelly	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
it	O
,	O
Wellkin	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
might	O
easily	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
learn	O
'd	O
his	O
Lesson	O
in	O
Newgate	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
intirely	O
:	O
Wellkin	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
two	O
Hats	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
snatched	O
from	O
a	O
Boy	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
because	O
in	O
tossing	O
up	O
for	O
Half-pence	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
losing	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
sufficient	O
People	O
appearing	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Laughland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cloth	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
she	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
offering	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Table-cloth	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
it	O
his	O
Sister	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
12	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Grandfather	O
appearing	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Name	O
is	O
T	O
,	O
H	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
,	O
M	B-pers
,	I-pers
P	I-pers
,	O
S	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
,	O
N	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swear	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Middle-Temple	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hatsell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
3	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
5	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hatsell	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Room	O
open	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
fetching	O
the	O
Watch	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Body	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
he	O
made	O
further	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
understood	O
that	O
a	O
Porter	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
his	O
Landlady	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
Tom	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hatsell	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
Sherley	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
Eleven	O
:	O
After	O
a	O
strict	O
Search	O
Mr.	O
Hatsell	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
such	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Candey	I-pers
the	O
Porter	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
one	O
Nash	O
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
Candey	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Devereaux	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
his	O
Looks	O
would	O
not	O
obey	O
his	O
Orders	O
:	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
found	O
Nash	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
sent	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hatsell	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hatsell	O
's	O
Laundress	O
brought	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
Tom	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Devereaux-Court	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
about	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hatsell	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Cold	O
and	O
wanted	O
his	O
Key	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
this	O
Deponent	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
earnest	O
Pressures	O
of	O
his	O
Sister	O
)	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
invented	O
that	O
Contrivance	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
actually	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
them	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Particulars	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
:	O
This	O
Paper	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
written	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
several	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Crispin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
between	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
and	O
5	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
eleven	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
an	O
empty	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
William	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
finding	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
(	O
his	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbours	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
idle	O
People	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
their	O
House	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
empty	O
Cask	O
,	O
the	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Brandy	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Gowns	O
on	O
the	O
Persons	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Green	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
in	O
Leicester-street	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bays	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
all	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Robert	O
Green	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
(	O
this	O
lookt	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
industrious	O
on	O
an	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
kick	O
'd	O
against	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
N	O
B.	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Beef	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
Composition	O
for	O
a	O
Bundle	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
withal	O
)	O
now	O
I	O
being	O
honest	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
Crispin	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Green	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
we	O
all	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
together	O
)	O
to	O
contrive	O
how	O
the	O
right	O
Owners	O
might	O
come	O
by	O
their	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
wherewithal	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Cryer	O
,	O
and	O
Whilst	O
we	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
prosecute	O
this	O
honest	O
Intention	O
,	O
we	O
was	O
all	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
;	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
fine	O
Pretence	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
justify	O
a	O
bad	O
Action	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
too	O
evident	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
be	O
impos	O
'd	O
on	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Women	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
Power	O
and	O
Influence	O
of	O
their	O
Husbands	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	O
and	O
Crispin	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
22	O
Guineas	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
accidentally	O
fell	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
altogether	O
at	O
his	O
Expences	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
waking	O
,	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powess	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
perceive	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
hearing	O
next	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
losing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
Directions	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
deposd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perswade	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laying	O
one	O
Leg	O
over	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Posture	O
,	O
as	O
betray	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
good	O
Design	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willsom	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Apple	O
in	O
Little	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
with	O
14	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
other	O
Account	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
evidently	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Ernest	B-pers
Swissleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
65	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Captain	O
William	B-pers
Scuthby	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
missing	O
his	O
Gold	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
Serjeant	O
Crawford	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
Expedition	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
Crawford	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
first	O
to	O
some	O
Places	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
mounted	O
on	O
Horseback	O
with	O
a	O
Guide	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
of	O
his	O
Retinue	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
seizing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
60	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
telling	O
Mr.	O
Crawford	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Rochester	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Chattersen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
5	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
evidently	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Stuff-Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	O
,	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachael	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
which	O
she	O
barbarously	O
stript	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	B-place
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Billcox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Boyer	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver-Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
29	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hotchkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Efferidge	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fussian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bedson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pomphret	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Frock	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
frisky	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
does	O
not	O
wear	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
did	O
like	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Owner	O
hearing	O
or	O
suspecting	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
instead	O
of	O
ordering	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
bound	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
;	O
(	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
:	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
my	O
Money	O
to	O
a	O
fine	O
Purpose	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Bedson	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
prove	O
that	O
Frock	O
was	O
his	O
which	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
allow	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
under	O
an	O
Obligation	O
,	O
has	O
slipt	O
his	O
Neck	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Lurch	O
:	O
Thus	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
not	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blanchervill	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Hibernian	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Hannah	B-pers
Prout	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Degauge	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
Madam	O
Maria	B-pers
Chevilliere	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
Me	O
come	O
fro	O
Franca	O
,	O
whear	O
de	O
Preshoner	O
have	O
de	O
toder	O
Wife	O
,	O
it	O
be	O
at	O
de	O
great	O
Shirte	O
da	O
call	O
Doway	O
,	O
me	O
be	O
upon	O
da	O
Wedding	O
,	O
me	O
see	O
'd	O
it	O
wid	O
me	O
own	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
will	O
prove	O
dat	O
Man	O
,	O
Monsieur	O
Blanchervill	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
de	O
ver	O
Perso	O
-	O
after	O
he	O
mar	O
Madam	O
Degauge	O
,	O
he	O
go	O
keep	O
de	O
great	O
Inn	O
at	O
Ghent	O
,	O
it	O
be	O
de	O
Sign	O
of	O
de	O
-	O
Sign	O
of	O
de	O
-	O
Sign	O
of	O
de	O
-	O
I	O
forget	O
dat	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
be	O
de	O
great	O
Inn	O
-	O
by	O
the	O
shame	O
Token	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
hire	O
-	O
wat	O
you	O
call	O
datting	O
like	O
de	O
little	O
Coach	O
wid	O
two	O
Weel	O
-	O
de	O
Sha	O
-	O
ow	O
-	O
de	O
Sha	O
-	O
me	O
hire	O
de	O
Sha	O
,	O
and	O
dare	O
me	O
she	O
his	O
toder	O
Wife	O
-	O
dis	O
me	O
swear	O
upon	O
bot	O
de	O
Bible	O
and	O
de	O
Testementee	O
But	O
though	O
this	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
his	O
former	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Degage	O
,	O
his	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Prout	I-pers
was	O
not	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
married	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Blanchervill	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
by	O
his	O
Register	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
with	O
Stones	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
Face	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
yet	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
:	O
The	O
Court	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Questions	O
to	O
put	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
owe	O
him	O
any	O
Thing	O
for	O
Milk	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
My	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
seeing	O
some	O
Stones	O
,	O
I	O
flung	O
'em	O
at	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
House	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sate	O
upon	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
considerable	O
Time	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
laid	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
her	O
with	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
his	O
Examination	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
it	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
Quarrelling	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Son	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pulled	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
kill	O
them	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Son	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
Time	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
hinder	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
)	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Mignard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
found	O
two	O
Contusions	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
the	O
Left	O
Eye	O
and	O
Ear	O
bruised	O
and	O
torn	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Nose	O
slatted	O
to	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Susmith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
Crazy	O
Person	O
,	O
not	O
taking	O
his	O
natural	O
Rest	O
,	O
but	O
magotting	O
and	O
rambling	O
like	O
a	O
Mad-man	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
at	O
Times	O
he	O
was	O
besides	O
himself	O
,	O
especially	O
at	O
Spring	O
and	O
Fall	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
seldom	O
in	O
a	O
Capacity	O
to	O
follow	O
Business	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
desired	O
the	O
Question	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
Whether	O
he	O
was	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Examination	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
answered	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
13	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
sometimes	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
Houses	O
and	O
demand	O
such	O
Things	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
Opposition	O
he	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
tyrannized	O
over	O
them	O
that	O
feared	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
Son	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
troubled	O
in	O
Mind	O
on	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
cheated	O
of	O
an	O
Estate	O
by	O
his	O
Brother	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
a	O
Soldier	O
for	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
several	O
dangerous	O
Wounds	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
still	O
several	O
Marks	O
to	O
shew	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
it	O
probable	O
those	O
Wound	O
's	O
might	O
weaken	O
his	O
Intellectuals	O
.	O
Mr	O
Allen	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
during	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
like	O
a	O
Madman	O
,	O
telling	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
a	O
Hat	O
full	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
shewing	O
his	O
empty	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
bidding	O
them	O
take	O
them	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
these	O
Extravagancies	O
he	O
performed	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
as	O
plainly	O
shew	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
in	O
Court	O
being	O
little	O
different	O
from	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Bedlamite	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Non	O
compos	O
mentis	O
.	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Amey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
Furnished	O
of	O
her	O
Weekly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
she	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Note	O
where	O
she	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
affirming	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
,	O
they	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
and	O
Paul	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edgworth	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Nichols	O
,	O
searched	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Nichols	O
then	O
confest	O
Bridges	O
was	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Carcasses	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Pond	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
slung	O
them	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
with	O
Stones	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
sink	O
;	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
Bridges	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
Confessions	O
being	O
both	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
murdering	O
John	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Not	O
guilty	O
Robert	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Mr.	B-place
Stokes	I-place
's	I-place
Amphitheatre	I-place
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Boxing	O
Match	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
getting	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Gallery	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Person	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
till	O
near	O
2	O
Hours	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
'd	O
for	O
climbing	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Gallery	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
getting	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Gallery	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
stoop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looking	O
another	O
way	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
further	O
Notice	O
taken	O
:	O
Neither	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
mention	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
being	O
murder	O
'd	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
Battle	O
on	O
the	O
Stage	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
this	O
being	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
before	O
it	O
began	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
this	O
Deponent	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
'd	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Staple	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
fall	O
which	O
James	O
kick	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Mischief	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Contusion	O
on	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Discolouration	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Starky	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Gillett	I-pers
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Boy	O
without	O
Habitation	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Stables	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Masham	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
broke	O
through	O
a	O
Wall	O
into	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Hay-lost	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
through	O
another	O
Wall	O
,	O
which	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Servants	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gillett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
5	O
Guineas	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
evident	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Deborah	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
thrust	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
herself	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
her	O
Girl	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Night	O
's	O
Lodging	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
little	O
Brother	O
2	O
Silver	O
Two-pences	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
remarkable	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
considerably	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Ring	O
in	O
Pawn	O
,	O
which	O
Ring	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
treat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
lived	O
very	O
merrily	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
former	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
concluding	O
,	O
that	O
since	O
her	O
being	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
bad	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
but	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Committing	O
several	O
mad	O
Disorders	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
stark	O
naked	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rose	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
4l	O
.	O
and	O
Seal	O
18d	O
.	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Nanded	I-pers
,	O
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Me	O
lost	O
me	O
wash	O
in	O
my	O
Kishin	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
take	O
de	O
Preshoner	O
pon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
me	O
did	O
no	O
tink	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
sush	O
a	O
Place	O
as	O
dish	O
;	O
but	O
de	O
Shustice	O
bound	O
me	O
to	O
proshecute	O
,	O
cause	O
my	O
Wash	O
was	O
found	O
pon	O
her	O
.	O
Her	O
Hushband	O
come	O
o	O
'	O
me	O
tree	O
Week	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
be	O
ver	O
glad	O
I	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
but	O
me	O
stay	O
,	O
me	O
foreshtand	O
,	O
me	O
Wash	O
be	O
upon	O
de	O
Pawn	O
for	O
the	O
Guinea	O
and	O
de	O
half	O
Guinea	O
if	O
dey	O
bring	O
me	O
dat	O
,	O
get	O
I	O
my	O
Wash	O
and	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
day	O
bring	O
me	O
no	O
Wash	O
and	O
no	O
Lorshon	O
;	O
so	O
me	O
tak	O
her	O
to	O
de	O
Shustice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
mak	O
me	O
come	O
upon	O
dish	O
Plause	O
,	O
dish	O
be	O
all	O
me	O
can	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Rashfield	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sugar-loaf	O
,	O
valued	O
4s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
valued	O
3	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Talkington	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Sugar-loaf	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wing	O
in	O
Strong	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Rashfield	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Talkington	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
valued	O
29s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Currant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Milliard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
on	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Shoplifters	O
,	O
left	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
try	O
their	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
11	O
Years	O
of	O
age	O
)	O
who	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
leaning	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
some	O
Spittle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
only	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
wipe	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
Coat-lappet	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
Defence	O
being	O
weak	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stamper	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tinworth	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
valued	O
7d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fout	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
and	O
Owen	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
For	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Fat	O
,	O
valued	O
10d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Crafto	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Curtains	O
and	O
a	O
Seat-cloth	O
,	O
valued	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
sitting	O
with	O
his	O
Partner	O
to	O
refresh	O
themselves	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
their	O
Chair	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
another	O
Watchman	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
very	O
busy	O
among	O
the	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Shelton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Velvet	O
Breeches	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
not	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Willaw	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Cofton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Quaker	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
through	O
Inadvertency	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
told	O
,	O
took	O
Pet	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
without	O
staying	O
to	O
take	O
either	O
Oath	O
or	O
Affirmation	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
valued	O
2s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Lodg	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Hood	O
at	O
a	O
Christning	O
,	O
and	O
fetching	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
she	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
gossips	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
proving	O
her	O
Design	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Farnham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Coleman-Street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Bibles	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
3	O
Common-Prayer	O
Books	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Gunnell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Books	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pew	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bibles	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Boswell	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
the	O
Bookseller	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
finding	O
Mr.	O
Boswells	O
Name	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
;	O
sometime	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Boswell	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Books	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Hawkens	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Lamp	O
,	O
Frame	O
,	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
Punch-ladle	O
,	O
valued	O
3l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Joyns	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Fire	O
breaking	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
near	O
Kensington	O
Palace	O
,	O
a	O
Bell	O
was	O
rung	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Men	O
together	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Majestro	O
Works	O
;	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
very	O
officious	O
in	O
helping	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
extinguished	O
he	O
missed	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
cryed	O
by	O
the	O
common	O
Bell-man	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
considently	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
Hesitation	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Silver	O
Lamp	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
further	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Joyns	O
's	O
Order	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Lamp	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
lifting	O
up	O
a	O
Tyle	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Lamp	O
from	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lamp	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Tester	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
Place	O
this	O
Deponent	O
made	O
him	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Silver	O
Sauce-pan	O
and	O
Punch-ladle	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Assistant	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
off	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Joyns	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
several	O
Things	O
into	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Apron	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
jingling	O
Noise	O
like	O
Silver	O
;	O
this	O
Deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Joyns	O
's	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Things	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
had	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joynes	O
's	O
Lady	O
,	O
though	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Possession	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
attended	O
with	O
several	O
aggravating	O
Circumstances	O
the	O
Jury	O
bought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hitchin	I-pers
(	O
under	O
City	O
Marshal	O
,	O
formerly	O
a	O
Cabinet-maker	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Churchyard	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
wickedly	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
commit	O
that	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
commit	O
that	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Evening	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Savoy	O
Gate	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
shew	O
some	O
little	O
Sodomitical	O
Civilities	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
pleasing	O
the	O
Taste	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
Leave	O
to	O
go	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
neglected	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
a	O
smooth	O
Face	O
and	O
a	O
fresh	O
Countenance	O
without	O
shewing	O
some	O
greater	O
Marks	O
of	O
his	O
Brutallity	O
,	O
bound	O
him	O
under	O
an	O
Obligation	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
leave	O
his	O
Hat	O
for	O
a	O
pledge	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
fair	O
promises	O
:	O
After	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Return	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
some	O
unnatural	O
Kisses	O
,	O
and	O
shewing	O
several	O
beastly	O
Gestures	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Bed	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Nightcaps	O
:	O
Here	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Writer	O
of	O
this	O
paper	O
would	O
draw	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
express	O
the	O
rest	O
with	O
Decency	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Curiosity	O
of	O
the	O
Reader	O
let	O
this	O
susfice	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
a	O
beastly	O
Appetite	O
could	O
prompt	O
him	O
to	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
an	O
actual	O
penetration	O
.	O
)	O
Next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
under	O
frightful	O
Apprehensions	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
should	O
come	O
thither	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
accordingly	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Relation	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cockrost	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
such	O
filthy	O
Actions	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
taking	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
saving	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
draw	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
whip	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Gills	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
frequent	O
coming	O
there	O
with	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
offer	O
some	O
beastly	O
Actions	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Cook	O
of	O
the	O
Talbot	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Proposals	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
intimated	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
two	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
most	O
Material	O
was	O
Micah	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
curb	O
the	O
Vice	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
actual	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Hogs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dollinson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
Information	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
search'd0	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
found	O
3	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Hogs	O
alive	O
,	O
pent	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
others	O
he	O
found	O
cut	O
in	O
Pieces	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
brought	O
'em	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
was	O
only	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
kill	O
them	O
and	O
cut	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
considered	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
Five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
one	O
Tablecloth	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Andrew	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vevers	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
21d	O
.	O
3	O
Peruk	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Bag	O
2d	O
.	O
a	O
Pigeon	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
by	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weavers	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Pigeon	O
to	O
Too-waters	O
,	O
which	O
Pigeon	O
was	O
to	O
fly	O
that	O
Day	O
for	O
a	O
Wager	O
,	O
-	O
Passing	O
through	O
a	O
Field	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
Pancras	O
Church	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
of	O
lesser	O
size	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Bag	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Pigeon	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
off	O
the	O
Tail	O
,	O
let	O
it	O
fly	O
,	O
then	O
taking	O
my	O
Wig	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Pigeon	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
resist	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
me	O
cross	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
-	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
thus	O
proceeded	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Knowledge	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
from	O
this	O
Occasion	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
(	O
we	O
moving	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
backwards	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
build	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
doing	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Weeks	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Times	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
perfect	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
Why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sooner	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
taking	O
him	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
without	O
the	O
Pigeon	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
Pickle	O
with	O
my	O
being	O
thrown	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tho	B-pers
Weavers	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
shift	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Carrier	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
accordingly	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
to	O
Too-waters	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
That	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
That	O
,	O
said	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
is	O
Vevers	O
the	O
noted	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
before	O
which	O
Time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
so	O
well	O
by	O
fight	O
.	O
My	O
Friend	O
advis	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
too	O
forward	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
defer	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Oportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
considering	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
really	O
he	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
begin	O
to	O
prosecute	O
without	O
good	O
Ground	O
of	O
Assurance	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Advice	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Mind	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Harwood	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
examining	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
and	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
withdrew	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
calling	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
swore	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
if	O
it	O
Cost	O
him	O
500	O
l.	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weavers	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
severally	O
repeated	O
;	O
this	O
latter	O
Deponent	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
Too-Waters	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
assaulted	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Feathers	O
of	O
the	O
Pigeon	O
's	O
Tail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
into	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
thrown	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Marks	O
remaining	O
of	O
some	O
Body	O
's	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
Violence	O
.	O
And	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
this	O
Place	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wig	O
in	O
the	O
Pigeon-bag	O
William	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
close	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
Velvet	O
Cape	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Vevers	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Coat	O
on	O
exactly	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
describ	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
furthermore	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
bring	O
his	O
white	O
Frock	O
and	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
;	O
the	O
Reason	O
Mr.	O
Vever	O
's	O
gave	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
Frock	O
and	O
Apron	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
put	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
soon	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
might	O
with	O
the	O
wore	O
Ease	O
recollect	O
themselves	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
living	O
two	O
Doors	O
from	O
Mr.Vevers	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
pass	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
having	O
on	O
a	O
white	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
Apron	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bine	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.Vevers	O
's	O
House	O
before	O
6	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Building	O
in	O
Holloway	O
Lane	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
after	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
to	O
a	O
Timber	O
Merchant	O
's	O
in	O
White-Lion	O
Yard	O
near	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
Deponent	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Timber-Merchant	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Yard	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
,	O
leaving	O
Orders	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
on	O
a	O
white	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
clean	O
grey	O
Stockings	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
about	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Barnaby	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
passing	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sealey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harkevelt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
about	O
3	O
Quarter	O
after	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meyson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mowle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Juke	I-pers
's	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
all	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
was	O
ready	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
was	O
that	O
Morning	O
at	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
some	O
seeing	O
him	O
at	O
6	O
,	O
others	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
,	O
some	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
others	O
3	O
Quarters	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
to	O
10	O
,	O
passing	O
and	O
repassing	O
about	O
his	O
lawful	O
Employment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Harwood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Gun	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
before	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Hesitation	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
during	O
his	O
Examination	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
several	O
Lies	O
,	O
Equivocations	O
and	O
Contradictions	O
,	O
telling	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
a	O
Watch	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
such	O
like	O
Inconsistencies	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
before	O
ever	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Harwood	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
associating	O
with	O
Moorfields	O
Sharpers	O
,	O
and	O
idly	O
and	O
extravagantly	O
spending	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
Boys	O
in	O
tossing	O
up	O
for	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Master	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
Robert	O
Gun	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
common	O
Practice	O
to	O
embezzle	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
being	O
judiciously	O
examin	O
'd	O
into	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
consider	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
granted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Table	O
cloth	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Barbara	B-pers
Maugham	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parde	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
to	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
and	O
taking	O
in	O
Pawn	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloth	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
)	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
proving	O
herself	O
unjustly	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
against	O
her	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
herself	O
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
came	O
by	O
accident	O
into	O
the	B-place
Barly-Mow	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
Water-Works	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
some	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
his	O
Company	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
want	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
his	O
treating	O
them	O
with	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Things	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
Silver	O
lac	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
,	O
fine	O
clock	O
'd	O
Stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
very	O
cheap	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
;	O
accordingly	O
they	O
innocently	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
lest	O
they	O
should	O
bring	O
a	O
Scandal	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
bringing	O
Women	O
into	O
his	O
Bed-chamber	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
their	O
Shoes	O
off	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
blew	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Maid	O
blew	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
blew	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
again	O
blew	O
it	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
willing	O
the	O
Room	O
should	O
be	O
as	O
dark	O
as	O
his	O
Deeds	O
,	O
wetted	O
his	O
Fingers	O
and	O
quite	O
extingush	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
rude	O
Manner	O
;	O
Presently	O
comes	O
up	O
his	O
Comrade	O
,	O
and	O
diverted	O
Mary	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Innocent	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
made	O
a	O
Sacrifice	O
;	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
without	O
some	O
Noise	O
,	O
insomuch	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
an	O
honest	O
Hybernian	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
address	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Ravishers	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
native	O
Language	O
,	O
His	O
House	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
Baudy-House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Kelly	O
willing	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Fort	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Chimney-Corner	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
up	O
his	O
Musket	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
thro	O
the	O
Head	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
interrupt	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Chamber	O
was	O
his	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
Death	O
should	O
be	O
his	O
Portion	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
incroach	O
upon	O
his	O
Territories	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
bidding	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
l	O
and	O
the	O
P	O
-	O
x	O
be	O
with	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Opposition	O
she	O
made	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
repeated	O
his	O
Familiarities	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
unmerciful	O
Man	O
had	O
once	O
,	O
twice	O
,	O
thrice	O
,	O
four	O
times	O
-	O
And	O
then	O
very	O
much	O
tore	O
her	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
Breath	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Comrade	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Companion	O
Mary	B-pers
Burns	I-pers
undress	O
'd	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Thus	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
till	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
Lutterill	O
the	O
Landlord	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
call	O
'em	O
a	O
few	O
Names	O
at	O
parting	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
drank	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Familiarity	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
proposing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
to	O
enjoy	O
themselves	O
,	O
they	O
very	O
readily	O
consented	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
taking	O
the	O
Candle	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
taking	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
Prosture	O
they	O
marched	O
from	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
loving	O
Order	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Lusterels	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
letting	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
both	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
Burns	O
turn	O
about	O
and	O
kiss	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
their	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
as	O
loving	O
with	O
them	O
both	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
no	O
more	O
Opposition	O
-	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Leah	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
in	O
drawing	O
up	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Writing	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Pay	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bar	I-pers
,	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
vile	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
makes	O
a	O
Practice	O
of	O
drawing	O
up	O
false	O
Powers	O
,	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
Administration	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
cheating	O
and	O
defrauding	O
the	O
Widows	O
of	O
such	O
Seamen	O
as	O
die	O
in	O
the	O
Voyage	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
in	O
particular	O
was	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
forged	O
a	O
Will	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
But	I-pers
,	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Mary	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Will	O
she	O
annex	O
'd	O
a	O
Probate	O
,	O
and	O
filled	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
She	O
pleaded	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
Incapacity	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Administrations	O
,	O
Probates	O
,	O
and	O
broad	O
Seals	O
.	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
Dexterity	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
had	O
been	O
educated	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
persuading	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
to	O
personate	O
and	O
take	O
upon	O
her	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Bar	I-pers
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
the	O
Relief	O
of	O
William	O
Bar	O
of	O
17	O
l.	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Wages	O
.	O
Of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cavernor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
Will	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Dartford	O
,	O
she	O
personating	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
herself	O
Eliz	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
;	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
and	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
on	O
his	O
Duty	O
impressing	O
Seamen	O
for	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
evil	O
minded	O
Persons	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
and	O
bruised	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
examining	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
Letters	O
of	O
Administration	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
defrauding	O
the	O
Relict	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Mariner	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Faulkland	O
.	O
Of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
rather	O
Rogers	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
obtaining	O
Letters	O
of	O
Administration	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
false	O
Pretence	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
Heirs	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
13	O
l.	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Service	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
Nassaw	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
proving	O
her	O
Marriage	O
to	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Locks	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
In	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Tash	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
13	O
Weeks	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Possession	O
of	O
both	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Waller	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
made	O
over	O
all	O
Pretentions	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Goods	O
;	O
though	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
clandestinly	O
granted	O
a	O
Judgement	O
on	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
last	O
Sessions	O
convicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
seizing	O
and	O
exposing	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
malicious	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulcher	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burgulary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
Bridle	O
2s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
Richard	B-pers
Confins	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Henry	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
Pawn	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Norton	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
Henry	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Rug	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Contine	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
which	O
being	O
evidently	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
insulting	O
,	O
threating	O
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
divers	O
opprobrious	O
Words	O
to	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
Lady	O
of	O
the	O
Bed-Chamber	O
to	O
her	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
the	O
Princess	O
of	O
Wales	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gradey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Partner	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
himself	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Countess	O
of	O
Bristol	O
's	O
Chair	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Countess	O
for	O
their	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hearing	O
from	O
a	O
Servant	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
stopt	O
for	O
their	O
absenting	O
themselves	O
from	O
Business	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Names	O
,	O
damning	O
and	O
cursing	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Chambers	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
insulted	O
the	O
Countess	O
with	O
vile	O
Oaths	O
and	O
Threatnings	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
Madam	O
Howard	O
's	O
Appartment	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
continued	O
his	O
Abuses	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Misdemeanour	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
Shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
Manner	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
4	O
viz	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Ernest	B-pers
Swissleman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
Transportation	O
32.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ransford	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Perrine	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ball	O
,	O
Joshus	O
Laughland	O
,	O
Crispin	O
Green	O
,	O
Robert	O
Green	O
,	O
Penelope	B-pers
Challerson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coak	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Rachael	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Starky	I-pers
,	O
Deborah	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
Rose	B-pers
Bradshow	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Rashfield	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
Issac	O
Pearson	O
,	O
Owen	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Crafto	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vint	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hitchins	I-pers
for	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
,	O
was	O
fined	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Catherine	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
for	O
counterfeiting	O
Letters	O
of	O
Administration	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pilory	O
at	O
the	O
Victualing-Office	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Leah	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Will	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pay-office	O
in	O
Broadstreet	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
5	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Month	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
for	O
insulting	O
the	O
Countess	O
for	O
Bristol	O
,	O
two	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve-month	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
Published	O
,	O
A	O
Merry	B-pers
Conversation	I-pers
that	O
lately	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
a	O
very	O
noted	O
Quaker	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
and	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
merry	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Hearken	O
,	O
oh	O
,	O
ye	O
Sons	O
of	O
Darkness	O
to	O
the	O
Sayings	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
of	O
Light	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
A.	O
Moore	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
Pr	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
by	O
J	O
.	O
Read	O
,	O
for	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
