TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
and	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probin	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Cumins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wellford	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Tringer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Barnett	I-pers
,	O
Herbert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dore	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Tesmer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wellson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wellson	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Patte	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Deavenisb	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Linnell	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
Bear-and-ragged-Staff-Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
18	O
1.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb	O
,	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Country	O
Man	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
Bear-and-ragged-Staff-Inn	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
his	O
Landlord	O
,	O
excepting	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Chamber	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
lockt	O
as	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
rising	O
at	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Assistance	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
him	O
searching	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
on	O
whom	O
they	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Midgley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Wastcoat	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gay	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Wamersly	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Landlord	O
,	O
who	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
convey	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
Occasion	O
,	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Colechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Druggist	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
)	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Piece	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Crown	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mr.	O
Norris	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
loose	O
Liver	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
once	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Warrant	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
by	O
the	O
Assistant	O
of	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Sky-light	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
descended	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edmond	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wallnut-Tree	O
Board	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
:	O
Which	O
appearing	O
evident	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Arter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Half	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
one	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sometimes	O
did	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
Money	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Forset	I-pers
she	O
had	O
mark	O
'd	O
several	O
Pieces	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Half	O
Jacobus	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Forset	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harwood	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
of	O
Lothbury	B-place
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Saucepan	O
and	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Picer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
loosing	O
his	O
Things	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
Merry-making	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
Cause	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
two	O
several	O
Places	O
:	O
The	O
Pawn-brokers	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
making	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	O
Plumly	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cowly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
an	O
Each-bone	O
of	O
Beef	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
wanting	O
Money	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
:	O
He	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Defence	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
Shillings	O
with	O
several	O
Shoemakers	O
Tools	O
,	O
as	O
Knives	O
,	O
Pinchers	O
.	O
Awls	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
for	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
his	O
Things	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
working	O
Tools	O
too	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
him	O
)	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ilewood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cheese	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Feb	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
a	O
Watchman	O
who	O
stopt	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Petty	O
Treason	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
willfully	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
murder	O
her	O
late	O
Husband	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tewson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
living	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
some	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
others	O
,	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
out	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Stall	O
in	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
Arms	O
;	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
kissing	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Blows	O
and	O
bad	O
Language	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
his	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
Hand	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
something	O
(	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
)	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceased	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
saw	O
something	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Guts	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
Quarrelling	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
behind	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Chopping	O
Knife	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
Meat	O
without	O
any	O
more	O
Disturbance	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
then	O
telling	O
him	O
of	O
Stepney	O
Moll	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
kick	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Custom	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
fight	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
this	O
last	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
fatal	O
Blow	O
given	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
flung	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
till	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reduced	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
2	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Knife	O
had	O
penetrated	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
small	O
Guts	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
belive	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
from	O
her	O
all	O
day	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
Rogue	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
further	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Scales	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Chopping	O
Knife	O
lay	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Back	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Knife	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
catched	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Left	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Dick	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
wilfully	O
.	O
Sampson	B-pers
Killum	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tell	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Stepney	O
Moll	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
lying	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
again	O
the	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very	O
barbarous	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Saph	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Yoak	O
to	O
carry	O
Milk-pails	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
affirming	O
that	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
that	O
End	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Iron	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Inkly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Coaker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Coaker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Parott	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellentine	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
a	O
careful	O
industrious	O
Women	O
,	O
but	O
weak	O
in	O
her	O
intellectuals	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
every	O
trivial	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Shoes	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
Stall	O
to	O
be	O
clean	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempting	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calimanco	O
Gown	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
Hens	O
,	O
1.s	O
.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
Harrow-on-the-Hill	B-place
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
refresh	O
my	O
zelf	O
,	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
Mistris	O
Betts	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
bout	O
4	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
ver	O
drunk	O
and	O
ver	O
sleepish	O
;	O
dat	O
Mar	O
Brown	O
dare	O
at	O
de	O
Bar	O
,	O
she	O
bick	O
my	O
Bocket	O
of	O
de	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
and	O
tak	O
de	O
Ring	O
of	O
my	O
Finger	O
:	O
I	O
she	O
her	O
the	O
Day	O
afrer	O
wit	O
one	O
my	O
Necklashe	O
bout	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
de	O
Constable	O
take	O
de	O
rest	O
,	O
here	O
da	O
be	O
,	O
lookey	O
,	O
see	O
dem	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
Jew	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Merchant	O
who	O
sells	O
Necklaces	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
comes	O
our	O
Way	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
by	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
lost	O
these	O
Goods	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
a	O
slippery	O
Character	O
of	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
search	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hillday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Copper-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cape	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
1	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Row	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
borrow	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Shift	O
and	O
Handkercief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquited	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dollison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
:	O
Of	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Confession	O
before	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
,	O
18	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
small	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
:	O
Which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Caper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
one	O
who	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
would	O
have	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dird	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pilfering	O
Person	O
,	O
had	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
from	O
his	O
Shop	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
.	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Frankling	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cane	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
It	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Neck	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Pinfold	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
worsted	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
9	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
marked	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
know	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodsalls	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
of	O
Sense	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Thief	O
without	O
Conduct	O
;	O
for	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Women	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
secured	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
which	O
was	O
Pulling	O
down	O
adjoining	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Overseer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
selling	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Dimensions	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lead	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
agreeing	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
besides	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
Hop	O
Merchant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Damask	O
Tablecloths	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
1	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
1	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Clouts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kimber	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Room	O
ready	O
furnished	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
carried	O
off	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
rest	O
converted	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
Use	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
Labourer	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
3	O
Rasors	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Roths	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Hat	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Millkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
:	O
Which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Stock-Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Stud	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rhodeway	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Design	O
but	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rowland	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Peruke	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
being	O
the	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
had	O
privately	O
taken	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Stove	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brampton	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ashcomb	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
conveying	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellars	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
at	O
divers	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
particularly	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
50	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Oyl	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
Journeymen	O
to	O
his	O
Cooper	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
take	O
two	O
Casks	O
of	O
Oyl	O
,	O
containing	O
16	O
Gallons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Celler	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Close	B-place
;	O
which	O
Oyl	O
they	O
had	O
fold	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
Use	O
:	O
That	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
other	O
Casks	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Oyl	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Cellar	O
under	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
saw	O
Ashcomh	O
take	O
Oyl	O
at	O
sundry	O
other	O
Times	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
converted	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
.	O
To	O
confront	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
Worth	O
appeared	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ashcomb	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Peacock	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
and	O
intrusted	O
him	O
in	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Consequence	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
discharged	O
his	O
Truth	O
with	O
great	O
Fidelity	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewife	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glanvel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
beings	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
had	O
heard	O
Higgins	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Ashcomb	O
and	O
Shaw	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
really	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Oyl	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
swore	O
against	O
them	O
but	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Ashcomb	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ashcomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
150	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Oyl	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Wallbrook	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
draw	O
the	O
Oyl	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Vessels	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
Casks	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
providing	O
;	O
which	O
Oyl	O
they	O
converted	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
filled	O
a	O
Beer	O
Firking	O
of	O
12	O
Gallons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
Conjunction	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
till	O
he	O
grew	O
weary	O
of	O
the	O
Practice	O
,	O
and	O
betrayed	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Oyl	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Miers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
took	O
two	O
Casks	O
of	O
Oyl	O
,	O
containing	O
9	O
Gallons	O
each	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
which	O
Oyl	O
they	O
sold	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Gardner	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Mayo	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Lucas	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
living	O
an	O
idle	O
Life	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
one	O
Hastings	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Which	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beaks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goddin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alderman	B-place
Bury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
Coat	O
Value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
Hat	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Spalding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
finding	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Gattorp	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulcbre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Ounces	O
of	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Meckling	I-pers
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Meckling	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
Mary	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
missing	O
his	O
Hair	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Confederacy	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
strict	O
Search	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Hair	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
Mary	O
Spurling	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
Martha	O
Williams	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transp	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
considered	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
and	O
discharged	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Davenant	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Gold	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
l	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
standing	O
with	O
some	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
at	O
a	O
Sale	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lady	O
Dover	O
's	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
suspected	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
peremptorily	O
denied	O
;	O
but	O
making	O
a	O
strict	O
Search	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Excuse	O
too	O
mean	O
to	O
pass	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
judicious	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
51.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Wyvall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1723	O
.	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sent	O
out	O
of	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pack	O
at	O
Huntington	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Dally	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Coat	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
living	O
at	O
Newington	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Sister	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Deponent	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
these	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Wyvall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
then	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
made	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
After	O
Examination	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
plain	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
Mender	B-pers
the	I-pers
Jew	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Jonathon	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confirmed	O
upon	O
the	O
old	O
Testament	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Volumes	O
of	O
Statute-Books	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Cook	B-pers
Attorney	O
at	O
Law	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
prosecuter	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
embezzle	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
ignorant	O
in	O
some	O
points	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Books	O
home	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
inform	O
his	O
Judgment	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
great	O
Distress	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
borrowed	O
4l	O
.	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Clerks	O
of	O
Cook	O
,	O
he	O
frankly	O
confes	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
solicitous	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
the	O
very	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
through	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
falling	O
under	O
so	O
severe	O
a	O
prosecution	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
Worth	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Patterson	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
both	O
sober	O
,	O
just	O
,	O
and	O
honest	O
:	O
Which	O
being	O
considered	O
with	O
each	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Hat	O
the	O
Property	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lorriatt	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lorriat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
aBaker	O
)	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
before	O
his	O
usual	O
Time	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
other	O
Servants	O
at	O
work	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
they	O
mist	O
both	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
his	O
Watch	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Horse	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
confirmed	O
in	O
his	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
overtook	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Goods	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
Which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
fraudulently	O
stealing	O
3	O
Beds	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
Pounds	O
,	O
3	O
Bedsteds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
pounds	O
,	O
3	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
one	O
Quilt	O
and	O
one	O
Rug	O
;	O
besides	O
Bed-Curtains	O
,	O
Windows-Curtains	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Table-cloaths	O
,	O
Looking-Glasses	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Tash-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
violently	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
Possession	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
a	O
Scire	O
Facias	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
not	O
only	O
seized	O
and	O
confiscated	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
,	O
but	O
likewise	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Ring	O
from	O
her	O
Finger	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
carry	O
off	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
to	O
Philip	O
Green	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
to	O
corroborate	O
her	O
Evidence	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
of	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
19	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Waller	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
a	O
Judgement	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
was	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Waller	O
owing	O
him	O
21	O
Pounds	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
immediately	O
served	O
an	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
80	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
examine	O
Woller	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
and	O
Title	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Means	O
that	O
could	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
such	O
Proceedings	O
.	O
Waller	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
had	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
properly	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
himself	O
guilty	O
of	O
no	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
But	O
to	O
confront	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
Barbary	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
Waller	O
write	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
over	O
all	O
Pretension	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
resigned	O
it	O
intirely	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Officers	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
Waller	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Note	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
laid	O
against	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
was	O
2	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Corner	O
Cupboard	O
;	O
taking	O
thence	O
several	O
Bills	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
600	O
Pounds	O
:	O
Which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
aggravated	O
by	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cuton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Adey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hounslow	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Will	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lemmon	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
bring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
receive	O
the	O
Malt	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
privately	O
conveyed	O
away	O
by	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Froom	O
Waggon	O
to	O
Castle	O
Cary	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
appeared	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cohoon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
Pounds	O
,	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
3	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dimity	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Keymour	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Walking	O
Cane	O
,	O
Cloaths-Brush	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
and	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
bundled	O
up	O
and	O
moved	O
from	O
their	O
proper	O
Place	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
busy	O
with	O
Madam	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
tumbled	O
in	O
their	O
by	O
Accident	O
;	O
which	O
Excuse	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Kennett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Barbary	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Hand	O
whip	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
whipp	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
a	O
Trifle	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
which	O
shew	O
'd	O
Barbarity	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
both	O
acquitted	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
1	O
Diaper	O
Tablecloth	O
,	O
one	O
pillow	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
with	O
Knives	O
,	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
18	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
a	O
wilful	O
Mistake	O
had	O
carried	O
off	O
her	O
Landlord	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
;	O
which	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
one	O
Wilson	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
Produced	O
Lawson	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Children	O
's	O
Coats	O
and	O
Frocks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
he	O
bringing	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
they	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
marching	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
lucky	O
Accident	O
discovered	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
convicted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Buttocks	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
seven	O
Ribs	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Endfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1725	O
.	O
hunt	O
and	O
kill	O
two	O
Fallow	O
Deer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
bearing	O
Fire	O
Arms	O
,	O
did	O
shoot	O
at	O
the	O
Persons	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
surrendring	O
himself	O
within	O
40	O
Days	O
after	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
arraigned	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
as	O
by	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Punishment	O
of	O
such	O
Offenders	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
denying	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
proceeded	O
as	O
in	O
other	O
Cases	O
,	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Buckle	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
Endfield-Chace	B-place
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
aforementioned	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Information	O
thereof	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clargis	I-pers
,	O
which	O
Information	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
evidently	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
Conjunction	O
with	O
William	O
Gates	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Vulcan	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
kill	O
'd	O
two	O
Fallow	O
Deer	O
&	O
c.	O
Henry	B-pers
Best	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
whose	O
Information	O
was	O
also	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
undeniable	O
:	O
But	O
in	O
Objection	O
to	O
this	O
latter	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Best	I-pers
confessed	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
guilty	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
he	O
concern	O
himself	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
at	O
his	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Henry	B-pers
Best	I-pers
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
facetious	O
Manner	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
for	O
finding	O
my	O
self	O
among	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
Rogues	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
without	O
Occasion	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Comrades	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vevers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
stop	O
the	O
Chariot	O
of	O
Justice	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
between	B-place
Hackney	I-place
and	I-place
Dalston	I-place
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
Value	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
his	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
distinguished	O
him	O
from	O
among	O
16	O
or	O
18	O
People	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
then	O
being	O
a	O
Star-light	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
perfectly	O
discover	O
the	O
Beast	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
rode	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
,	O
or	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
loose	O
riding	O
Coat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chariot	O
with	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Highway	O
Man	O
came	O
on	O
that	O
Side	O
the	O
Chariot	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
demanding	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
made	O
the	O
like	O
Demand	O
on	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
rode	O
gently	O
towards	O
Hummerton	O
,	O
swearing	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
Newgate	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
so	O
perfect	O
and	O
Idea	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
though	O
there	O
was	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
persons	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
once	O
fix	O
'd	O
his	O
Eyes	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Surprize	O
;	O
verily	O
believing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
Coachman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
positively	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
stopp	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
short	O
,	O
bid	O
this	O
Deponent	O
stand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
putting	O
forward	O
,	O
demanded	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Willson	O
;	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
Money	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Resolution	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
more	O
:	O
The	O
Justice	O
finding	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
hastily	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
Sure	O
such	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
as	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
without	O
some	O
Gold	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Justice	O
pulling	O
up	O
the	O
Lappits	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
espied	O
the	O
Chain	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
valued	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
his	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
of	O
little	O
Value	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
at	O
another	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
after	O
asking	O
his	O
Name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
Abode	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Footman	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
behind	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
further	O
Argument	O
for	O
Confirmation	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ride	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
Heighth	O
,	O
Shape	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Sprig-tail	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
Beast	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Farrier	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Sight	O
of	O
a	O
Mare	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
waiting	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Holloway	O
Lane	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
swear	O
at	O
a	O
Person	O
for	O
driving	O
a	O
Brick	O
Cart	O
beyond	O
its	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Accent	O
of	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
further	O
Confirmation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
In	O
Opposition	O
to	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Deponent	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
produced	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
from	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
near	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gramprie	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Vever	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
John	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Holloway	O
Lane	O
to	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
said	O
till	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
during	O
which	O
Time	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
Person	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Willi	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Jerem	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Corn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
All	O
made	O
positive	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
John	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
6	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
stir	O
out	O
till	O
10.	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
looks	O
after	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
especially	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Water	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
positive	O
than	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
to	O
gain	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
much	O
Elocution	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
be	O
remember	O
one	O
Action	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
's	O
Adventure	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Confederacy	O
with	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
buying	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hill	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
convicted	O
for	O
that	O
Trifle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
unjust	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Damask	O
Tablecoths	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kimber	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Kimber	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
fictious	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
they	O
carried	O
off	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
before	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
ac-	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Lateman	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
13s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boaring	I-pers
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Skews	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Coltis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
't	O
is	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
had	O
a	O
more	O
Natural	O
Entertainment	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
his	O
Drawer	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Men	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Sodomites	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
kissing	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
such	O
Actions	O
as	O
was	O
very	O
unseemly	O
for	O
Men	O
to	O
offer	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
raised	O
a	O
Ladder	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
the	O
Drawer	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber-Window	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
an	O
ocular	O
Proof	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
both	O
suspected	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
particular	O
Relation	O
being	O
too	O
Beastly	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
,	O
we	O
refer	O
the	O
Reader	O
to	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
may	O
see	O
the	O
Heads	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Brentford	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Orchard	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shoot	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
to	O
mild	O
to	O
accuse	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spurbrick	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Coat	O
,	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
could	O
then	O
have	O
found	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
given	O
him	O
Opportunity	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
hurried	O
away	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Time	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
confess	O
'd	O
even	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dring	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
both	O
of	O
a	O
loving	O
Disposition	O
,	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
awaking	O
at	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
mist	O
both	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
his	O
Bedfellow	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
he	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
learn	O
him	O
another	O
Time	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
watchful	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
with	O
one	O
(	O
Nell	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
)	O
who	O
was	O
laughing	O
at	O
how	O
they	O
Nickt	O
the	O
Culls	O
that	O
were	O
so	O
credulous	O
to	O
trust	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
boasted	O
of	O
her	O
biting	O
a	O
Cull	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Compasses	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
which	O
Watch	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
rude	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pickt	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
her	O
known	O
Modesty	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
enough	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
self	O
honest	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
her	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drinking	O
Gin	O
and	O
Ale	O
in	O
the	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Rods	O
to	O
whip	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
none	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
otherways	O
by	O
the	O
honest	O
Landlord	O
(	O
asking	O
his	O
Pardon	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Compasses	O
in	O
Sweet	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Thomas	B-pers
Can	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
chief	O
Crime	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
the	O
telling	O
of	O
a	O
Lie	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Wainscot	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
:	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
contradiction	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Haddock	O
's	O
Wood-Yard	O
on	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
they	O
affirmed	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
on	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
500	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
take	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Lead	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
that	O
Occassion	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
several	O
Contradictions	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
neglected	O
that	O
Reverence	O
which	O
is	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
behaved	O
himself	O
with	O
much	O
Insolence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
from	O
several	O
worthy	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Learwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
put	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
(	O
aforementioned	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Boot	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
sate	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Honesty	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Padget	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
commit	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
5	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
beating	O
,	O
wounding	O
and	O
abusing	O
the	O
said	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
on	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
Nurse	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
lacerated	O
,	O
bruised	O
and	O
inflamed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Parts	O
had	O
received	O
Infection	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
not	O
suffer	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Penetration	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
Injection	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
on	O
the	O
Orifice	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Barbarity	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tobias	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Candle-stick	O
,	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Salero	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dullerson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Brass	O
Inscriptions	O
from	O
several	O
Tomb-stones	O
and	O
Monuments	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
Church	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoredith	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Brass	O
Plates	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
detected	O
him	O
in	O
stealing	O
another	O
from	O
the	O
Tomb-stone	O
of	O
Justice	O
Pitfield	O
's	O
late	O
Lady	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
scandalous	O
and	O
reflecting	O
Words	O
on	O
His	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Pretender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Weatly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	B-place
and	I-place
Harrow	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
King	O
George	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
the	O
Turnips	O
grows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hoped	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
both	O
the	O
Pretender	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
here	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holdford	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
both	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
Words	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
repeating	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bellison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Stocking	O
Framework-knitter	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
taking	O
them	O
to	O
shew	O
another	O
Master	O
what	O
a	O
Workman	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
of	O
them	O
among	O
bad	O
Company	O
at	O
a	O
Ginshop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
3.	O
James	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Judgement	O
of	O
Death	O
against	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
on	O
the	O
Waltham	O
Black	O
Act	O
,	O
was	O
respited	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
Doubts	O
in	O
Law	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
5	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Kennett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
Tobias	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
4.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Gervase	O
Charlton	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
45.	O
John	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Arter	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Plumly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ilewood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Caper	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
Rowland	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Asbcomb	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Padget	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Skews	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Coltis	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
one	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
one	O
Year	O
more	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darlington	I-pers
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
2	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
fined	O
20	O
Pounds	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
1	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Books	O
printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
COnnection	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Testament	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
and	O
Neighbouring	O
Nations	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Declension	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdoms	O
of	O
Israel	O
and	O
Judah	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Christ	O
.	O
By	O
Hamphry	O
Prideaux	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Dean	O
of	O
Norwich	O
,	O
2	O
Vols	O
.	O
Folio	O
,	O
with	O
Cutts	O
and	O
Maps	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Dealers	O
in	O
Stocks	O
Assistant	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Calculation	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
any	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Stock	O
,	O
from	O
1000	O
l.	O
to	O
1	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
to	O
200	O
l.	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Ease	O
of	O
the	O
Proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Transferrable	O
Stocks	O
,	O
in	O
Buying	O
,	O
Selling	O
,	O
and	O
Casting	O
up	O
Dividends	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Clerke	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
House	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Physical	O
Dictionary	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Causes	O
of	O
Diseases	O
,	O
Chirurgical	O
Instruments	O
,	O
their	O
Use	O
,	O
are	O
accurately	O
described	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Virtues	O
of	O
Medicinal	O
Plants	O
,	O
Minerals	O
,	O
Stones	O
,	O
Gums	O
,	O
Salts	O
,	O
Barths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Method	O
of	O
chusing	O
the	O
best	O
Drugs	O
:	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
Chymistry	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Art	O
:	O
The	O
various	O
Forms	O
of	O
Medicines	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ways	O
of	O
compounding	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
Stephen	B-pers
Blancard	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
at	O
Middleburg	O
in	O
Zealand	O
.	O
The	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
many	O
Thousand	O
Terms	O
of	O
Art	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Explanation	O
(	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
and	O
best	O
Edition	O
of	O
Castellu	O
's	O
Lexicon	O
Medicum	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Authors	O
)	O
more	O
than	O
in	O
any	O
former	O
Impression	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
the	O
Characters	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
Physick	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Latin	O
and	O
English	O
,	O
curiously	O
Engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
Interest	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
from	O
One	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
to	O
one	O
Shilling	O
for	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Exactly	O
computed	O
to	O
the	O
Thousandth	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
Also	O
Tables	O
of	O
Compound	O
,	O
Interest	O
.	O
By	O
The	O
.	O
Lydal	O
,	O
Accomptant	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Excise	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
.	O
The	O
Words	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
for	O
exercising	O
the	O
Musket	O
,	O
and	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carbine	O
,	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
performed	O
by	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
:	O
With	O
Observations	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Beats	O
of	O
the	O
Drum	O
;	O
of	O
Ranks	O
and	O
Files	O
;	O
of	O
their	O
several	O
Distances	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
II	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
miraculous	O
Conversion	O
from	O
Popery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
three	O
Parts	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Edition	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
III	O
.	O
A	O
Practical	O
Discourse	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Sovereignty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
E.	O
Cole	O
.	O
The	O
Eighth	O
Edition	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
;	O
containing	O
A	O
,	O
B	B-pers
,	I-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Children	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Alphabets	O
and	O
Syllables	O
,	O
with	O
stort	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
of	O
dividing	O
Words	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
fifth	O
Edition	O
.	O
V.	O
Marshall	O
's	O
Short	O
and	O
Practical	O
Discourse	O
upon	O
the	O
Holy	O
Fast	O
of	O
Lent	O
.	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
The	O
Cambro	O
Britannic	O
Engineer	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Original	O
Mouse-trap	O
Maker	O
,	O
a	O
Mock	O
heroic	O
Poem	O
,	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
St.	O
David	O
's	O
Day	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Oxford	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
The	O
Singing-Master	O
's	O
Guide	O
to	O
his	O
Scholars	O
,	O
with	O
t	O
he	O
Psalms	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
and	O
new	O
Translations	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
Ewelmr	O
in	O
Oxford-shire	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
A	O
Further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Psalm-Tunes	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Psalms	O
are	O
sung	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
6d	O
.	O
IX	O
.	O
A	O
Small	O
Cambridge	O
Concordance	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
various	O
Significations	O
of	O
Words	O
of	O
most	O
Importance	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
annex	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
Supplement	O
;	O
wherein	O
is	O
considered	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
Christians	O
in	O
every	O
Condition	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
9d	O
.	O
X.	O
Baptism	O
discover	O
'd	O
plainly	O
and	O
faithfully	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Word	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Narcott	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
corrected	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6d	O
.	O
