TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pengelly	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
.	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
,	O
Bowen	B-pers
Witlidge	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pomphret	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bonwick	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Yard	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Boheme	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Heard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ogbourn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Penfold	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
140	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Lead	O
from	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cover	O
,	O
in	O
Brew-house-Yard	O
in	O
Hockley	O
o'the	O
Hole	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
leave	O
the	O
Proof	O
to	O
his	O
other	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blea	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
he	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
examine	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Sack	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
desirous	O
of	O
further	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
demanded	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refusing	O
,	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Blows	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lead	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
both	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
say	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
really	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
affirm	O
'd	O
might	O
possibly	O
fall	O
into	O
their	O
Company	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
some	O
Reasons	O
to	O
further	O
this	O
Belief	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Marriat	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Marriat	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Country	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
subtle	O
Means	O
inveigling	O
herself	O
into	O
her	O
Family	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
privately	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Manner	O
quitted	O
her	O
Service	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
converting	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Sheets	O
(	O
being	O
Holland	O
)	O
into	O
Caps	O
.	O
Shifts	O
and	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
which	O
was	O
coarser	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fawcett	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
Violence	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fawcett	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Gate	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	B-place
,	O
3	O
Persons	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
confess	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
about	O
me	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
loose	O
it	O
like	O
a	O
Coward	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
tore	O
my	O
Shirt	O
Collar	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
offering	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Intrim	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
though	O
the	O
others	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
so	O
close	O
,	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
their	O
committing	O
the	O
Action	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
night	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
met	O
us	O
,	O
or	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
upon	O
us	O
to	O
disturb	O
my	O
View	O
;	O
I	O
likewise	O
keeping	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
so	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
advise	O
him	O
to	O
surrender	O
,	O
and	O
protested	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
quit	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
thus	O
we	O
ran	O
from	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
to	O
Saffron-Hill	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blea	I-pers
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
Hatton-Garden	O
near	O
Saffron-Hill	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
full	O
Speed	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
then	O
being	O
in	O
pursuit	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
Post	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
Bell-Court-Gate	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pass	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
some	O
Body	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
(	O
probably	O
)	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Watchmen	O
who	O
take	O
three	O
Steps	O
to	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
their	O
Shoo	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
Coast	O
was	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
therefore	O
be	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Case	O
appearing	O
evident	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blea	I-pers
who	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stubs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Peercy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
a	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
alive	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
such	O
Tokens	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
as	O
gave	O
her	O
no	O
little	O
Uneasiness	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
about	O
found	O
a	O
Child	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
by	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
;	O
telling	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
Still-born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
her	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
immediate	O
Birth	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
Assistance	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
then	O
found	O
such	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
as	O
was	O
convenient	O
for	O
the	O
Reception	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
her	O
Delivery	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
such	O
Things	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Deposition	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Still-born	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
with	O
Violence	O
,	O
no	O
Marks	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
graze	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
might	O
happen	O
from	O
her	O
Want	O
of	O
Assistance	O
in	O
the	O
Delivery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
Noise	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
this	O
been	O
very	O
importunate	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
be	O
her	O
Bedfellow	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Husband	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
except	O
once	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
exprest	O
a	O
great	O
liking	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
Lover	O
of	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
her	O
desiring	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
no	O
other	O
End	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Secret	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
Advice	O
and	O
Assistance	O
in	O
her	O
Delivery	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
believing	O
from	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gothard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Sale	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Rogers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Play-house	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
she	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Rogers	O
had	O
a	O
Cloak	O
to	O
sell	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
reasonable	O
Price	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
employed	O
Lake	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Cloak	O
also	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
likewise	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
Goods	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
yet	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
several	O
Reasons	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Returns	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
positively	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
China	O
Bowls	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Durdain	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
idlely	O
for	O
some	O
considerable	O
Time	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
her	O
Apron	O
over	O
them	O
to	O
conceal	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
coming	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
Bowls	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Parker	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
undisputably	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	O
Barking	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
Ward	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
male	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
Smothering	O
,	O
suffocating	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
the	O
said	O
male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
Covering	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Allibear	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Charr	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Carbonell	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
thither	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
get	O
Breakfast	O
ready	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
Housekeeper	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
's	O
Indisposition	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Housekeeper	O
immediately	O
got	O
something	O
warm	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
this	O
Deponent	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
she	O
eat	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
bring	O
up	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
and	O
a	O
Brush	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
informed	O
the	O
Housekeeper	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
,	O
who	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
saw	O
that	O
which	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
Reasons	O
to	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
of	O
their	O
Suspicion	O
she	O
confidently	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Opinion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
still	O
denied	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
searching	O
about	O
found	O
a	O
Child	O
naked	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Garret	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Marks	O
appearing	O
of	O
any	O
Violence	O
offered	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
got	O
her	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
then	O
Child	O
's	O
Nails	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
their	O
full	O
Proportion	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
its	O
Birth	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
strict	O
Examination	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Still-born	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
affirm	O
'd	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
flattered	O
hereself	O
with	O
concealing	O
her	O
Shame	O
,	O
by	O
carrying	O
it	O
off	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
Privacy	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gastrill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Fryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
14	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Leather	O
Skin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Skin	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
being	O
gone	O
they	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
another	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
two	O
Skins	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
refusing	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Faiths	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
8d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
;	O
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
Basket	O
Carrier	O
belonging	O
to	O
Newgate-Market	O
,	O
and	O
ant	O
please	O
your	O
Majesty	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
ant	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
pickt	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
any	O
please	O
your	O
Worship	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
Dick	O
-	O
Dick	O
-	O
Dick	O
,	O
I	O
forgot	O
his	O
t'other	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
be	O
it	O
,	O
come	O
either	O
Dick	O
.	O
Richard	O
,	O
(	O
alias	O
Dick	O
)	O
Lyn	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
blow	O
himself	O
up	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
out	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
's	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
us	O
thought	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
fair	O
,	O
for	O
to	O
rob	O
a	O
Man	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
asleep	O
,	O
is	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
kick	O
a	O
Man	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Nick	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
much	O
Money	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
being	O
told	O
the	O
Indictment	O
mentioned	O
but	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
much	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
12	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
about	O
as	O
much	O
Sense	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Mind	O
for	O
Gaming	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
his	O
Coat	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
Dick	O
Lyn	O
,	O
they	O
sell	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
won	O
Dick	B-pers
Lyn	I-pers
's	O
Shoes	O
from	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Swore	O
this	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Reasons	O
for	O
writing	O
this	O
Trial	O
directly	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
spoke	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
others	O
may	O
provide	O
themselves	O
with	O
proper	O
Terms	O
of	O
Speech	O
before	O
they	O
appear	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Court	O
of	O
Judicature	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
please	O
the	O
vulgar	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
with	O
Buffoonry	O
,	O
this	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Entertainment	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
a	O
nd	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Carballo	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Snuff	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Brave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stratford	B-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Zipporah	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Charge	O
being	O
only	O
made	O
good	O
against	O
Carbello	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Zipporah	O
Cowen	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Crovent-Garden	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kenneda	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
evidently	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pepper-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
Mantle	O
,	O
a	O
Side-Board	O
Cloth	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watridge	I-pers
;	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Maud	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Catheril	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Theal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ryce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Solicitor	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
making	O
up	O
a	O
Broil	O
between	O
Theal	O
and	O
one	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
cheat	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
calling	O
it	O
a	O
clean	O
Snuff	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
fair	O
Palm	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
Foundation	O
of	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
proceeded	O
only	O
from	O
a	O
drunken	O
Squabble	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitepchapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
and	O
a	O
Duck	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Shortly	I-pers
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Fowls	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Readmourn	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
not	O
evident	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
indefatigable	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
so	O
industrious	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
Suspence	O
for	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
about	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
a	O
Bull	O
,	O
a	O
Dog	O
and	O
two	O
Chickens	O
;	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
dressed	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
a	O
Duck	O
for	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Game	O
Cock	O
or	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
Cock	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
aver	O
,	O
protesting	O
a	O
Cock	O
was	O
a	O
Thing	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Judgement	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Denison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hamiton	B-pers
Howit	I-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Knives	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
Report	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Highwaymen	O
and	O
evil	O
disposed	O
Persons	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
near	O
the	O
Pindar	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
he	O
raised	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
proceeding	O
so	O
far	O
in	O
his	O
Suspicions	O
as	O
to	O
bring	O
himself	O
into	O
a	O
Broil	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Assertions	O
evident	O
,	O
the	O
Consequence	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Blows	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
)	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Rouden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
;	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Pewter	O
and	O
China	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
William	O
Rouden	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
by	O
Evidence	O
that	O
his	O
Confinement	O
was	O
occasioned	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
Malice	O
of	O
Norton	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
Jealously	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Foundation	O
proceeding	O
only	O
from	O
Jealously	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
likewise	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Shoes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burningham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Manchester	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
before	O
a	O
just	O
and	O
curious	O
Inspection	O
into	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
strict	O
Examination	O
found	O
her	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
l	O
d.	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kitchin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
going	O
to	O
Hackney	O
Church	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
their	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
after	O
Sermon	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
Stanford	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kitchin	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
Husband	O
lock	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
pulled	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
found	O
an	O
old	O
rusty	O
Key	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
Confession	O
:	O
The	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Newgent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willsom	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
Goswell-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
Occasion	O
for	O
some	O
ready	O
made	O
Shirts	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
Stockings	O
;	O
insomuch	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
with	O
his	O
shuffling	O
and	O
shabby	O
Appearance	O
they	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
what	O
they	O
soon	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
saw	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
hang	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Nolfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bushel	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Coachman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Boots	O
in	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
Servant	O
likewise	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
besides	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Belief	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Boots	O
of	O
his	O
aforesaid	O
Master	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Boots	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
having	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
a	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
they	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
they	O
was	O
too	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
too	O
large	O
for	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Leather-Clog-maker	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
London	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
and	O
7	O
Loaves	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Barley	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
pitch	O
'd	O
his	O
Basket	O
of	O
Bread	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Nag's-head-Court	B-place
near	O
Salters	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Customers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
his	O
Bread	O
and	O
Basket	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Basket	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Bread	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Bread	O
both	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
with	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Clou	O
s	O
,	O
Tablecloths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Baccus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Business	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Linnen	O
belonging	O
to	O
Furnival's-Inn	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
made	O
Affidavit	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Antholin	I-place
's	I-place
Friday-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Tablecloths	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Randall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
intrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
or	O
Chair-woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Vice	O
,	O
an	O
Anvil	O
,	O
a	O
Tarning	O
Wheel	O
,	O
a	O
Polishing	O
Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Cellar	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Cellar	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
Occassion	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
considering	O
the	O
Folly	O
of	O
letting	O
necessary	O
Implements	O
rust	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Use	O
,	O
very	O
orderly	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
Excuse	O
for	O
such	O
Proceedings	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
a	O
Cypher	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Diamond	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Coral	O
and	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sumnars	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackhoon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Strays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
on	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bew	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
and	O
2	O
Penny	O
Buns	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woolveridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Utensils	O
that	O
are	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
Midnight	O
Plunderers	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bigs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blacksmith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
she	O
was	O
drying	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
Marybone	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
when	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curd	I-pers
came	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
Authority	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
dry	O
Clothes	O
there	O
?	O
she	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
quiet	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curd	I-pers
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
follow	O
me	O
I	O
'll	O
stab	O
you	O
this	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
Marg	O
.	O
Stoaks	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
that	O
lay	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
Way	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Industry	O
and	O
Courage	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bigs	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
they	O
appeared	O
equally	O
guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Margaret	O
Stoaks	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Elizabeth	O
Curd	O
,	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
yet	O
a	O
Secret	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Tyrant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Tyrant	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
male	O
Infant	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
John	O
Tyrant	O
,	O
did	O
strangle	O
,	O
suffocate	O
,	O
and	O
wilfully	O
murther	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thorndale	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyrant	I-pers
had	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
before	O
which	O
she	O
asked	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyrant	I-pers
how	O
long	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
coming	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Tenant	O
lighter	O
,	O
enquired	O
into	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
miscarried	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
her	O
Country	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
burried	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Relation	O
giving	O
this	O
Deponent	O
some	O
Uneasiness	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
till	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
People	O
of	O
Judgment	O
viewing	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
all	O
its	O
Parts	O
being	O
in	O
their	O
full	O
Proportion	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
(	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
Surprize	O
)	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
Midwife	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
more	O
narrowly	O
if	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
come	O
by	O
its	O
Death	O
by	O
the	O
using	O
any	O
Violence	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Means	O
used	O
that	O
might	O
contribute	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
only	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
an	O
Indiscretion	O
which	O
should	O
be	O
avoided	O
by	O
those	O
who	O
would	O
preserve	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
since	O
Order	O
and	O
Decency	O
is	O
consistent	O
with	O
Humanity	O
,	O
and	O
ought	O
more	O
especially	O
to	O
be	O
observed	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
lest	O
a	O
Neglect	O
thereof	O
should	O
bring	O
uncautious	O
People	O
under	O
the	O
Imputation	O
of	O
private	O
Murtherers	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
believing	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
such	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hawbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Spindle	O
,	O
a	O
Hammer	O
and	O
a	O
Winch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wittingham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Plane	O
,	O
a	O
Chief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
working	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Bakon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
saying	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
cheated	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
as	O
the	O
saying	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
as	O
the	O
Saying	O
is	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rafford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Paintman	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Burdet-Gown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Barnfather	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gillford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sells	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
near	O
Hounslow-Heath	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
for	O
London	O
in	O
his	O
Chaise	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
Brown	O
stopping	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
Timms	O
fell	O
to	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
whilst	O
Perry	O
held	O
a	O
Truncheon	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
till	O
the	O
others	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
got	O
Assistance	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Iver	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
a	O
Hedge	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
Cane	O
:	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
undeniable	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
proved	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
each	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Elms	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
10	O
Inches	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
and	O
the	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
:	O
Richard	B-pers
Elms	I-pers
,	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
over	O
against	O
Suffolk-street	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
very	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Father	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
immediately	O
fell	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
use	O
a	O
Cane	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
could	O
use	O
a	O
Sword	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
Deponent	O
being	O
kept	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
coming	O
of	O
other	O
People	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
Eye-witness	O
to	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
heard	O
his	O
Father	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Pass	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
's	O
Sword	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
his	O
Father	O
did	O
not	O
Strike	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
when	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
Said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
Whether	O
his	O
Father	O
did	O
not	O
thrust	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
before	O
a	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
?	O
Said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Gilliere	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
seeing	O
several	O
People	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
strike	O
Mrs	O
Clifton	O
in	O
a	O
Violent	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
the	O
Blow	O
sounded	O
like	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
neither	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Obstruction	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
might	O
have	O
passed	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
obstinately	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
to	O
insult	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Violence	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
before	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Time	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
Pastrycook	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
a	O
leaning	O
Posture	O
,	O
using	O
his	O
Sword	O
only	O
as	O
a	O
Guard	O
,	O
not	O
offering	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Pass	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
beat	O
down	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
fell	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Body	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Motion	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cammeron	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
a	O
Pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
between	O
his	O
Fingers	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
flourishing	O
a	O
Stick	O
or	O
Cane	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
draw	O
your	O
Sword	O
Rascal	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
value	O
your	O
Sword	O
of	O
a	O
Farthing	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
use	O
a	O
Cane	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
giving	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
a	O
hard	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
length	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Pass	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
with	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
Violence	O
,	O
he	O
hit	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
which	O
beat	O
down	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
staggered	O
forwards	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cliston	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
running	O
at	O
him	O
like	O
a	O
mad	O
Man	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
fatal	O
Wound	O
he	O
struck	O
a	O
desperate	O
Blow	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
him	O
hit	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
Hour	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
against	O
Suffolk-street	O
End	O
,	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
learning	O
against	O
a	O
Pastry-cook	O
's	O
Grate	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
Care	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
must	O
I	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
flourishing	O
his	O
Cane	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Cliston	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
Struck	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
reeling	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Cliston	O
drew	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
only	O
striking	O
,	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
by	O
running	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
push	O
'd	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Hearing	O
of	O
these	O
Evidences	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
made	O
a	O
moving	O
Defence	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
express	O
'd	O
himself	O
under	O
the	O
utmost	O
Concern	O
for	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
that	O
brought	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
think	O
his	O
Life	O
too	O
short	O
to	O
lament	O
the	O
fatal	O
Necessity	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
of	O
preserving	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
Fellow-Creature	O
.	O
My	O
Grief	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
Occasion	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
far	O
less	O
supportable	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
attended	O
with	O
the	O
Consciousness	O
of	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
I	O
can	O
affirm	O
with	O
Truth	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
my	O
Hand	O
was	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
my	O
Heart	O
was	O
entirely	O
free	O
:	O
He	O
observed	O
,	O
that	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
already	O
given	O
,	O
nothing	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
that	O
carried	O
with	O
it	O
the	O
least	O
Colour	O
of	O
malice	O
against	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Man	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
very	O
Blows	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
were	O
a	O
plain	O
Indication	O
how	O
little	O
he	O
had	O
Mischief	O
at	O
Heart	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
unanimously	O
agreed	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
several	O
Blows	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
Attempt	O
upon	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Gilliere	O
,	O
Cameron	O
,	O
and	O
Lambert	O
were	O
in	O
this	O
Point	O
all	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Time	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Decased	O
receiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
forced	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Circumstance	O
that	O
offered	O
him	O
no	O
small	O
Comfort	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
doubted	O
not	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
its	O
just	O
Weight	O
with	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
then	O
giving	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
short	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
spending	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
the	O
Tragical	O
Scene	O
,	O
desired	O
Leave	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Liberty	O
to	O
call	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
might	O
lay	O
it	O
still	O
in	O
a	O
clearer	O
Light	O
than	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
took	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
hitherto	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
appeared	O
one	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
;	O
even	O
Mr.	O
Ehnes	O
himself	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
clear	O
in	O
this	O
Particular	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
might	O
have	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
.	O
That	O
such	O
Language	O
from	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
seemed	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
humble	O
Opinion	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
weakening	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
,	O
that	O
confirm	O
'd	O
it	O
beyond	O
Contradiction	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Night	O
on	O
which	O
this	O
unlucky	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Cavendish	O
Market-place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
standing	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
rushing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
almost	O
flung	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Deponents	O
's	O
only	O
saying	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
stand	O
there	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
most	O
opprobrious	O
Language	O
on	O
this	O
trivial	O
Occasion	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
followed	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
overtake	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
the	O
forementioned	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fitzgerald	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wounds	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
desired	O
the	O
Company	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
intimated	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
present	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
this	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
convince	O
their	O
Lordships	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Rank	O
and	O
Quality	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
;	O
who	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
others	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
behaved	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Civility	O
and	O
good	O
Manners	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
peaceable	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
commit	O
Disorders	O
;	O
even	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
his	O
Mirth	O
was	O
attended	O
with	O
Modesty	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
then	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
Quarrelling	O
or	O
Extravagance	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
begg	O
'd	O
Leave	O
to	O
mention	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
what	O
appeared	O
to	O
him	O
upon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Result	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
:	O
To	O
this	O
End	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
proved	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
several	O
unexceptionable	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
those	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
as	O
those	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
which	O
were	O
more	O
immediately	O
concerned	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
insinuated	O
,	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
,	O
even	O
by	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
I	O
ever	O
made	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gilliere	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cameron	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lambert	O
it	O
was	O
positively	O
affirmed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
the	O
immediate	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Destruction	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Case	O
stands	O
thus	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
humbly	O
conceive	O
it	O
does	O
,	O
I	O
question	O
not	O
but	O
your	O
Lordships	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
more	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
compassionate	O
my	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
than	O
condemn	O
the	O
Action	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
judiciously	O
weigh-every	O
minute	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
greatest	O
Stress	O
which	O
could	O
be	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
Action	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
simple	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
humane	O
Hair	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
:	O
To	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
produced	O
a	O
Lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Colour	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
inferr	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
his	O
Hair	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
time	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Identity	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
no	O
clear	O
Argument	O
to	O
confirm	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Senior	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-bone	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thresher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
as	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Interim	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
by	O
making	O
Oath	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
returned	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
confessing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
in	O
a	O
Value	O
.	O
These	O
plain	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
Value	O
3d	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
walking	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
disturbed	O
by	O
any	O
Person	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
jostled	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
he	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
And	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
in	O
contriving	O
and	O
procuring	O
Letters	O
Testamentary	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
the	O
Heirs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Moulso	I-pers
of	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
service	O
on	O
board	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ships	O
.	O
Honest	O
Dame	O
Wetheridge	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
was	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Will	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
they	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
the	O
Powers	O
to	O
one	O
Elliard	O
:	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
Disputes	O
arising	O
in	O
Law	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
Mistakes	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Anchors	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
Will	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Volantine	O
Cloyson	O
,	O
for	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Service	O
on	O
Board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Leopard	O
:	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
moved	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Clerk	O
to	O
several	O
Captains	O
of	O
Ships	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
private	O
Mariners	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
therefore	O
the	O
better	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
prosecute	O
his	O
wicked	O
Intentions	O
;	O
that	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
Practice	O
of	O
Counterfeiting	O
Wills	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
some	O
evil	O
disposed	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
died	O
on	O
Board	O
any	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
within	O
the	O
Compass	O
of	O
his	O
knowledge	O
he	O
immediately	O
fell	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
making	O
his	O
Will	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
assign	O
over	O
in	O
some	O
fictitious	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
a	O
well	O
beloved	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
deceased	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Detriment	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Discouragement	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
hazard	O
their	O
Lives	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
married	O
Man	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
form	O
a	O
Will	O
assign	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
employ	O
a	O
Sister	O
of	O
Wapping	O
to	O
personate	O
the	O
said	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
Justice	O
at	O
one	O
Time	O
or	O
other	O
overtakes	O
the	O
most	O
secure	O
Offenders	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
laid	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
suffer	O
such	O
Shame	O
and	O
Disgrace	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
for	O
such	O
Offenders	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catharine	B-pers
Banfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
inhumane	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
old	O
,	O
by	O
willfully	O
burning	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Fire	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Concern	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
burnt	O
from	O
the	O
Waist	O
so	O
the	O
Toes	O
in	O
a	O
surprising	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
its	O
Nurse	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
acquaint	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
its	O
Death	O
,	O
which	O
happened	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Nurse	O
would	O
have	O
buried	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
without	O
letting	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
secret	O
Cause	O
of	O
its	O
Death	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
died	O
of	O
an	O
After-clap	O
Fit	O
(	O
a	O
difficult	O
Term	O
to	O
Construe	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fire	O
happened	O
by	O
Accident	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
burnt	O
before	O
any	O
one	O
could	O
come	O
to	O
its	O
Assistance	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
believe	O
this	O
Account	O
from	O
the	O
following	O
Circumstances	O
:	O
First	O
,	O
Because	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
conscious	O
or	O
fore	O
apprized	O
of	O
the	O
Accident	O
.	O
And	O
2dly	O
,	O
It	O
seem	O
'd	O
a	O
Contradiction	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
should	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
contribute	O
,	O
or	O
be	O
any	O
Ways	O
assistant	O
towards	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
but	O
for	O
weekly	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Consequence	O
proposed	O
some	O
Advantage	O
to	O
herself	O
from	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
propose	O
none	O
from	O
its	O
Death	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Consideration	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Billbary	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
them	O
:	O
Which	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rose	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Router	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Examination	O
it	O
appeared	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
gilt	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Assault	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
a	O
Geneva	O
Jostle	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
Grandmother	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Christening	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
near	O
Windmill-Hill	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
Necklace	O
from	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
which	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Friends	O
made	O
Overtures	O
to	O
her	O
of	O
making	O
it	O
up	O
without	O
a	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
agreeing	O
to	O
their	O
Proposition	O
,	O
was	O
arraign	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
granted	O
her	O
.	O
Thus	O
they	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Court	O
of	O
Justice	O
a	O
Handle	O
to	O
commit	O
unjust	O
Actions	O
,	O
are	O
brought	O
under	O
the	O
Cognizance	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
for	O
such	O
unlawful	O
Proceedings	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Huoyes	I-pers
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
with	O
one	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
who	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
see	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
produce	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
made	O
him	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
;	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
hoped	O
the	O
just	O
Measures	O
the	O
Court	O
took	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
that	O
Occasion	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
Lesson	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
that	O
honest	O
Prosession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sylvia	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Noron	B-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Headman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
having	O
made	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
proving	O
undeniably	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Gin	O
and	O
Wormwood	O
,	O
which	O
raising	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
Elevation	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
Rudeness	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
perswading	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
would	O
there	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
familiar	O
than	O
her	O
Modesty	O
would	O
admit	O
of	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
his	O
Rudeness	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
his	O
Design	O
was	O
only	O
on	O
her	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
on	O
her	O
Property	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
P.	O
S.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Robbery	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Rape	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
Ill-natur	O
'd	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Galen	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
his	O
Wife	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
Accident	O
had	O
not	O
happened	O
)	O
need	O
not	O
fear	O
his	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
true	O
Inhabitant	O
of	O
Creed-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
Liberty	O
and	O
Property	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pickt	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	B-pers
Camickle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
his	O
Lordship	O
ordered	O
his	O
Servants	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
due	O
Correction	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
finding	O
several	O
Handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
thought	O
convenient	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
publick	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
a	O
Sapping	O
Loom	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
for	O
stealing	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
but	O
begg	O
'd	O
Corporal	O
Punishment	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
Sylvia	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Senior	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Cliston	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
27.	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Carballo	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newgent	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Haybourn	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Willingham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rafford	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Norfold	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Fenkins	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Anchors	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
over-against	O
the	O
Victualling-Office	O
,	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
Six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
for	O
stealing	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
but	O
begg	O
'd	O
Corporal	O
Punishment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
published	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
whip	O
for	O
the	O
Quack	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
M	O
-	O
N	O
's	O
Supplement	O
to	O
his	O
Coania	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
Answer	O
and	O
Consuration	O
of	O
his	O
boasted	O
of	O
and	O
long	O
promised	O
curious	O
Piece	O
from	O
Sekmeider	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
Arguments	O
for	O
the	O
Seed	O
's	O
return	O
into	O
the	O
Blood	O
after	O
its	O
Secretion	O
.	O
By	O
Muth	O
Rosos	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
likewise	O
Onania	O
Examined	O
and	O
Detected	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
stitcht	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
,	O
the	O
Words	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Exercising	O
the	O
Musket	O
and	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
with	O
Observations	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Beats	O
of	O
the	O
Drum	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Approved	O
of	O
by	O
several	O
great	O
Commanders	O
,	O
and	O
Adjutants	O
.	O
By	O
W.B	O
.	O
Gent	O
.	O
the	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
miraculous	O
Conversion	O
,	O
from	O
Popery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Glory	O
of	O
Divine	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Protection	O
of	O
Divine	O
Providence	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
God	O
manifested	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
.	O
A	O
Warning	O
to	O
Youth	O
,	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
twice	O
executed	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Maid-Servant	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
,	O
never	O
done	O
before	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Funeral	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
stitcht	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
.	O
Heaven	O
began	O
here	O
on	O
Earth	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Help	O
to	O
young	O
Persons	O
,	O
under	O
their	O
first	O
Convictions	O
,	O
and	O
Closure	O
with	O
the	O
Lord	O
C	O
hrist	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
continued	O
.	O
In	O
three	O
Dialogues	O
,	O
between	O
a	O
Minister	O
and	O
a	O
private	O
Christian	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Drawn	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
advancing	O
of	O
the	O
free	O
Grace	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
a	O
dear	O
Redeemer	O
to	O
the	O
Chief	O
of	O
Sinnets	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
in	O
Calf	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
6	O
.	O
Baptism	O
Discovered	O
plainly	O
and	O
faithfully	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Word	O
of	O
God	O
;	O
where	O
in	O
set	O
forth	O
the	O
glorious	O
Pattern	O
of	O
our	O
Blessed	O
Saviour	O
Jesus	O
Christ	O
,	O
the	O
Pattern	O
of	O
all	O
Believers	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Norcot	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
7	O
.	O
A	O
Further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Psalm	O
Tunes	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Psalms	O
are	O
sung	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
Introduction	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Four	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
