TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Pigg	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellit	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Giles	B-pers
Henchman	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Squirril	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Darvell	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sipsey	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pinnock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ansom	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Bermondsey	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
50	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Oil	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Oil	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
therefore	O
accessory	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
William	O
Wall	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Probyn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jottle	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
slipt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
him	O
and	O
searching	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
recollecting	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
possibly	O
have	O
did	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Barrat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Branches	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Morris	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
saved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
evidently	O
appearing	O
otherwise	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
small	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Money	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
particular	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
these	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
till	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
when	O
giving	O
him	O
but	O
too	O
much	O
Cause	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
mark	O
'd	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
which	O
Shilling	O
he	O
afterwards	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
12	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elisha	B-pers
Lynes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
with	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Padget	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
quarrelling	O
and	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
behind	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church	I-place
at	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
Hill	O
with	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
;	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
she	O
said	O
began	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
cheating	O
them	O
of	O
some	O
Cinders	O
which	O
were	O
given	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
lending	O
them	O
a	O
Sieve	O
to	O
sift	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
took	O
a	O
greater	O
Part	O
than	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Jane	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
catching	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
Passion	O
.	O
The	O
deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
this	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
complaining	O
;	O
till	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
Deponent	O
further	O
adding	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
broke	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Ribs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
and	O
a	O
Day	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
rest	O
in	O
his	O
Grave	O
without	O
Blood	O
for	O
Blood	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Plaister	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
some	O
Bruises	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
him	O
narrowly	O
about	O
the	O
Ribs	O
he	O
fancied	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
crack	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
recovering	O
and	O
going	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
for	O
some	O
Weeks	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Blows	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
were	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
himself	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Rib	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Callice	O
was	O
grown	O
strong	O
and	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
Nature	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
its	O
Course	O
and	O
no	O
real	O
Damage	O
remaining	O
on	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Accident	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Court	O
considering	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
above	O
Eighty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
natural	O
Weakness	O
and	O
Infirmitics	O
attending	O
that	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Sarsenet	O
Hood	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
their	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
privately	O
and	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
in	O
all	O
likelihood	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
'll	O
keep	O
her	O
sober	O
this	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Boother	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lyver	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
30	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
burst	O
open	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
with	O
much	O
Barbarity	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Lilley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
Work	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
William	B-pers
Norcoat	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
and	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
but	O
looking	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
desperate	O
Fellow	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seize	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Norcoat	O
confessed	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
Deponent	O
Directions	O
to	O
Girdler	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
remaining	O
Part	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norcoat	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
About	O
six	O
Weeks	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
steal	O
some	O
Fowls	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
soon	O
consented	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
,	O
though	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
no	O
Money	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
drank	O
heartily	O
,	O
and	O
crept	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
Door	O
to	O
be	O
clear	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White-House	O
at	O
Marybone	O
,	O
where	O
Boother	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
Fowls	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Hay	O
there	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
furniz	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
calling	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
Boother	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
Fowls	O
:	O
Before	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
we	O
began	O
upon	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
for	O
finding	O
a	O
Stool	O
we	O
broke	O
off	O
the	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
them	O
made	O
the	O
Glass	O
fly	O
about	O
heartily	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
we	O
soon	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beat	O
the	O
Maid	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
I	O
beat	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
Shirt	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
were	O
rifling	O
the	O
Rooms	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Deponent	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Boother	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Chaplin	O
likewise	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
actually	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
perswade	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
Pretence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
aiding	O
.	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
carrying	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
both	O
Chaplin	O
and	O
Boother	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stoke-Newington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Newins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Pasture	O
in	O
Newington	B-place
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
discovering	O
him	O
further	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
a	O
great	O
Occasion	O
for	O
Money	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
Agreement	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
45	O
s.	O
but	O
riding	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Grass	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
Falsity	O
,	O
and	O
comparing	O
this	O
with	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
speaking	O
those	O
Words	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
spoke	O
good	O
English	O
at	O
his	O
Examinations	O
,	O
this	O
Excuse	O
was	O
but	O
of	O
little	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ager	I-pers
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Devil	O
bid	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
being	O
prompted	O
on	O
by	O
an	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Excuse	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Bread	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
Chest	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
asked	O
Leave	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
returning	O
at	O
Night	O
they	O
concluded	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Custom	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
who	O
to	O
suspect	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
she	O
leaped	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
with	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Haynes	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
free	O
with	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
sending	O
out	O
for	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
restore	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
she	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
afore	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
an	O
undeniable	O
Confirmation	O
,	O
she	O
deliberately	O
signed	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mincher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dinah	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wittermore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foaks	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
ludicrous	O
Tarpollian	O
)	O
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
pickt	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Thames	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
4	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
then	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
-	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
there	O
for	O
it	O
-	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Anger	O
between	O
us	O
its	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
its	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
-	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
no	O
Body	O
search	O
her	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Constable	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
design	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lewd	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
-	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
modest	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
swore	O
this	O
against	O
her	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
disappointed	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Garonet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	O
,	O
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
of	O
St.Andrew	B-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skillback	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
Turn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Barge	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
so	O
satisfactory	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Forward	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Eades	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Bason	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Thornely	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
besides	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
about	O
him	O
a	O
Chisel	O
,	O
two	O
Gimlets	O
,	O
an	O
Auger	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
Flint	O
,	O
Steel	O
and	O
Matches	O
,	O
with	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
variety	O
,	O
as	O
made	O
it	O
evident	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
absolute	O
Master	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Profession	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
every	O
way	O
qualified	O
for	O
a	O
Midnight	O
Plunderer	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Virgell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nightrale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Routhmeal	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
and	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dellbeer	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Crow	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
(	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coxen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Allegation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Clement	B-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Johannah	B-pers
Armshaw	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
resolute	O
in	O
her	O
Deposition	O
;	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
more	O
heat	O
than	O
became	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
of	O
Justice	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Place	O
only	O
to	O
Swear	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
too	O
,	O
with	O
Decorum	O
,	O
Caution	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
calm	O
undisturbed	O
Disposition	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
not	O
forward	O
to	O
give	O
their	O
own	O
Opinion	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
Reverence	O
submit	O
their	O
own	O
Judgement	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
dictated	O
by	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
but	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
with	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
that	O
Justice	O
may	O
be	O
executed	O
with	O
Ease	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
due	O
Regard	O
shewed	O
to	O
those	O
in	O
Authority	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Evidences	O
on	O
her	O
Behalf	O
,	O
who	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
been	O
disordered	O
in	O
her	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
fell	O
into	O
such	O
Extravagancy	O
at	O
Times	O
,	O
as	O
discovered	O
her	O
Lunacy	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
sudden	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Hamilton	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
particular	O
in	O
this	O
Account	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
start	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
with	O
such	O
dreadful	O
Agitations	O
,	O
as	O
frightened	O
this	O
Deponent	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Wits	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
scarcely	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
recovered	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Ring	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Rose-Alley	O
,	O
Golden-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
2	O
strict	O
Search	O
and	O
Examination	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Tobijah	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Funge	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Lookinglasses	O
with	O
Walnut-tree-Frames	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Lookinglasses	O
with	O
Walnut-tree	O
Frames	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
Gerrard-Street	B-place
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Son	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Glasses	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.Simpson	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
another	O
Glass	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Glasses	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
son	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
Time	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wiggons	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
one	O
Looking-Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
likewise	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
Looking-Glasses	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
2	O
Looking-Glasses	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goodyson	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Glass	O
Jonas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
three	O
Facts	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Willsom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Morpeth	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
hear	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lord	O
Morpeth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Watchman	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
breaking	O
in	O
at	O
Lord	O
Morpeth	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
coming	O
he	O
laid	O
himself	O
down	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
dead	O
as	O
a	O
Herring	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Windows	O
crack	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
something	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
more	O
than	O
extraordinary	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
rapt	O
out	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
bloodily	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
stir	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
I	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knockt	O
him	O
,	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
assisted	O
Lockwood	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
raised	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
gotten	O
his	O
Body	O
partly	O
in	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
was	O
the	O
more	O
sharp	O
upon	O
him	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
returned	O
from	O
Transportation	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
Sunday	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
common	O
Road	O
near	O
Hackney	B-place
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
Jun	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
Sen.	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Coach	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Daughter	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
surprized	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
assaulted	O
him	O
bid	O
them	O
not	O
be	O
frighten	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
them	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
Jun	O
.	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
5	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Eye-brows	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
Dalston	O
and	O
Hackney	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stop	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
pursued	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
extending	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
presented	O
them	O
at	O
himself	O
,	O
without	O
offering	O
them	O
at	O
those	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Corn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
quit	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
jump	O
over	O
some	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Pistols	O
snapt	O
them	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Ears	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
pull	O
out	O
some	O
Powder	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
prim	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Being	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Blackhall	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Patient	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
frequently	O
Fits	O
of	O
Lunacy	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
but	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Deponent	O
administred	O
such	O
Medicines	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
with	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
another	O
Physician	O
was	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
remove	O
his	O
Indisposition	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pit	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Blackhall	O
had	O
advised	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Indisposition	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Blackhall	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
or	O
25th	O
May	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Worms	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
extravagant	O
Expressions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
this	O
Deponent	O
was	O
confirmed	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
frequently	O
acted	O
like	O
one	O
distracted	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
reality	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Senses	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
he	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
River	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Thames	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
persuaded	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
jump	O
over	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drown	O
the	O
Waterman	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
the	O
Water	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
fight	O
the	O
Indians	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
staid	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
some	O
Opium	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Journey	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
World	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
these	O
Extravagancies	O
was	O
acted	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blackhall	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Lunancy	O
had	O
ran	O
in	O
the	O
Blood	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
disordered	O
in	O
their	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Brothers	O
shot	O
himself	O
.	O
To	O
corroborate	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
Sen.	O
(	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
was	O
so	O
generous	O
as	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
coming	O
to	O
understand	O
what	O
Family	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
(	O
for	O
Montgomery	O
is	O
a	O
fictitious	O
Name	O
)	O
she	O
knew	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
weak	O
in	O
their	O
Intellectuals	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
considered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
compared	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
stopping	O
the	O
Coach	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Town	O
at	O
Noon	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
People	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
that	O
was	O
thought	O
not	O
worth	O
20	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Non	O
compos	O
mentis	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bewley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Handy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Canvas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Cleavland	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
at	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
thought	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
40	O
Pounds	O
allowed	O
by	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
baulk	O
their	O
Expectations	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
:	O
Being	O
told	O
he	O
must	O
plead	O
or	O
be	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Confession	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
indicted	O
on	O
his	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Presley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
by	O
running	O
over	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Croyden	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
picking	O
up	O
Gravel	O
Stones	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
near	O
Old-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
along	O
in	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
with	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
lead	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
ran	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
running	O
over	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
immediate	O
Cause	O
of	O
its	O
Death	O
was	O
indisputable	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Cart	O
when	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
deter	O
others	O
from	O
the	O
like	O
Practice	O
,	O
if	O
Examples	O
can	O
have	O
any	O
Effect	O
on	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
so	O
notorious	O
for	O
Carelessness	O
and	O
Insolence	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Constance	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
this	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eve	B-pers
Hans	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
evidently	O
demonstrated	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
(	O
a	O
little	O
Taylor	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniouly	O
marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
former	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
be	O
alive	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
Ann	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
in	O
Marriage	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1723.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
his	O
second	O
Marriage	O
Patience	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
second	O
Wife	O
being	O
present	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
Certificate	O
to	O
confirm	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
thought	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
to	O
confront	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
and	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
Sketch	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
abused	O
his	O
first	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
not	O
allowing	O
her	O
the	O
common	O
Necessaries	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
inhumanly	O
turning	O
her	O
out	O
nine	O
Days	O
after	O
her	O
Lying-in	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
turn	O
out	O
and	O
get	O
to	O
Work	O
he	O
would	O
set	O
the	O
Bed	O
on	O
Fire	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
which	O
inhumane	O
Actions	O
and	O
unnatural	O
Expressions	O
,	O
made	O
him	O
justly	O
contemptible	O
in	O
the	O
Eyes	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
Aggravation	O
to	O
the	O
Crime	O
of	O
Bigamy	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stephney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
and	O
2	O
Iron	O
Pots	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
6s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
began	O
with	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
Rented	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
herself	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
what	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
there	O
for	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
her	O
Poverty	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
extream	O
,	O
had	O
occasioned	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
loose	O
Liver	O
.	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
however	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
compassionately	O
considering	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
an	O
Object	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
acquitted	O
and	O
discharged	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Petty	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
wilfully	O
,	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
committing	O
Murder	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
is	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
at	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
came	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
Work	O
with	O
a	O
wrong	O
Tool	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Blockhead	O
you	O
'll	O
break	O
the	O
Drill	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
use	O
the	O
Pliers	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
more	O
Words	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Closer	O
adjoining	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
thus	O
Deponent	O
heard	O
his	O
Father	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
when	O
to	O
his	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
close	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
second	O
Thrust	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Decesed	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
you	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
then	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
already	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
mortal	O
between	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Rib	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Yerwood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
Occasion	O
for	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
to	O
use	O
at	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
saying	O
as	O
was	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
Reason	O
or	O
Occasion	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
Violence	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
aggravated	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
any	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
calling	O
him	O
Blockhead	O
for	O
using	O
a	O
Drill	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
Pliers	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
least	O
Excuse	O
to	O
make	O
for	O
his	O
committing	O
this	O
inhumane	O
Murder	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
what	O
they	O
alledge	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
and	O
Susanne	B-pers
Man	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Marriet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leaper	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Women	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Mug	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
flopp	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
kicking	O
,	O
beating	O
and	O
abusing	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Powel	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
Manners	O
as	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
's	O
Elegy	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
cry	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Elegy	O
before	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
my	O
Husband	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
why	O
he	O
kickt	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
him	O
old	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Stone	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stamp	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Belly	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
Cole	O
knock	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Fall	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
which	O
bled	O
excessively	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rideot	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Ribs	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Diffusion	O
in	O
the	O
Cavity	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
believe	O
that	O
his	O
Death	O
was	O
occasoned	O
by	O
any	O
Violence	O
that	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bartley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
remitting	O
Pulse	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Consumption	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
from	O
any	O
Blows	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
small	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
possible	O
hasten	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
of	O
no	O
Consequence	O
.	O
These	O
Depositions	O
were	O
corroborated	O
by	O
several	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Birchmore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Chawkley	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
Coach	O
Glass	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
it	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chawkley	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Benjamin	O
Hall	O
,	O
alias	O
Clark	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
Glass	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Cabinet-Maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
gave	O
extraordinary	O
Prices	O
for	O
such	O
Glasses	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
the	O
Pains	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Chawkley	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
very	O
wisely	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
applied	O
himself	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
further	O
Directions	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Examination	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
so	O
many	O
different	O
Stories	O
and	O
Contradictions	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
commit	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
of	O
Confinement	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Chawkley	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Hall	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Coat	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
borrowed	O
20	O
s.	O
more	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
telling	O
nothing	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
John	O
Gun	O
being	O
only	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
several	O
credible	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Peter	B-pers
Carefoot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
that	O
heinous	O
and	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Peterful	O
Carefoot	O
,	O
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
coming	O
a	O
Stranger	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
had	O
Commendations	O
to	O
the	O
Landlord	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Guy	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warwick	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
immediately	O
fell	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
Letter	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
in	O
Burleigh-Street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
his	O
Service	O
to	O
conduct	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
I	O
accepted	O
of	O
his	O
Offer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
Curiosities	O
of	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
consented	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
there	O
till	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sitting	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
kiss	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
the	O
Rogue	O
with	O
the	O
Girls	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
prevailed	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Guy	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warwick	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
kiss	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Such	O
Sort	O
as	O
is	O
Scarce	O
decent	O
to	O
express	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
himself	O
upon	O
my	O
Body	O
in	O
a	O
Beastly	O
Manner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rowe	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Guy	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warwick	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
never	O
consent	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
importuned	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
sometimes	O
Customers	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
asked	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Charge	O
sooner	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
committed	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
making	O
it	O
known	O
till	O
August	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Ways	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
on	O
Such	O
Occasions	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
Offence	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Guy	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warwick	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Indecencies	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
acquainted	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
with	O
it	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Reformation	O
of	O
Manners	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
examining	O
into	O
those	O
Niceties	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
mentioned	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
,	O
Paper	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Actions	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
their	O
Nature	O
both	O
immodest	O
and	O
filthy	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
that	O
grand	O
Action	O
of	O
Inhumanity	O
call	O
'd	O
Sodomy	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mullenux	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
young	O
Whore	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Bawd	O
)	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
upon	O
our	O
agreeing	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
conducted	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mullenux	I-pers
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Mead	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
before	O
my	O
Friend	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
old	O
Bawd	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mullenux	I-pers
came	O
just	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
young	O
Whore	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
was	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
immediately	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
my	O
Friend	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
Martin	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
Mullenux	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
's	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
After	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
pickt	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
Mullenux	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
to	O
please	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
loving	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
he	O
pretented	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
strip	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
-	O
Ann	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
Whoremonger	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
that	O
Night	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
at	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
that	O
is	O
noted	O
(	O
or	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
honest	O
Tom	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Wine-Office-Court	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Bawdy-house	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Woman	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
pawned	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Watch	O
itself	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
all	O
Persons	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Charactor	O
,	O
acting	O
without	O
a	O
Regard	O
to	O
Truth	O
or	O
Honesty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lutford	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
at	O
Islington	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Martha	O
Cambell	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
getting	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
the	O
old	O
Dog	O
's	O
Throat	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Sadler's-Wells	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Martha	O
Cambell	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
have	O
his	O
Blood	O
;	O
this	O
Martha	O
Cambell	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
formerly	O
been	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
married	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
Fortune	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
her	O
off	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
go	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
Insight	O
into	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
occasioned	O
such	O
a	O
strict	O
Enquiry	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
as	O
made	O
it	O
evident	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Robbery	O
either	O
designed	O
or	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
Martha	O
Cambell	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
Familiarity	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
using	O
her	O
with	O
Contempt	O
lately	O
,	O
was	O
grown	O
outrageous	O
;	O
and	O
Anthony	O
Lutford	O
being	O
her	O
present	O
Friend	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
Things	O
as	O
Friendship	O
in	O
a	O
vicious	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
)	O
had	O
assisted	O
her	O
in	O
insulting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Anthony	O
Lutford	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
been	O
familiar	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Solicitor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
reposed	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Confidence	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
instrusting	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
his	O
Debts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Consequence	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
of	O
late	O
uttered	O
some	O
spightful	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Law	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
Circumstances	O
being	O
compar	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
lookt	O
upon	O
it	O
only	O
as	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
37	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hollyhope	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
Personating	O
Ann	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
receiving	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bar	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Service	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Mary	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Flaw	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joel	B-pers
Lob	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
riding	O
over	O
him	O
on	O
Hampstead	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ventris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
riding	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
going	O
so	O
fast	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
unfortunately	O
rode	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
full	O
Speed	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
unhappily	O
not	O
hearing	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
so	O
much	O
Hurt	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
the	O
immediate	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Truth	O
of	O
this	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bewley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Handy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ladyman	I-pers
,	O
by	O
riding	O
over	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
near	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Several	O
others	O
were	O
riding	O
Gentlemens	O
Horses	O
to	O
Breath	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
full	O
Gallop	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
Design	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pendred	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Ducks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Pendred	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
some	O
Ducks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waitman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
knock	O
'd	O
some	O
Ducks	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pendred	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Noah	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Noah	O
Hollis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waitman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Pendred	O
,	O
knock	O
down	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
these	O
Depositions	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
more	O
Signification	O
than	O
the	O
Cackling	O
of	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
several	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Sherwin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
(	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
made	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
which	O
had	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
guard	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
Family	O
being	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
)	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
sharing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
amounted	O
to	O
about	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
each	O
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mayow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Isgig	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Honestly	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Blinco	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blinco	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
afterwards	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
near	O
Welch	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
stole	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
neither	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
nor	O
Mr.	O
Blinco	O
appeared	O
very	O
rigid	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
from	O
several	O
People	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Trifles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Stepney	B-place
Church-Porch	I-place
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
indecent	O
Posture	O
as	O
plainly	O
betrayed	O
they	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jeffereys	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
his	O
Round	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
Stepney	O
,	O
Church-Porch	O
in	O
each	O
others	O
Arms	O
,	O
naked	O
from	O
the	O
Waist	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
towards	O
them	O
they	O
laid	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
they	O
were	O
asleep	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
believed	O
then	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
a-swore	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
other	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
Beastly	O
Posture	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Shamefulness	O
of	O
the	O
Posture	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
concluded	O
they	O
were	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
two	O
of	O
those	O
degenerated	O
Miscreants	O
from	O
the	O
Race	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
called	O
Sodomites	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
perpetrating	O
,	O
contriving	O
,	O
and	O
wickedly	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Legard	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
Murder	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Legard	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
formerly	O
had	O
contracted	O
a	O
slight	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
since	O
run	O
through	O
his	O
Fortune	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
reduced	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Degree	O
of	O
Misery	O
and	O
Poverty	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
and	O
relieved	O
his	O
Necessities	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
never	O
have	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Ingratitude	O
and	O
Barbarity	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
fighting	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
overcoming	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Davis	O
came	O
and	O
proposed	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
Advantage	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
by	O
assisting	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
doubted	O
not	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
make	O
6	O
or	O
700	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Job	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
private	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doler	I-pers
obliging	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
detect	O
this	O
Villany	O
;	O
yet	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
home	O
Davis	O
applied	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
stout	O
Fellow	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
Meetings	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
to	O
get	O
privately	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Legard	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
least	O
Resistance	O
,	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
Davis	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
safe	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
otherwise	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
betrayed	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
this	O
End	O
he	O
provided	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doler	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
Doler	O
acting	O
from	O
a	O
better	O
Principle	O
.	O
very	O
ingeniously	O
told	O
his	O
Friends	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Prudence	O
and	O
Caution	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
appointed	O
Day	O
,	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
horried	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
by	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
Officers	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
wait	O
to	O
surprize	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
accordingly	O
:	O
The	O
whole	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
aggravating	O
Circumstances	O
it	O
was	O
attended	O
with	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Trifles	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
seeming	O
malicious	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
granted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Stennet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
and	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
being	O
adjourn	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
procceded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
6.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Boother	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bewley	O
,	O
alias	O
Handy	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
5.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Presley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
privately	O
1.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
21.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Barrat	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	O
Green	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
for	O
designing	O
to	O
Murder	O
Mr.	O
Legard	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
near	O
Gray's-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
their	O
Enlargement	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Sodomitical	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
Fined	O
6	O
Marks	O
and	O
two	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Painet	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	O
Green	O
,	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
near	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
,	O
for	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
.	O
