TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
and	O
,	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Four	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
-	O
Bench	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prudom	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mayward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Playstake	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Grundy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pate	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Leppage	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humpstone	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thame	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sams	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Steel	O
Trap	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
entering	O
the	O
Gardens	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
36	O
Peaches	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Apricocks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Love	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Trap	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
deny	O
'd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Growen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Trap	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
James	O
Johnson	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Depositions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
clamber	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Garden-Wall	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Trap	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
placed	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
to	O
catch	O
Thieves	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
Scull	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Waterman	O
)	O
into	O
the	O
Trap	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
snap	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
slung	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
appearing	O
a	O
felonious	O
Action	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Peaches	O
and	O
Apricocks	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Crimson	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
an	O
Undertaker	O
,	O
and	O
intrusted	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
such	O
Things	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
Occasion	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
home	O
the	O
Work	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
finish	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
he	O
carried	O
home	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Apparel	O
to	O
Madam	O
Phipps	O
for	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
fit	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
embezzel	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
sent	O
in	O
his	O
Bill	O
some	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Madam	O
Phipps	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Account	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Water	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ursilla	B-pers
Warter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
sen.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Aug	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
his	O
Stockings	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
by	O
several	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dinah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Tonge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Pounds	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
Embroderer	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Poor	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
this	O
Lace	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
carelesly	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
to	O
trap	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
it	O
was	O
soon	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Caul	O
of	O
her	O
Cap	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
Silver	O
Groats	O
,	O
and	O
Two	O
Pences	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
,	O
open	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
49	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
my	O
hired	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Closet	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
,	O
or	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
likewise	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
quitted	O
my	O
House	O
without	O
Notice	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
some	O
Soap	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
took	O
Coach	O
for	O
Worcester	O
;	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
finding	O
my	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
to	O
suspect	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Evening-Post	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
Bewley	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
seems	O
she	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Search	O
I	O
made	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Way	O
again	O
for	O
London	O
in	O
the	O
Worcester	O
Waggon	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
Circumstances	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
in	O
Friday-Street	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
,	O
found	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
they	O
found	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
Rings	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Savill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
her	O
Examination	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
opend	O
she	O
Locks	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
very	O
extravagantly	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
never	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Passenger	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Grayson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Friday-Street	O
with	O
a	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
by	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Evening-Post	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Rings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Confession	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
opening	O
the	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Rings	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
indisputably	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scurrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hadley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Market	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
opening	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
Money	O
down	O
whilst	O
she	O
Struck	O
a	O
Light	O
;	O
immediately	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Four	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Eggs	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
appear	O
'd	O
strong	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
Apples	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Geese	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
loaded	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Eggs	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
?	O
But	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
given	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.George	B-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
8s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gunter	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rosamond	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
say	O
nothing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
said	O
enough	O
against	O
herself	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
directed	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
d	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Ansles	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ansells	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lawrence	O
Mac	O
oy	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Low	I-pers
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Skreen	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Washing-tub	O
,	O
two	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
eighteen	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
and	O
Several	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1726	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Mother-in-law	O
,	O
I	O
married	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
dead	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
moving	O
away	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
her	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
Skreen	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Caps	O
of	O
no	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Washing-tub	O
that	O
dropp	O
'd	O
to	O
Pieces	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
move	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
Theft	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Goods	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
properly	O
call	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
supplying	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
Necessaries	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
never	O
learn	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
himself	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
really	O
give	O
his	O
late	O
Wife	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Hesitation	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
Wife	O
bought	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
earned	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
indigent	O
Person	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
could	O
lay	O
out	O
such	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
without	O
this	O
immediate	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
moving	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Noon-day	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Cart	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
believing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bons	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
Money	O
cut	O
of	O
his	O
Drawer	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Partition	O
of	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
Staple	O
of	O
his	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Seales	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Officer	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Suspicions	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Eye-witness	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Lyn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Apparel	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Napkins	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Whitechapel-Fields	O
with	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloathes	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
Russians	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
Seize	O
him	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
him	O
afterwards	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
his	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
a	O
farther	O
Confirmation	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depose	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
old	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Geese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Letitia	B-pers
Redmons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Raynhold	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Susan	O
Raynhold	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
near	O
the	O
Short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
(	O
a	O
Pastry-Cook	O
's	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Plumb	O
Cake	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Coronation	O
Favor	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
accept	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
There	O
has	O
Favours	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
before	O
now	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Words	O
arising	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Saucy	O
for	O
affronting	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
before	O
now	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
resenting	O
,	O
threatned	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
hitting	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hines	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Transactions	O
mention	O
'd	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Baxter	O
hiss	O
'd	O
and	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turning	O
back	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
desist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
at	O
Small	O
Sword	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
(	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
lay	O
his	O
Sword	O
by	O
)	O
for	O
10	O
Guineas	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
chuck	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
under	O
the	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Lip	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
broke	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
away	O
the	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
run	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
before	O
the	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
struck	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
hinder	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
this	O
Deponent	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
persuaded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
not	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
persuaded	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
stroak	O
or	O
a	O
knock	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Several	O
Blows	O
succeeded	O
with	O
their	O
Canes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
a	O
Practice	O
of	O
taking	O
Women	O
away	O
from	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
?	O
answer	O
'd	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
such	O
Things	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Turvin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
he	O
had	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ridout	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
sincerely	O
griev	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
humbly	O
hop	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Danger	O
he	O
apprehended	O
of	O
being	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Avery	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Pastry-Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
insulting	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
josled	O
him	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
others	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
or	O
Canes	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
going	O
to	O
beat	O
down	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mournsey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
striking	O
him	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
before	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
hold	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cane	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
hit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
Business	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Odebar	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
adding	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
his	O
Cane	O
was	O
twisted	O
our	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
dying	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
my	O
Soul	O
,	O
a	O
family	O
forgive	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
for	O
't	O
was	O
through	O
my	O
own	O
Neglect	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
addicted	O
to	O
mobbing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
Reputation	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
mild	O
,	O
and	O
discreet	O
Gentleman	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mapp	I-pers
;	O
of	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morrill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
And	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecuter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Morrill	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
there	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
waking	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
with	O
Grace	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Constable	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
however	O
they	O
both	O
promised	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
producing	O
it	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
followed	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Morrell	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
Grace	O
Brown	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
as	O
Accessory	O
.	O
[	O
Brown	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bewley	B-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
filing	O
and	O
demolishing	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
in	O
particular	O
13	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
18	O
Shillings	O
and	O
5	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
Made	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mixed	O
Metals	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
and	O
distribute	O
for	O
good	O
and	O
lawful	O
Money	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nut	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Johnson	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
bargaining	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
flung	O
down	O
two	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Nut	O
examining	O
,	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
they	O
Search	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
betrayed	O
Watson	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
searching	O
Watson	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
found	O
the	O
Moulds	O
,	O
Crucible	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Utensils	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
made	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Watson	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
eny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Air	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Purse	O
value	O
1	O
d	O
and	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
1	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
stopping	O
my	O
Coach	O
,	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
your	O
Purse	O
,	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Purse	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Men	O
hanging	O
in	O
Chains	O
.	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
in	O
Sight	O
of	O
the	O
Gibbet	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
verily	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Mare	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
that	O
Mare	O
when	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
my	O
Coach	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
concurring	O
with	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Holliday	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Toothpick-case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pencil	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sermon	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joyce	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
and	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Nightgown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gibeon	B-pers
Waldon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Grace	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Katherine	B-pers
Upp	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Winterton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
and	O
Swivels	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holliston	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Glazier	O
,	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
mend	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
passing	O
through	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
lay	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cabbage	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
returned	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Distemper	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
cured	O
without	O
coming	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
returning	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowdon	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hucks	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stoko	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Hannah	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Farrell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Henry	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
120	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Syprus	B-pers
Prestoe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Patience	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
an	O
evil	O
dispos	O
'd	O
Person	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Fowler	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
Chick-lane	B-place
)	O
where	O
after	O
committing	O
some	O
lewd	O
Actions	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ox	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
Tongue	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hanah	B-pers
Twinning	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Daucey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keeps	O
a	O
notorious	O
Bawdy-House	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Anchor	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
on	O
New-street	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
6.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lyn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Morrill	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cabbage	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
Moses	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Man	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
12.	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Dinah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bone	I-pers
,	O
Rosamond	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Ansills	I-pers
,	O
Letitia	B-pers
Redmourns	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
Patience	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
1	O
.	O
Syprus	O
Prestoe	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Murrill	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
