TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Edward	O
Becher	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
1st	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1728	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
.	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Price	O
Four	O
Pence	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Eyre	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Price	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ellington	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colebran	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Blizard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Anslow	I-pers
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Pinkfat	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hesketh	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Shippey	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boyde	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Witherington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fog	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Bayley	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grose	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Faringdon	I-place
without	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
153	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Opinion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
100	O
Guineas	O
more	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
133	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Pocket-piece	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
133	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
Confest	O
the	O
whole	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
what	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Directions	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
an	O
Uncle	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
undeniably	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ben	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ben	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ben	I-pers
,	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
last	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
strict	O
Enquiry	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
.	O
Dutton	O
Raymond	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Watch	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
Watch	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
William	B-pers
Cudbut	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Gun	O
,	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
in	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
declare	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
perverted	O
Truth	O
by	O
Shuffling	O
Evasions	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
show	O
himself	O
a	O
just	O
Witness	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
every	O
way	O
qualified	O
to	O
serve	O
an	O
unjust	O
Pawn-broker	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Indictment	O
appearing	O
full	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
,	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Lettice	I-pers
Gregory	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
)	O
from	O
behind	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Nicholas	I-place
Langham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sugar	O
Loaves	O
,	O
and	O
6lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Croxen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Blank	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
370	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rud	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunsan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1050	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Akers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
s	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
though	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
Success	O
than	O
Honesty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Grace	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Murs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stinton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Spring	O
of	O
Port	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Winstall	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wailey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wainscoat	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Migneon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Peartree	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Plumtree	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Plumridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	B-pers
Peartree	I-pers
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
lies	O
backwards	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
awak	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
finding	O
himself	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
again	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
such	O
Moveables	O
as	O
were	O
left	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
finding	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
Susan	O
Migneon	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
nap	O
hold	O
at	O
his	O
Cole	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
frighten	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
Stairs	O
pretending	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
detect	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
Whoredoms	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Shard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Byron	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Murphew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
Mary	O
Murphew	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Flack	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Rotherham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calimanco	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Binyan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Stockings	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
each	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
only	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Williams	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
Some	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
nine	O
Inches	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
And	O
James	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
aiding	O
,	O
assisting	O
,	O
and	O
comforting	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Savage	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
separately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Absence	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Limery	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Robinson	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-house	I-place
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
One	O
or	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
there	O
two	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
just	O
concluding	O
to	O
go	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
was	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
setting	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
down	O
our	O
Table	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
answered	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
we	O
retreated	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Gregory	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Villain	O
deliver	O
your	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Thrust	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
defended	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
Push	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Caul	O
,	O
or	O
Fat	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
kneeled	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
to	O
such	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
:	O
Being	O
cross	O
examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
Put	O
up	O
your	O
swords	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
such	O
an	O
Expression	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
call	O
to	O
Mind	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
spoke	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Limery	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
at	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
when	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
some	O
Body	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlady	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
lighted	O
them	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
rudely	O
came	O
into	O
ours	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
kicke	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Rascal	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Sword	O
;	O
(	O
all	O
our	O
Company	O
retreated	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
made	O
a	O
Thrust	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
stoop	O
'd	O
and	O
cried	O
oh	O
!	O
at	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
stood	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
astonish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
pale	O
,	O
then	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lights	O
were	O
then	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
Struggled	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
clung	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
striving	O
to	O
force	O
himself	O
from	O
her	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
and	O
got	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
gave	O
the	O
Wound	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
but	O
pointed	O
downwards	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Sides	O
As	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
after	O
the	O
Play	O
began	O
,	O
the	O
Candles	O
being	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Savage	O
.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
drawn	O
first	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
pale	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
opened	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
suck	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Blood	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Death-Bed	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
least	O
in	O
Black	O
gave	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
,	O
)	O
(	O
for	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
was	O
in	O
coloured	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Tallest	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
)	O
pass	O
'd	O
or	O
struck	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
Stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Sword	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
open	O
his	O
Lips	O
,	O
or	O
speak	O
one	O
Word	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Endersby	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
finding	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Liquour	O
when	O
she	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
Shew	O
'd	O
then	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
rude	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Liquour	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
Struggle	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
and	O
the	O
Mischief	O
done	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
sworn	O
by	O
others	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
's	O
kicking	O
down	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Foulding	O
Table	O
with	O
two	O
Leaves	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Tables	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
publick	O
Coffee	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
;	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
or	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Mistress	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
very	O
rudely	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
resisting	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
Company	O
who	O
had	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
were	O
just	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
Patience	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
this	O
Deponent	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Sinclair	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
with	O
the	O
Point	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
Jane	O
Leader	O
said	O
,	O
Poor	O
dear	O
Sinclair	O
is	O
Kill	O
'd	O
;	O
She	O
suck	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
bleed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
this	O
Deponent	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
an	O
Eye-witness	O
after	O
to	O
the	O
Encounter	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
.	O
The	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Nov.	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
pray	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
recommending	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
few	O
Questions	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Province	O
,	O
modestly	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
,	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Words	O
of	O
a	O
dying	O
Man	O
,	O
persuaded	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
to	O
stay	O
whilst	O
he	O
himself	O
should	O
ask	O
him	O
a	O
Question	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
from	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
you	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answered	O
,	O
From	O
the	O
shortest	O
in	O
Black	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
)	O
the	O
tallest	O
commanded	O
my	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stabbed	O
barbarously	O
before	O
his	O
sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
learning	O
his	O
Head	O
upon	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
stabbed	O
Cowardly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkey	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
parallel	O
with	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
had	O
grazed	O
on	O
the	O
Kidney	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
Wound	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
could	O
receive	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
was	O
Left-handed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Table	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
by	O
Accident	O
:	O
He	O
then	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
under	O
the	O
Imputations	O
of	O
Loose-lives	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
that	O
had	O
no	O
Regard	O
to	O
Justice	O
of	O
Morality	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
insinuated	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Disorder	O
was	O
committed	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
infamous	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
leaving	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Richmond	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
being	O
necessitated	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Night	O
in	O
a	O
Manner	O
not	O
suitable	O
to	O
his	O
Inclinations	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
disappointed	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Limery	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Leader	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
presum	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Incoherencies	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
invalidate	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
of	O
inhumane	O
or	O
barbarous	O
Dispositions	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Inclemencies	O
of	O
a	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Expences	O
which	O
must	O
necessarily	O
follow	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
too	O
extravagant	O
to	O
be	O
supported	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
called	O
Henry	B-pers
and	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
Spectators	O
at	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Broil	O
,	O
their	O
Evidence	O
confirmed	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
's	O
being	O
engag	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
Struggling	O
for	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
appeared	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Extent	O
of	O
her	O
Deposition	O
amounted	O
to	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Leader	O
,	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Jane	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
idle	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Place	O
of	O
Residence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
from	O
other	O
People	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rainby	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
Happened	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Convenient	O
Place	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
escape	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
their	O
Throats	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cheeseborough	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Nuttal	O
produced	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
good	O
Manners	O
and	O
Civility	O
;	O
acknowledging	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
barbarous	O
Treatment	O
his	O
Friend	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
do	O
Justice	O
himself	O
.	O
There	O
appeared	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Persons	O
of	O
Honour	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
being	O
peaceable	O
and	O
quiet	O
in	O
their	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
hop	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Suddenness	O
of	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Accident	O
would	O
intitle	O
them	O
to	O
Favour	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
Sum	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Notice	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
Inconsistencies	O
that	O
might	O
make	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
his	O
Company	O
were	O
in	O
Possession	O
of	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Aggressors	O
,	O
by	O
kicking	O
down	O
the	O
Table	O
and	O
drawing	O
their	O
Swords	O
immediately	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
retreated	O
,	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
attack	O
'd	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
as	O
is	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Death-Bed	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Provocation	O
on	O
his	O
Part	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Murder	O
as	O
well	O
in	O
him	O
that	O
gave	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
others	O
who	O
aided	O
and	O
abetted	O
in	O
this	O
Violence	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
heard	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
objected	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
reply	O
'd	O
on	O
their	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
credit	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Verdict	O
accordingly	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
should	O
influence	O
a	O
Jury	O
where	O
the	O
Proof	O
is	O
doubtful	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
defeat	O
plain	O
and	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
suddenness	O
of	O
this	O
Accident	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sudden	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Provocation	O
from	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
Persons	O
mutually	O
attack	O
each	O
other	O
and	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
is	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
heat	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
but	O
where	O
one	O
is	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
,	O
pursues	O
his	O
Insult	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
kills	O
the	O
Person	O
attack	O
'd	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
on	O
his	O
Part	O
,	O
though	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
the	O
Law	O
implies	O
Malice	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
Murder	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Favour	O
from	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
,	O
that	O
lies	O
properly	O
before	O
the	O
Fountain	O
of	O
Mercy	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
are	O
to	O
proceed	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Law	O
:	O
The	O
Court	O
indulg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
to	O
remind	O
them	O
if	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
they	O
thought	O
material	O
on	O
their	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
unobserved	O
in	O
summing	O
up	O
so	O
long	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Notice	O
accordingly	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Hearing	O
of	O
about	O
eight	O
Hours	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Savage	O
and	O
Gregory	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Merchant	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Merchant	O
:	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Letter	O
Case	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Letter	O
Case	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
or	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
130	O
l.	O
which	O
Note	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lant	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
near	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
making	O
her	O
Defence	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
her	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
from	O
several	O
People	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Horse-whips	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	O
Hatton	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
Castle	I-place
Baynard	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Coffin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
being	O
evidently	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
:	O
But	O
not	O
withstanding	O
it	O
evidently	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keeps	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salkeld	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Night	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
amorous	O
Man	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
Gratuity	O
for	O
her	O
obliging	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
only	O
dress	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
their	O
Amount	O
might	O
be	O
carried	O
on	O
without	O
the	O
Hazard	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
detected	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Deposition	O
being	O
directly	O
opposite	O
to	O
this	O
pretence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Faringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
home	O
very	O
soberly	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
outside	O
Case	O
she	O
had	O
conveyed	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
remarkable	O
to	O
that	O
he	O
Swore	O
.	O
She	O
endeavoured	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ridiculous	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
ludicrous	O
Tale	O
of	O
their	O
Familiarity	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
;	O
but	O
let	O
his	O
Crime	O
be	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
,	O
hers	O
was	O
too	O
conspicuous	O
to	O
escape	O
without	O
Punishment	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachael	B-pers
Mew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hearne	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Barbary	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Barbary	O
Scot	O
,	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Rachael	O
Mew	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Sugar	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
;	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
and	O
a	O
May-day	O
Hat	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Milk-woman	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
his	O
Glass-Case	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
9	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
was	O
Stolen	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Hearing	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
in	O
Barbakin	O
had	O
stopt	O
a	O
Watch	O
which	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
by	O
that	O
Means	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
at	O
Cards	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leg	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
she	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
stifly	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
next	O
Day	O
perceiving	O
her	O
something	O
less	O
in	O
Body	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
searching	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
Opinion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
wrap	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Violence	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
True	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
might	O
be	O
lost	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Help	O
in	O
the	O
Delivery	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
had	O
neither	O
Mark	O
nor	O
Blemish	O
which	O
might	O
denote	O
its	O
being	O
murdered	O
Mary	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
to	O
mend	O
,	O
sometime	O
before	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
furthermore	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
give	O
Earnest	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
actually	O
taken	O
for	O
the	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
her	O
Lying-in	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
confirmed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
her	O
Time	O
of	O
Delivery	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
concurning	O
therewith	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shereditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pot	O
,	O
Porringer	O
,	O
Salts	O
,	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
Beds	O
,	O
Boulsters	O
,	O
Pillows	O
,	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
Looking-glasses	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
,	O
he	O
living	O
a	O
contentious	O
Life	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
empty	O
handed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Mackmasters	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
by	O
Crompton-street	B-place
End	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Leicester-Fields	I-place
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
first	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
then	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
the	O
Pocket	O
from	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
remembered	O
him	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
viewing	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Lamp	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
same	O
Person	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
in	O
her	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
who	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
found	O
him	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
.	O
One	O
Eaton	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Rider	O
's	O
Court	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Bristol	O
.	O
Either	O
Bagshaw	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Drink	O
together	O
,	O
She	O
saw	O
something	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Pocket	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
among	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
;	O
the	O
Same	O
Pocket	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
undeniable	O
Marks	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
(	O
which	O
by	O
Description	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
against	O
some	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Some	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Duroy	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crocum	I-pers
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Drumming	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunston	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Canckate	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Wittington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
China	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Crampton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pricklove	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Greenoway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawkins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
taking	O
a	O
Bar	O
of	O
Iron	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
mayor	I-pers
and	I-pers
the	I-pers
Commonalty	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
City	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
(	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Conduit	O
in	O
Pancras	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
Iron	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
weighing	O
94	O
lb	O
.	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul's-Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Molosses	O
Spirit	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Scissars	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
fancied	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Body	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
a	O
Light	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
any	O
Rudeness	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
begg	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
raising	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
the	O
Scissars	O
Case	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Appointment	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
one	O
Levy	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
Goods	O
moved	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
through	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
Levy	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mendez	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Plate	O
committed	O
on	O
his	O
Case	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Kenneda	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
Election	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	B-place
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Freeman	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
o	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Livery-Man	O
of	O
Merchant	O
Taylors	O
Company	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Right	O
or	O
Title	O
thereto	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Leaker	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Clerks	O
who	O
were	O
appointed	O
to	O
administer	O
the	O
Oath	O
and	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Polled	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Kenneda	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
coming	O
to	O
Poll	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Harrison	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
likewise	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
Irish	O
Papist	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
Poll	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Election	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Kerney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Kingdom	O
and	O
Profession	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
perjury	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Occasion	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
Election	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Flaw	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Spring	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
2	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
14	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
2	O
Bacchanalian	O
Banquet	O
,	O
and	O
stragling	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
nor	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
a	O
long	O
Story	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
Gartered	O
both	O
above	O
Knee	O
and	O
below	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
asleep	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
Posture	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
open	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
so	O
plain	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
as	O
the	O
Drunkenness	O
and	O
Extravagance	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow-Case	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Towels	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gascoin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pecks	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Roan	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dollinson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Gelding	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Dollinson	O
gave	O
above	O
40	O
s.	O
To	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
his	O
Field	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Crump	O
of	O
Wanstead	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crump	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
five	O
Shillings	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Battey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Durley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Coat	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
turnovers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hortitch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
)	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Eaton	O
's	O
a	O
notorious	O
Bawdy	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Rider	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
near	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
complaining	O
of	O
his	O
hard	O
Usage	O
,	O
the	O
Landlady	O
and	O
others	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Watch	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
stopping	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
A	O
Watchmen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
demanded	O
Entrance	O
into	O
Eaton	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Outrage	O
,	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
made	O
a	O
general	O
Complaint	O
of	O
the	O
perpetual	O
Disorders	O
committed	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
calling	O
them	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
B	O
-	O
es	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
withstanding	O
the	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Facts	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Magson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
and	O
Heaters	O
,	O
2	O
Pot	O
,	O
some	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
2	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Quilt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Frogmorton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bloxam	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
had	O
defrauded	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
:	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Shirts	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
stealing	O
them	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
familiar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
pass	O
'd	O
sometimes	O
for	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
for	O
Brother	O
and	O
Sister	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
Matter	O
yet	O
farther	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
done	O
a	O
wrong	O
Thing	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
locket	O
value	O
12	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margery	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
seven	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Grinwood	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
being	O
found	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
going	O
about	O
as	O
a	O
Vagabond	O
with	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
sham	O
Pretence	O
of	O
Legging	O
for	O
the	O
Whitechapel	O
Prisoner	O
s	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
fined	O
three	O
Nobles	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
6.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kemp	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
2.	O
Martin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
1.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
42.	O
Hugh	B-pers
German	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bane	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rud	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Murse	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Walley	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Shard	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Binyan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salkey	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Mew	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Drumming	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Whittington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hagut	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Durley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bloxam	I-pers
,	O
Margery	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
gave	O
Security	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pricklove	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Greenoway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dawkins	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
five	O
Nobles	O
each	O
,	O
to	O
remain	O
Prisoners	O
till	O
paid	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Kenneda	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Kerney	I-pers
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
6	O
Weeks	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
