TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
AND	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1728	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Pengelly	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Land	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Allibone	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Wittacre	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Tunks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maud	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Elisha	B-pers
Impey	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Allen	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cowmbe	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cork	O
Screw	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
on	O
Addle-Hill	B-place
,	O
near	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Sabbath	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Eye	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
locked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Eye	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Corner-Cupboard	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
an	O
Instrument	O
,	O
the	O
Hinges	O
tore	O
off	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Drawers	O
rifled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
though	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
Home	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
Failings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
Work	O
early	O
and	O
late	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
not	O
coming	O
home	O
again	O
confirmed	O
them	O
the	O
more	O
in	O
this	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Reeves	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Char-woman	O
that	O
she	O
employ	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Reeves	O
acknowledging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
telling	O
a	O
plausible	O
Story	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
bad	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
one	O
Diston	O
pittying	O
his	O
Case	O
,	O
lent	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Bristol	O
,	O
to	O
Trade	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
to	O
retrieve	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
daring	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
in	O
the	O
Week	O
Days	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
unfortunately	O
on	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
:	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Petty	O
Larceny	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach	O
Wheel	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Newport	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
lovingly	O
drank	O
4	O
Pints	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
look	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
she	O
returned	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
she	O
say	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
mis	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
her	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
yet	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
before	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
)	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
directly	O
how	O
the	O
Matter	O
stood	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Fifty	O
Pounds	O
and	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coxall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Business	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
Good-Will	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
several	O
Drams	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Greaves	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Customer	O
,	O
with	O
Cyder	O
,	O
Brandy	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
likewise	O
treated	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
return	O
,	O
wip	O
'd	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
fine	O
Nosegay	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
to	O
cheer	O
his	O
Heart	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
(	O
as	O
his	O
Expression	O
was	O
)	O
she	O
weagled	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
kept	O
him	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Passage	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
scarce	O
sensible	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
his	O
Sorrow	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
missing	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
hearing	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Place	O
of	O
Confinement	O
,	O
by	O
conducting	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
Back	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
Officers	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desiring	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
no	O
Drink	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Publicans	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
all	O
for	O
dry	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
None	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Fifty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
for	O
save	O
only	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
neither	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
nor	O
Child	O
,	O
nor	O
Dog	O
nor	O
Cat	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
Cyder	O
,	O
Usquebaugh	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
disguis	O
'd	O
in	O
Liquor	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Scoundrel	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Greaves	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
to	O
treat	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
familiarly	O
stroaking	O
his	O
cheeks	O
,	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
his	O
Footing	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
looking	O
down	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
her	O
with	O
Usquebaugh	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
11	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
several	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Passage	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
supplied	O
with	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
letting	O
him	O
into	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Husband	O
thrust	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Greaves	I-pers
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
every	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Deposition	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
that	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
her	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
so	O
rudely	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
threaten	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
away	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
Greens	O
out	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
being	O
Drunk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Adventure	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
charge	O
no	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
charge	O
no	O
particular	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
indict	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
from	O
several	O
reputable	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
eleven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mannio	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hayden	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
invited	O
there	O
to	O
Dinner	O
with	O
some	O
Gentlemans	O
Servants	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Amey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
attended	O
the	O
Gentlemens	O
Servants	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Haydon	O
sent	O
them	O
word	O
of	O
the	O
Spoon	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
match	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Make	O
and	O
Mark	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
thus	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Holborn	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Thickpenny	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
being	O
at	O
Little	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
she	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
,	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Chelsea	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
some	O
Tea	O
2	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Cyder	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
go	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
faith	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
Dry	O
lips	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
out-staid	O
her	O
Time	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
Hand	O
around	O
her	O
Waist	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
pinn	O
'd	O
it	O
so	O
to	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Phoebe	O
Thickpenny	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Girl	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Girl	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
seeming	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
7	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
she	O
heard	O
it	O
beat	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
soon	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
the	O
maid	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Sweetheart	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
laid	O
her	O
Head	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
could	O
live	O
and	O
die	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
no	O
little	O
Aggravation	O
to	O
his	O
Crime	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
so	O
good	O
Natur	O
'd	O
a	O
Creature	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8d	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rawbone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
presently	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Bundle	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
returned	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
them	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Corn	O
Field	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
by	O
their	O
Directions	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Visage	O
of	O
a	O
Theft	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Vagarr	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Valley	B-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Sanecon	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Vagarr	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
Value	O
20s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Forks	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
French	O
Church	O
at	O
Amsterdam	O
,	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
to	O
think	O
her	O
otherwise	O
than	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Girl	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Puncho	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Forks	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
this	O
Deponent	O
took	O
the	O
Forks	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Puncho	O
refusing	O
she	O
bit	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
her	O
a	O
Bite	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Foreigner	O
,	O
and	O
unacquainted	O
both	O
with	O
our	O
Laws	O
and	O
Language	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
but	O
receive	O
Corporal	O
Punishment	O
.	O
Sylvester	B-pers
Sullevane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1726	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	O
Gun	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
only	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
his	O
Landlord	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
The	O
Nurse	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
being	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Market	O
to	O
buy	O
Provision	O
,	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
,	O
though	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
so	O
weak	O
she	O
was	O
fit	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Moulden	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
an	O
Irish	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Countryman	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Books	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
back	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
:	O
But	O
what	O
the	O
Man	O
told	O
her	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
back	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
produced	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
being	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Ankles	O
,	O
were	O
converted	O
to	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
than	O
could	O
be	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
Part	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
Acquaintance	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
this	O
Family	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
being	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
knew	O
one	O
another	O
better	O
and	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
fell	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pitied	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Trouble	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Nurse	O
run	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Charges	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
getting	O
could	O
not	O
support	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Nurse	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
Market	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
more	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
than	O
I	O
would	O
of	O
either	O
my	O
own	O
Wife	O
,	O
or	O
indeed	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Mother	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
self	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
stiff	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
perform	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
so	O
much	O
Care	O
of	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
be	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
which	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Health	O
should	O
be	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
lying	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
for	O
my	O
Kindness	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
designs	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Wife	O
home	O
they	O
grew	O
very	O
ungrateful	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
demanded	O
her	O
Pail	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
fetched	O
it	O
to	O
wash	O
her	O
Feet	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
fetch	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
for	O
her	O
cross-grain	O
'd	O
Child	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
demanding	O
my	O
Money	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
demanding	O
my	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
them	O
(	O
for	O
my	O
Face	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
handsome	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
a	O
Pride	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
to	O
Quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
his	O
Soul	O
to	O
Ninety-nine	O
Devils	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
Prosecute	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cast	O
him	O
and	O
recovered	O
Damages	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
brought	O
here	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
will	O
consider	O
it	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
desire	O
no	O
more	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
'quitted	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
my	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
promised	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Trouble	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
looking	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
recovered	O
a	O
Verdict	O
and	O
Judgement	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
not	O
making	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bete	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
Time	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Peter	O
Pemberton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
Peter	O
Pemberton	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tun	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
Wager	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
apprehended	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Peter	O
Pemberton	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
actually	O
deposit	O
Three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
in	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hands	O
for	O
that	O
End	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
before	O
whom	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
them	O
to	O
compound	O
a	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Pemberton	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Note	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
yet	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
rather	O
pay	O
than	O
suffer	O
wrongfully	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
then	O
very	O
sick	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
sooner	O
than	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
cost	O
him	O
50	O
l.	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary	O
Mason	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
considered	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
staying	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
other	O
Company	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
proceeded	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Sollicitor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
especially	O
(	O
Peter	O
Pemberton	O
)	O
having	O
several	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
their	O
Character	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Matthews	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Polliter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	O
Polliter	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
fetch	O
Salmon	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
drank	O
two	O
full	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
she	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
his	O
Silver	O
lace	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
which	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
was	O
worth	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
l.	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
taken	O
out	O
four	O
Pieces	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
she	O
took	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Honest	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Salmon	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Half	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
holding	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
her	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
Necklace	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
dear	O
Polliter	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
asking	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
only	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
better	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Drawer	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
tell	O
with	O
some	O
Concern	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
'wakd	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
both	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
Money	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
wicked	O
dissolute	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
Drunk	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
some	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
to	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Leave	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
too	O
well	O
acquainted	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
deny	O
her	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
he	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Shoemaker	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
discovered	O
the	O
Intriegue	O
between	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Folly	O
would	O
not	O
excuse	O
her	O
Theft	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
evidently	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Lace	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Perukes	O
,	O
two	O
Razors	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Humane	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Wigs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
Moses	O
Freeman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
humble	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
to	O
be	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Business	O
of	O
Peruke-making	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Friends	O
were	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
his	O
other	O
Servants	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Eye	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
seeming	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
soon	O
gave	O
him	O
Occasion	O
to	O
repent	O
of	O
his	O
Credulity	O
,	O
for	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceiving	O
something	O
white	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
near	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Wig	O
Box	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
not	O
suspecting	O
any	O
Thing	O
)	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
inspect	O
further	O
into	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Wigs	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Gravesend	O
Boats	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
their	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
Darkhouse-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
for	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
getting	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Oars	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Humane	O
Hair	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Core	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tabby	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Topley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
Petticoat	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
:	O
This	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pickup	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
9	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Coral	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Kid	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Tucker	O
,	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pounds	O
and	O
15	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
29	O
Pounds	O
and	O
16	O
Shillings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
1727	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yew	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
1727	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
rainy	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
Din	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
carry	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
granted	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
continued	O
till	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
rise	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
Sheet	O
flew	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
Sheet	O
was	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
surprized	O
at	O
this	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
when	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
further	O
Surprize	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Chest	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
occasioned	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
out	O
a	O
Cousin	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Haddock	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Pickup	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
advertised	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Philpot	O
,	O
near	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Porter	O
brought	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
contained	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
Box	O
was	O
directed	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Haddock	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Lawson	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Haddock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
Occasion	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Philpot	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Philpot	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Holden	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
directed	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Haddock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Purse	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
purse	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Forster	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Pickup	O
.	O
The	O
Circumstances	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
Grass	O
,	O
near	O
Dantry	B-place
in	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
1727	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bonus	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	O
,	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
said	O
Horse	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Bonus	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Bonus	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
two	O
Year	O
since	O
near	O
Michaelmas	O
)	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Fair	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Geldling	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Little	B-place
Hoton	I-place
,	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Gelding	O
almost	O
two	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Little	O
Hoton	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Charlton	O
of	O
Wetstone	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Finchley	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charlton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Gelding	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cheston	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cheston	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Gelding	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sylvester	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Sylvester	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Mare	O
stole	O
from	O
a	O
Stake	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Gumley	B-place
,	I-place
by	O
Market	B-place
Harborough	I-place
,	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
his	O
Mare	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
be	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
but	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
Friends	O
at	O
Totenhem	O
which	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
going	O
there	O
they	O
refused	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
last	O
Midsummer	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
threatning	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mare	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Mare	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
had	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Gumley	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
Market	O
Harborough	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
tedious	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
from	O
Market	O
Harborough	O
to	O
Wellenborough	O
,	O
and	O
overtaking	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
led	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
Stories	O
being	O
plentifully	O
invented	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
what	O
he	O
asserted	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Phllip	B-pers
Markmillar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pea	O
Jacket	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	O
Harrison	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Mother	O
keeping	O
a	O
Sale	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Jacket	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
lay	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
snatch	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Jacket	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
himself	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
this	O
Deponent	O
never	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stubbs	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Jacket	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
exactly	O
tell	O
the	O
Particulars	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
idle	O
Excuse	O
,	O
without	O
Witness	O
availed	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buttery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
's	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
7	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Womens	O
Kid	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bathmettle	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Boot-catcher	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell-Inn	B-place
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
,	O
and	O
2	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Kid	O
Gloves	O
being	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Room	O
found	O
the	O
Gloves	O
,	O
when	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
by	O
opening	O
Flap	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guinea	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
's	O
Chest	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
both	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
heard	O
him	O
make	O
the	O
same	O
Confession	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Beddow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldersgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Moulton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Apron	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Glass	O
hid	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
felt	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
slip	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
immediately	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
This	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ox	O
's	O
Hide	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Hide	O
taken	O
from	O
others	O
that	O
lay	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
in	O
Leadenhall-Market	B-place
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
surrender	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
found	O
with	O
his	O
Mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
remembering	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Skin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Distress	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
extravagant	O
Excuse	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Distress	O
)	O
or	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helen	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sagathy	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Rymer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Woman	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
but	O
shifting	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
length	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
followed	O
her	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
the	O
Shoes	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mark	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Guin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
lock	O
'd	O
but	O
the	O
Casement	O
open	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
done	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
neither	O
them	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Dishes	O
were	O
wanting	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
which	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hinchcliff	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
betimes	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
there	O
,	O
saying	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
beat	O
and	O
abused	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
some	O
where	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
;	O
(	O
this	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
)	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
taken	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dishes	O
which	O
she	O
left	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Hinchliff	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Comber	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Laundress	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bayley	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
she	O
had	O
bundled	O
up	O
his	O
Shirts	O
with	O
three	O
Stocks	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
invited	O
to	O
a	O
Burial	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Surprize	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
whom	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
always	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
Story	O
of	O
her	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
Stock	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
further	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
another	O
Stock	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
kneel	O
'd	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Shirts	O
or	O
she	O
was	O
ruined	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kneeled	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Balls	O
in	O
Holborn	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brinklow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Culpepper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Cecilia	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Culpepper	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
,	O
a	O
Book-seller	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
Bundle	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
laying	O
it	O
on	O
some	O
Books	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
stay	O
till	O
his	O
Sister	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lady	O
where	O
his	O
Sister	O
lived	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Consequence	O
of	O
that	O
Suspicion	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
Lady	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Lady	O
Culpepper	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
after	O
securing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Bundle	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Faithful	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Beadle	O
who	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Culpepper	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Swift	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
,	O
the	O
Bookseller	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
deserved	O
a	O
greater	O
Punishment	O
than	O
the	O
Law	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
wronging	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Lady	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Northorp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Abraham	B-pers
Danbrine	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Henry	B-pers
Par	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Par	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Pen	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
Par	O
is	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
last	O
Husband	O
Mr.	O
Danbrine	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
Money	O
due	O
to	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
give	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
bring	O
himself	O
into	O
Trouble	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Husband	O
alive	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Danbrine	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Danbrine	I-pers
is	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
half	O
married	O
to	O
Henry	O
Par	O
,	O
for	O
before	O
the	O
Parson	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
he	O
repented	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
Cohabited	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Husband	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
good	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Benless	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Butterfield	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
(	O
that	O
credible	O
House	O
)	O
the	O
Feathers	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
drank	O
till	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Body	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Company	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fendiamond	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers	O
Tavern	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Disputes	O
arising	O
between	O
them	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
this	O
Deponent	O
saw	O
the	O
Seal	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
stealing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
relate	O
the	O
Affair	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
forasmuch	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
each	O
other	O
with	O
stealing	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
drunk	O
and	O
extravagant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bound	O
them	O
both	O
over	O
,	O
believing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
wild	O
Youth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
a	O
wicked	O
and	O
abandon	O
'd	O
Creature	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
no	O
further	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dalby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Semms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billinsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Rice	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Govan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
and	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Clouts	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
2	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Pan	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
Nieces	O
,	O
who	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
Mouth	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
forgetting	O
in	O
whose	O
Presence	O
they	O
stood	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
Scolding	O
and	O
Quarrelling	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Language	O
of	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
The	O
Foundation	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
rais	O
'd	O
on	O
a	O
Family	O
Broil	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stagner	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
evil	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
,	O
erase	O
,	O
cut	O
and	O
diminish	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
change	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pew	O
Sat	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
light	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
weighing	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Edges	O
they	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Fild	O
and	O
new	O
Mill	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
curiously	O
but	O
the	O
Deceit	O
might	O
be	O
easily	O
discern	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
stopt	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
(	O
and	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
quite	O
off	O
)	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
deposited	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
them	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
Swore	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
received	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Trade	O
of	O
going	O
about	O
to	O
change	O
Guineas	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
go	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
the	O
Father	O
's	O
Transaction	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
no	O
Regard	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Father	O
had	O
taken	O
4	O
Guineas	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
one	O
Morning	O
,	O
of	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
drank	O
Brandy	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
,	O
and	O
changing	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
presently	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Four	O
Guineas	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
those	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
indicted	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
considerable	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Guineas	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
light	O
;	O
particularly	O
Mr.	O
Landey	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Guineas	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Guineas	O
question	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hymus	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28lb	O
.	O
of	O
brown	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Object	O
of	O
Compassion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
only	O
be	O
whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
;	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
Henry	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
of	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
120	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Towers	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Way	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
one	O
Way	B-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
no-body	O
appear	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
Evidence	O
against	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
her	O
Husband	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
pleased	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
hearing	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
indicted	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
nobody	O
else	O
laid	O
Claim	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tomkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
he	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Tomkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
broke	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
crept	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
hid	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
reasonable	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
himself	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
stupified	O
Sots	O
in	O
Christendom	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Joyner	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
Drunk	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
entirely	O
Senseless	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
lay	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
or	O
mistake	O
another	O
's	O
Cellar	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
any	O
Action	O
that	O
was	O
dishonest	O
,	O
either	O
Drunk	O
or	O
Sober	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
Abroad	O
in	O
the	O
Wars	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Piece	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Skull	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
supply	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Plate	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
made	O
Crazy	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
being	O
the	O
second	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Street	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
second	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pallet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calamanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Pallet	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
Smart	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
all	O
the	O
old	O
Shoes	O
in	O
a	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dearing	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
kind	O
and	O
familiar	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joyce	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
nor	O
even	O
Circumstance	O
appearing	O
against	O
Barnet	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
Joyce	O
Hall	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
on	O
Joyce	O
Hall	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sterril	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
35	O
Shillings	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
whole	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
insinuate	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
and	O
she	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
confirm	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
weary	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea-Pot	O
,	O
some	O
Tea-Cups	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Lambel	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Etherington	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
700	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
from	O
Belsize	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Philip	B-pers
,	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Chesterfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pack	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Selby	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
William	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Francis	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
from	O
Stamford	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Horns	B-place
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
another	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
Marriage	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Hinkins	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Caldecut	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
willful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
up	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Statute	O
of	O
Bankrupt	O
against	O
Richard	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
all	O
three	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Caldecut	I-pers
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
procuring	O
Evidences	O
to	O
forswear	O
themselves	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
against	O
Richard	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
