TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
29th	O
,	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probin	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edm	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Radley	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Spinks	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Joy	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Tesman	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Threnkill	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Brawton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pathic	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Genoway	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Purcival	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Faiths	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Within	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Sons	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
came	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
she	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
and	O
remember	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
her	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnorth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Herman	B-pers
Long	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
at	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church	I-place
in	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
his	O
Pocket	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
studs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wixen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kennet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1726-7	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
made	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
acquainted	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
without	O
her	O
knowledge	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Veracity	O
being	O
question	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
several	O
Contradictions	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
most	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
herself	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collingwood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
.	O
David	O
Betty	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
sometimes	O
Mr.	O
Collingwood	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
sending	O
the	O
Coat	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
yet	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
pretence	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
wanting	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
Jane	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
Depositions	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Effect	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Thief	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
run	O
him	O
to	O
Charges	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
not	O
being	O
actually	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
inoffensive	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
comply	O
with	O
the	O
malicious	O
Desires	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
Consequence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
's	O
Actions	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
swear	O
the	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
secure	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
intimidate	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
indebred	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Capacity	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
discharge	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Debts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
,	O
by	O
Menaces	O
and	O
Threatnings	O
,	O
had	O
extorted	O
several	O
promissory	O
Notes	O
from	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
no	O
Obligation	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Cloud	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
good	O
Character	O
being	O
indisputable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
granted	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Terror	O
to	O
such	O
unwarrantable	O
Proceedings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kenneda	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Tann	O
'd	O
Bezzles	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Captain	B-pers
Cristie	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Feb	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Star	B-place
Inn	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Breeches	O
under	O
his	O
Pillow	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
there	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Night	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
staying	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
him	O
:	O
This	O
being	O
an	O
evident	O
Demonstration	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Bauldry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Stove-Grate	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hillock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stormey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Money	O
at	O
divers	O
Times	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
past	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
his	O
utmost	O
Diligence	O
in	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
considerable	O
Returns	O
of	O
Money	O
he	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
found	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
sinking	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
too	O
much	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
,	O
he	O
mark	O
'd	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
before	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
put	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
detecting	O
her	O
the	O
mark	O
'd	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Circumstances	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherin	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Rosted	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
to	O
light	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
so	O
much	O
Trouble	O
without	O
some	O
Advantage	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Half	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
into	O
Discourse	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Butcher	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dispised	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
question	O
his	O
Courage	O
and	O
Abilities	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
(	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
powerful	O
Operation	O
of	O
the	O
Liquor	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
)	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
positive	O
in	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Courage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
stifle	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
with	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kennings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Thomison	B-pers
Freestone	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Susanna	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
plead	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
John	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
26	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
John	O
and	O
Moses	O
Davis	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hestridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Tallow	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Convent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
;	O
and	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
her	O
singular	O
Penitence	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
procuring	O
the	O
Whole	O
that	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
consider	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
further	O
Mercy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
pound	O
of	O
Bees-Wax	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Picket	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Fox	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Maccoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sharpwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Cows	O
and	O
a	O
Bull	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
and	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Cows	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodfield	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
,	O
who	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drove	O
the	O
Cattle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
,	O
or	O
City	O
Pound	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
Proportion	O
to	O
the	O
Quantity	O
he	O
brought	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
uncommon	O
piece	O
of	O
Villany	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
Felony	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
Yet	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
escape	O
with	O
Impunity	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
detain	O
'd	O
and	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Henry	B-pers
Weatly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Iron	O
Harness	O
of	O
a	O
Carr	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
valued	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shorey	I-pers
;	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
9	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bloxon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2nd	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
;	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Winnock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
Stocks	O
and	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Washer	O
woman	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sayer	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
wash	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
hard	O
Ware	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Braud	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bar	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Haymore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
32	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Currant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
52	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Seals	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
becoming	O
familiar	O
,	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
confessing	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
asham	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Nelliss	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Moidores	O
,	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
an	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Toogood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Tun	I-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Whitechappel	B-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
one	O
Beal	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
sought	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
directly	O
swore	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
has	O
frequently	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
Actions	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
afterwards	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
has	O
been	O
found	O
upon	O
himself	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilfull	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reynold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Esther	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
and	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Persons	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
treated	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
that	O
inspir	O
'd	O
by	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Back-Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
-	O
and	O
there	O
-	O
and	O
there	O
-	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
-	O
that	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
notwithstanding	O
his	O
loving	O
Disposition	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
his	O
Resentment	O
by	O
changing	O
his	O
Passion	O
from	O
the	O
Amorous	O
on	O
the	O
Outragious	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Bully	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
who	O
without	O
any	O
Dispute	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
Kicking	O
and	O
Cuffing	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Shirt	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
render	O
'd	O
him	O
more	O
inexcusable	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
on	O
a	O
Sabbath-Day	O
at	O
Night	O
get	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
fall	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Probability	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
escape	O
without	O
falling	O
under	O
some	O
unhappy	O
Dilemma	O
,	O
or	O
committing	O
some	O
Extravagance	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
taking	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
otherwise	O
than	O
as	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Change	O
when	O
he	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
more	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
as	O
his	O
vicious	O
Inclinations	O
would	O
not	O
excuse	O
her	O
Actions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Hemstead	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Jane	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Pieces	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
her	O
,	O
thrust	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Keys	O
and	O
Seal	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Sight	O
;	O
that	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
satisfied	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Trowell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Persons	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
something	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
honest	O
Men	O
,	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
refused	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
at	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
the	O
Weapon	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Beezley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Trowell	O
,	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Trowell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
desired	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
plain	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
were	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
on	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Feb	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
12	O
pounds	O
of	O
sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Giles	O
Holliday	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
disturbed	O
by	O
a	O
Noise	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
four	O
Rogues	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
Places	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
Advertised	O
the	O
Silk	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
he	O
received	O
Advice	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
Samuel	O
Temperal	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confes	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
taken	O
30	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silk	O
;	O
eight	O
pair	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
fitted	O
on	O
their	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
21	O
pair	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Sykes	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Temperal	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Silk	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
finding	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
Confession	O
of	O
making	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Elianor	B-pers
Sykes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
twenty-one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
the	O
Confession	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
on	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
pieces	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
Brocaded	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
Silver	O
and	O
Pearl	O
,	O
Value	O
2000	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Mountagu	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
those	O
pieces	O
of	O
Velvet	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Press	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Passage	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
wardrobe	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
taking	O
out	O
two	O
pains	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
pearls	O
scattered	O
about	O
a	O
Room	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Wardrobe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Velvet	O
(	O
about	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
)	O
behind	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
three	O
Keys	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
Keys	O
opened	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
out	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
opened	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Grace	O
's	O
House	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
nine	O
Days	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rooms	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
pieces	O
of	O
very	O
rich	O
Hangings	O
of	O
the	O
Dukes	O
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
Pearls	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
(	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
handful	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
one	O
single	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hangings	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proposed	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Oxford	O
with	O
the	O
Hangings	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
allow	O
him	O
a	O
Share	O
in	O
the	O
Advantage	O
,	O
which	O
should	O
accrue	O
from	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
then	O
told	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Keys	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
convey	O
any	O
Thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Duke	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
commit	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Ingratitude	O
of	O
wronging	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
saved	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bade	O
him	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Edges	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
could	O
perceive	O
it	O
was	O
Velvet	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
still	O
persisted	O
in	O
persuading	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Lord	O
Duke	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
at	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
persuading	O
Mr.	O
Blackwell	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
with	O
that	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
mentioned	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Mountagu	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bickford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
examined	O
the	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Keys	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
would	O
open	O
seven	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
alter	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Command	O
of	O
the	O
Steward	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
asking	O
the	O
Steward	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
his	O
ever	O
giving	O
such	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
New-Prison	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
a	O
plain	O
Country	O
Man	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
mistaking	O
their	O
Way	O
,	O
asked	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Thoroughfare	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
a	O
Woman	O
seiz	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Dungeon	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
tore	O
down	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Caddie	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
back	O
Way	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
complaining	O
of	O
the	O
hard	O
Usage	O
of	O
the	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
Shaw	O
,	O
the	O
Under	O
Keeper	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
this	O
Deponent	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
very	O
generously	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
innocent	O
Countrymen	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
Keeper	O
,	O
who	O
threatened	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
missing	O
their	O
Way	O
,	O
Shaw	O
,	O
the	O
Turnkey	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
back	O
Way	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
confirming	O
likewise	O
what	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
pull	O
out	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
loose	O
from	O
those	O
Villains	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
terrified	O
and	O
foam	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
though	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
scarce	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
Margaret	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
in	O
their	O
Behalf	O
,	O
who	O
strengthen	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Behalf	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Shaw	O
the	O
Under-keeper	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
back	O
Way	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
hurried	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cordes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Casteels	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Vaughn	O
's	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Vaughn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
described	O
in	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
;	O
the	O
Plate	O
being	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
by	O
the	O
Cypher	O
engraven	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Painter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
engrav	O
'd	O
the	O
Cypher	O
on	O
the	O
Plate	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Merrit	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Virginia	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
she	O
produced	O
not	O
proving	O
this	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shann	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shann	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
eight	O
Moidores	O
,	O
two	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Half	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Closet	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Windows	O
of	O
his	O
Closet	O
were	O
broken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
fast	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
Hertford	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
were	O
both	O
kept	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Shann	I-pers
's	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
Girl	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
suspect	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
tax	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Shann	I-pers
had	O
squandered	O
away	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
Trifles	O
he	O
press	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
more	O
home	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
break	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
supported	O
his	O
Extravagance	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
both	O
his	O
Brother	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
them	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
this	O
Deponent	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
secret	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
their	O
taking	O
more	O
than	O
22	O
l.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
William	B-pers
Shann	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
Moidores	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Tyreman	I-pers
.	O
But	O
he	O
not	O
proving	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
all	O
this	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
squandered	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
being	O
considered	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stagles	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Howard	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Pocket-pieces	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Home	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
between	O
Bow	B-place
and	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Passengers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
not	O
stopping	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believes	O
,	O
was	O
fired	O
at	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
robb	O
'd	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Passengers	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
Horse	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
he	O
rode	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
Observation	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Colour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
plainly	O
saw	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
demand	O
their	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
near	O
Bear-binder	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
full	O
Speed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
after	O
him	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Drayman	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
his	O
Horse	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
remarkable	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Green	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Roads	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
Passengers	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Witness	O
thereupon	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
indisputably	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Staining	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
5	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
4	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Mo	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Top-knot	O
,	O
a	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Lace	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
Brocaded	O
Silk	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
frighten	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
both	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
the	O
Thief	O
were	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
conceal	O
'd	O
herself	O
till	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
likewise	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Bolted	O
and	O
Barr	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pink	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Pewter	O
not	O
agreeing	O
with	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
detain	O
'd	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
detected	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ruffian	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
undeniably	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Capon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millnor	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Culler	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Stewing-Pan	O
,	O
and	O
Warming-Pan	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Duncan	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach-Door	O
and	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
O'Caryl	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Glass	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
thought	O
convenient	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
clear	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Owner	O
.	O
Arra	O
Dear	O
Joy	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
hanging	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
transporting	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
indeed	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
excepting	O
on	O
it	O
yourself	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
welcome	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
dear	O
Joy	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
Trouble	O
about	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
having	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
Regard	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
to	O
stifle	O
the	O
Matter	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
detected	O
dear	O
Joy	O
in	O
his	O
Villany	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
buying	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
he	O
gave	O
12	O
Shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
yet	O
and	O
indeed	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Holdep	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beezley	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
Faculty	O
of	O
sitting	O
up	O
a	O
Nights	O
,	O
pretending	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
sate	O
up	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Custom	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
going	O
down	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Tablecloaths	O
about	O
her	O
shoulders	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
being	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Table-cloaths	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
confes	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Jackson	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Marshes	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Dogs	I-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
making	O
it	O
plainly	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
actually	O
his	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
still	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
East	O
Marshes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Dogs	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
helped	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
kill	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
steal	O
Sheep	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
betray	O
him	O
for	O
Crimes	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
afore-time	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
had	O
several	O
Captains	O
of	O
Ships	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
Repute	O
,	O
been	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Vessel	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
This	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
another	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Anthony	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Year	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Marshes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
Information	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
from	O
one	O
Vincent	B-pers
Morril	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
who	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
taken	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Marshes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
considerable	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Mutton	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Skins	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
which	O
he	O
stole	O
was	O
slung	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Sheep	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plumb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Dun	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Bruises	O
with	O
a	O
Coach	O
Wheel	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Bruises	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Corner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
deposd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
Coach-wheel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appeared	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
surprize	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
the	O
Reins	O
tight	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Horses	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Body	O
bruised	O
in	O
a	O
frightful	O
Manner	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Daughters	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
over	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
leaning	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
fell	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
either	O
Drunk	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Coach	O
come	O
thro	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Horses	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mico	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
Care	O
at	O
a	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
out	O
the	O
Morning	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
finding	O
him	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
obstinate	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
fatal	O
Accident	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dingle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Dowgate	B-place
Ward	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Feather-Beds	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
6	O
Cain	O
Chairs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
an	O
Oval	O
Mohogeny	O
Table	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
Sett	O
of	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
a	O
Stove-Grate	O
,	O
a	O
Jack	O
,	O
an	O
Easy	O
Chair	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Dressing-Table	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Concrant	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
under	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
finding	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Excuse	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
Security	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
indebted	O
,	O
or	O
under	O
any	O
Obligation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
for	O
six	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
Contract	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
People	O
would	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
;	O
for	O
though	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
two	O
Children	O
,	O
which	O
pass	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
several	O
Letters	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
together	O
as	O
Husband	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
directed	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gonorant	I-pers
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scaldwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrel	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kelme	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Yellowly	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
Saddle-cloath	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mare	O
and	O
Gelding	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Livery	O
Stable	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Advertised	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Advice	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
Ms.	O
Haynes	O
of	O
Oxford	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
secured	O
both	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cattle	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
some	O
Contradictions	O
in	O
his	O
Discourse	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
he	O
read	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
exactly	O
described	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Stable-Door	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Mare	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
abundance	O
of	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Who	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
discharg	O
'd	O
himself	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Person	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
represented	O
as	O
an	O
Object	O
of	O
Mercy	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
Consequence	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Earwigs	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Parcel	O
to	O
the	O
Lancashire	O
Carriers	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
their	O
Time	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Inn	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Porter	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
Parcel	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
common	O
Thief	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
sow	O
'd	O
up	O
very	O
neatly	O
,	O
and	O
stuffed	O
up	O
with	O
Hay	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
strict	O
Enquiry	O
amongst	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
if	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
culpable	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Packing	O
Needle	O
and	O
some	O
Packthread	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
still	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
enquiring	O
for	O
one	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
some	O
Shirts	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
directly	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Hesitation	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-loft	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anthors	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Feb	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
Barbers	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
his	O
Customers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asking	O
him	O
to	O
treat	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Lombard-Court	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
rudely	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Bamboozle	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
Bamboozled	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
Bully	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
produced	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
he	O
was	O
reconciled	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ale	O
and	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
away	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
herself	O
,	O
being	O
got	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
flung	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
got	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
running	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
after	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
about	O
his	O
Heels	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anchers	I-pers
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
acted	O
so	O
like	O
a	O
Beast	O
,	O
in	O
Cohabiting	O
with	O
one	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
abhorring	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
Resentment	O
at	O
their	O
ludicrous	O
preposterous	O
Brutality	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
Last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Kicks	O
and	O
Bruises	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rustan	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Chapman	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
was	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
I	O
'll	O
fight	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refusing	O
to	O
fight	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
stuck	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Coward	O
's	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
repeating	O
it	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Since	O
he	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
earnest	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Falls	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
,	O
shook-Hands	O
,	O
and	O
Drank	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
complain	O
,	O
of	O
any	O
Hurt	O
or	O
Bruise	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brinkman	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
and	O
Water	O
in	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Distemper	O
'd	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Spleen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
weighed	O
five	O
pound	O
save	O
two	O
Ounces	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
Bruises	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Blood	O
and	O
Water	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Liver	O
was	O
defective	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
fine	O
,	O
his	O
whole	O
Body	O
Dropsical	O
and	O
Distemper	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
sudden	O
Bruises	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
in	O
Conjunction	O
with	O
his	O
Distemper	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Import	O
with	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rustan	I-pers
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
obliged	O
to	O
fight	O
against	O
his	O
Consent	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fround	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicated	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cap	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Cheese	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Cheese	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mark	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackmau	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
from	O
several	O
reputable	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mayson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
17	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hog	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millnor	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jervis	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Chickens	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sausages	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowlin	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Askill	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Purdis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
miserable	O
Object	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Consequence	O
of	O
her	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Arabella	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Suit	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Green	O
Silk	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
3	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
4	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
white	O
Silk	O
,	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Twilight	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
covering	O
for	O
a	O
Tea-Table	O
)	O
a	O
Pillow	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
accidentally	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
she	O
intrusted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
her	O
Affairs	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
Goods	O
to	O
Bath	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
herself	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lattimbre	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
;	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
one	O
Night	O
at	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
apply	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
without	O
her	O
Consent	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
pawn	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
55	O
s.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
they	O
arrested	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Interim	O
they	O
carried	O
off	O
all	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
of	O
their	O
robbing	O
her	O
in	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
saw	O
,	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Press-Gang	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
troubled	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
an	O
incoherent	O
Harrangue	O
of	O
her	O
pawning	O
her	O
Rings	O
to	O
discharge	O
some	O
Debts	O
she	O
had	O
contracted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
making	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
them	O
without	O
her	O
Consent	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
Depositions	O
not	O
concurring	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Effect	O
than	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Whole	O
was	O
a	O
misterious	O
Labyrinth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
a	O
contentious	O
malicious	O
People	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
Depositions	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
some	O
Expence	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Charges	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
her	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
herself	O
indebted	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
furthermore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
consented	O
to	O
the	O
Pawning	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
Goods	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Goat	O
's	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wigmore	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Hair	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Charge	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
could	O
not	O
weigh	O
so	O
much	O
after	O
curl	O
'd	O
and	O
drawn	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
from	O
several	O
reputable	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
advising	O
about	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
depending	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivane	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Clark	B-pers
,	O
in	O
Rider	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Castle	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
in	O
Castle	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
had	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
former	O
Difference	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
all	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
secured	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
quarreling	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
and	O
Wilcox	O
in	O
a	O
high	O
Dispute	O
,	O
she	O
complaining	O
of	O
his	O
assaulting	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
Dirty	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
charg	O
'd	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
and	O
Wilcox	O
charg	O
'd	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
each	O
complaining	O
of	O
the	O
Wrong	O
they	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Dirt	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
that	O
Wilcox	O
had	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
several	O
Disputes	O
in	O
Law	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
Wilcox	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
produc	O
'd	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
directly	O
,	O
that	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
knowing	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
tempted	O
to	O
forswear	O
herself	O
.	O
This	O
evidently	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Charge	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
unjust	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulcbre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
Six-Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Savin	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Colvert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Oviat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
by	O
extorting	O
Money	O
from	O
Rodolphus	B-pers
Blank	I-pers
,	O
threatning	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Demands	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
Sodomy	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
indecently	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
approving	O
of	O
,	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dog	O
'd	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
insolently	O
demanded	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
Sodomy	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
fearing	O
his	O
Reputation	O
might	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
Question	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
knew	O
himself	O
Innocent	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
frequently	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Demands	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
chose	O
rather	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Villany	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
impos	O
'd	O
on	O
any	O
longer	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
an	O
uncommon	O
Share	O
of	O
Impudence	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
denying	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
represent	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
insolently	O
demanding	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Mortification	O
of	O
this	O
vile	O
Bravado	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
himself	O
and	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
joyfully	O
receiv	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
old	O
Acquaintances	O
of	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
who	O
express	O
'd	O
a	O
Surprize	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
from	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
His	O
Villany	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Brumpton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
driving	O
away	O
11	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Practice	O
of	O
driving	O
Cattle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
an	O
Advantage	O
of	O
that	O
Practice	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
were	O
stray	O
'd	O
Cattle	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kitwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Husband	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shackle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
35	O
pound	O
of	O
Mohair	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
five	O
pound	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Randolph	B-pers
Knipe	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Sidebottom	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Wood	O
,	O
did	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
bring	O
the	O
Mohair	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
encouraged	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
began	O
to	O
question	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Wood	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Sir	O
Randolph	B-pers
Knipe	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Mohair	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Mohair	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sidebottom	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
Sir	O
Randolph	O
's	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
Sir	O
Randolph	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Certainty	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
though	O
to	O
oblige	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Sidebottom	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Mate	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sidebottom	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
some	O
New	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
,	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
counting	O
the	O
Plates	O
under	O
a	O
Lamp	O
Which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Reaves	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
13	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
,	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
her	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
pleaded	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardon	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
Bail	O
were	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
three	O
Nobles	O
,	O
for	O
riding	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shann	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stainens	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Murphew	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stagles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Kehne	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
4.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kidnell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hookey	O
Lovett	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
1	O
.	O
Gervis	O
Sheldon	O
.	O
Transportation	O
37.	O
John	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kenneda	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Bauldry	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hestridge	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Maccoy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartlett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bloxom	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Winnock	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Easter	O
Wheatley	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
Duncam	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shackle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
three	O
Nobles	O
,	O
for	O
riding	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
for	O
driving	O
away	O
Cattle	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
,	O
fined	O
five	O
Marks	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Oviat	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
three	O
Nobles	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
qualify	O
him	O
to	O
prosecute	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
plead	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
pleaded	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
convicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
.	O
As	O
did	O
George	B-pers
Kidger	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Sodomy	O
:	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Pocket	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
:	O
Peter	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murder	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
:	O
And	O
James	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
for	O
different	O
Felonies	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
or	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
:	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George-Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
.	O
Price	O
One	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
Excellent	O
for	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
Eight	O
Pence	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Daffy	O
's	O
Elixir	O
,	O
truly	O
prepar	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
in	O
the	O
