TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
AND	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1728	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crowcher	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caten	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Saulfrey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Oder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ollier	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fayram	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
and	O
intic	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
familiarities	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
falling	O
of	O
it	O
caused	O
the	O
Case	O
to	O
fly	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
up	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
conveyed	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
promised	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
that	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
letting	O
it	O
fall	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Fever	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
not	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
himself	O
so	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
with	O
an	O
uncommon	O
Share	O
of	O
Assurance	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
was	O
a	O
Party	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
But	O
her	O
Evidence	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
Weight	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bembridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
her	O
Char-woman	O
,	O
she	O
intrusted	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
leaving	O
her	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Chest	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Smith	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
which	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
some	O
hesitation	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Bit	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
d.	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darvill	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
46	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Hilliard	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
twice	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
coming	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
took	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darvill	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linnen	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
she	O
had	O
clandestinely	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wincopp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
under	O
Sarah	O
Darvills	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
which	O
Piece	O
he	O
discovered	O
by	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
hanging	O
down	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
fastned	O
up	O
almost	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
her	O
Waist	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
perceived	O
they	O
would	O
search	O
her	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
this	O
likewise	O
being	O
confirmed	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Piece	O
hanging	O
down	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
being	O
proved	O
in	O
Confederacy	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
three	O
Suits	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
two	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pearcy	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
led	O
by	O
the	O
Malice	O
and	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
Malice	O
afore-thought	O
,	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
Jane	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
not	O
having	O
stricken	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
then	O
having	O
any	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
12	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
bid	O
him	O
stay	O
below	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
her	O
Mother	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
her	O
Father	O
would	O
Dine	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
immediately	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
below	O
for	O
some	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
up	O
heard	O
them	O
at	O
high	O
Words	O
about	O
the	O
Correction	O
of	O
their	O
Children	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
some	O
further	O
Words	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeming	O
to	O
resent	O
something	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
flung	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Handle	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
)	O
full	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
entered	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
starting	O
up	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
I	O
am	O
stuck	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
great	O
surprize	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
help	O
,	O
help	O
,	O
then	O
running	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
this	O
Deponent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wilks	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Words	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Correction	O
of	O
their	O
eldest	O
Child	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
then	O
chastis	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Fault	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
it	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
continuing	O
to	O
Jar	O
,	O
and	O
express	O
themselves	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
Anger	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Sunday	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
for	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
last	O
Night	O
you	O
could	O
provide	O
for	O
yourself	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
-	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
provide	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
instantly	O
flung	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
Left	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
soon	O
perceiving	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
Mischief	O
,	O
run	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
caught	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Provey	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
went	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
no	O
Life	O
remaining	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
probing	O
the	O
Wound	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
touch	O
'd	O
the	O
Ventricles	O
of	O
her	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
mortal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
was	O
inwards	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sate	O
about	O
6	O
Foot	O
distant	O
from	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
neither	O
Stays	O
or	O
Waistcoat	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wilks	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
dress	O
the	O
Dinner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Coals	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
which	O
his	O
Wife	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Coals	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Pattey	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
Coals	O
home	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
being	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Wilks	O
's	O
,	O
had	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
with	O
Mrs.Wilks	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
angry	O
that	O
the	O
Dinner	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
detain	O
'd	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
detain	O
'd	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
When	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
Disputes	O
arose	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
angry	O
at	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
Expression	O
,	O
slung	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
her	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
reputable	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
Depositions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
ever	O
behaved	O
as	O
a	O
kind	O
indulgent	O
Husband	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
some	O
having	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
others	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
few	O
but	O
what	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
extraordinary	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
this	O
last	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
very	O
loving	O
Couple	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
wrangle	O
,	O
or	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
Extravagance	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Willson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
officiated	O
as	O
Clerk	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
himself	O
by	O
his	O
Industry	O
,	O
Sobriety	O
and	O
good	O
Manners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
kind	O
,	O
indulgent	O
Husband	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tender	O
Father	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
considered	O
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Freckleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
led	O
by	O
the	O
Malice	O
and	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
assault	O
,	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
Words	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Barge	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Minutes	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
away	O
he	O
died	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Abdomen	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
any	O
external	O
Mark	O
or	O
Bruise	O
,	O
save	O
only	O
one	O
about	O
the	O
Bigness	O
of	O
a	O
Pea	O
;	O
it	O
likewise	O
appeared	O
that	O
his	O
Spleen	O
was	O
3	O
Times	O
bigger	O
than	O
is	O
common	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
an	O
ill	O
State	O
of	O
Health	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
provok	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
contented	O
when	O
he	O
could	O
fight	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
Sunday	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
confirmed	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Internal	O
Damage	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
such	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Abdomen	O
,	O
might	O
come	O
from	O
a	O
Fall	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
little	O
Accident	O
,	O
considering	O
his	O
being	O
inform	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wiechard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Katharine	B-pers
Brandal	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
six	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
stripping	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Frock	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brandal	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
School	O
with	O
the	O
Cap	O
and	O
Frock	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
stripp	O
'd	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
without	O
both	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
a	O
Crowd	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
suspicious	O
Person	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stripping	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
she	O
pull	O
d	O
out	O
the	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cap	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
she	O
obstinately	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
of	B-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Hornsey-Lane	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
one	O
behind	O
him	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
kick	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Feet	O
and	O
run	O
cross	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cockayn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
thence	O
9	O
Cheshire	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cockayn	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Shop	O
safe	O
at	O
Night	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Shutter	O
cut	O
through	O
and	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
gone	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tomlin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
her	O
Mother	O
sent	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
:	O
The	O
Cheeses	O
being	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Barbary	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Levershire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Barbary	O
Withers	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Subcliff	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bottle	O
Case	O
,	O
2	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whale	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
he	O
absented	O
from	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
finding	O
him	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Whale	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
The	O
Facts	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
both	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
real	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Streets	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
two	O
Children	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pickd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
betwixt	O
his	O
Shirt	O
and	O
his	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
flocking	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Toon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Artillery	B-place
Ground	I-place
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
seeing	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
Exercise	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
seiz	O
d	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
own	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
four	O
others	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Joyns	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
s	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Denby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brigs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Gown	O
,	O
3	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
8	O
Suits	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
5	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
five	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
5	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Spelling	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
which	O
Goods	O
she	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nanney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Buckland	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
Turn	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
every	O
other	O
Night	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
missing	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
Notice	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
those	O
Nights	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sate	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Byron	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
Beer	O
in	O
his	O
Store-house	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
strictly	O
examining	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
had	O
bought	O
both	O
the	O
Beer	O
and	O
the	O
Ale	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Price	O
which	O
must	O
satisfy	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
gave	O
but	O
2	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Barrel	O
both	O
for	O
the	O
Beer	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Ale	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
willing	O
to	O
favour	O
him	O
,	O
suffered	O
him	O
to	O
escape	O
with	O
Impunity	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Biddle	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eckling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
pawn	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
trifling	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
actually	O
taken	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
severe	O
Reprimand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
such	O
un	O
ust	O
Proceedings	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lovejoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Silver	O
Pence	O
and	O
Twopences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Matchin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Burg	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beverstock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Porringers	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Boon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
stole	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beverstock	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sign	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Purport	O
of	O
it	O
amounted	O
to	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Beverstock	O
's	O
Pewter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Push	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
who	O
assisted	O
him	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
they	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
helped	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Confession	O
not	O
proving	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
or	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gately	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Dingley	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
confessing	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pendall	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
Ward	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Olive	O
Oyl	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Porter	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
privately	O
conveying	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Oil	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Cask	O
of	O
Oil	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Key	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
(	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
)	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
feloniously	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pottage-pot	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
22	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
;	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Westbury	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Westbury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
his	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
somebody	O
else	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Girl	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Coats	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Thighs	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
she	O
discover	O
more	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
than	O
this	O
ludicrous	O
Action	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thursly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
naught	O
with	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
peep	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
play	O
with	O
her	O
Thighs	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
further	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
a	O
forward	O
wicked	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
wicked	O
Appetite	O
,	O
took	O
and	O
Advantage	O
of	O
her	O
Folly	O
,	O
and	O
deluded	O
her	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ravished	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
his	O
Charge	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
could	O
do	O
no	O
otherways	O
than	O
bring	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Renough	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Renough	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Watchman	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Corner	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
others	O
seeing	O
him	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Chissel	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
was	O
broken	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Ridoubt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
led	O
by	O
the	O
Malice	O
and	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
her	O
male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
which	O
being	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
she	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
did	O
sling	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Easement	O
,	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
human	O
Excrements	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Place	O
it	O
was	O
suffocated	O
and	O
.......	O
thenand	O
there	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
since	O
at	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
knocked	O
against	O
the	O
Partition	O
.	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
himself	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
Woman	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
compose	O
herself	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
she	O
knocked	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
to	O
that	O
Degree	O
she	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
like	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Travail	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
his	O
Master	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Master	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complained	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Cholick	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
this	O
Deponent	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
some	O
Chicken	O
Broth	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
telling	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Fit	O
of	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
Vial	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
something	O
easy	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
violent	O
Indisposition	O
in	O
her	O
Bowels	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
gentle	O
Puke	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Bolus	O
and	O
Draught	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Family	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
herself	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
any	O
further	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Brother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
making	O
answer	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Room	O
very	O
foul	O
from	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Purging	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
to	O
empty	O
the	O
Chamber-pot	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
since	O
easier	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
the	O
Room	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barkhill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
had	O
Milk	O
in	O
her	O
Breasts	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
obstinately	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woolhead	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Ladies	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
told	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Indisposition	O
,	O
were	O
surprized	O
at	O
the	O
Incidents	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
related	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
Opinion	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
bore	O
a	O
Child	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
Milk	O
in	O
her	O
Breasts	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
bore	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Vomit	O
from	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Purging	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
something	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
account	O
for	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
slung	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber-Pot	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
:	O
She	O
likewise	O
told	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
Women	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
for	O
nine	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
nevertheless	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
the	O
Potion	O
which	O
brought	O
away	O
something	O
Extraordinary	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
where	O
upon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
giving	O
her	O
Opinion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bore	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Provisions	O
for	O
the	O
Reception	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
at	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
her	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Materials	O
suitable	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
Occasion	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
hard	O
Labour	O
and	O
no	O
Help	O
,	O
it	O
were	O
next	O
to	O
impossible	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
should	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
alive	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
immediately	O
die	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
being	O
disengag	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Navel-String	O
might	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Extremity	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
sensible	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
not	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Child	O
but	O
what	O
cried	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Child	O
never	O
cry	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
's	O
Birth	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
evident	O
from	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Binks	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
Cries	O
and	O
Groans	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Cry	O
or	O
Noise	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Modest	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
accidentally	O
in	O
Black-fryars	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
asking	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
he	O
readily	O
consented	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
laid	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Sleep	O
,	O
he	O
awaked	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
however	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Dormey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leathern	O
Breeches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Button	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Breeches	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pearce	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
stopt	O
selling	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Faulkoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
weigh	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
seeing	O
it	O
mark	O
'd	O
and	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
thought	O
convenient	O
to	O
examine	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
making	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
one	O
Shift	O
,	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mayson	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mayson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
this	O
Suspicion	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Check	O
Apron	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
by	O
the	O
Bosom	O
Mark	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Shirt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Check	O
Apron	O
with	O
the	O
Bosom	O
to	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
Child	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Doll	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
those	O
in	O
Court	O
who	O
could	O
prove	O
both	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
Muslin	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pretended	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
's	O
by	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
one	O
Corner	O
being	O
darn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Muslin	O
being	O
too	O
long	O
for	O
the	O
Lace	O
at	O
one	O
Corner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Millington	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Lace	O
that	O
was	O
sew	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
very	O
well	O
remember	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Lace	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
:	O
Several	O
others	O
appearing	O
to	O
her	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Dutton	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
willful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Harness	O
Buckles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Single	O
Felony	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
absented	O
herself	O
from	O
her	O
Service	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
soon	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Everage	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Anne	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
Mother	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
from	O
Newcastle	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
her	O
those	O
Goods	O
as	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Payment	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Excuse	O
differing	O
very	O
much	O
from	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
sending	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
she	O
paid	O
all	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
clandestinely	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Appleyard	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Nyehouse	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
.	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
two	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Appleyard	I-pers
being	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
bade	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lock	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
pulling	O
too	O
and	O
not	O
locking	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
it	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Lock	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
in	O
surprize	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
really	O
broke	O
,	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
length	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
Tea	O
and	O
Sugar	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
saying	O
that	O
was	O
false	O
for	O
she	O
loved	O
neither	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cut	O
herself	O
off	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
(	O
her	O
Master	O
keeping	O
a	O
Linnen-Draper	O
's	O
Shop	O
)	O
her	O
Examination	O
and	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Pupose	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
with	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Nyhouse	I-pers
,	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Master	O
of	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
those	O
Things	O
to	O
Dorothy	O
Nyhouse	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Confession	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Nyhouse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Appleyard	I-pers
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
and	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnorth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Apples	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winstandley	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Peachey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chancey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Peachey	I-pers
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
dying	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
Condition	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
Habitation	O
to	O
retire	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
Compassion	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
suffered	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
kindly	O
supplied	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Necessaries	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
stood	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
Kindness	O
and	O
Humanity	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
ungrateful	O
Wretch	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
Drawers	O
and	O
take	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
though	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
recovered	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Drawers	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1727	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
happened	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
treat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
light	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
an	O
old	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
make	O
me	O
Drink	O
?	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
whilst	O
she	O
sent	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
that	O
Burgess	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
and	O
he	O
sate	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
caught	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
understood	O
she	O
gave	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
one	O
Guinea	O
to	O
hold	O
her	O
Tongue	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
sooner	O
,	O
this	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
1727	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
would	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
since	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
indicted	O
her	O
now	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Law	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
indicted	O
him	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
indict	O
one	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
since	O
for	O
this	O
very	O
Fact	O
wherewith	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
confess	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
7	O
Guineas	O
from	O
Jacob	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
desiring	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
recovered	O
a	O
Judgment	O
and	O
Execution	O
on	O
him	O
for	O
Money	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
Liquors	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
hesitation	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
equivocated	O
on	O
that	O
Head	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Jacob	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Law	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
or	O
transport	O
her	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
his	O
Terms	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
being	O
another	O
Law	O
Suit	O
now	O
depending	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
,	O
yet	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
granted	O
,	O
they	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
contentious	O
wicked	O
People	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
further	O
Occasion	O
to	O
exert	O
their	O
Malice	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Loggerhead	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
seven	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
two	O
Marling	O
Pikes	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Upton	B-place
Galley	I-place
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Deenford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Clout	O
,	O
a	O
Tablecloath	O
,	O
5	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
three	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Onley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Keys	O
and	O
2	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leflewer	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Padget	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanker	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boucer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
(	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
)	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
was	O
inquiring	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
giving	O
him	O
some	O
Encouragement	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
Punch	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
finding	O
his	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
Guineas	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
his	O
Seal	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
likewise	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
as	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
trap	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
by	O
some	O
Evidence	O
and	O
accordingly	O
his	O
Scheme	O
had	O
the	O
desired	O
Effect	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
afterwards	O
denied	O
receiving	O
a	O
Guinea	O
on	O
such	O
Account	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Hair	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Harvey	O
,	O
whom	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
was	O
so	O
hardy	O
as	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Bawd	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
live	O
well	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
refusing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
Curse	O
and	O
Swear	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
avoid	O
his	O
Insults	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Artifice	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
Effect	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
his	O
Language	O
(	O
French	O
)	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
speak	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Crimes	O
were	O
too	O
notorious	O
for	O
that	O
Liberty	O
to	O
he	O
admitted	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
willing	O
immediately	O
to	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Punishment	O
which	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
on	O
such	O
Occasions	O
,	O
ordered	O
the	O
Sentence	O
should	O
be	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
indulg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
Time	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Preamble	O
is	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prison	O
from	O
whence	O
be	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
mean	O
House	O
stopp	O
'd	O
from	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
shall	O
be	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
bare	O
Ground	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Litter	O
,	O
Straw	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Covering	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
Garment	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
saving	O
something	O
to	O
cover	O
his	O
Privy	O
Members	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
shall	O
lie	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Face	O
shall	O
be	O
covered	O
and	O
his	O
Feet	O
bare	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Arms	O
shall	O
be	O
drawn	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
to	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Arm	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Legs	O
shall	O
be	O
used	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
Body	O
shall	O
be	O
laid	O
so	O
much	O
Iron	O
and	O
Stone	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
bear	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
after	O
be	O
shall	O
have	O
three	O
Morsels	O
of	O
Barley	O
Bread	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
Day	O
he	O
shall	O
drink	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
Prison	O
Door	O
,	O
saving	O
running	O
Water	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
shall	O
be	O
his	O
Diet	O
until	O
be	O
dies	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
ill	O
Consequence	O
which	O
would	O
attend	O
his	O
Obstinacy	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Griffin	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Medlin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
five	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
living	O
at	O
Winchmore-Hill	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
on	O
Saturdays	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Slippery	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
forward	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Lane	O
,	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Edmonton	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
stop	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
yet	O
they	O
dismounted	O
him	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
Pounds	O
four	O
Shillings	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
7	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
they	O
had	O
dropt	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
observation	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Same	O
Persons	O
he	O
saw	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Persons	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
describe	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Hyat	O
took	O
them	O
by	O
his	O
Description	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
he	O
saw	O
Harris	O
and	O
Medlin	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Discourse	O
about	O
Deen	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Drinking	O
together	O
,	O
Ones	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
,	O
of	O
Robberies	O
done	O
by	O
such	O
People	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Hulse	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Hayman	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
those	O
Men	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
House	O
in	O
Brick	O
Lane	O
,	O
Old-street	O
,	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
only	O
Dear-stealers	O
,	O
but	O
other	O
wife	O
of	O
dissolute	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
come	O
on	O
Horseback	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
fire	O
off	O
their	O
Pistols	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Hulse	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Persons	O
he	O
drank	O
with	O
at	O
Islington	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
has	O
them	O
apprehended	O
,	O
when	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
swore	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
particularly	O
described	O
their	O
Persons	O
,	O
Habits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Scar	O
in	O
Owen	O
's	O
Face	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
Drank	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
the	O
Horses	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
as	O
swore	O
by	O
Barker	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Harris	O
would	O
seign	O
have	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
discovered	O
Medlin	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Owen	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Griffin	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Dr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hulse	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Hulse	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
4	O
Men	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
Ponder's-End	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edmonton	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bear	O
his	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
assaulted	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Coach	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
Scar	O
upon	O
his	O
Cheek	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
plainly	O
discover	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
bright	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
contented	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
beat	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Teeth	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
broke	O
his	O
own	O
Whip	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
others	O
oblig	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Positive	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Persons	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
This	O
Fact	O
likewise	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Reddey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isabella	O
and	O
Jane	O
Dawson	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Read	I-pers
confess	O
before	O
Justice	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
That	O
She	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
her	O
Mistress	O
Jane	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
stood	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
whilst	O
she	O
watch	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
letting	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
privy	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
present	O
Executioner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
likewise	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
she	O
let	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
consented	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
Sign	O
her	O
Confession	O
;	O
but	O
though	O
this	O
Confession	O
did	O
not	O
effect	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
without	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Menaces	O
or	O
Threatnings	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
this	O
Effect	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Convent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	I-place
and	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Crown-Tavern	I-place
they	O
drank	O
very	O
plentifully	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
remember	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
falling	O
asleep	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Snuff-Box	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
about	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Slugs	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
's	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
condemn	O
'd	O
this	O
Sessions	O
)	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
such	O
Uses	O
as	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
State	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
now	O
is	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
these	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
Marks	O
or	O
the	O
Maker	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Snuff-Box	O
to	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
agreeing	O
either	O
with	O
his	O
Story	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
his	O
Actions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Humble	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
38	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hanney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flaxon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mudrey	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
Several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crosley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Table	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gascoin	I-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Hearing	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
clear	O
and	O
substantial	O
Evidence	O
,	O
vindicated	O
herself	O
from	O
the	O
Imputations	O
she	O
lay	O
under	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
Honour	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
Times	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
indicted	O
her	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
private	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Manner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sculls	O
,	O
a	O
Sail	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Cusheons	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
properly	O
a	O
Share	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Boat	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Akrons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grimbolt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bocea	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
weak	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
6.	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
alias	O
Harris	O
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Medling	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Red	I-pers
dey	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
4.	O
George	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pearce	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
29.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darvel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Neaves	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wiechard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Subcliff	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lovejoy	I-pers
,	O
May	O
Bolton	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Dormey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
An	O
drew	O
Green	O
,	O
Ann	O
Green	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Appleyard	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leftewer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Padget	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilt	I-pers
shire	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Humble	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Flaxton	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
one	O
Month	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
CHARACTERS	O
of	O
the	O
TIMES	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Writings	O
,	O
Characters	O
,	O
Education	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
several	O
Nobleman	O
and	O
Gentleman	O
libell	O
'd	O
by	O
P	O
-	O
e	O
and	O
Company	O
;	O
particularly	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dodington	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Burner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Welsted	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Eusden	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Theobald	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
,	O
Lady	O
M.	O
Wortley	O
,	O
the	O
late	O
Dean	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
Aw	O
'd	O
by	O
no	O
Shame	O
,	O
by	O
no	O
Respect	O
controll	O
'd	O
,	O
In	O
Scandal	O
busy	O
,	O
in	O
R	O
eproaches	O
hold	O
:	O
With	O
witty	O
Malice	O
,	O
Studious	O
to	O
defame	O
;	O
Scorn	O
all	O
their	O
Joy	O
,	O
and	O
Laughter	O
all	O
their	O
Aim	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
;	O
T.	O
Read	O
,	O
in	O
White-Fryars	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
FEMALE	O
DUNCLAD	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Fair	O
Maids	O
of	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
Containing	O
,	O
a	O
faithful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Intrigues	O
,	O
Gallantries	O
,	O
and	O
Amours	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
new	O
LIST	O
of	O
PARLIAMENT	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
Places	O
of	O
the	O
Members	O
Abode	O
,	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
Price	O
I	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Angelick	O
Imperial	O
Tincture	O
,	O
THE	O
most	O
certain	O
Cure	O
for	O
Agues	O
,	O
and	O
Intermitting	O
Fevers	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
rage	O
so	O
violently	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
is	O
faithfully	O
prepared	O
by	O
an	O
eminent	O
and	O
noted	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
hath	O
been	O
used	O
with	O
an	O
uncommon	O
Success	O
;	O
continues	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
Wholesale	O
and	O
Retail	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Appointment	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cliffs	O
,	O
Stationer	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Rummer-Tavern	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
with	O
good	O
Allowance	O
to	O
Country	O
or	O
Town	O
Shopkeepers	O
.	O
Its	O
sold	O
Retail	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
Woodstreet	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lye	O
,	O
a	O
Picture	O
Shop	O
,	O
over-against	O
South-Sea	O
House	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cheek	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
,	O
Horsly-Down	O
,	O
Fair-street	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Bray	O
,	O
Chandler	O
,	O
near	O
Guildhall-Yard	O
,	O
Basingshall-street	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
many	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
Seal	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
Vials	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
A	O
Tyger	O
trampling	O
on	O
a	O
Ducal	O
Coroner	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Helmets	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
Words	O
(	O
Non	O
Quis	O
,	O
sed	O
Quid	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
Scroll	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Shilling	O
each	O
.	O
