TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1728-9	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Pengelly	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Post	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Evered	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Schooley	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Penner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Peach	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Arnott	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Renn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Power	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pettey	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Chaney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leflewer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Stop	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
wedth	O
of	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Woodstreet	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
dropt	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
whose	O
Coat	O
was	O
unbuttoned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
ill	O
Design	O
,	O
followed	O
them	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
bringing	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
empty	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
second	O
Dive	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
brought	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
finding	O
himself	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
dropt	O
it	O
between	O
his	O
Feet	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
likewise	O
did	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
produced	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Millford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Christmas	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
on	O
a	O
loose	O
Coat	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
own	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
under	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Flap	O
being	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
examining	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
seeming	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Weight	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
afterwards	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
other	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Sailor	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
to	O
hold	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
since	O
hear	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
idle	O
Tale	O
not	O
being	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horn	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Leather	O
String	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Seal	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
giving	O
Evidence	O
in	O
a	O
clear	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Fuddling	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Design	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Eadey	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Barbary	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
2	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
2	O
China	O
Saucers	O
,	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
7	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
80	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
390	O
Yards	O
of	O
Russia	O
Cloth	O
and	O
Diaper	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Hector	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Eadey	O
Wood	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
from	O
last	O
July	O
to	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
finding	O
her	O
negligent	O
,	O
and	O
adicted	O
to	O
drinking	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
teaching	O
his	O
Children	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Resolution	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
provided	O
himself	O
with	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
appointed	O
for	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Counting-house	O
and	O
was	O
Surpris	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
his	O
Letters	O
and	O
Accompts	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
recovering	O
from	O
his	O
Surprise	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Assistance	O
putting	O
out	O
the	O
Flames	O
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
Fire	O
had	O
been	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
lower	O
Shelf	O
on	O
which	O
some	O
Papers	O
were	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
burnt	O
up	O
to	O
another	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
destroy	O
'd	O
abundance	O
of	O
Writings	O
of	O
Consequence	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Counting-house	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Fire	O
quite	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
revers	O
'd	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
their	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
Children	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
finding	O
his	O
House	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
set	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
done	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Things	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
who	O
receive	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
several	O
Pawn-brokers	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eadey	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
were	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
intrusted	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Eadey	O
Wood	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
an	O
Inventory	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
clear	O
against	O
Barbary	O
Jennings	O
,	O
otherwise	O
then	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wire	O
Grate	O
for	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Poperty	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Bacon	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
a	O
Tin	O
Cannister	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Battledores	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sheval	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sheval	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
charitable	O
good	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
ask	O
Relief	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
relieve	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
mov	O
'd	O
to	O
Pity	O
,	O
fetch	O
'd	O
her	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
immediate	O
Relief	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
have	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
surprising	O
Instance	O
of	O
the	O
Charity	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
otherwise	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sheval	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
confessing	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Plumber	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
5	O
Shillings	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Tappey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
her	O
the	O
Favour	O
to	O
hand	O
her	O
over	O
a	O
dirty	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
that	O
noted	O
Person	O
Mrs.	O
Harvey	O
,	O
(	O
whose	O
Character	O
has	O
so	O
often	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
)	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
apprehend	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Harvey	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
confident	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Woman	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Harvey	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
her	O
ever	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
other	O
Women	O
were	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Harvey	O
's	O
in	O
Hedge-Lane	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harvey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
complaining	O
for	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
his	O
Mistress	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
only	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
herself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
her	O
Landlord	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
commit	O
that	O
wicked	O
and	O
detectable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lad	O
of	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Nature	O
and	O
Consequence	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
Truth	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
liking	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke-Maker	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
his	O
offering	O
unseemly	O
Actions	O
for	O
some	O
Nights	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
at	O
10	O
or	O
a	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
actually	O
commit	O
the	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
following	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Following	O
he	O
told	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
Katherine	O
Cox	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
disorder	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Violence	O
he	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
coroborated	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
's	O
Shirt	O
,	O
which	O
bore	O
some	O
Marks	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
was	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Usage	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Parts	O
enrag	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Muscles	O
extended	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Caceration	O
about	O
the	O
Anus	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
might	O
possibly	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
natural	O
Disorders	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Boyl	O
on	O
his	O
Fundament	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Disorder	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fearn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
upon	O
liking	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
least	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
make	O
any	O
Complaint	O
in	O
his	O
hearing	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
Usuage	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ludgate	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Killingsley	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
Examination	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Stockings	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
trac	O
'd	O
from	O
one	O
Buyer	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
selling	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
her	O
Employment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
Things	O
at	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
several	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
those	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
partly	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
and	O
sold	O
Goods	O
,	O
living	O
a	O
very	O
regular	O
Life	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hubank	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Bibles	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Grey	O
Coat	O
Hospital	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cousens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Weale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privatley	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Ballance	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Downer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Clandel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Richard	O
Green	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
Watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
this	O
Information	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pledg	O
'd	O
for	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
whom	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
Sixpence	O
for	O
her	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	B-pers
two	O
Shillings	O
.	O
This	O
odd	O
Proceeding	O
of	O
Stealing	O
to	O
pay	O
Debts	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
ill	O
Conduct	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Service	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
former	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Wymon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
32	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dennet	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Dennet	I-pers
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jenkinson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
half	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pursuing	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Musquet	I-pers
of	O
Hanover-Square	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Cope	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pretended	O
Message	O
from	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Astin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
not	O
being	O
stirring	O
,	O
he	O
bade	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wait	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
on	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
clear	O
'd	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neeves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Duroy	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
300	O
Yards	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
doing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chattey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
assisted	O
in	O
seizing	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Thief	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
his	O
Practice	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
to	O
catch	O
Thieves	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Men	O
,	O
People	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
Opinion	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Marr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boake	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Berrisford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
R.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
and	O
Found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Cummins	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Disgrace	O
of	O
Humane	O
Nature	O
,	O
the	O
Displeasure	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
on	O
this	O
Occasion	O
will	O
not	O
bear	O
mentioning	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
the	O
Account	O
given	O
was	O
so	O
monstrous	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
material	O
Points	O
in	O
the	O
Depositions	O
appear	O
'd	O
incongruous	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Crawfoot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
in	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
13	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dixon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
somebody	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Maid	O
went	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Money	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
she	O
spoke	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
her	O
dead	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
Deponent	O
)	O
and	O
kept	O
making	O
his	O
Demands	O
till	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
Gold	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bade	O
her	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
(	O
pulling	O
out	O
another	O
Pistol	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
slipt	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
were	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dixon	O
confirm	O
'd	O
every	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
hold	O
up	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mischief	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
a	O
Pistol	O
which	O
afterwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
loaded	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
searching	O
him	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
3	O
Farthings	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Mask	O
fell	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
another	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Entry	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
Vizard	O
Mask	O
excepted	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
Effect	O
against	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
fifty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Weedon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Gelding	O
was	O
at	O
Grass	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
brought	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
Fair	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tunks	I-pers
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gelding	O
had	O
a	O
shorn	O
Mane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Star	O
in	O
the	O
Forehead	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tunks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Gelding	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
of	O
Southwark	O
,	O
for	O
forty	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Gelding	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
Fair	O
,	O
which	O
began	O
the	O
Day	O
following	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gelding	O
had	O
a	O
shorn	O
Mane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Star	O
in	O
the	O
Forehead	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
George-Inn	O
in	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
Justice	O
Weedon	O
's	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
carry	O
'd	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
by	O
Tunks	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sell	O
the	O
Gelding	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tunks	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
(	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
leading	O
to	O
Hackney	O
)	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
Horseback	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
was	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
more	O
Money	O
or	O
Money	O
's	O
Worth	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
gave	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
clear	O
Moon	O
Light	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Surprise	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
kept	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
in	O
his	O
Memory	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
distinguish	O
him	O
from	O
several	O
others	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
on	O
another	O
Occasion	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
remembered	O
the	O
Horse	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
rode	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
bay	O
Colour	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
his	O
Tail	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
likewise	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
others	O
since	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
directed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
also	O
remember	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Coat	O
with	O
close	O
Sleeves	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fouch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
highest	O
Ground	O
,	O
could	O
remember	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
likewise	O
remember	O
the	O
Horse	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
rode	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Passengers	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
ride	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
swearing	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
rode	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Mind	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
standing	O
still	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Passengers	O
let	O
down	O
the	O
Sashes	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
commanded	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
contented	O
,	O
made	O
him	O
drive	O
faster	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Gallop	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
towards	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Stones	O
Cast	O
from	O
Shoreditch	O
Church	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
pitted	O
with	O
the	O
Small-Pox	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
wearing	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
was	O
described	O
before	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
anxious	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
about	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
Home	O
again	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Horse	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
Seven	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
Horse	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Person	O
rode	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bowcock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Nag	O
s-Head-Inn	O
,	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
he	O
riding	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Servant	O
should	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Keeping	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
in	O
Pledge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Buckley	O
,	O
by	O
Inquiry	O
,	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
suspecting	O
that	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
defraud	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
.	O
That	O
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
relieve	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Deponent	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
riding	O
away	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Buckley	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
Horse	O
Home	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bowcock	O
's	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
aforemention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaded	O
,	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
and	O
prim	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
with	O
close	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
as	O
describ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
.	O
He	O
utterly	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Horse	O
Home	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
this	O
Deponent	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
several	O
idle	O
Tales	O
,	O
his	O
Evidence	O
was	O
of	O
little	O
use	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lobe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
four	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
eleven	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lobe	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Drawers	O
ransack	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Hewlet	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
heard	O
of	O
their	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
E	O
and	O
O.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Joyns	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
E	O
and	O
O	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Person	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Spoons	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
them	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
Business	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ansley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Hewlet	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Hearing	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
greal	O
deal	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
dispose	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
some	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
two	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
Davis	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
they	O
perswaded	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joyns	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
The	O
Spoon	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
likewise	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Lobe	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
fastned	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
very	O
securely	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Purport	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
,	O
One	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewlet	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
Three	O
therein	O
till	O
Two	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
Davis	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
together	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Padlock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Davis	O
in	O
Suffolk-Street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
2	O
foreign	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
Dr.	O
Oldfield	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
forty	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
of	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Sum	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
miss	O
'd	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
more	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Connivance	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
mark	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
heard	O
somebody	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
(	O
though	O
she	O
shuffled	O
about	O
his	O
Bed	O
Side	O
)	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Guineas	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
by	O
his	O
Bedside	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
without	O
her	O
Shoes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Hesitation	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
likewise	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
foreign	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
likewise	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
her	O
taking	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Oldfield	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
Confession	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Oldfield	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
mark	O
'd	O
Guineas	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
as	O
Dr.	O
Oldfield	O
had	O
describ	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
Guilty	O
in	O
Part	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Revell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Convent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tea	O
Canister	O
,	O
two	O
Cases	O
of	O
Desert	O
Knives	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
Caters	O
,	O
eight	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
Exstinguisher	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Bason	O
,	O
four	O
Salts	O
,	O
three	O
Salvers	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Thorold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sentement	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
late	O
Mr.	O
Sentement	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Broadway	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
late	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Sentement	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
herself	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Charlwood	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Stow	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Lady	O
Thorold	O
's	O
Trunk	O
stood	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
large	O
Plate	O
scatter	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Trunk	O
open	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Desk	O
were	O
likewise	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
several	O
Bars	O
were	O
fasted	O
,	O
was	O
broken	O
down	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
certain	O
she	O
bolted	O
the	O
Cellar	O
down	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
Consequence	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Seal	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
never	O
broke	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Observation	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
somebody	O
who	O
knew	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Charlwood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Sentement	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
usually	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Sentement	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
distrub	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Sleep	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
nothing	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
at	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prentice	O
bound	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
unbinding	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Disorders	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
as	O
mentioned	O
by	O
Katharine	O
Broadway	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Hascoat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Thorold	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Plate	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sentement	O
's	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
whilst	O
her	O
Lady	O
remain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Trunk	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
seal	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
corded	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
her	O
Lady	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawlin	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
M.	O
Sentement	O
,	O
to	O
long	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
perswade	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Confederate	O
in	O
robbing	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
with	O
frequent	O
Importunities	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
to	O
a	O
Complyance	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Charlwood	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
being	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
false	O
Keys	O
opened	O
several	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Plate	O
from	O
the	O
Lady	O
Thorold	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
his	O
Hands	O
full	O
of	O
Guineas	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
more	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Till	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
the	O
Still-Room	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
betimes	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ry	O
'd	O
this	O
Deponent	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Colour	O
on	O
the	O
Knavery	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
common	O
Housebreakers	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
off	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
to	O
amuse	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
Alarum	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Robbers	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Money	O
exhausted	O
,	O
he	O
consulted	O
with	O
this	O
Deponent	O
about	O
melting	O
down	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
bought	O
a	O
melting	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
melting	O
it	O
,	O
ran	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Hearth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropping	O
it	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
perswaded	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
,	O
to	O
vouch	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
see	O
him	O
find	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Silversmith	O
being	O
cautious	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
industriously	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Scene	O
of	O
Iniquity	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
Appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Weaks	O
the	O
Silversmith	O
corroborated	O
the	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Deposition	O
,	O
in	O
relating	O
every	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
his	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Several	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
Worth	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
Word	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
serv	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
others	O
as	O
a	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
faithful	O
Servant	O
;	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
his	O
former	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
an	O
Indorsment	O
on	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
following	O
Words	O
and	O
Figures	O
,	O
800	O
l.	O
pay	O
to	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
-	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Heinousness	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
first	O
,	O
forging	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
of	O
800	O
l.	O
made	O
payable	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
Robert	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
indorsing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
which	O
Note	O
he	O
drew	O
upon	O
a	O
Paper	O
he	O
had	O
obtain	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Pretence	O
of	O
a	O
frank	O
'd	O
Cover	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
send	O
News	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
thus	O
he	O
abused	O
the	O
Courtesy	O
and	O
good	O
Nature	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
by	O
cutting	O
off	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
contain	O
'd	O
the	O
Directions	O
and	O
drawing	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
the	O
Name	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Word	O
Free	O
,	O
should	O
serve	O
his	O
Purpose	O
in	O
the	O
Indorsment	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
borrowing	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
450	O
l.	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harl	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Gredit	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
indors	O
'd	O
Note	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
had	O
observ	O
'd	O
that	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
had	O
several	O
frank	O
'd	O
Covers	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
six	O
blank	O
Covers	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
Covers	O
might	O
be	O
frank	O
'd	O
without	O
a	O
Superscription	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Master	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
writing	O
the	O
Superscription	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Word	O
Free	O
and	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
he	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
his	O
Master	O
give	O
any	O
promissary	O
Notes	O
on	O
any	O
Occasion	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
The	O
six	O
frank	O
Covers	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
believe	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Covers	O
that	O
Robert	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
frank	O
'd	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
than	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
Later	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
finding	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
had	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
frank	O
his	O
Letters	O
without	O
writing	O
the	O
Directions	O
himself	O
,	O
had	O
sent	O
three	O
several	O
Directions	O
in	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
six	O
Franks	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Master	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
or	O
Note	O
of	O
Directions	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
frank	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Letters	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
both	O
a	O
Brother	O
and	O
Nephew	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Members	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philip	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
he	O
wrote	O
this	O
Note	O
of	O
Directions	O
.	O
The	O
Contents	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Bristol	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Levett	O
.	O
Huntington	O
.	O
To	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mitford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Exeter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
crouded	O
o	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Addition	O
,	O
were	O
different	O
Ink	O
from	O
the	O
F	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Name	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
some	O
Letters	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
.	O
A	O
Remark	O
was	O
likewise	O
made	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
common	O
Custom	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
Val	O
.	O
received	O
,	O
but	O
Val	O
.	O
receiv	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Word	O
Free	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
well	O
ras	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Purpose	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
For	O
,	O
though	O
done	O
so	O
bunglingly	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
easily	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Spicer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
above	O
twenty	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquaintted	O
very	O
well	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Affairs	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Dealings	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Name	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
F	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Indorsment	O
as	O
was	O
made	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Braithwait	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
brought	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
as	O
mentioned	O
before	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Order	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harl	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
450	O
l.	O
which	O
Note	O
or	O
Order	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
two	O
Notes	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
250	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
220	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Charlton	O
Thurp	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
being	O
above	O
the	O
Sum	O
mentioned	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Harl	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Sum	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harl	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
brought	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
800	O
l.	O
(	O
which	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
indicted	O
)	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
450	O
l.	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
upon	O
his	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
450	O
l.	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
Pledge	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
which	O
Note	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
alter	O
'd	O
but	O
was	O
directly	O
as	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
6400	O
l.	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
had	O
paid	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
460	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
very	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Memorandum	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
attach	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
to	O
have	O
counterfeited	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Sight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Name	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Indorsment	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
Forgery	O
;	O
the	O
Note	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
eight	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
three	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
,	O
for	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
May	O
the	O
13th	O
1728.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
And	O
on	O
the	O
Backside	O
indors	O
'd	O
thus	O
:	O
800	O
l.	O
pray	O
pay	O
to	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
-	O
For	O
the	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
And	O
here	O
it	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Word	O
For	O
,	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
Free	O
,	O
as	O
wrote	O
on	O
a	O
Cover	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
the	O
o	O
being	O
crouded	O
between	O
the	O
F	O
and	O
r	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ee	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Free	O
,	O
made	O
to	O
serve	O
for	O
the	O
contracted	O
the	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
e	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
y	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Harl	O
had	O
his	O
450	O
l.	O
paid	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
concluded	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
brought	O
under	O
the	O
Imputation	O
of	O
defrauding	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
450	O
l.	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
paid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harls	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
as	O
a	O
Discharge	O
of	O
that	O
Debt	O
,	O
but	O
placed	O
to	O
accompt	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
indebted	O
in	O
other	O
Sums	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harl	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Instance	O
given	O
.	O
That	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
otherwise	O
,	O
his	O
Crime	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
If	O
a	O
Thief	O
steals	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
does	O
not	O
keep	O
,	O
but	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
still	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
33	O
Harry	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
for	O
obtaining	O
Money	O
by	O
false	O
Tokens	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Harl	I-pers
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
450	O
l.	O
mentioned	O
on	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
defranded	O
Mr.	O
Harl	O
of	O
,	O
under	O
false	O
Colours	O
and	O
Pretences	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
of	O
800	O
l.	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
indors	O
'd	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
bearing	O
Date	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
1727	O
,	O
for	O
1260	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
sing	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
indors	O
'd	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
opened	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
Persons	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
a	O
false	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
did	O
publish	O
the	O
same	O
Fraudulently	O
for	O
a	O
true	O
Note	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
intending	O
to	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
Samuel	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
forg	O
'd	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Writing	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
melancholy	O
Scene	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
in	O
that	O
Habit	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
appearing	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
's	O
Habit	O
,	O
arraign	O
'd	O
for	O
such	O
unjust	O
Proceedings	O
,	O
in	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
in	O
contriving	O
counterfeiting	O
and	O
forging	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
stood	O
indicted	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
good	O
Nature	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
frank	O
Covers	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
this	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
counterfeit	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
contrive	O
Mr.	O
Edward	O
's	O
Name	O
to	O
the	O
Indorsment	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Paper	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
or	O
torn	O
from	O
some	O
Writing	O
,	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
several	O
Letters	O
being	O
visible	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
indented	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
more	O
Room	O
for	O
the	O
Note	O
to	O
he	O
wrote	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Word	O
Free	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
all	O
Probability	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
Appearance	O
,	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
was	O
chang	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Word	O
For	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Purpose	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Ink	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
o	O
,	O
which	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Note	O
was	O
crouded	O
between	O
the	O
F	O
and	O
the	O
r	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
additional	O
Writing	O
were	O
much	O
blacker	O
than	O
the	O
Name	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
together	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
there	O
be	O
any	O
Foundation	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
such	O
Consequence	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
of	O
1260	O
l.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
his	O
Writing	O
all	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
managed	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
750	O
l	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
this	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
deposited	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
demanded	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
undone	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
must	O
apply	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
who	O
indors	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
wealthy	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
under	O
Confusion	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
minded	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confusion	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
hinder	O
'd	O
by	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
so	O
far	O
retracted	O
,	O
as	O
even	O
to	O
deny	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
opposite	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
in	O
Dukestreet	O
Westminster	O
,	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
frequently	O
got	O
frank	O
'd	O
Covers	O
for	O
Letters	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
likewise	O
repeated	O
her	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
deliver	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
contain	O
'd	O
three	O
Directions	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Levet	O
of	O
Huntington	O
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mitford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Exeter	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
having	O
before	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
Frank	B-pers
Letters	I-pers
without	O
he	O
wrote	O
all	O
the	O
Directions	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Spicer	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
holding	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
brought	O
the	O
Note	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
that	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
promissary	O
Note	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
750	O
l.	O
in	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
following	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
brought	O
him	O
400	O
l.	O
and	O
indors	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
promissary	O
Note	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
paying	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Attorney	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tompkins	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
indors	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
ruin	O
'd	O
and	O
undone	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
make	O
himself	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
demanded	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
who	O
indors	O
'd	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Substance	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Note	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
since	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Alterations	O
:	O
The	O
Contents	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
16th	O
1727	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
one	O
thousand	O
two	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
for	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
1260	O
l.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
.	O
And	O
indros	O
'd	O
,	O
1260	O
l.	O
pray	O
pay	O
to	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
-	O
For	O
the	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Indorsment	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
Jury	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
several	O
Letters	O
were	O
visible	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
paper	O
cut	O
and	O
indented	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Ends	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
though	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
effectually	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Words	O
to	O
make	O
as	O
if	O
indors	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
were	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
Ink	O
from	O
F	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
Samuel	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
Note	O
all	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
the	O
Indorsment	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	O
Edwards	O
being	O
likewise	O
there	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
draw	O
up	O
a	O
Note	O
payable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
together	O
,	O
not	O
had	O
he	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Sum	O
mentioned	O
in	O
that	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
asking	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
should	O
make	O
it	O
payable	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
further	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Note	O
being	O
indors	O
'd	O
,	O
pretendedly	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Note	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Mitford	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
committed	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
upon	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Note	O
to	O
be	O
indors	O
'd	O
by	O
Samuel	O
Edwards	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
than	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
drew	O
up	O
the	O
Note	O
so	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
seem	O
'd	O
before	O
him	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
minded	O
to	O
made	O
an	O
ingenious	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
hinder	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Interposition	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
he	O
understood	O
was	O
Mitford	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
execute	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Inventions	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
too	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
repeat	O
)	O
but	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
's	O
Council	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
's	O
Advantage	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
seem	O
partial	O
to	O
escape	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
of	O
his	O
running	O
and	O
sending	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
little	O
Effect	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
got	O
Admittance	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
Person	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
deny	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
asking	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
young	O
Couple	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
marry	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
License	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
Licenses	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
perform	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
Bird	O
of	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
asking	O
if	O
she	O
the	O
young	O
Gentlewoman	O
was	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
answered	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
marry	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Penalty	O
for	O
doing	O
such	O
an	O
Action	O
was	O
50	O
l.	O
by	O
Law	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
satisfy	O
the	O
young	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
undertake	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
decoy	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Freedom	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Warrant	O
did	O
not	O
extend	O
to	O
the	O
Suburbs	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
lived	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Sham	O
not	O
taking	O
,	O
he	O
waited	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Ends	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
observ	O
'd	O
on	O
this	O
Conduct	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
acted	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Conscience	O
,	O
in	O
not	O
performing	O
an	O
Act	O
so	O
unlawful	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
so	O
frequently	O
practis	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
had	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
seven	O
Months	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
frequently	O
had	O
private	O
Meetings	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
Manner	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
reasonably	O
be	O
believed	O
they	O
mutually	O
agreed	O
together	O
to	O
form	O
these	O
Designs	O
,	O
and	O
doubtless	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Forgery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
Peel	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
for	O
the	O
greatest	O
Part	O
of	O
last	O
Summer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
one	O
would	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Coffee-Room	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
would	O
retire	O
,	O
one	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
Brook	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Downing-Street	O
Westminster	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
frequently	O
met	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
would	O
come	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
refus	O
'd	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Janeway	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
Janeway	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
near	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
)	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
sometimes	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
always	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
Particulars	O
.	O
Two	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
a	O
considerable	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
being	O
one	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Account	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
say	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Weakness	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
made	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
's	O
Council	O
confess	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Witness	O
was	O
quite	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
better	O
never	O
been	O
found	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
Hales	O
and	O
Kinnersley	O
had	O
Dealings	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
transacted	O
Affairs	O
for	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
clearly	O
prove	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
was	O
really	O
indebted	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
.	O
Others	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Strength	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
mentioning	O
the	O
Interposition	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mitford	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
seem	O
'd	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Living	O
and	O
True	O
God	O
to	O
witness	O
for	O
his	O
Innocence	O
;	O
yet	O
this	O
,	O
without	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
little	O
Effect	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Indulgence	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
750	O
l.	O
by	O
false	O
Tokens	O
,	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
were	O
once	O
more	O
together	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
and	O
forging	O
a	O
false	O
Note	O
,	O
or	O
Writing	O
purporting	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
1650	O
l.	O
was	O
drawn	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
made	O
payable	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
,	O
dated	O
March	O
the	O
30th	O
1728	O
,	O
and	O
indors	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Observations	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
wrote	O
on	O
the	O
Covers	O
,	O
frank	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
crouding	O
one	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
obliterating	O
another	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
order	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
pass	O
for	O
a	O
true	O
Note	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thrup	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
this	O
false	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thrup	O
lent	O
him	O
in	O
Notes	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
400	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Maddox	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spicer	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Methods	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
to	O
procure	O
frank	O
Covers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
then	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thrup	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
brought	O
this	O
Note	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
)	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
400	O
l.	O
in	O
Notes	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
reposing	O
so	O
much	O
Confidence	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
as	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Guilty	O
of	O
so	O
vile	O
an	O
Action	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
paid	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
the	O
Note	O
been	O
alter	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Churchwarden	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
own	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Parish-Book	O
,	O
to	O
compare	O
it	O
with	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
had	O
there	O
written	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
compar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
believ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lenton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
likewise	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
this	O
Note	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Writing	O
.	O
Then	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
March	O
the	O
30th	O
1728	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
six	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
one	O
thousand	O
six	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
for	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
Per	O
me	O
Samuel	O
Edwards	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
was	O
all	O
wrote	O
in	O
Secretary	O
Hand	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Name	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
visible	O
remains	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
Free	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
round	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
alone	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Forgery	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
substantial	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
was	O
then	O
indicted	O
singly	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
4700	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Order	O
sing	O
'd	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
fraudulently	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
true	O
Note	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
This	O
Note	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
likewise	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Foundation	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Alterations	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
clear	O
and	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
aggravating	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
in	O
Particular	O
this	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
being	O
under	O
an	O
Arrest	O
this	O
Time	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Kinnerslay	O
to	O
Sir	O
Bibey	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Bail	O
,	O
which	O
friendly	O
Office	O
Sir	O
Bibey	O
Lake	O
perform	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
July	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
sent	O
to	O
Sir	O
Bibey	O
Lake	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
Bail	O
for	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Writ	O
of	O
Error	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
Sir	O
Bibey	O
Lake	O
hesitate	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
Bail	O
to	O
a	O
Writ	O
of	O
Error	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Desire	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Peel	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Bibey	O
Lake	O
insisting	O
on	O
Security	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
gave	O
him	O
this	O
Note	O
of	O
4700	O
l.	O
for	O
his	O
Security	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Sir	O
Bibey	O
Lake	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Bail	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Note	O
was	O
read	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
March	O
the	O
30th	O
1727	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
four	O
thousand	O
and	O
six	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
six	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
,	O
for	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
Per	O
me	O
Samuel	O
Edwards	O
:	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
indors	O
'd	O
:	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
:	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
this	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
indigent	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
not	O
could	O
his	O
Dealings	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
be	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
though	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Children	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
likewise	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
:	O
Next	O
Sessions	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
indicted	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
Crime	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lustring	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
12	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennison	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Carter	O
Frigate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
likewise	O
for	O
stealing	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Revis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Fidgin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashburner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sugar-Loaf	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Barroway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Noxen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Sen	O
.	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Axtead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Comber	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Crawfoot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ives	O
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincint	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
2	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
30.	O
Charles	B-pers
Chaney	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Millford	I-pers
,	O
Eadey	O
Wood	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Mes	I-pers
senger	O
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hu	I-pers
bank	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Weale	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Clandel	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Masquct	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Adams	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Barroway	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Axtead	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
together	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
once	O
over	O
against	O
Fetter-Lane	O
End	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
50	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
five	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
after	O
:	O
The	O
latter	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
suffer	O
two	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
three	O
Years	O
after	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
Published	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
all	O
Persons	O
both	O
in	O
Town	O
and	O
Country	O
,	O
DIRECTIONS	O
for	O
PROSECUTING	O
THIEVES	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
those	O
false	O
Guides	O
,	O
the	O
Sollicitors	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Ease	O
and	O
little	O
Expence	O
:	O
Wherein	O
is	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
indicting	O
a	O
Felon	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Affizes	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Lesson	O
very	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
perused	O
by	O
those	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
serve	O
as	O
Jurors	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Courts	O
of	O
Judicature	O
.	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
Read	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Dogwell-Court	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
