TOKEN	NE
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1729	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Four	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gettings	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
Leonard	B-pers
Tillet	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Latten	I-pers
James	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Ewsden	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Murden	I-pers
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winchborough	I-pers
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
.	O
Kichard	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Brumley	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hugget	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Friday-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
to	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
of	O
Ross	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
loading	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
immediately	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Winsford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coatsworth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Bags	O
of	O
Sugar	O
were	O
found	O
nigh	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Hogsheads	O
that	O
lay	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
actually	O
steal	O
the	O
Sugar	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lily	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Leonard	B-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Bunstal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
slaying	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Hill	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
challeng	O
'd	O
him	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
fight	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
into	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
fight	O
,	O
several	O
Persons	O
being	O
present	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
first	O
Fall	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
fought	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Fall	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
putting	O
on	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlord	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
beat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
some	O
other	O
Time	O
;	O
that	O
sitting	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Stool	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
:	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
viewing	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
outward	O
Contusions	O
;	O
but	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
bursting	O
of	O
some	O
large	O
Blood-Vessels	O
by	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Courtman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harbut	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hannover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Macculler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparels	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
of	O
8	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fowles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach-House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worcester	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
,	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mark	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gross	O
of	O
Pipes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Felony	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
John	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Botolph	B-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gloucestershire	O
Cheeses	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Person	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
Twopence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edger	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lamb	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Lamb	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hannover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Dufty	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
shewing	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
Civility	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
prompted	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
especially	O
,	O
having	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
putting	O
her	O
upon	O
getting	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
Guinea	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Susanna	O
Dufty	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
Mary	O
Painter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Susanna	O
Dufty	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Edrington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Inn-Yard	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mackintosh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
drunk	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
or	O
spent	O
5	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sherton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Dryer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Swindun	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Rogers	O
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
foot	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hellier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
cutting	O
off	O
3	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Hair	O
from	O
the	O
Mane	O
of	O
a	O
grey	O
Mare	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Allhallows	I-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Esther	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ear-ring	O
,	O
one	O
Velvet	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Suits	O
of	O
silk	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Silk	O
and	O
Linen	O
,	O
as	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
Laces	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
80	O
l.	O
and	O
40	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	O
Thorold	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	B-pers
Thorold	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
Home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Eight	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
Entrance	O
;	O
whereupon	O
her	O
Footman	O
went	O
round	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
Back-way	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
backwards	O
all	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
fore-Door	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Madam	O
you	O
are	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
her	O
Rooms	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Cabinet	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
thrown	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
them	O
;	O
Betty	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
bound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
were	O
Men	O
in	O
Women	O
's	O
Cloths	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Servants	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
who	O
the	O
Persons	O
were	O
that	O
had	O
commited	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
'till	O
her	O
Mistress	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Laurence	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Men	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
thrown	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
took	O
off	O
her	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
her	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
for	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
having	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
large	O
Bundle	O
under	O
their	O
Riding-Hoods	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
She	O
being	O
busy	O
in	O
getting	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
Thorold	O
's	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
heard	O
Betty	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
shriek	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
rob	O
Mrs.	O
Thorold	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
her	O
Conscience	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
If	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Weldon	O
(	O
two	O
former	O
Servants	O
)	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
glad	O
of	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
consenting	O
,	O
but	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
damn	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
or	O
Opposition	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
at	O
first	O
ty	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
let	O
her	O
loose	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Thorolds	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
lodged	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Forster	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
in	O
Tash-Street	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
menacing	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Trunkmaker	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
Enquiry	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Morgan	O
having	O
bought	O
a	O
large	O
Trunk	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Porter	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Busby	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
not	O
had	O
they	O
yet	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
apprehending	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Busby	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
Person	O
;	O
that	O
meeting	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
recommend	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
an	O
honest	O
House	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
a	O
Bundle	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
:	O
The	O
Constable	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
?	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
for	O
Want	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
Spite	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
us	O
'd	O
her	O
ill.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
,	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
that	O
the	O
Stays	O
,	O
Gowns	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
were	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
having	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
those	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
Hester	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
that	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
her	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
bind	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
Gag	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
might	O
have	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Evidences	O
,	O
Loyd	O
,	O
Hart	O
,	O
and	O
Morgan	O
,	O
had	O
contriv	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
four	O
Several	O
times	O
to	O
commit	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
down	O
into	O
Wales	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
but	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Stays	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
but	O
of	O
12	O
Guineas	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
by	O
Morgan	O
.	O
The	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
At	O
receiving	O
Sentence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
plead	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
but	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
consider	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
herself	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Blue-Anchor-Alley	B-place
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
5	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Chrystal	O
Locket	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
immediately	O
crying	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
an	O
Outcry	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Several	O
People	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Locket	O
and	O
Ear-rings	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
at	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
distance	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
her	O
dropping	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
suspected	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
lurk	O
'd	O
about	O
there	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
seen	O
that	O
Day	O
viewing	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
the	O
their	O
ill	O
Design	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Man	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
to	O
observe	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
the	O
Horse	O
over	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
hearing	O
another	O
Person	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Hedge	O
putting	O
him	O
forward	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
stopping	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
quitted	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
break	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
on	O
the	O
Field-side	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
?	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
intended	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
two	O
Hours	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pinhorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallow	B-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
Call	O
'd	O
George-Alley	B-place
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
take	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
deceased	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
Entertainment	O
,	O
in	O
Oldstreet	O
,	O
returning	O
Home	O
at	O
Night	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Relation	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
expecting	O
him	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
Home	O
to	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dwelt	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
Home	O
as	O
was	O
expected	O
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
having	O
been	O
sent	O
out	O
,	O
brought	O
word	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
,	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Warrant	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Body	O
brought	O
to	O
St.	O
Magnes	O
Church	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
interr	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
Vault	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Corpse	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Strutton	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
the	O
Grave-digger	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Coffin	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
Lad	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
four	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
Pinhorn	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Discharge	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
two	O
Rings	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
Pinhorn	O
did	O
pretend	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
declin	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Rings	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
where	O
they	O
met	O
together	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Miles	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Joynes	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
for	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Rings	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Hat	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
Pinhorn	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
procur	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Strutton	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
Son	O
's	O
making	O
the	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
giving	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
end	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
George-Alley	O
,	O
did	O
hear	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
Bustle	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
;	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
Several	O
Persons	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
by	O
Cole	O
Harbour	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
and	O
enquiring	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
said	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
had	O
been	O
sodomiting	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
which	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
elderly	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wig	O
was	O
a	O
light-colour	O
'd	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Button	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
menacing	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
got	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
would	O
have	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
content	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
?	O
That	O
having	O
given	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
or	O
Rings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Brass	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Gold	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
insist	O
upon	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Throw	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
coming	O
up	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Strutton	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Strutton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
own	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
Consideration	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
justifiable	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
given	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
the	O
Receivers	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Ditcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Breast	O
and	O
Neck	O
of	O
Lamb	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ham	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elliver	I-pers
.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicated	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Mantle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Randal	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
than	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
fighting	O
with	O
one	O
Vandike	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no-body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
,	O
himself	O
and	O
Servants	O
gathering	O
Pease	O
,	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
lathed	O
and	O
plaster	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
broken	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
running	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
cross	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
advertised	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
News-Paper	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
l.	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Purse	O
with	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Papers	O
;	O
this	O
Purse	O
and	O
Note	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
happening	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
17	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
to	O
change	O
into	O
Gold	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
giving	O
10	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
for	O
17	O
l.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
17	O
l.	O
offer	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Money	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clows	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Discharge	O
of	O
the	O
Captain	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
the	O
Sirname	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Judge	O
suspecting	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
Relations	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Question	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Son	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
Sons	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
stout	O
,	O
tall	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
40	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
The	O
Uncle	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
offer	O
to	O
restore	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
l.	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Prosecute	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
seem	O
'd	O
so	O
un-paternal	O
.	O
being	O
against	O
an	O
only	O
Son	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
3	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Vassal	I-pers
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Money	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
3	O
Broad-Pieces	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Constable	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Broad-Piece	O
dropp	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Stocking	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Walkins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
House	O
being	O
a	O
notorious	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
3	O
Broad-Pieces	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
readily	O
stripp	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Gold	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
till	O
pulling	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Broad-Piece	O
dropp	O
'd	O
cut	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
?	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Because	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
when	O
they	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Woman	O
a	O
Present	O
,	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Broad-Piece	O
for	O
her	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Udney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
up	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
home	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
trying	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
with	O
her	O
Teeth	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
drinking	O
of	O
Punch	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
Home	O
a	O
Gown	O
to	O
the	O
Women	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
or	O
Prisoner	O
knocking	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
the	O
Gown	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
then	O
sitting	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mop	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
been	O
sick	O
,	O
had	O
vomited	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
broad	O
,	O
thin	O
Peace	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
out	O
a	O
Pawn	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
being	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
should	O
alter	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
making	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
provide	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
it	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
Nurse	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Broad-piece	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Jesse	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jessop	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
to	O
clean	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
stood	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Child	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
very	O
lately	O
,	O
when	O
upon	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
selling	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tail	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
dwelt	O
at	O
Ashamstead	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
lost	O
two	O
Horses	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
he	O
missing	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
an	O
old	O
blind	O
Horse	O
left	O
in	O
their	O
stead	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
Sweat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Saddle-mark	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
then	O
conjectur	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Horses	O
were	O
but	O
newly	O
stolen	O
;	O
there	O
upon	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
rid	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
2	O
Horses	O
,	O
whose	O
Marks	O
exactly	O
answer	O
'd	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
pass	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
several	O
Enquiries	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Carrier	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
at	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
rode	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
rode	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Rose-Inn	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
there	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Horse	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
sold	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Toll-Man	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
coming	O
to	O
vouch	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
but	O
the	O
Hostler	O
,	O
the	O
Buyer	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hyburn	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Voucher	O
,	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Toll-man	O
's	O
)	O
Hand	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
more	O
satisfactory	O
Vouchers	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
secur	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
owning	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hyburn	O
,	O
the	O
Buyer	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
sometimes	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
bred	O
him	O
;	O
neither	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Oath	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
Arnold	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
All-Saints	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Rolls	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
be	O
Apprentice	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
3	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
Door	O
and	O
Desk	O
had	O
been	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Plate	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Pewter	O
and	O
Brass	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
were	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
near	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
a	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
however	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
'till	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
Thief	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
searched	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
Home	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Cup	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
between	O
some	O
Joists	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greneway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
missing	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
self	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Children	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Mammy	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
'fright	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
your	O
Tankard	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Greneway	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
at	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
2	O
Tankards	O
,	O
but	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
Tankard	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
bought	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
not	O
produc	O
'd	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
2	O
Persons	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Top	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
undy	O
'd	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Convel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Patten	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pottenger	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
printed	O
Linen	O
and	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Willoughby	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Goodrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Head-Dresses	O
,	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodg	O
'd	O
and	O
boarded	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
ill	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingsberry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
and	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Wigs	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
aquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joshua	B-pers
Shermandine	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hamstead	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Geese	O
and	O
a	O
Gander	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
at	O
a	O
Sessions	O
held	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
,	O
did	O
return	O
from	O
Transportation	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
a	O
Medal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ester	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
Eagle	B-place
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Hetherington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pinzack	I-pers
,	O
Haberdasher	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
exercis	O
'd	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
a	O
Felt-maker	O
,	O
or	O
Hat-maker	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
serv	O
'd	O
7	O
Years	O
to	O
that	O
Trade	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Felt-maker	O
,	O
having	O
serv	O
'd	O
7	O
Years	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
wrought	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Defendant	O
from	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
to	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
who	O
mix	O
'd	O
and	O
weigh	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
the	O
Wool	O
;	O
gave	O
him	O
Directions	O
for	O
making	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
Sizes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Defendant	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
a	O
Freeman	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
incorporated	O
and	O
intrusted	O
with	O
many	O
Privileges	O
by	O
a	O
Charter	O
in	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Hen	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
and	O
16th	O
of	O
Hen	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Hen	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
under	O
the	O
Denomination	O
of	O
Hurrers	O
,	O
Cappers	O
,	O
and	O
Hatter	O
Merchants	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
united	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
one	O
Company	O
;	O
they	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Defendant	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
an	O
Apprenticeship	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cam	O
,	O
a	O
Haberdasher	O
of	O
Hats	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
likewise	O
had	O
married	O
a	O
Widow	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
Wife	O
to	O
2	O
Hat-makers	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
allow	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Title	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
The	O
Informant	O
's	O
Counsel	O
urg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
was	O
subsequent	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
Charter	O
;	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Liberties	O
of	O
the	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
by	O
their	O
Charters	O
,	O
were	O
restrain	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Defendant	O
guilty	O
of	O
practising	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
a	O
Felt-maker	O
for	O
one	O
Month	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Crowes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
34	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
Coronation	B-place
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
several	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Col.	O
Bell	O
,	O
Comptroller	O
of	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Postmaster-General	O
having	O
had	O
several	O
Complaints	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
concerning	O
Money	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
being	O
inclos	O
'd	O
and	O
sent	O
in	O
Letters	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
laid	O
the	O
following	O
Scheme	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
a	O
full	O
Discovery	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
He	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Sawtell	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
Cornwall	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Posthouse	O
,	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
in	O
as	O
ordinary	O
a	O
Hand	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
seal	O
'd	O
the	O
Letter	O
with	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Dickenson	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
among	O
other	O
Letters	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
stamp	O
and	O
face	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
gave	O
Dickerson	O
Orders	O
how	O
to	O
behave	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sawted	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
write	O
the	O
Letter	O
according	O
to	O
Col.	O
Bell	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Letter	O
seal	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Letter	O
then	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
writ	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dickerson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Eyes	O
were	O
never	O
off	O
the	O
Box	O
'till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Letters	O
out	O
to	O
stamp	O
and	O
face	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Office	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
that	O
Letter	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Letter	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Pocket	O
between	O
his	O
great	O
Pocket	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dickerson	O
being	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
sent	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Pipes	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Letter	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
W.	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Comptroller	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Letter	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
feeling	O
about	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
Lump	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Way	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
cut	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
Opening	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
narrow	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
doubled	O
up	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
Mr.	O
W.	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Inland	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dickerson	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Dickerson	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
Letter	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
challang	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
carrying	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Comptroller	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Little	O
Pocket	O
between	O
the	O
Pocket	O
and	O
the	O
outward	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
private	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
that	O
Morning	O
to	O
wear	O
:	O
His	O
Plea	O
being	O
incredible	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
,	O
having	O
by	O
Council	O
mov	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
praying	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
this	O
Sessions	O
be	O
either	O
Try	O
'd	O
,	O
Bail	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
Discharg	O
'd	O
;	O
his	O
Prayer	O
was	O
allow	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Attorney-General	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
giving	O
sufficient	O
Bail	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
4000	O
l.	O
viz	O
.	O
2000	O
l.	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
2000	O
l.	O
more	O
his	O
other	O
Bail	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Security	O
that	O
he	O
shall	O
appear	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Tryal	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
ensuing	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convict	O
James	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convict	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Judgement	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5.	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
26.	O
Charles	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lily	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lovey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dufty	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Jesse	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jessop	O
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greneway	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Top	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Patten	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pottenger	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Goodrick	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingsbury	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
Whipt	O
6.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shermandine	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
