TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
V.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXX	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raly	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
Bethel	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Pinkney	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Prichard	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bargeman	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Basnet	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radley	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Nurden	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warral	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Calson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Guenin	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hannel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Robert	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
Water	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Francklin	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
laying	O
Claim	O
to	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Francklin	I-pers
said	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Gown	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Francklin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
buy	O
the	O
Gown	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
her	O
to	O
bear	O
her	O
harmless	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
laid	O
claim	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rowland	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
a	O
Bushel	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Wheaten	O
Flower	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Buthel	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Peas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
Crose-Keys	O
Inn	O
in	O
Barbicane	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
a	O
Waggon	O
which	O
Inn	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
lost	O
Goods	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
when	O
that	O
Waggon	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
any	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Servants	O
to	O
watch	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-loft	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-loft	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
out	O
the	O
Dog	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
empty	O
into	O
the	O
Bean	O
loft	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
standing	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Flower	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
fill	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
Peas	O
which	O
stood	O
there	O
in	O
Sacks	O
,	O
first	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
thrown	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
likewise	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
to	O
strike	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Candle	O
lighted	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Street	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Double	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Airy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
entering	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Gilner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
about	O
Eight	O
or	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
offering	O
the	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
taking	O
Care	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
procure	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
being	O
deficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hayes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stinton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Brown	B-pers
Mare	I-pers
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
as	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stinton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Bristol	O
towards	O
London	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Miles	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Bristol	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Cirencester	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
also	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
Cirencester	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Cirencester	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
being	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
,	O
between	O
Cirencester	O
and	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
having	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
disappointed	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
Oxford	O
to	O
Loud-Water	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
lodg	O
'd	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
off	O
on	O
the	O
Right-hand	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Hayes	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Botwel	B-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Way	O
being	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
better	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
ride	O
cross	O
some	O
Lands	O
over	O
Hedges	O
and	O
Ditches	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Way	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
River	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
either	O
a	O
Fool	O
or	O
a	O
Knave	O
to	O
lead	O
him	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
visible	O
Way	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turning	O
his	O
Horse	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
large	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
violent	O
Blow	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Blood	O
flow	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
abundance	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
strangled	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
recovering	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Mares	O
Bridles	O
ty	O
'd	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
getting	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
the	O
Kindness	O
you	O
show	O
to	O
your	O
Friend	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
presently	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
Strength	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Gloves	O
were	O
all	O
over	O
bloody	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
;	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
little	O
Use	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
Detriment	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
Home	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
that	O
should	O
carry	O
him	O
Home	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
firing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
shot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
recover	O
'd	O
some	O
strength	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
but	O
saw	O
neither	O
Prisoner	O
nor	O
Mares	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
Help	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Loud-water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
talking	O
of	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
letting	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
let	O
Blood	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Lancets	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hucks	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
those	O
Lancets	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
Loud-water	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
having	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
not	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Home	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hartwel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Upholsterer	O
had	O
had	O
Dealings	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
recommend	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
recommended	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Corn-Market	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
persuade	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
towards	O
London	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
two	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
at	O
Loud-water	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
lie	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
lay	O
in	O
two	O
Beds	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sate	O
up	O
and	O
smoak	O
'd	O
a	O
Pipe	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
he	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
no	O
longer	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
alledg	O
'd	O
in	O
extenuation	O
of	O
his	O
Crime	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
that	O
indeed	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
shoot	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hand	O
shaking	O
,	O
it	O
chanc	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Words	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
sworn	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
something	O
shall	O
carry	O
you	O
home	O
presently	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
Man	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
neither	O
had	O
committed	O
,	O
not	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
commit	O
Murder	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
submitted	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Law	O
with	O
the	O
more	O
Pleasure	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
preceeding	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
90	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Satin	O
Petticoat	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
de	I-pers
Voe	I-pers
,	O
also	O
a	O
Norwich	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
de	I-pers
Voe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
1727	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
taking	O
her	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
shipwrack	O
'd	O
coming	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
lost	O
all	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
dress	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
dress	O
'd	O
Dinner	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
she	O
dress	O
'd	O
herself	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
Dishonesty	O
,	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
not	O
coming	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
some	O
Mischief	O
had	O
befallen	O
her	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
examine	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Closet	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
(	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
suppos	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
)	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Mantle-Tree	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
she	O
put	O
out	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
beforemention	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mrs	O
de	O
Voe	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
substance	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
Madam	O
de	O
Voe	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
down	O
Stairs	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
passing	O
with	O
her	O
Mistress	O
for	O
a	O
Single	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
shut	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
imagin	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
,	O
gotten	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bristol	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
married	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
Madam	O
de	O
Voe	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
late	O
in	O
preparing	O
the	O
Dinner	O
,	O
inquir	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Lady	O
din	O
'd	O
abroad	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
did	O
hasten	O
the	O
Dinner	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
went	O
thither	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
while	O
the	O
Ladies	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
One	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
saw	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
go	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
should	O
give	O
her	O
Reason	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
went	O
out	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Edwa	O
rd	O
Season	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
heard	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
inquired	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Dear	O
Neddy	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
betray	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
another	O
Woman	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
thereupon	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
which	O
Madam	O
Brooks	O
claim	O
'd	O
as	O
hers	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Ditcher	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Hounsditch	B-place
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Tibbals	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Wells	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
honest	O
Man	O
that	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
hang	O
Dalton	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Coat	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
Ditcher	O
laid	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Tibbals	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Wig	O
also	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
had	O
that	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Vine	O
(	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
)	O
in	O
Featherstone-street	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
(	O
meaning	O
a	O
Constable	O
)	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
got	O
away	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
apprehended	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
:	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Ditcher	O
had	O
his	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ditcher	O
had	O
the	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
claim	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
it	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Barbicane	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
one	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
at	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Ditcher	O
call	O
'd	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Ditcher	O
had	O
had	O
that	O
Coat	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
:	O
Wells	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidences	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
that	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
at	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
others	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
one	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ozenbrook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
from	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
rap	O
your	O
Life	O
away	O
too	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Twacher	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
vile	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
Felony	O
upon	O
you	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Lydea	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Lionel	B-pers
Chancey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Door	O
opposite	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
seeing	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
God	O
sake	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cherriton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Servants	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Spoons	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Conium	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Spoons	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
which	O
was	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Pocket	O
that	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
behind	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
that	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lydiat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reaching	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Spoons	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Brass	O
Ware	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
and	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Ballad	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Information	O
by	O
Letter	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Holton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
nor	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Irons	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
Fork	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Akerman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brookin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
,	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Blind	O
Jones	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Casks	O
and	O
18	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Rum	O
Value	O
36	O
s	O
.	O
and	O
6	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1727	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
drive	O
his	O
Dray	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Brewer	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Casks	O
and	O
Liquors	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
stealing	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
afterwards	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
blind	O
?	O
Answer	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
Colours	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
driven	O
his	O
Dray	O
all	O
over	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
bad	O
a	O
Place	O
as	O
any	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
self	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
of	O
loosing	O
a	O
Cask	O
with	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
Rum	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
answering	O
yes	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Broke	I-pers
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Casks	O
of	O
Liquor	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
Sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Wallis	O
in	O
Spittle	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Leonard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Show-Glass	O
with	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
Pen-knives	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Cutlary	O
Wares	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Conquest	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
hard	O
Ware	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gascoon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
went	O
slily	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Buckles	O
and	O
such	O
Ware	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
among	O
the	O
Dirt	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Dog	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursuing	O
him	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
a	O
Buckle	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
also	O
by	O
-	O
Taylor	O
,	O
another	O
Watchman	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
was	O
also	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
positive	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Madget	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dimity	O
Value	O
20	O
s	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Twilight	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
42	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawney	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dawney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
finding	O
her	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
finding	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Amy	B-pers
Wedgewood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
laid	O
his	O
cold	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
lie	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Mug	O
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
going	O
out	O
about	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
being	O
Neighbours	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Chickens	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
Galoon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Haberdashery	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
before	O
she	O
married	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
losing	O
of	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
abused	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
her	O
Wages	O
for	O
the	O
Spoon	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Wilmer	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
January	O
1728	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
living	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
indicted	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
beating	O
and	O
abusing	O
her	O
after	O
a	O
Barbarous	O
manner	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
Compounded	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
agreeing	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Attorney	O
and	O
himself	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
back	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
Sick	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
Releases	O
Sign	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
giving	O
her-but	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
Suing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
his	O
Charges	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
now	O
set	O
on	O
foot	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Soldering	O
Iron	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
staying	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
being	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Newham	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Foreman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
bid	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fetch	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
seeming	O
not	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
loitering	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
Philip	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
fetch	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
always	O
take	O
such	O
saucy	O
Answers	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
answer	O
was	O
good	O
enough	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
then	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
low	O
Stool	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
Foot	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
distant	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
toss	O
'd	O
under	O
Hand	O
,	O
a	O
Soldering	O
Iron	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
at	O
Work	O
with	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
no	O
other	O
Intent	O
or	O
Design	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
)	O
than	O
to	O
frighten	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Crown	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ready	O
to	O
fall	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
supported	O
by	O
something	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
)	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
have	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brookes	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
good	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
)	O
being	O
an	O
elderly	O
Man	O
,	O
sent	O
likewise	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Dobbins	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
Dr.	O
Butler	O
,	O
a	O
Physician	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
fuss	O
did	O
they	O
make	O
about	O
a	O
broken	O
Head	O
?	O
And	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
in	O
Trade	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
coming	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
possible	O
Care	O
was	O
taken	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
being	O
attended	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Surgeons	O
and	O
Physician	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
Night	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Presence	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Brother	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
good	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hinder	O
'd	O
his	O
Mistress	O
from	O
turning	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Iron	O
slipt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
with	O
good	O
Temper	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
a	O
quiet	O
inoffensive	O
Man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Substance	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
except	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
casting	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dothins	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Wound	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
possible	O
Care	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
no	O
hurt	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
Peaceable	O
inoffensive	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
passion	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
sufficiently	O
clear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
any	O
prepense	O
Malice	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
thinking	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
also	O
fully	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Broderick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
11	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Coopers	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
having	O
in	O
Charge	O
the	O
Disposal	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
a	O
School	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
Master	O
being	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
educated	O
in	O
Learning	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
commenc	O
'd	O
Batchelor	O
of	O
Arts	O
in	O
the	O
University	O
,	O
was	O
elected	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Teacher	O
,	O
or	O
Master	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
School	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
within	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
his	O
Attempts	O
upon	O
the	O
Boys	O
under	O
his	O
Care	O
,	O
by	O
sending	O
them	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
sometimes	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
another	O
,	O
making	O
them	O
take	O
down	O
their	O
Breeches	O
,	O
feeling	O
about	O
their	O
Bodies	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
such	O
Actions	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
therein	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
support	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
how	O
old	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
almost	O
11	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
knew	O
what	O
an	O
Oath	O
was	O
?	O
And	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
He	O
answering	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
lay	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
to	O
kiss	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
likewise	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
swear	O
what	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Sin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
Hell	O
fire	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
upon	O
Oath	O
.	O
Then	O
being	O
bid	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
;	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
thinks	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
move	O
some	O
Chairs	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
all	O
over	O
his	O
naked	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
down	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
strok	O
'd	O
all	O
over	O
his	O
naked	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Marble	O
cover	O
'd	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
half	O
penny	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
what	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
went	O
and	O
sate	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
put	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
before	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wonder	O
'd	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
shut	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
pull	O
down	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
Privy	O
member	O
between	O
my	O
Thighs	O
,	O
-	O
[	O
the	O
Evidence	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
]	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
other	O
Boys	O
(	O
his	O
School	O
fellows	O
)	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
like	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Rue	O
Lewis	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meer	I-pers
,	O
Eward	O
Lewis	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
Senior	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
using	O
frequently	O
to	O
examin	O
his	O
Son	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
minded	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
beaten	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Reason	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
shameful	O
thing	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
dark	O
dismal	O
Scene	O
should	O
come	O
upon	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
School	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
dep	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
?	O
And	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
expect	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
Truth	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Oath	O
?	O
Answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
Hell-Fire	O
;	O
and	O
answering	O
to	O
several	O
Enquiries	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
He	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Buttons	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
thinks	O
)	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
Rod	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
all	O
about	O
my	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
gentle	O
Stroke	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
[	O
This	O
Evidence	O
proceeded	O
and	O
very	O
fully	O
proved	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
]	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
any	O
Body	O
how	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Bedfellow	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
(	O
he	O
thinks	O
)	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
notice	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
first	O
upon	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
then	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
That	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
Grandfather	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
examining	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Blister	O
between	O
his	O
Thighs	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Toy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Grandfather	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Boy	O
very	O
uneasie	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
But	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
stir	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
a	O
very	O
active	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
naught	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
whipp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
so	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
unlucky	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
his	O
Aunt	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
himself	O
,	O
what	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
one	O
another	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
serv	O
'd	O
other	O
Boys	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
these	O
Facts	O
,	O
he	O
interrogated	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
Reason	O
he	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
Boys	O
thus	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
improve	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Studies	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
any	O
other	O
Excuse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Council	O
upon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
remark	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
indeed	O
the	O
Offence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
heinous	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
strongest	O
Proof	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
make	O
such	O
an	O
Attempt	O
without	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Caution	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
mentioned	O
by	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
)	O
given	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
nothing	O
had	O
been	O
produc	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
before	O
any	O
such	O
Inclination	O
,	O
as	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Desendant	O
being	O
chosen	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Free-School	O
of	O
the	O
Coopers	O
Company	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Vote	O
and	O
Will	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Electors	O
,	O
his	O
Resentment	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
Interest	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
setting	O
on	O
foot	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
and	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
for	O
a	O
Pious	O
and	O
Religious	O
young	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
intimately	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
ever	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
all	O
Trinity	O
College	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Ridgwell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
immodest	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
immodesty	O
acted	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Character	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
for	O
Piety	O
and	O
Regularity	O
of	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lain	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
Attempt	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
he	O
ever	O
heard	O
an	O
immodest	O
Word	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Body	O
speak	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Here	O
his	O
Council	O
remark	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
tender	O
Age	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
and	O
his	O
Character	O
being	O
justly	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
might	O
be	O
thought	O
to	O
counterpoise	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
additional	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hennoker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
Sense	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
gave	O
so	O
Satisfactory	O
an	O
Account	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
permitted	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
since	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
stroaked	O
all	O
about	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
String	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
String	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
himself	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
what	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Sprig	O
of	O
a	O
Rod	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
over	O
his	O
Knee	O
and	O
whipp	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
:	O
That	O
another	O
time	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Coat	O
gave	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
School	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
inveigh	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Parents	O
of	O
the	O
Boys	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
Evidences	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Persons	O
of	O
so	O
vile	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
good	O
Word	O
was	O
a	O
Scandal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
malicious	O
,	O
being	O
carried	O
on	O
by	O
his	O
Enemies	O
who	O
had	O
voted	O
for	O
Mr	O
.	O
Veer	O
,	O
the	O
present	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
School	O
,	O
now	O
in	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
Charge	O
laid	O
upon	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
without	O
any	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Ham	O
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Ground	O
of	O
the	O
Clamour	O
rais	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answered	O
nothing	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ham	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
fit	O
a	O
Man	O
should	O
loose	O
his	O
Reputation	O
for	O
nothing	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
would	O
tear	O
the	O
House	O
down	O
about	O
our	O
Ears	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
Evidences	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
name	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Child	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
handsome	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Veer	I-pers
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Council	O
,	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Mr.	O
-	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
threatned	O
to	O
send	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
to	O
Newgate	O
that	O
should	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
Defendant	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Bambrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulcher	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
overtaken	O
in	O
Liquor	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pyed	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	O
Billers	O
,	O
who	O
discharg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
where	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Buckles	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Brother	O
of	O
Dalton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
beaten	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
his	O
Rings	O
were	O
?	O
Said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
his	O
Finger	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
she	O
not	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
sworn	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
long	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
together	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
till	O
5	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepphard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bushby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Gunsmith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
Plain	O
against	O
Bushby	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
deficient	O
as	O
to	O
Gunsmith	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pressing	O
Irons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Flectwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
Counties	O
of	O
Kent	O
and	O
Surrey	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
without	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Milkson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wagg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Binstead	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cabel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cabel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Coals	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
at	O
the	O
Wharf	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
they	O
making	O
it	O
their	O
Business	O
to	O
loiter	O
about	O
the	O
Shoar	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
,	O
of	O
picking	O
up	O
Coals	O
,	O
that	O
are	O
scatter	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
did	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
A	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessory	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
Buying	O
the	O
said	O
Coals	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
producing	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
fair	O
and	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian-Frock	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
Value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Pawn	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainy	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brabant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
brass	O
Clock	O
Weights	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blossom	I-pers
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shirt	O
was	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
Pole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
it	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
presending	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
half	O
hundred	O
Iron	O
Weights	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
four	O
half	O
hundred	O
Weights	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Night-Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
King's-Yards	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Weights	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
these	O
Weights	O
?	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
broad	O
R	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bringing	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
had	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
brought	O
sufficient	O
Witness	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
demand	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Weights	O
,	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Weights	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Sinclar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
115	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish-Linen	O
Value	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dover	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
,	O
that	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linen	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Quaker	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
Swear	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
therefore	O
a	O
deficiency	O
in	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeweller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Belladine	O
Silk	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
a	O
Skein	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
seen	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
suddled	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Silk	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultrey	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Governour	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
1400	O
and	O
odd	O
Pounds	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Banks	O
,	O
a	O
Teller	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Effects	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
a	O
1000	O
Pound	O
in	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Clay	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Stick	O
,	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Heap	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drawing	O
away	O
the	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
separated	O
the	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Heap	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Inches	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Baylis	O
,	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
that	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
in	O
taking	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
1400	O
l.	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
a	O
1000	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
telling	O
it	O
over	O
again	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
there	O
wanted	O
just	O
one	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
under	O
great	O
Necessity	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Bill	O
discounted	O
,	O
or	O
borrow	O
Money	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
much	O
Distraction	O
and	O
Confusion	O
,	O
scarce	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gutridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
Value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
any	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
had	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
their	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
2	O
s.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
that	O
of	O
Sheffield	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
three	O
Women	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
t	O
ook	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
Home	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
refus	O
,	O
d	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
presently	O
coming	O
with	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
fetch	O
him	O
Change	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
Sign	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
also	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
up	O
all	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
ran	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
draw	O
it	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Thing	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
cost	O
him	O
40	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
Drinking	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
among	O
her	O
own	O
Friends	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bellenger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Hounsditch	B-place
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
clapt	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
immediately	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
14	O
s.	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Bulk	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Rod	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
whipt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Rails	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Plea	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
deliver	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
above	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
28	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Master	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
withdraw	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
depart	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
defraud	O
her	O
said	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
convert	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Trust	O
and	O
Confidence	O
repos	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
John	B-pers
Bushby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
usual	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
buy	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Cheese	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Garret	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Flander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
Second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Proof	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Cheney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
Second	O
Husband	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dudart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leornard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Griel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
1728	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Closet	O
and	O
steal	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
one	O
Cap	O
that	O
was	O
hers	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Pinners	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
at	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
dwelt	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Cap	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
being	O
more	O
particularly	O
interrogated	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Lace	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Lace	O
for	O
the	O
Cap	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wore	O
the	O
Cap	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
(	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
Sister	O
)	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
besides	O
,	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
Wages	O
,	O
she	O
serving	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
very	O
small	O
Wages	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Relation	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Rich	O
,	O
and	O
promising	O
to	O
provide	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
Fortune	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Ondart	I-pers
,	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Relation	O
,	O
and	O
Rich	O
,	O
and	O
promising	O
to	O
provide	O
well	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
permit	O
his	O
Daughter	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
griping	O
miserly	O
Wretch	O
,	O
and	O
using	O
her	O
not	O
handsomly	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
lent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
20	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
demanding	O
his	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Child	O
,	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Cap	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
set	O
on	O
foot	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
praying	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
3.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bambreyd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Barbara	B-pers
Newall	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
22	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
alias	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Eaton	O
,	O
Rowland	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeweller	I-pers
,	O
N	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Milkson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wagg	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Binstead	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
Lydia	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Young	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Busbby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bostwick	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bostock	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roch	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
2.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Broderick	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
once	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
nearest	O
convenient	O
Place	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
;	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Nobles	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
.	O
LA	O
Or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
hard	O
improved	O
.	O
Being	O
and	O
Easy	O
Mec	O
of	O
Shorthand	O
Completed	O
her	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
Practice	O
and	O
Improvement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Art	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Observation	O
of	O
Methods	O
and	O
Study	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Additions	O
of	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
he	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
amended	O
.	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Miraculous	O
Conversion	O
from	O
Popy	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Glory	O
of	O
Divine	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Protection	O
of	O
Divine	O
Providence	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
God	O
Manifested	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Divine	O
Poems	O
(	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Paraphrase	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Ten	O
Comments	O
.	O
In	O
Twelve	O
Parts	O
:	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Twelve	O
Copper-Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
George	B-pers
Wither	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Heaven	O
begun	O
here	O
on	O
Earth	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Help	O
to	O
young	O
Persons	O
,	O
under	O
their	O
first	O
Convictions	O
,	O
and	O
Closure	O
with	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Christ	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
help	O
to	O
Backsliders	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Hidings	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Face	O
for	O
Decays	O
in	O
Spirituals	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
help	O
to	O
strong	O
Christians	O
,	O
who	O
can	O
,	O
through	O
Grace	O
,	O
read	O
their	O
Evidences	O
for	O
Heaven	O
.	O
Contained	O
in	O
Three	O
Dialogues	O
between	O
a	O
Minister	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
private	O
Christian	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
in	O
Calf	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
.	O
The	O
Word	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Exercising	O
the	O
Musket	O
and	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carbine	O
,	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
performed	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
B.	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Onania	O
examined	O
and	O
detected	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
Error	O
,	O
Impertinence	O
,	O
and	O
Contradiction	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Onania	O
,	O
discovered	O
and	O
exposed	O
.	O
Wherein	O
also	O
is	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Differences	O
and	O
sundry	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Self-Politrion	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
.	O
By	O
Philo-Castiratis	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
Singing	O
Master	O
's	O
Guide	O
to	O
his	O
Scholars	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Psalms	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Translations	O
;	O
the	O
Old	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
By	O
several	O
Hands	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sternhold	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
Barton	O
,	O
Patrick	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
.	O
Milbourne	O
and	O
Sandys	O
.	O
Contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
Common	O
Use	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Tunes	O
in	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ewelm	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Christian	O
's	O
hidden	O
Life	O
.	O
A	O
Funeral	O
Sermon	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Rev	O
.	O
and	O
Learned	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Netbitt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
departed	O
this	O
Life	O
October	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
67th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
Preached	O
October	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Hunion	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Whip	O
for	O
the	O
Quack	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
M	O
-	O
N	O
's	O
Supplement	O
to	O
his	O
Onania	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
full	O
Answer	O
and	O
Contutation	O
of	O
his	O
boasted-of	O
,	O
and	O
long-promised	O
curious	O
Piece	O
from	O
Sckmeider	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
Arguments	O
for	O
the	O
Seed	O
's	O
return	O
into	O
the	O
Blood	O
after	O
its	O
Secretion	O
.	O
By	O
Matthew	B-pers
Rothos	I-pers
,	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
A	O
further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clarks	O
:	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
religiously	O
and	O
devoutly	O
desposed	O
to	O
make	O
Use	O
of	O
these	O
Instructions	O
.	O
Being	O
continued	O
for	O
common	O
Use	O
,	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
Ewlem	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
,	O
B	B-pers
,	I-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Children	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Alphabets	O
and	O
Syllables	O
,	O
with	O
short	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
of	O
dividing	O
Words	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Rules	O
for	O
true	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
Writing	O
of	O
English	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Two	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
useful	O
Words	O
,	O
whose	O
Spelling	O
or	O
Sense	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Also	O
Christian	O
ames	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
fifth	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
Price	O
9	O
d.	O
A	O
short	O
and	O
practical	O
Discourse	O
upon	O
the	O
Holy	O
Fast	O
of	O
Lent	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marshall	B-pers
,	I-pers
L.	I-pers
L.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Greatness	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Unspeakableness	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
thereof	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
the	O
Losing	O
it	O
.	O
First	O
preached	O
in	O
Pinners-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
enlarged	O
,	O
and	O
published	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2d	O
.	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Shop	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
to	O
all	O
Stationers	O
and	O
School-masters	O
in	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
,	O
Pieces	O
for	O
Christmas	O
,	O
Easter	O
and	O
Whitsunside	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
wholesale	O
and	O
retale	O
,	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
on	O
Copper-plates	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
II	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Jerusalem	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Temple	O
of	O
Solomon	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Geometry	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Haman	O
hanged	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Hunting-Piece	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Grammar	O
and	O
Writing-School	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Christ	O
's	O
Burial	O
.	O
10	O
The	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Show	O
.	O
11	O
Moses	O
in	O
the	O
Ark	O
of	O
Bull-rushes	O
.	O
12	O
History	O
of	O
Tobit	O
.	O
13	O
Christ	O
's	O
Ascension	O
.	O
14	O
The	O
seven	O
Sciences	O
.	O
15	O
Dorastis	O
and	O
Fawnia	O
.	O
16	O
History	O
of	O
Judith	O
and	O
Holosernis	O
.	O
17	O
The	O
four	O
Evangelists	O
.	O
18	O
Stool-Bal	O
19	O
Joseph	O
flying	O
into	O
Egypt	O
.	O
20	O
Crucifixtion	O
;	O
And	O
many	O
others	O
in	O
whole	O
Sheets	O
and	O
half	O
Sheets	O
:	O
Likewise	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
Elegiac	O
Poem	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Most	O
Sacred	O
Majesty	O
K.	O
George	O
,	O
engraven	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Also	O
Gospel	O
Mystery	O
Emblematically	O
illustrated	O
,	O
engraven	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Copper-plate	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Short	O
Time	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
:	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George-Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
near	O
Hick's-Hall	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
Excellent	O
for	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Lite	O
,	O
called	O
Daffy	O
's	O
Elixir	O
,	O
truly	O
prepared	O
,	O
so	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
in	O
the	O
greatest	O
Exigencies	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
Spiritual	O
Songs	O
for	O
Children	O
,	O
or	O
Poems	O
on	O
several	O
Subjects	O
and	O
Occasions	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
:	O
London	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
Six	O
pence	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
Price	O
Six	O
pence	O
,	O
Light	O
in	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Impartial	O
Chuchman	O
;	O
Containing	O
the	O
Celebrated	O
Discourses	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Croxall	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Trapp	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
and	O
Court	O
of	O
Aldermen	O
.	O
Wherein	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
just	O
Praise	O
of	O
their	O
Merits	O
,	O
Respect	O
to	O
their	O
Characters	O
,	O
and	O
Deference	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
:	O
their	O
Matter	O
,	O
Method	O
,	O
Explanations	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
Deductions	O
from	O
Scripture	O
are	O
observ	O
'd	O
especially	O
as	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Trapp	O
's	O
Notion	O
of	O
visiting	O
the	O
Sins	O
of	O
the	O
Fathers	O
on	O
the	O
Children	O
.	O
With	O
Readings	O
in	O
the	O
Hebrew	O
,	O
Chaldoe	O
,	O
Arabick	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
Vulgate	O
,	O
noted	O
:	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
what	O
is	O
most	O
remarkable	O
on	O
this	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Reflection	O
on	O
a	O
Principle	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Sarum	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dispute	O
of	O
Milton	O
and	O
Salmasins	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Milbourn	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bradbury	O
:	O
With	O
a	O
Rule	O
to	O
judge	O
and	O
apply	O
all	O
Sermons	O
on	O
that	O
deplorable	O
Occasion	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Henley	B-pers
,	I-pers
M.	I-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
Founder	O
of	O
the	O
Oratory	O
.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
(	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Hon	O
