TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Year	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXX	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Purnel	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Maybue	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Buxton	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Delafee	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burket	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gawthorp	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Boulden	I-pers
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
York	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Lawn	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
and	O
Company	B-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
buying	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wilson	B-pers
alias	O
Allison	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
Trust	O
with	O
the	O
House	O
while	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
were	O
absent	O
at	O
their	O
Country	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Direction	O
found	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
contrary	O
not	O
being	O
made	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
95	O
Pound	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
German	I-pers
and	O
Company	B-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cotton	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Barnet	I-place
's	I-place
Fink	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Girl	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	O
Brooks	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jugus	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Snuff	O
,	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
1	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
10	O
Pound	O
of	O
Starch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lying	O
asleep	O
on	O
a	O
Laystall	O
in	O
Upper	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lying	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Paper	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
upon	O
Shaw	O
and	O
Jugus	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
acquitted	O
James	O
Ford	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joanna	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
for	O
Coining	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
I.	O
and	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
for	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
did	O
return	O
into	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Dominions	O
in	O
England	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Term	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
defective	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
his	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
pawned	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
Pawn	O
by	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
met	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
producing	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Bridger	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Blakeway	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blakesly	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Artillery	I-place
Ground	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Lithon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Stocks-Market	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
his	O
Garter	O
being	O
loose	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
Thomas-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
fatigued	O
by	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
for	O
three	O
Nights	O
,	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
awake	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Box	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
turning	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
both	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
catching	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Hat	O
under	O
a	O
Cart	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Broomhall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Copington	I-pers
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
setting	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
Copington	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
fearing	O
she	O
was	O
calling	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Bullies	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
Murther	O
him	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
35	O
s.	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
in	O
Gaming	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
a	O
Whoring	O
and	O
Thieving	O
all	O
her	O
Days	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rose	B-pers
Ridgway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Piner	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Hazey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bucknel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
Hazey	I-pers
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
while	O
Anne	B-pers
Piner	I-pers
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
,	O
were	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Luer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Owen	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Charwoman	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Black-Friars	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
Watson	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Joyce	O
,	O
Watson	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Joyce	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Wastecoat	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Oyster-Boat	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Linen	O
was	O
lost	O
wet	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laying	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Butcher's-Stall	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-Market	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Little-Britain	B-place
,	O
had	O
laid	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Sash	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
thrown	O
the	O
Hat	O
away	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tar-pawling	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Butlin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Tar-pawling	O
from	O
his	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage-Dock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mud	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	B-pers
Honourable	I-pers
William	I-pers
,	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stables	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Nicholson	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach	O
Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Earl	O
of	O
Coventry	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
likewise	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
Quarter	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Keilly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Night-Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Morgan	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
,	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
and	O
wickedly	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
Nature	O
,	O
did	O
Bugger	O
the	O
said	O
Paul	O
Oliver	O
.	O
Paul	O
Oliver	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
a	O
Gilder	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
almost	O
stifled	O
,	O
his	O
Breath	O
being	O
almost	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
strove	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
kept	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
though	O
there	O
were	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
far	O
off	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hurt	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
Pr	O
-	O
y	O
M	O
-	O
r	O
into	O
his	O
Fundament	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Wet	O
and	O
Nastiness	O
which	O
he	O
wip	O
'd	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
tore	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
his	O
Needs	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
before	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
offers	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Nights	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
his	O
Master	O
us	O
'd	O
him	O
otherwise	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
him	O
severely	O
in	O
any	O
Thing	O
before	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
When	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
this	O
Usage	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Complaint	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
Oliver	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
Paul	O
Oliver	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
complained	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Blaney	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Justice	O
Blaney	O
.	O
Jean	B-pers
Barbat	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
Lad	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Fundament	O
quite	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
penetrated	O
above	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
lacerated	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
a	O
Finger	O
and	O
Thumb	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Fundament	O
was	O
Black	O
all	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
like	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Hen	O
after	O
laying	O
an	O
Egg	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
call	O
'd	O
any	O
one	O
Witness	O
to	O
that	O
nor	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
substantially	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Head	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
sen.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
as	O
a	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Maid	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Bed	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Stables	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
through	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
examining	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Rawlins	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
young	O
Master	O
home	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bevins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
5	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
any	O
squeaks	O
after	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Secret	O
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
intrust	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Robbed	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
forg	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Hand	O
for	O
ten	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Wig	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Rawlins	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
him	O
Orders	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
Air	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
sitting	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
return	O
;	O
but	O
falling	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
two	O
idle	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gilburn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
fifty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Paudesoy	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Watford	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
near	O
Paddington	B-place
at	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
some	O
Town	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Boh	O
!	O
Stand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bidding	O
the	O
other	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
dismount	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
rifled	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pence	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
:	O
He	O
bid	O
the	O
other	O
also	O
cut	O
the	O
Bags	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
several	O
Questions	O
;	O
why	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
little	O
Money	O
?	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
Name	O
and	O
Trade	O
?	O
Where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
having	O
taken	O
his	O
Bags	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
off	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
detain	O
'd	O
him	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flourish	O
'd	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
mount	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
rode	O
to	O
Paddington	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
Assistance	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
afterwards	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Paddington	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Highway-Man	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
at	O
Vaux-Hall	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Jail	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
expected	O
in	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Impeachment	O
of	O
Wilson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Hang	O
'd	O
last	O
Kingston	O
Assizes	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
felonious	O
slaying	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
White	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
King	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forster	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
at	O
Skettles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
having	O
won	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
play	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Mr.	O
Fen	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
carry	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
play	O
according	O
to	O
Contract	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
having	O
each	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
Seconds	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Principals	O
having	O
fought	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
very	O
eager	O
to	O
fight	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
several	O
Present	O
did	O
all	O
they	O
could	O
to	O
dissuade	O
him	O
from	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
did	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Forster	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
threw	O
him	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
resolute	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stripp	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Skins	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
fight	O
very	O
briskly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
threw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rising	O
kick	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
roguish	O
Action	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
engag	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
first	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
then	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
spoke	O
more	O
.	O
These	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
blooded	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sparrow	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
did	O
Bleed	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
not	O
to	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Swelling	O
under	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Ear	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Compression	O
of	O
the	O
jugular	O
Veins	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
the	O
Blood	O
to	O
flow	O
too	O
hastily	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
much	O
after	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
in	O
an	O
Apoplexy	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
se	O
Defendendo	O
,	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
suffocated	O
and	O
strangled	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
felonious	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Female	O
Infant	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
Aunt	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Fellow-Servant	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
Notice	O
she	O
was	O
uneasy	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
lay	O
till	O
the	O
usual	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
ail	O
'd	O
her	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Looseness	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
backwards	O
and	O
under-ground	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
possibly	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
heard	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
seeming	O
very	O
Ill	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Vault	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
appeared	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
?	O
But	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
possible	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
surprized	O
as	O
a	O
Birth	O
might	O
happen	O
after	O
that	O
manner	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
likewise	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
Whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
found	O
one	O
Child	O
's	O
Cap	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
Things	O
to	O
make	O
sit	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Sherehog	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
507	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
French	O
and	O
Spanish	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chancey	I-pers
,	O
sen.	O
and	O
jun	O
.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
having	O
Advice	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Blossom's-Inn	O
in	O
Laurence-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
himself	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
receiving	O
it	O
.	O
Chancey	O
Townsend	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
bring	O
the	O
Money	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
counted	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Silver	O
from	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Compting	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
after	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Harwich	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Harwich	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
480	O
Pistoles	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Ulysses	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Ulysses	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fossey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
lodging	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
One	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
also	O
in	O
Company	O
Mr.	O
Fitz-Gibbons	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Macartney	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lister	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Upton	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
between	O
sleeping	O
and	O
waking	O
,	O
did	O
hear	O
very	O
high	O
Words	O
pass	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
,	O
except	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Lye	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
who	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Upton	O
call	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
awake	O
)	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Macartney	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Murphey	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Upton	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanger	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
accidentally	O
in	O
Chiswick-Fields	O
,	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
hastily	O
before	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Night-Gown	O
loose	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Lynch	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
his	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
push	O
'd	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
retreated	O
several	O
Yards	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushing	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fitz-Gibbons	O
interpos	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dropp	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
his	O
Coat	O
being	O
off	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vickars	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Chiswick-Fields	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Lynch	O
walking	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
naked	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pushing	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
violently	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
two	O
Minutes	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fitz-Gibbons	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
down	O
their	O
Swords	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
along	O
Side	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
jumping	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
he	O
surrendered	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
bloody	O
about	O
two	O
Inches	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
no	O
ways	O
avoid	O
doing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
urg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
first	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
began	O
last	O
October	O
,	O
that	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Chiswick	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
that	O
Morning	O
that	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
walking	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Garden	O
reading	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
observe	O
some	O
Coldness	O
in	O
the	O
Behaviour	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
apply	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
themselves	O
to	O
satisfy	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Lye	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
such	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Coward	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
dar	O
'd	O
resent	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
Cane	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
publick	O
Coffee-House	O
he	O
should	O
meet	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Kilmurry	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
inoffensive	O
Person	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Polson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
Bridle	O
,	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Andrews	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Canewood-Lane	B-place
,	O
between	O
Highgate	B-place
and	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
s.	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
dismount	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
mounted	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
towards	O
Highgate	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
being	O
by	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
near	O
Cambray	O
House	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
dismount	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
just	O
before	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
Four	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
near	O
Cambray	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
some	O
Drovers	O
,	O
who	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dismounted	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
his	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
-	O
Tibbons	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
abuse	O
me	O
,	O
keep	O
off	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clarin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
crying	O
out	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
quitted	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
should	O
offer	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
got	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Parrot	O
Fenton	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
Hang	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
should	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
him	O
his	O
Horse	O
?	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Not	O
willingly	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
borrow	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
Pistol	O
in	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Saws	O
,	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
two	O
Hammers	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
the	O
Tools	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Work-shop	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martin	B-pers
Wander	I-pers
Eyken	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shed	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lucy	B-pers
Bolder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Largin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
her	O
Company	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Stables	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
1	O
or	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
s	O
it	O
down	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
falling	O
asleep	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
opend	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
Lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
awake	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Golstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Irons	O
belonging	O
to	O
Ploughs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Tankeard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hallet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Bruff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
London	O
by	O
Anne	O
Bruff	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
Access	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
pretending	O
to	O
Court	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Barne	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
le	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sumart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Aliff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Aliff	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Mantua-Maker	O
,	O
she	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
Work	O
as	O
a	O
Journey-woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Strong	B-pers
Faith	I-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stratford	B-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Tug-pins	O
and	O
other	O
Irons	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vanlute	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Guys	I-pers
and	O
Rowland	B-pers
Bouchet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
unwrought	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Pons	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Pons	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
Piece	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guys	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
Errands	O
;	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Examination	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bouchet	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Plate	O
of	O
Bouchet	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
4	O
s.	O
Several	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
did	O
at	O
his	O
first	O
Discovery	O
six	O
the	O
receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bouchet	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
persist	O
in	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
Weeks	O
;	O
but	O
prevaricating	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
wanting	O
Proof	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
upon	O
Bouchet	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Curtains	O
and	O
a	O
Coverlid	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Singdel	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
194	O
Silk	O
Garters	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Box	O
containing	O
the	O
Goods	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
reach	O
his	O
Hand	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
got	O
clear	O
off	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cornet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cornish	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Phalix	B-pers
Dixen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Backwards	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
Drawer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
slinging	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
Money	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Mob	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bundy	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Harvest	O
People	O
,	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Barn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
having	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
as	O
Partners	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
were	O
disputing	O
about	O
parting	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
Hands	O
down	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
their	O
Coats	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Bosoms	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
their	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
searching	O
for	O
it	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Vestry	O
Clerk	O
of	O
Kensington	O
being	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
Whipping-Post	O
for	O
Pilsering	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Kendrick	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Scour	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
his	O
Shop-Window	O
in	O
Ratcliffe	B-place
;	O
that	O
about	O
three	O
Hours	O
after	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
lye	O
at	O
a	O
Calender	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
Calender	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Calender	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
bringing	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pomfrey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Delascure	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Isaac	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Pearce	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Providence	O
Field	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapt	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
off	O
of	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Wrist	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Drayman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
him	O
about	O
Old-Street	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
instead	O
of	O
flying	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
Dray	O
publickly	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Customers	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
intirely	O
Innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
absconded	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
those	O
Places	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
publickly	O
enough	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
upon	O
doing	O
this	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
sworn	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Last	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
April	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
getting	O
140	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Buckle-Street	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
that	O
Evening	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Burdet	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
were	O
both	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
before	O
Eleven	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
at	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
,	O
being	O
spoke	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Shirt	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Saturday	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cat	O
his	O
Supper	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
weary	O
with	O
his	O
Day	O
's	O
Work	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Shirt	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
.	O
-	O
Carricomb	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Robbed	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
Robbed	O
him	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
Care	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
or	O
be	O
it	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Man	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wicked	O
and	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
set	O
on	O
Foot	O
merely	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
140	O
l.	O
order	O
'd	O
Isaac	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
;	O
and	O
granted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beningfield	I-pers
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mac-Raby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
300	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ferret	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
Buying	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Ferrets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
10	O
Pieces	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eaves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
about	O
last	O
Easter	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Oats	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
assist	O
them	O
in	O
selling	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wyburn	O
,	O
and	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Morris	O
gave	O
the	O
Receipt	O
as	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Old-Blind	O
Woman	O
's	O
Barge	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Barge	O
lay	O
off	O
from	O
Bear-Key	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Oats	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
measur	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
eight	O
Quarters	O
of	O
the	O
Quantity	O
there	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Perkins	O
drew	O
the	O
Hatches	O
of	O
the	O
Lighter	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Oats	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eaves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Corn	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
at	O
Bear-Key	B-place
,	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fielder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
their	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Fielder	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
stinking	O
Corn	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Dowby	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Turbey	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Peas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eaves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Perkins	O
and	O
himself	O
fill	O
'd	O
the	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
Turbey	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wyburn	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
their	O
Share	O
;	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
also	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Kidd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnorth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glynn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
carried	O
her	O
about	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
from	O
Place	O
to	O
Place	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
turning	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
ease	O
her	O
in	O
carrying	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
snatched	O
the	O
Cloth	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
quite	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anne	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
selling	O
Oysters	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
paying	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Oysters	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
To	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Gown	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saying	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
wont	O
part	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
Anger	O
,	O
and	O
hal	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
tore	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Emps	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulling	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
threatned	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
nigh	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pull	O
his	O
Guts	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
other	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
since	O
the	O
Hanging	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Nowland	O
,	O
she	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Emps	I-pers
,	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
Foot	O
at	O
his	O
Instigation	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
not	O
interrupt	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
Prosecuted	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Bond	O
not	O
to	O
molest	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
ancient	O
,	O
could	O
give	O
the	O
Jury	O
so	O
little	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stratford	B-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Oxen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Oxen	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Notice	O
sent	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Southby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Oxen	O
at	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Right	B-pers
Hon	I-pers
.	I-pers
William	I-pers
,	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Coventry	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rusher	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hayes	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Athoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
21	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Cotton	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Fenton	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Delenny	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hindon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Ginger	O
Bread	O
Moulds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dowdswell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Dollar	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-Lane	I-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
asking	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
good	O
Drink	O
;	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Drink	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
Drams	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awak	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mcconnell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Christening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Child	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Heywood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
lent	O
her	O
for	O
Service	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
in	O
her	O
Lying-in	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvas	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
Duck	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
King	B-pers
George	I-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carmuck	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Deal	O
Castle	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
is	O
Boatswain	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
put	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvas	O
into	O
the	O
Scuttle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
finding	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Ship	O
if	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Sheet	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Duck	O
hanging	O
in	O
her	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
,	O
malicious	O
Woman	O
,	O
whose	O
common	O
Usage	O
was	O
to	O
threaten	O
those	O
whom	O
she	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
to	O
swear	O
Felony	O
or	O
Treason	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Quail	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
rather	O
in	O
a	O
drunken	O
Frolick	O
,	O
than	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
Cups	O
proceeded	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
offer	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
Drunk	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harvey	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Macheing	B-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
last	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Windmill-Street	B-place
,	O
did	O
hear	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Willis	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Informers	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
her	O
Sister	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Michael	O
Willisand	O
Thomas	O
Willis	O
,	O
who	O
now	O
says	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
John	O
;	O
that	O
Michael	O
Willis	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
Michael	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
the	O
Skin	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
the	O
Stone	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Ring	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
dry	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
John	O
Willis	O
,	O
in	O
Duke's-Court	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
an	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Justice	O
Burk	O
would	O
believe	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Macheig	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
last	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Show	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Fight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Philips	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
murther	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Windmill-Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
leaning	O
,	O
or	O
kneeling	O
on	O
Mrs.	O
Philips	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Gutter	O
in	O
a	O
muddy	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Blows	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ireton	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Rings	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Finger	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Devins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ireton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
about	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Philips	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
your	O
Sister	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
take	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Finger	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stone	O
was	O
bit	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Ring	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Stone	O
in	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
said	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
Sister	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Channel	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Philips	O
had	O
shifted	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
they	O
overtook	O
John	O
Willis	O
in	O
Duke's-Court	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
cross	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
28th	O
or	O
29th	O
Day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Moonlight	O
Night	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Eaton	B-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
last	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
thought	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Show	O
,	O
supp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
with	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
Willis	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
Sister	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
in	O
Windmill-Street	O
,	O
John	O
Willis	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
forcibly	O
took	O
her	O
Rings	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
her	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
leaving	O
her	O
Sister	O
for	O
Dead	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
the	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
Robbing	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bourk	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
Coach	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Michael	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
stop	O
the	O
Robbers	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Robbed	O
of	O
my	O
Rings	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
George	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
in	O
Windmill-street	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Robbed	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
us	O
'd	O
after	O
this	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
struck	O
down	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
go	O
to	O
her	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
having	O
one	O
Ring	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
holding	O
it	O
on	O
with	O
his	O
Fingers	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Ring	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
Rob	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
Rings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
Willis	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Justice	O
Burk	O
will	O
take	O
Bail	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
wont	O
take	O
your	O
Oath	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Archdeacon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
following	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
Windmill-Street	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Women	O
the	O
Informers	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
that	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scuffle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Finger	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
great	O
Complaints	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Philips	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
Eaton	O
keeping	O
disorderly	O
Houses	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
continual	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
Robbed	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
their	O
Houses	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
taking	O
up	O
Isabel	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
taken	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
Clubs	O
,	O
who	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
Rings	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
set	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
on	O
Foot	O
so	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
molested	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
disorderly	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
frequently	O
threatened	O
to	O
be	O
Reveng	O
'd	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
that	O
Robbery	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
Robbery	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
Hang	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
Evidence	O
had	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clough	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
frequent	O
Disorders	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
Murther	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
at	O
Nights	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Body	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
taken	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
by	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Philips	O
came	O
with	O
several	O
Men	O
with	O
Mop-Staves	O
and	O
Broom-Sticks	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
a	O
Meat-Fork	O
to	O
stick	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
her	O
Sister	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Engagement	O
and	O
Fighting	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Willis	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
one	O
Eye	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
there	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Philips	O
and	O
her	O
Company	O
took	O
one	O
Woman	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
Philips	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
throwing	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
taking	O
her	O
Rings	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Body	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Warrant	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
taken	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
Mob	O
with	O
Staves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fork	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
swearing	O
violently	O
she	O
would	O
kill	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
stabbed	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Michael	O
Willis	O
was	O
beat	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
Michael	O
Willis	O
's	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
holding	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulling	O
with	O
Violence	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
John	O
Willis	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
losing	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
assisting	O
Mr	O
.	O
Body	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
in	O
apprehending	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Men	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
cursing	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
using	O
many	O
wicked	O
Expressions	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
stab	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
shrunk	O
her	O
self	O
down	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
to	O
skreen	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
the	O
Blows	O
while	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
laying	O
on	O
with	O
their	O
Sticks	O
upon	O
Michael	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
;	O
that	O
Sullivan	O
got	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
