TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXX	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Garton	I-pers
.	O
David	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stackhouse	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Grosbury	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Petley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Backwith	I-pers
.	O
Hammond	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coggin	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Tasman	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brearcliff	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
the	O
Fowls	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Shed	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
one	O
Burnham	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Francis	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
clasp	O
'd	O
Knife	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Blue	O
Coat	O
Boys	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Walter	B-pers
James	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	O
Molineux	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
take	O
this	O
Man	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
being	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Sugar-Loaf	B-place
,	O
and	O
forced	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
Knife	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
holding	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
afterwards	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
by	O
James	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
Molineux	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
Day	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
have	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
so	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Plea	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sheppard	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Plane	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Grandmother	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Grandmother	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
in	O
Pledge	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
pretence	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Baggerly	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
at	O
times	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
pawned	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
others	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Frankwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
plead	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bush	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Malin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
twenty-nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
Cheeks	O
,	O
Bars	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Worster	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robinson	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Johnson	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Cremer	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Five	B-place
Bells	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
missing	O
Things	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
watched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
Candles	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Peeling	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Peeling	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
likewise	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
miss	O
'd	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
Room	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Cremer	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
Fact	O
likewise	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Faithful	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
Vanderhurst	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
him	O
.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Jane	B-pers
Brereton	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powduch	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
31	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
31	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Beef	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
stolen	O
and	O
carried	O
Home	O
the	O
Beef	O
came	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
also	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
a	O
full	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elderkin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Halters	O
having	O
been	O
unty	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
outward	O
Gate	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
was	O
hasp	O
'd	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chain	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
's	O
Hay-loff	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Stepney	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
fetcht	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
rid	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
turn	O
sometimes	O
to	O
the	O
Right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Moor-gate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Watchman	O
examining	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
carry	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Lake	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Devereux	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Gate-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
Watch	O
at	O
Moor-gate	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
saw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Howard	O
with	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
so	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gourney	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ducket	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
No-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
thro	O
'	O
Peter's-Alley	B-place
at	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
being	O
come	O
near	O
the	O
Turning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
one	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
which	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
put	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
other	O
Hand	O
at	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
draw	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
into	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
calling	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watchman	O
apprehended	O
her	O
near	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sight	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
while	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
on	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
indeed	O
searched	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
being	O
none	O
but	O
Men	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
bid	O
her	O
make	O
haste	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stopping	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
searched	O
3	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
private	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
tumbled	O
all	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
his	O
Watch	O
?	O
Answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
No-body	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
him	O
in	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Peter's-Alley	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Constable	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
?	O
Answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
indeed	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
indeed	O
some	O
Dirt	O
upon	O
his	O
Coat	O
-	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
indeed	O
his	O
Foot	O
had	O
slipt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Fall	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leather	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leather	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Duke's-Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Vanderhouse	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Fowls	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
following	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fowls	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelberghs	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
dozen	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
2	O
dozen	O
of	O
Penknives	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Cutlery	O
Ware	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
Stall	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
,	O
the	O
Stationer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
green	O
Rug	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
Buildings	O
,	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
getting	O
drunk	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
there	O
for	O
safety	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cow	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
his	O
Cow	O
from	O
Hackney	B-place
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunny	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Cow	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
6	O
l.	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Cow	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Newal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Delaport	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Grierson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Barbara	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
altho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Delaport	I-pers
bought	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Hair	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
while	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Heifer	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
the	O
Heifer	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
John	B-pers
Bunnil	I-pers
's	O
Slaughter-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bunnil	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Heifer	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Heifer	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wall	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stanley	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gwin	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
28	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Sherard-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
or	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Supper	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
strutting	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
shewing	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
why	O
should	O
she	O
not	O
wear	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
there	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
any	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Bottolph-lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
Value	O
20l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ginn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherring	I-pers
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Coggin	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Foot	O
of	O
Leaden	O
Pipes	O
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Martindale	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pipe	O
was	O
fix	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
the	O
Conveyance	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
nailing	O
was	O
loosned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pipe	O
taken	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lord	B-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Allhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
224	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Steward	O
,	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Lead	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
without	O
his	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Lead	O
upon	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
always	O
sends	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Cart	O
he	O
has	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
weigh	O
it	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
carrying	O
the	O
Lead	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
several	O
Evidences	O
.	O
They	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Plumbery	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
Plumber	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
never	O
gave	O
Orders	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
examined	O
Durham	O
about	O
carrying	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
conceal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
their	O
Master	O
used	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
their	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
openly	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
lay	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
brought	O
Lead	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ask	O
'd	O
no	O
Questions	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Lord	O
and	O
Durham	O
guilty	O
,	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
B	O
-	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Work	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Master	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
thousand	O
of	O
Sprig	O
Nails	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Nails	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Spears	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Nails	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
rattling	O
Traps	O
;	O
that	O
looking	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
Glaziers	O
Sprigs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Board	O
a	O
Holland-Trader	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
flung	O
down	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Nails	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Saddle	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Tredwel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Parkinson	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
chac	O
'd	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Eddoes	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
King	B-place
Street	I-place
at	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Ferguson	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Coat	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
Alley	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Foreside	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
one	O
Blackbourn	O
's	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tredwel	O
came	O
and	O
sate	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
sate	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
treated	O
you	O
before	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Money	O
you	O
should	O
treat	O
me	O
now	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hands	O
round	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
such	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
describ	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
ventured	O
his	O
Life	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
into	O
any	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
or	O
till	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hacker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampton-Court	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
,	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
4	O
Cocks	O
,	O
17	O
Hens	O
,	O
5	O
Drakes	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Ducks	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Tilson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
Teddington	B-place
,	O
they	O
went	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
one	O
Guy	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
fling	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fleetwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
washing	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Styres	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Sheets	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Simon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Sheets	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
two	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Francklin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pittam	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mobberly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
and	O
striking	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Bruises	O
he	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
John	O
Pittam	O
and	O
John	O
Mobberly	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
unlawful	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Fox	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
as	O
John	O
Lough	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
on	O
some	O
Straw	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Francklin	O
fighting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
sometimes	O
one	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
another	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Son	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
three	O
Fellows	O
,	O
mentioning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Names	O
,	O
had	O
fallen	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
knocked	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
blooded	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Looseness	O
,	O
a	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
five	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fox	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Father	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
Die	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Inflammation	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Bruises	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Bruises	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
Whence	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Inflammation	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
proceeded	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
from	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Fall	O
and	O
Blows	O
might	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Fever	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Francklin	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Pittam	O
and	O
Mobberly	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Russ	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Northall	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilchin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Blundel	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jolls	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Torbuch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
by	O
Elizabeth	O
Jolls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Thorn	O
,	O
stood	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Book	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Elizabeth	O
Jolls	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10s	O
.	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
twelve	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
;	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pot	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
full	O
Pots	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Timothy	O
Crawley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Rising-Sun	B-place
in	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
sitting	O
with	O
his	O
Landlady	O
;	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
a	O
School-Master	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
such	O
Discourse	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
third	O
Pot	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Glass	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Beer	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
his	O
Landlady	O
objected	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
usual	O
to	O
drink	O
common	O
Beer	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Glass	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
but	O
two	O
Glasses	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
sink	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
very	O
much	O
disordered	O
,	O
and	O
intoxicated	O
,	O
that	O
finding	O
himself	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
stumbled	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
Capt	O
.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
sate	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Dawson	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
towards	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Feet	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Breeches	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Breeches	O
to	O
be	O
pulled	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
they	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Glass	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
nevertheless	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Senses	O
and	O
Reason	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
affront	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Estate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Dawson	O
flung	O
his	O
Gloves	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
burnt	O
your	O
Gloves	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Midshipman	O
,	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Crawley	O
finding	O
himself	O
disorder	O
'd	O
,	O
desired	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Foot	O
slipping	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
more	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
two	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
screen	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
Home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
and	O
Harrow	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Bed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Board	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
and	O
Harrow	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
himself	O
is	O
always	O
the	O
last	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carries	O
the	O
Key	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Young	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Isabella	O
Car	O
,	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
17s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
charging	O
Mary	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
with	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lighton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cypher	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berrington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
being	O
married	O
to	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Susannah	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
spin	O
.	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
apearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
15s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beckinton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Worril	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Shevalier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Fender	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Shevalier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Wisbich	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ibraham	B-pers
Israel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jonas	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
five	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Canisters	O
,	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
250	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
90	O
l.	O
three	O
Diamond	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
de	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mendez	O
de	O
Costa	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
Abroad	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
after	O
him	O
divers	O
Ways	O
,	O
to	O
Dover	O
,	O
Harwich	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
viewing	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pisin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
at	O
Canterhury	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Simpkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
2	O
Silver	O
Canisters	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
asking	O
4s	O
.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tizzard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Tenters	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Tenters	O
in	O
the	O
Dog-house	B-place
Ground	I-place
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
out	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
Johnson	O
's	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
Davis	O
(	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
advise	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
that	O
could	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jarret	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Jarret	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
that	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
length	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Jarret	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
did	O
promise	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
self	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
talking	O
with	O
his	O
Mother	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Child	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
hang	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
hard	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
first	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
a	O
pair	O
Shoes	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jarret	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Philips	O
did	O
bring	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Method	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
's	O
making	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
present	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Dogs	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeping	O
the	O
Tap-House	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	B-place
Brewhouse	I-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
having	O
laid	O
their	O
great	O
Coats	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
that	O
stood	O
near	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Curtain	O
being	O
drawn	O
before	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Coats	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Coats	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
Doors	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kitson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
Doors	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Coats	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Walter	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
twenty-one	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Warcopp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Irish	O
Linen	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
dislik	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
reach	O
another	O
Piece	O
,	O
but	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
kept	O
his	O
Eye	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
shewing	O
her	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
that	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
upon	O
casting	O
her	O
Eye	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
hastily	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stolen	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Cloth	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
being	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Goodchild	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
25	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
five	O
Ducats	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
a	O
three	O
Guilder	O
Piece	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Holland	O
's	O
Trader	O
,	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
some	O
Tea	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
received	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
returning	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
at	O
Pancras	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Link	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Field	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
between	O
Tottenham-Court	B-place
and	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Bundle	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
on	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Gingham	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
likewise	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threatened	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
Gingham	O
Wastecoat	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
blow	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Pistol	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
,	O
thick	O
,	O
knobbed	O
Pistol	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Guard	O
to	O
the	O
Trigger	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
that	O
answered	O
this	O
Descripion	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
dropp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
attack	O
'd	O
Dr.	O
Mead	O
's	O
Coach	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
near	O
Leather-Lane	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
which	O
Pistol	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Pistol	O
he	O
presented	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
Waller	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Light	O
or	O
Dark	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
Dark	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Link	O
was	O
lighted	O
when	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Pistol	O
that	O
he	O
attack	O
'd	O
Dr.	O
Mead	O
's	O
Man	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
attack	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brerecliff	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attack	O
'd	O
Dr.	O
Mead	O
,	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
did	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
that	O
flash	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
charged	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
Waller	O
,	O
exclaim	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
vile	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
Affidavit	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
but	O
lately	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
charg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
done	O
many	O
ill	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
deserv	O
'd	O
Death	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
yet	O
not	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
Innocent	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Rogue	O
as	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
Barrel	O
the	O
better	O
Herring	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
wore	O
a	O
Gingham	O
Wastecoat	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
falsify	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
that	O
end	O
desired	O
that	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
might	O
be	O
fetch	O
'd	O
from	O
Newgate	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
North	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Gingham	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Jemmy	O
Dalton	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
Dalton	O
,	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
wrong	O
you	O
?	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Penny	O
in	O
your	O
Life	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
this	O
Discourse	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
after	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
therefore	O
thought	O
scarce	O
probable	O
he	O
should	O
then	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
was	O
also	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
for	O
falsely	O
charging	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swearing	O
the	O
Fact	O
positively	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Evidences	O
being	O
Persons	O
of	O
no	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Aubert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Kettle	O
and	O
Lamp	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
three	O
Castors	O
,	O
fourteen	O
Forks	O
,	O
six	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Ecklin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
his	O
Butler	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
stolen	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pantry	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
under	O
Ground	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
the	O
Bar	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Floor	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
or	O
fourteen	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ecklin	O
's	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Pantry	O
Window	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Plate	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
his	O
own	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
.	O
The	O
Plate	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
broken	O
to	O
Pieces	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
or	O
Crest	O
,	O
being	O
Engraven	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Servant	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Swiss	O
by	O
Nation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Thimbles	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
ten	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
an	O
Emerald	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Rock	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sutcliff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
an	O
Accessory	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
,	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
to	O
advertise	O
them	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
being	O
pretty	O
remarkable	O
;	O
the	O
Rings	O
being	O
made	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Brazil	O
;	O
and	O
offering	O
10	O
l.	O
Reward	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
proportionable	O
for	O
any	O
part	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Jasper	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Reward	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
direct	O
him	O
to	O
recover	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Brother	O
up	O
again	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answering	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Information	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
's	O
)	O
Custody	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
speaks	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
George	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
George	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
positively	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pen	O
,	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Lines	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
his	O
Brother	O
William	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
reading	O
it	O
,	O
immediately	O
tore	O
it	O
in	O
Pieces	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
tearing	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Suspicion	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
taxing	O
him	O
more	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
them	O
in	O
Hemming	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Shame	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
never	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
sent	O
to	O
inquire	O
in	O
Hemming	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
five	O
Guineas	O
for	O
her	O
Reward	O
,	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
lost	O
,	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
several	O
Meetings	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
discourse	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Partnership	O
in	O
Trade	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
advance	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
a	O
Partnership	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
dealing	O
in	O
Cutlery	O
Ware	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
indeed	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Gracechurch-Street	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Suffolk-Street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
Suffolk-Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Persons	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
talk	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langton	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
his	O
File	O
of	O
Advertisements	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
George	O
Downing	O
,	O
who	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
Intimation	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
Partnership	O
propos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
sometimes	O
promising	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
Gold	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
keeping	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
Up-Park	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Tankerville	O
;	O
the	O
Matter	O
rested	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Design	O
of	O
getting	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
George	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Brother	O
William	O
,	O
who	O
protested	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
utter	O
Stranger	O
to	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
his	O
Brother	O
should	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Action	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
consult	O
his	O
Brother	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
flung	O
them	O
in	O
Hemming	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
Brother	O
having	O
committed	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Tin	O
Box	O
and	O
Things	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
printed	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
received	O
the	O
Information	O
from	O
Jasper	O
Robins	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Discovery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
before	O
been	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
Susan	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
five	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Tin	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
in	O
Hemming	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
five	O
Guineas	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
them	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
George	O
Downing	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
William	O
also	O
as	O
an	O
Accessory	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
[	O
William	O
Downing	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
jun	B-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
sen	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Copper	O
Stew	O
Pan	O
,	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
an	O
Accessory	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Casement	O
was	O
opened	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
hasped	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
sen.	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
others	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
the	O
Father	O
)	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
hid	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Robbing	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Nattris	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Nattris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
Sen.	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
drew	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Squire	O
Parkinson	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Son	O
a	O
Thieving	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
let	O
him	O
get	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ready	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Thieving	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Punch	O
that	O
he	O
uses	O
in	O
Shoe-making	O
,	O
and	O
stamp	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
was	O
laid	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
which	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
lay	O
upon	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
a	O
Thieving	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
lay	O
himself	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
the	O
Son	O
brought	O
him	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
no	O
Discovery	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Nattris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
that	O
Williams	O
broke	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
could	O
make	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
five	O
Pair	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
.	O
The	O
Shoes	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
also	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
the	O
Sash	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Wood	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nailed	O
on	O
with	O
Tin	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Wig	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
Block	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Wood	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Nattris	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Tin	O
and	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
young	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wore	O
the	O
Wig	O
several	O
Sundays	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Flavel	O
confirmed	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
wearing	O
Wig	O
;	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
being	O
also	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Pridgeon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-Stopper	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
ten	O
Keys	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
upon	O
Edward	B-pers
Powney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pridgeon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Stepney-fields	B-place
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Ferdinand	B-pers
Slrimpton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Frier	O
,	O
alias	O
Drummond	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-stopper	O
,	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
him	O
naked	O
all	O
but	O
his	O
Stockings	O
,	O
took	O
also	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
Stock	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
Buckles	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
warm	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Keys	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Moon-shine	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Breeches	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Spot	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
impudent	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
again	O
?	O
and	O
Frier	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Horse-whip	O
,	O
and	O
whipt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Keys	O
from	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Southwark	O
Goal	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Stock	O
and	O
Shirt	O
again	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Powney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
off	O
Pridgeon	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Money	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
strip	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
slip	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
convicted	O
Frier	O
and	O
Ferdinando	O
Srimpton	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
this	O
very	O
Fact	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
thought	O
his	O
Case	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
intimated	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Case	O
should	O
be	O
favourably	O
represented	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Norton	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Stephen	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sorrel	B-pers
Gelding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Austwick	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mail	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
fifty	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Bristol	O
and	O
Gloucester	O
Mail	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
near	O
Knight's-Bridge	B-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Gateway	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
Stand	O
,	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
by	O
the	O
Bridle	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
mistaken	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
Post	O
Boy	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
before	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Bag	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
Side	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
pulled	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Mail	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
out	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
unbuckled	O
the	O
Mail	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Sack	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
several	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
hinder	O
Mail	O
Pin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cropper	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Sack	O
upon	O
the	O
sore	O
Mail	O
Pin	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
ty	O
'd	O
him	O
fast	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
bags	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
rid	O
away	O
,	O
threatened	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
offered	O
to	O
stir	O
before	O
the	O
People	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Oxen	O
sent	O
of	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
time	O
this	O
was	O
?	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Stature	O
and	O
Size	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
Coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
Cape	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
button	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
flapping	O
over	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Colour	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
Snowing	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Snow	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
divers	O
times	O
sollicited	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Bristol-Mail	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
short	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
raise	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Boy	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
ever	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
his	O
Proposal	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
one	O
Mason	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
proposing	O
to	O
rob	O
Mrs.	O
Marlow	O
some	O
Night	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Danger	O
if	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
turn	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
away	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
did	O
turn	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
five	O
Pound	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Month	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
abate	O
him	O
10	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
robbing	O
of	O
the	O
Bristol-Mail	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
propos	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
propos	O
'd	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
five	O
Pound	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
gone	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
to	O
Change	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Broadhead	O
,	O
his	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stay	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Tap-house	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Clerks	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compting-house	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
asking	O
them	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Bill	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
looking	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
