TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXX	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blundel	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Ashbourn	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Ogbourn	I-pers
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Batley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Mattoon	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cramphorn	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bencroft	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Spinnage	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Mountany	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Katharine	O
Chambers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
Meeting	O
,	O
and	O
stepping	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Women	O
came	O
and	O
jostled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Madam	O
Jacomb	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Watch	O
Case	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Case	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
his	O
Mistress	O
cry	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Case	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
three	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Sarah	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Anne	B-pers
Huffman	I-pers
whom	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
Alive	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
about	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ealing	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hearsay	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goose	O
being	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Goose	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Cecil	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Clement	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Husband	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Sick	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
it	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Morgan	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
his	O
Lodging	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Gamaliel	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Dorothy	O
Man	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Gown	O
into	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
Water	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
an	O
Area	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
Iron	O
Rails	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Linen	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
of	O
nine	O
Foot	O
long	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Hook	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
following	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
back	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
holding	O
up	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
putting	O
in	O
wet	O
Linen	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Woman	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
which	O
broke	O
with	O
the	O
Blow	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Gown	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Watchman	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
's	O
Follower	O
,	O
supposed	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
going	O
to	O
Arrest	O
somebody	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
wet	O
Linen	O
putting	O
in	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
being	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
the	O
Owners	O
,	O
whereof	O
refused	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
two	O
Horses	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
lately	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
Bird	O
riding	O
through	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
had	O
hired	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
Lett	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
between	O
Islington	O
and	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
him	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
kept	O
him	O
publickly	O
,	O
and	O
Lett	O
him	O
out	O
publickly	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
Mobs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
and	O
Time	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
claiming	O
Kindred	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
about	O
four	O
Days	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
Lodgings	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lametta	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Miles	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Crowd	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
into	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
ripping	O
the	O
Lining	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Outside	O
and	O
Lining	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
four	O
Taverns	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
Tavern	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
drank	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
changing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
had	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Change	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deluded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
slipt	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
i.e	O
.	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
pawn	O
an	O
Apron	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Silver	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
her	O
with	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Pledge	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
half	O
Crown	O
chang	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
and	O
leaving	O
in	O
Writing	O
the	O
Posy	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
No	O
Riches	O
,	O
no	O
Content	O
,	O
she	O
stopt	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
before	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Lodging	O
,	O
spent	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
leaving	O
it	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
three	O
Shillings	O
for	O
carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
She	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Drunk	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
neither	O
drunk	O
nor	O
sober	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposing	O
,	O
The	O
Ring	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Ring	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
without	O
difficulty	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
,	O
a	O
Stander-by	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Ring	O
came	O
not	O
off	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Skagg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
five	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
eight	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
divers	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
out	O
on	O
Whit-Sunday	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
seemingly	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
calling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Skagg	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
did	O
with	O
some	O
Difficulty	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
having	O
been	O
her	O
Lodger	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Skagg	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
having	O
some	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
them	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
of	O
Skagg	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
Places	O
where	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Linen	O
was	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
laid	O
the	O
Fault	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
one	O
charging	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
putting	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
express	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Sorrow	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
ill	O
used	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Linen	O
in	O
Skagg	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
owning	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Stockdon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Geese	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
Chickens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
deficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gothridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
himself	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
denying	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Steel	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joanna	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Spurstow	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Tempest	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tesser	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jane	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
34	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Law-Suit	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Intimate	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
Judge	O
's	O
Warrant	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
Bail	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
Home	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complaining	O
of	O
their	O
Usage	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
call	O
and	O
abuse	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
high	O
Rate	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
going	O
away	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
paid	O
her	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
beating	O
her	O
,	O
pulled	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
enquiring	O
the	O
Reason	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Judge	O
's	O
Warrant	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tempest	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Tesser	I-pers
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
thinks	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
rising	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
wak	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
the	O
Judge	O
's	O
Warrant	O
had	O
been	O
Bail	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
only	O
,	O
went	O
not	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Tempest	O
had	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Tesser	I-pers
had	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Night	O
that	O
Bail	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
's	O
Warrant	O
the	O
Day	O
preceding	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
a	O
few	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
likewise	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Scolding	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
11	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
and	O
Outcry	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Welsh	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Constable	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Judge	O
's	O
Warrant	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
mention	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Alice	O
Tesser	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
forswore	O
herself	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
33	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereas	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
34	O
s.	O
This	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Tempest	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
practised	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
or	O
Solicitor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Practice	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Robbery	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
after	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
Robbery	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
she	O
did	O
pretend	O
to	O
have	O
legal	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
Abuses	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
38	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Leonard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Cooper	O
s	O
and	O
Servants	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Screws	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
staying	O
long	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Leonard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Screws	O
;	O
that	O
Walker	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
's	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
enough	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
A	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
James	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
stop	O
Leonard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
at	O
Cox	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	O
about	O
forty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
him	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Warehouse-Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
with	O
the	O
Screws	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Cooper	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Leonard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
going	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
suffer	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
when	O
these	O
Hogsheads	O
were	O
weigh	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
some	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
weigh	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Notice	O
taken	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ridgley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
some	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Irish	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
at	O
Mile-end	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Race	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Racers	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
perceiving	O
something	O
to	O
be	O
doing	O
about	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
clapt	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
clapt	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
By-standers	O
assisting	O
,	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
own	O
Penknife	O
,	O
Thimble	O
,	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
,	O
one	O
Buckle	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
Money	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Irish	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
another	O
Pocket	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
Penknife	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lunn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
being	O
about	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
and	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
to	O
get	O
through	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
Bess	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Hannah	B-pers
Whitman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clarety	I-pers
Hannah	I-pers
,	O
did	O
upon	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
assault	O
Barbara	B-pers
Minekin	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Minekin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
near	O
the	O
7	B-place
Dials	I-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Whitman	I-pers
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
damn	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
Dutch	O
Bitch	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Whitman	I-pers
holding	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Claret-fac	O
'd	O
Hannah	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
Murder	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
threatening	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
pleas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Nosegay	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
long	O
for	O
your	O
Nosegay	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Penknife	O
of	O
Claret-fac	O
'd	O
Hannah	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
half	O
naked	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
cut	O
Apron	O
hanging	O
about	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
.	O
Thomasin	O
Partridge	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
home	O
a	O
Gown	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
Pawn	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Whitman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
did	O
come	O
home	O
without	O
any	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
Apron	O
hanging	O
over	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
see	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
worst	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
only	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Transported	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Clarety	O
Hannah	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Avelins	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Nosegay	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Gowns	O
of	O
your	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
paid	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Clarct	O
Hannah	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
cut	O
her	O
Gown	O
off	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
matter	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
those	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
off	O
from	O
any	O
thing	O
ten	O
times	O
worse	O
than	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
cutting	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
hers	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
never	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
you	O
down	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
swear	O
her	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Obrine	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
Day	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
an	O
Apron	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
heard	O
her	O
swear	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
damn	O
her	O
Soul	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
Money	O
to	O
put	O
herself	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Whitman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
Scolding	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
she	O
thinks	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
her	O
Apron	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
Hungry	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Body	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
wronged	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
intrusted	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Dutch	O
Woman	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
Hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Fees	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
idle	O
Woman	O
since	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leadheater	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Dr.	O
Monroe	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
wronged	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Curseworth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
four	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Mary	O
Adams	O
kept	O
disorderly	O
Houses	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
and	O
entertain	O
'd	O
lewd	O
People	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
Seven-Dials	O
Society	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hang	O
a	O
Dog	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
fifty	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Orris	O
Weaver	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
acquaiuting	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
risen	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Work-room	O
,	O
and	O
wound	O
Silver-thread	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
an	O
Ounce	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
examining	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
the	O
said	O
Ounce	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Silver	O
Thread	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Parcels	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cotterel	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
buying	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
publickly	O
in	O
her	O
open	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
full	O
Price	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
she	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
themselves	O
all	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
full	O
Value	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
themselves	O
would	O
give	O
in	O
the	O
Condition	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
9	O
,	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Characters	O
for	O
fair	O
Dealing	O
,	O
Probity	O
,	O
Prudence	O
and	O
Vertue	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Laurence	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
Pence	O
in	O
half	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
at	O
Bethnel-Green	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
going	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
Watchmen	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
Sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
George	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
more	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Truncheon	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
unmerciful	O
manner	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
divers	O
very	O
great	O
Wounds	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
his	O
Partner	O
,	O
and	O
kneeling	O
on	O
his	O
Stomach	O
,	O
kept	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Comrade	B-pers
,	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
running	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Truncheon	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Rolling-pin	O
)	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
over	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
five	O
Pence	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
was	O
beating	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
assist	O
his	O
Comrade	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
.	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
almost	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
coming	O
,	O
got	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
bloody	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
bruis	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
almost	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
ran	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Beadle	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Black	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Black	O
Crape	O
Neckcloth	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
affirm	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Injury	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Cage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
affirm	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
swore	O
the	O
same	O
positively	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Enstace	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Stephen	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
way	O
of	O
discourse	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wadley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
know	O
the	O
Persons	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
That	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pain	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
waited	O
late	O
before	O
his	O
Master	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
came	O
Home	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
near	O
Bethnal-Green	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
wrong	O
laid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
William	B-pers
Flanders	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Macqueen	I-pers
being	O
Alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
deficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hired	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
work	O
up	O
what	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
in	O
Buckles	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
casting	O
Silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
180	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pot	O
Ashes	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ashes	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Keys	B-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Custom-House	I-place
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Savil	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Akers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
Savil	O
Hornby	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
would	O
not	O
abide	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Haskins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Wet	O
Nurse	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
sent	O
Word	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
deceas	O
'd	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
alledging	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
Sick	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Plea	O
not	O
seeming	O
probable	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
another	O
Plea	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
have	O
carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
also	O
not	O
being	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Blanchet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Lewer	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Oliver	O
's	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
Degrees	O
in	O
small	O
Sums	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
two	O
Years	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
grounds	O
for	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
with	O
another	O
Felony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
continued	O
,	O
and	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
Fact	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Macey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Knapton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Club	O
,	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
into	O
East-Smith-field	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Three	I-place
Tobacco-Rolls	I-place
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Doors	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
,	O
he	O
believes	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
Hours	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awak	O
'd	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
themselves	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Ramber	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
Sister	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Dwelling	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
hearing	O
her	O
walking	O
about	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
fear	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
killed	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
Mischief	O
had	O
befallen	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Places	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
likely	O
to	O
get	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Alehouse-Door	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
abused	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
an	O
Officer	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
herself	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
to	O
dress	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Sleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awak	O
'd	O
demanded	O
his	O
Gold	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Contract	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
than	O
the	O
Guinea	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
10	O
s.	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Money	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bluck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Bluck	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
five	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
credibly	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
some	O
Tokens	O
of	O
Distraction	O
in	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Plea	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Justice	O
Newton	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
upon	O
another	O
Occasion	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Entry	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
near	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
heard	O
some	O
Enquiry	O
made	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Conscience	O
accus	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Murther	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
some	O
Confusion	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Burdus	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
.	O
Justice	O
Burdus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
two	O
Justices	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
of	O
a	O
Murther	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
melancholy	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Sick	O
lately	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
inquire	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
Fact	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
one	O
Son	O
and	O
two	O
Daughters	O
,	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
use	O
his	O
little	O
Daughter	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Bluck	I-pers
,	O
hardly	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Hair-Line	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Noose	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Canopy	O
of	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
hang	O
for	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cut	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
an	O
Apoplectick	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
:	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
twice	O
attempted	O
to	O
Hang	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
;	O
and	O
once	O
to	O
Poison	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Heart	O
fail	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Conscience	O
troubling	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
publick	O
Justice	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Aldern	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
Apothecary	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
since	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
now	O
living	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
the	O
Body	O
narrowly	O
,	O
but	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Discoloration	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
subject	O
to	O
Convulsion-Fits	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
twice	O
cured	O
her	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Convulsions	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
his	O
usual	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
melancholy	O
Disposition	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Searchers	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
examine	O
both	O
the	O
Child	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
Convulsion-Fits	O
.	O
Joyce	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
always	O
acted	O
like	O
a	O
Madman	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
Child	O
was	O
dying	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
Water	O
and	O
Nutmeg	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
and	O
heard	O
visible	O
Tokens	O
and	O
Expressions	O
of	O
Distraction	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
over	O
and	O
given	O
away	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
capable	O
of	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Jointure	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
given	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
a	O
Minister	O
to	O
pray	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
away	O
400	O
l.	O
in	O
five	O
Weeks	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
scarce	O
a	O
Six	O
Pence	O
left	O
to	O
help	O
himself	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Binnel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Armsby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
on	O
Charity	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
had	O
Knowledge	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
abruptly	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
though	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Tifford	B-pers
Willington	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hawkswell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linen	O
,	O
Mobs	O
,	O
Aprons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
both	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
in	O
Custody	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Officer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shillingford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
carrying	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
Hawkswell	O
's	O
Pockets	O
bulk	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
some	O
Robbery	O
,	O
therefore	O
ask	O
'd	O
Hawkswell	O
(	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
)	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
whither	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
fear	O
that	O
his	O
Landlord	O
would	O
seize	O
them	O
for	O
Rent	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
found	O
wet	O
Linen	O
,	O
which	O
further	O
confirming	O
his	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Boy	O
,	O
which	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
New	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
pretending	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
Bird	O
's	O
Nests	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Things	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
coming	O
over	O
an	O
Hay-Field	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Boy	O
which	O
had	O
run	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Hay-cock	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Farthing-Pye-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
hid	O
a	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Hawkswell	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
out	O
late	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Goods	O
for	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
produc	O
'd	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
.	O
Willington	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
a	O
Bird	O
's	O
Nesting	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
Hawkswell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Things	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Fleming	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
discover	O
where	O
the	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
;	O
and	O
Willington	O
calling	O
some	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
both	O
him	O
and	O
Fleming	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Hawkswell	O
alone	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brimer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cloth	O
hung	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
Window	O
for	O
Show	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
asking	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
Shop	O
be	O
Robb	O
'd	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
Sold	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
living	O
over-against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
her	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
her	O
Window	O
?	O
That	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
saucy	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
Wheeler	O
take	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
Collins	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Shaftoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hog	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Hog	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Stye	O
in	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Hog	O
grunt	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
leading	O
the	O
Hog	O
in	O
a	O
String	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cushnee	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cushnee	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
come	O
lately	O
from	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
times	O
as	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
Money	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
himself	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
lay	O
the	O
eighteen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
scatter	O
'd	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
broken	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
wanting	O
Money	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
as	O
was	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Cushnee	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Conveniency	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Week	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
Days	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
another	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
sate	O
there	O
Reading	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bells	O
had	O
rung	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
so	O
soon	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prayers	O
were	O
ended	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
weary	O
of	O
standing	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
knowing	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
to	O
shift	O
herself	O
,	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Room	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
that	O
Drawer	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
hung	O
with	O
other	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Trunk	O
reading	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
suspecting	O
nothing	O
,	O
never	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
till	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
being	O
washing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Linen	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
by	O
what	O
foreboding	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
in	O
some	O
surprize	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Keys	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
some	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
them	O
among	O
some	O
Clothes	O
into	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
all	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
knowing	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
alone	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
complained	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
being	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
observing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
little	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
suspect	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
consent	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
but	O
before	O
higher	O
Powers	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
were	O
found	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
among	O
her	O
Guineas	O
two	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
took	O
Care	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
them	O
by	O
,	O
resolving	O
not	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
while	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
other	O
left	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Pig	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
i.	O
e.	O
an	O
Elephant	O
)	O
under	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
new	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
defac	O
'd	O
or	O
worn	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
such	O
Guineas	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
of	O
those	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
swore	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
shewn	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Justice	O
Webster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
before	O
him	O
describe	O
one	O
,	O
or	O
both	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
before	O
ever	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
his	O
Defence	O
with	O
a	O
florid	O
Harangue	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
Alleviation	O
to	O
the	O
Greatness	O
of	O
his	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
distant	O
from	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Happiness	O
to	O
stand	O
and	O
vindicate	O
his	O
Innocence	O
before	O
so	O
honourable	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Fame	O
of	O
whose	O
Justice	O
and	O
Impartiality	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
often	O
heard	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
intirely	O
Innocent	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
descended	O
of	O
a	O
reputable	O
Family	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Happiness	O
of	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
Gentleman-like	O
,	O
learned	O
,	O
and	O
virtuous	O
Education	O
;	O
had	O
commence	O
Master	O
of	O
Arts	O
in	O
the	O
University	O
of	O
A	O
;	O
was	O
capable	O
of	O
taking	O
his	O
Trial	O
in	O
Latin	O
or	O
Greek	O
;	O
was	O
always	O
train	O
'd	O
and	O
educated	O
in	O
Christian	B-pers
Principles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mind	O
embellish	O
'd	O
with	O
such	O
noble	O
Notions	O
of	O
Vertue	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
probable	O
,	O
may	O
,	O
possible	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
Guilty	O
of	O
so	O
base	O
a	O
Fact	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
several	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
Excise	O
in	O
Scotland	O
,	O
had	O
good	O
Recommendations	O
thence	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
indeed	O
married	O
unhappily	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
Expectation	O
of	O
some	O
Advancement	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
Money	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
prove	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
the	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
kept	O
it	O
conceal	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
sew	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Fob	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
Proof	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Isabel	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
discoursing	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
in	O
Scotland	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
willingly	O
do	O
any	O
harm	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
as	O
a	O
present	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
any	O
Rate	O
.	O
Justice	O
Webster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
Evidence	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Money	O
as	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
Usher	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Boarding-School	O
at	O
Chiswick	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
taking	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
them	O
good	O
enough	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
Capacity	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
act	O
in	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
three	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Crookshank	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
Matter	O
easy	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
willing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
should	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
prepare	O
himself	O
for	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
intimated	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
unlikely	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
eighteen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
complain	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
of	O
some	O
Words	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
need	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
complain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
Gold	O
enough	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
others	O
who	O
establish	O
'd	O
his	O
Character	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
honest	O
,	O
saving	O
,	O
and	O
industrious	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
generally	O
pass	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
for	O
Persons	O
aforehand	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
their	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
but	O
of	O
short	O
Continuance	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
broken	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
nine	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Swabey	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Chore-woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Esther	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Fordnon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
Home	O
from	O
Work	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
demanding	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
she	O
threatened	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
last	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
procure	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
prosecute	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	O
Alley	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Customers	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
Receipt	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
though	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Wages	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
telling	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
therefore	O
being	O
laid	O
wrong	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
another	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
otherGoods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Comb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blodwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
Hobson	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
Lambert	O
and	O
Belcher	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ferret	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Webster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
unload	O
some	O
Bales	O
of	O
Paper	O
at	O
Messieurs	O
Hoole	O
and	O
Brewer	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
by	O
with	O
an	O
empty	O
Cart	O
,	O
carelesly	O
run	O
his	O
Wheel	O
against	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
whip	O
,	O
striking	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
one	O
Blow	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
stagger	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
recover	O
himself	O
,	O
fell	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
Cart-Wheel	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
going	O
,	O
went	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
and	O
quiet	O
Behaviour	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
accidental	O
Death	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Maccouli	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hanmore	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Arnold	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
five	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
against	O
Mary	O
Thompson	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
Elizabeth	O
Hanmore	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Priglove	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Round	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Sheep	O
's	O
Kidneys	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Fat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
some	O
Sheep	O
which	O
hang	O
at	O
Butchers	O
Stalls	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cutting	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Fat	O
and	O
Kidneys	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
off	O
of	O
four	O
Sheep	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
,	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
London	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Sash-Window	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
an	O
Oar	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Oar	O
reared	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sash	O
being	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
)	O
that	O
having	O
undress	O
'd	O
himself	O
there	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
by	O
his	O
Clothes	O
being	O
found	O
there	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Bed	O
Chamber	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
awak	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
vile	O
Actions	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
immediately	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
rais	O
'd	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
those	O
vile	O
Actions	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
entered	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
she	O
lay	O
?	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Fright	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
her	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Leg	O
over	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Child	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
they	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
Posture	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
Backwards	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
way	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Not	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
awake	O
till	O
she	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
rais	O
'd	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Swasey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Rogues	O
and	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
without	O
any	O
Clothes	O
but	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
fear	O
'd	O
her	O
Children	O
were	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Clothes	O
lying	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
Bed	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
his	O
other	O
Clothes	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
's	O
Oar	O
rear	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
first	O
Chamber	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
