TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
V.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
,	O
Clifford	B-pers
Clutterbuck	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Silvester	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Swindal	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bottom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grout	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Dishes	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hames	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
that	O
of	O
John	O
Hames	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Labrum	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
promissory	O
Note	O
given	O
to	O
Zachary	B-pers
Mentz	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Labrum	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Money	O
due	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Warrant	O
having	O
been	O
served	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
discharged	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Note	O
was	O
drawn	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Labrum	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Note	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Note	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
neither	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
by	O
her	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pleading	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
for	O
a	O
Sum	O
greater	O
then	O
her	O
real	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Zachary	B-pers
Mentz	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Friars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
and	O
Bed-Fellow	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
deposited	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Closer	O
near	O
his	O
Bedside	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
himself	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Netherwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Redmayne	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Redmayne	I-pers
Mother	O
and	O
Daughter	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spangles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Anne	O
Redmayne	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Spangles	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
sometimes	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Redmayne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
Times	O
by	O
Anne	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
confess	O
'd	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
being	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
home	O
something	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Mother	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Daughter	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Wooley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawney	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
half	O
pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
-	I-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Headed-Cane	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
said	O
his	O
Cane	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
by	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Caswal	I-pers
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
by	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
the	O
Crests	O
;	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Smith	O
and	O
Redding	O
,	O
three	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Miller	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proper	O
Evidences	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackeg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
under	O
a	O
false	O
Pretence	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
first	O
for	O
one	O
Pair	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
,	O
she	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hern	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
)	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
another	O
Pair	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
return	O
'd	O
those	O
Stockings	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marriot	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
mentioning	O
this	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denying	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
any	O
Stockings	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hern	O
's	O
to	O
inquire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
procuring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
her	O
getting	O
the	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pair	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
had	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Pair	O
was	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
strict	O
Examination	O
she	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Been	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk-Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Shaley	O
Shadwell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Buckle	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
sent	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
fearing	O
some	O
harm	O
had	O
befallen	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
missing	O
the	O
Buckle	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
sent	O
thither	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
by	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
in	O
offering	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Sparks	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
false	O
Account	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
bringing	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
to	O
Match	O
,	O
he	O
telling	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Silk	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gilbert	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
a	O
Chapman	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
more	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Match	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Murphy	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Calamanco	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
difficult	O
to	O
be	O
pleased	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
immediately	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Silk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
her	O
Business	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
Goods	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
Drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
asking	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
get	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
enough	O
,	O
she	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Uriah	B-pers
Aldwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Longwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Journey-woman	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Pawned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Twiss	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
called	O
the	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
Plutarch	O
's	O
Lives	O
,	O
valued	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Peasly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Behn	O
's	O
Novels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Pyrates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Books	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Tokenhouse-Yard	B-place
,	O
from	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
detected	O
of	O
stealing	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
own	O
Books	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
2	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
Plutarch	O
's	O
Lives	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
a	O
Stall	O
in	O
Moor-fields	B-place
,	O
which	O
were	O
likewise	O
bought	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Books	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
both	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
against	O
a	O
Cart-Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
unlawful	O
Slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
Boxing	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
threw	O
Wells	O
twice	O
before	O
Wells	O
threw	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
their	O
Fighting	O
together	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
deceased	O
against	O
the	O
Iron	O
of	O
a	O
Cart-wheel	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
was	O
cut	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
raise	O
himself	O
up	O
,	O
nor	O
spoke	O
any	O
more	O
after	O
that	O
Fall	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
sudden	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
which	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Senseless	O
and	O
Speechless	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
superior	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Skull	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
opening	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
Dead	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
about	O
4	O
Ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
coagulated	O
Blood	O
between	O
the	O
Dura	O
and	O
Pia	O
mater	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
She-Ass	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
's	O
Ass	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
Common	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
feeding	O
at	O
Tottenham	B-place
High-Cross	I-place
.	O
John	B-pers
Hat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Ass	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
to	O
inquire	O
concerning	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
afterwards	O
examined	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ass	O
Grasing	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
decoyed	O
him	O
into	O
Petticoat-Lane	B-place
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
or	O
two	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Stephens	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
come	O
and	O
kiss	O
my	O
Husband	O
?	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
you	O
will	O
never	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
unless	O
it	O
falls	O
into	O
your	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
pick	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Longdon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
at	O
Work	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
's	O
in	O
Catharine-Wheel-Alley	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
;	O
and	O
another	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sallars	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
having	O
combed	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
ask	O
his	O
Master	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
brown	O
Wig	O
by	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Wigs	O
and	O
Hair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
being	O
so	O
daring	O
as	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
espying	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
then	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
near	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Wig	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clitheroe	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
some	O
considerable	O
Time	O
after	O
taken	O
at	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cantrel	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Cantrel	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
at	O
Purflet	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
for	O
near	O
20	O
Years	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cockerel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
marry	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
his	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cantrel	I-pers
,	O
20	O
Pounds	O
,	O
or	O
Guineas	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
deny	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ballass	O
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
besides	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
maintain	O
her	O
handsomely	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
could	O
come	O
and	O
sit	O
in	O
Captain	O
Grantham	B-pers
's	O
Paw	O
,	O
as	O
great	O
as	O
Captain	O
Grantham	B-pers
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Marriages	O
being	O
both	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburgh	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
half	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
4	O
Swan-Inn	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
Harwich	O
Coach	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lain	O
there	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
made	O
some	O
Excuses	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
first	O
for	O
Paper	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
for	O
a	O
Waser	O
to	O
seal	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
in	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Petit	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-Ax	I-place
,	O
flily	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
George	B-pers
Trim	I-pers
)	O
to	O
stand	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
running	O
,	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Linen-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hartup	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Backhouse	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
and	O
Bed-Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Body	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
defrauding	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
false	O
Pretences	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
Interrogatories	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
a	O
1000	O
l.	O
Stock	O
of	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
deceased	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
3	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
Drinking	O
in	O
King's-head-Court	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Coach	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
Swallow-street	B-place
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
commanded	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
side	O
,	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
snap	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Hat	O
too	O
;	O
that	O
pulling	O
him	O
almost	O
half	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
parlying	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Coachman	O
coming	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
snapping	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
kill	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
gotten	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
about	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
Yards	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
drive	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
in	O
Swallow-Street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
had	O
gotten	O
James	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
to	O
drive	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
cross	O
Traces	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
driving	O
,	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
stand	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
bidding	O
the	O
Boy	O
drive	O
on	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
snap	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
snapping	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Pistol	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
snapping	O
another	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Hat	O
too	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
Murther	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
how	O
should	O
he	O
come	O
by	O
his	O
fare	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
?	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Coach-box	O
?	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Shoot	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
believes	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
making	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
out-cry	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
having	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
Gray's-Inn-Gate	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
him	O
,	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
flashing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
frightened	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
creep	O
into	O
the	O
Hay-bag	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
hearing	O
his	O
Money	O
rattle	O
in	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
Business	O
,	O
being	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whetton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
four	O
Fellows	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
along	O
by	O
2	O
and	O
2	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
Street-Robbers	O
,	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
immediately	O
'Squire	O
Greenwood	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
's	O
Coach	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
100	O
Yards	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Men	O
before	O
run	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
's	O
Coach	O
,	O
2	O
on	O
one-Side	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
out-cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Leven	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
his	O
Rounds	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
out-cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
trifled	O
with	O
Justice	O
Giffard	O
.	O
'Squire	O
Greenwood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Hanger	O
drawn	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
4	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
2	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
almost	O
gotten	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Outcry	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
got	O
away	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
Henry	O
Whetton	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Corner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Catesby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
40	O
Guineas	O
and	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
Stepney-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
forty	O
Guineas	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Martin	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
threw	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
and	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
torn	O
and	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
but	O
28	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
the	O
10	O
Guineas	O
make	O
38	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
40	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
were	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
two	O
Men	O
coming	O
cross	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
a	O
Cow-Turd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Occasion	O
to	O
use	O
him	O
so	O
barbarously	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
also	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
search	O
'd	O
till	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
500	O
People	O
got	O
together	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
follow	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
3	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
80	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
heard	O
any	O
provoking	O
Language	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
or	O
saw	O
any	O
Blow	O
given	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
People	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Heap	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
started	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
a	O
pulling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Martin	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
no	O
Assistance	O
?	O
For	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
am	O
beat	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Money	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bear	O
him	O
harmless	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
before	O
Justice	O
Priestly	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
clear	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Charge	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
voluntarily	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
resist	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
down	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
People	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
Boys	O
a	O
Fighting	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
fight	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
help	O
,	O
help	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
murther	O
'd	O
too	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
struggle	O
any	O
longer	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Money	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
perhaps	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
10	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Wright	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
at	O
Cupid	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
77	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Timbrel	O
,	O
a	O
Timber	O
Merchant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
fifty	O
Pound	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Convent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
rest	O
themselves	O
on	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
gross	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Corner	O
's	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bidding	O
him	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
a	O
fighting	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
th	O
at	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
voluntarily	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Field	O
about	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
sitting	O
about	O
four	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Foot	O
Path	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
known	O
no	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
known	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
for	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
failed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Norway	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
accounted	O
him	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
both	O
engag	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
standing	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
am	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
led	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
voluntarily	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Stepney	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
or	O
Felony	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
Elizabeth	O
Corner	O
strike	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
with	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Thomas	O
Martin	O
for	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Martin	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
served	O
him	O
faithfully	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Weaver	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
leaving	O
off	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ethorn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Complaint	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Alam	B-pers
Peller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
three	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Purpose	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bringhurst	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
hearing	O
(	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Fray	O
had	O
been	O
)	O
did	O
say	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
Search	O
me	O
,	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Corner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Things	O
to	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
sitting	O
down	O
to	O
rest	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
of	O
his	O
Field	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
)	O
giving	O
them	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
and	O
haled	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dowley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Money	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
Elizabeth	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
intimated	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
Francis	B-pers
Riches	I-pers
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Bowling-Green	O
at	O
Stepney	O
about	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
three	O
Shilling	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Bowls	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Walnut-Tree	O
over-against	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
spent	O
their	O
Six-pence	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
much	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believes	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
.	O
-	O
Hargrove	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Condition	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
stupified	O
with	O
the	O
Blows	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Ogilby	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Larwood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Belfond	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Housewife	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Chariot	O
upon	O
Hounslow-Heath	B-place
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Gentle-woman	O
,	O
when	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
past	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
none	O
but	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
riding	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
,	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
bidding	O
me	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
Shillings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
out	O
much	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
Occasion	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
Money	O
but	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
Servants	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
ransack	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Housewife	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
more	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ogilby	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
Larwood	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
far	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
that	O
Ogilby	O
rode	O
on	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
one	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Poop	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Constable	O
of	O
Greenford	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
and	O
Housewife	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
Madam	O
Scott	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Ogilby	O
's	O
Pocket	O
by	O
-	O
Busby	O
,	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Ravenor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Ogilby	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
Larwood	O
upon	O
a	O
Gray	O
or	O
White	O
Horse	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
chang	O
'd	O
Horses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopping	O
Ogilby	O
,	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
by	O
the	O
Bridle	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
be	O
shot	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
dismounted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Northolt	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
and	O
Eat	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
Intimate	O
and	O
Familiar	O
together	O
as	O
two	O
Brothers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
Corn	O
for	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
White	O
or	O
Gray	O
Horse	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Smith	O
's	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Shoe	O
set	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Larwood	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
Beans	O
,	O
Ogilby	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
till	O
the	O
Gray	B-pers
Horse	I-pers
came	O
from	O
the	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
Ogilby	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
shoeing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horses	O
half	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
Beans	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
mounted	O
as	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
Ogilby	O
took	O
the	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
Minutes	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Notice	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
Simon	B-pers
Ravenor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Ogilby	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
invited	O
by	O
Larwood	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
to	O
an	O
Aunt	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
Miles	O
off	O
,	O
near	O
Eaton	O
,	O
Larwood	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
melancholy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
the	O
Reason	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
Langley	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ram-Inn	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
happended	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
-	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rode	O
directly	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
Hillenden	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
upon	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
good	O
Luck	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
good	O
Foundling	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Housewife	O
and	O
Cork-screw	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Mother-of-Pearl	O
Top	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
saying	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
matter	O
keeping	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
Proof	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
-	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
a	O
Chocolate-maker	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Ogilby	O
had	O
pleaded	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
buying	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
whether	O
this	O
Man	O
that	O
sold	O
Ogilby	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Larwood	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Ogilby	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Larwood	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
direct	O
as	O
against	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Hamlet	O
of	O
Mile-End	O
Old-Town	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
Victualler	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
falsely	O
and	O
feloniously	O
make	O
,	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
a	O
Bond	O
for	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
under	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holme	I-pers
of	O
Hanover-square	O
,	O
Grocer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
did	O
utter	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meah	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Bond	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Friend	O
scrupling	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
unless	O
the	O
Giver	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
real	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Holme	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
positively	O
denying	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
being	O
indebted	O
in	O
any	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Bond	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
execute	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
sign	O
'd	O
,	O
seal	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
executing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holme	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
positively	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Bond	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
the	O
Hand-writing	O
in	O
the	O
Bond	O
appear	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Holme	O
,	O
but	O
seem	O
'd	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
nor	O
was	O
the	O
Name	O
right	O
spelt	O
,	O
being	O
Homes	O
instead	O
of	O
Holme	O
;	O
several	O
Names	O
to	O
Receipts	O
written	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Holme	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
no	O
ways	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
signing	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Curlis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
2	O
Guineas	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
Toll	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
Toll	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Vouchers	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Fellow	O
that	O
rides	O
Horses	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Toll-Man	O
searching	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
had	O
been	O
advertised	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
immediately	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Makepeace	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cows	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rudley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cows	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ground	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cows	O
being	O
offered	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Value	O
,	O
it	O
gave	O
occasion	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
confessing	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
Word	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Parishioners	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
Work-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
pawn	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
to	O
supply	O
her	O
present	O
Necessity	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
should	O
receive	O
some	O
Money	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Cures	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
Children	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sconces	O
,	O
divers	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
Saucers	O
,	O
Bason	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wrought	O
Dimity-Toilet	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Summer-house	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
Who	O
comes	O
there	O
?	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Friends	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
but	O
West	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
That	O
Sherwood	O
had	O
the	O
Toilet	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Comrades	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Sherwood	O
where	O
West	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
found	O
West	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sconces	O
and	O
China	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hammers	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pincers	O
,	O
Awls	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Knives	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Shoemakers	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pairs	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Indictments	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
4	O
Punch-Bowls	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Aldern	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Walter	B-pers
Boram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
80	O
l.	O
of	O
Horse-flesh	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
dead	O
Horses	O
,	O
boil	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
Oil	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
Flesh	O
at	O
about	O
three	O
Pound	O
for	O
Two-pence	O
for	O
feeding	O
of	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Collar-maker	O
,	O
had	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
flea	O
dead	O
Horses	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
used	O
frequently	O
to	O
buy	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Horse-flesh	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
his	O
Horse-flesh	O
had	O
been	O
weigh	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
fling	O
other	O
pieces	O
,	O
not	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
used	O
to	O
allow	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Horse	O
flesh	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Horse	O
Oil	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
60	O
Pound	O
of	O
Horse-Flesh	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
Oil	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Flask	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
Oil	O
to	O
Oil	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
likewise	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
at	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
for	O
an	O
100	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Note	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
of	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Pound	O
;	O
which	O
Note	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
same	O
Note	O
that	O
was	O
then	O
shewn	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
offering	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
his	O
Trouble	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
several	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Major	O
Smith	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
following	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
Advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Note	O
from	O
one	O
Owen	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Note	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
4	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
one	O
Gilling	O
went	O
and	O
inquir	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
Advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
any	O
stop	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain-Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
waited	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
allow	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
for	O
the	O
Discount	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
get	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
Guineas	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
paying	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Queen's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gilling	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Swan-Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
go	O
and	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain-Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Robinson	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Note	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
the	O
four	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
it	O
was	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Paper	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
observing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Dirt	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
outward	O
Paper	O
was	O
Dirty	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Shields	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
knew	O
that	O
Owen	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
reflect	O
upon	O
me	O
now	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
help	O
'd	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frame	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edgerly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Loder	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Farrington	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
to	O
her	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
Turn-pike-House	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
lighting	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Turn-pike-House	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Edgerly	O
has	O
gotten	O
a	O
new	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Farrington	O
said	O
,	O
ay	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
Business	O
too	O
;	O
that	O
Farrington	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
one	O
Thing	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
kill	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Fowls	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
a	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
a	O
Stick	O
with	O
a	O
Wier	O
ty	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
the	O
Bodies	O
of	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
draw	O
their	O
Guts	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
any	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
two	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Frame	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
one	O
thing	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
set	O
Fire	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
unwilling	O
,	O
Farrington	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
nor	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
else	O
shall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
2	O
Nights	O
after	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
setting	O
Fire	O
,	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
frightned	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
still	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
this	O
Minute	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
a	O
Dancing	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
Day	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
Why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
this	O
till	O
so	O
long	O
time	O
after	O
?	O
(	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
since	O
she	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
)	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
easy	O
in	O
her	O
Mind	O
,	O
without	O
discovering	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
declare	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
jump	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
Touch-Wood	O
and	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
new	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
Pipe	O
and	O
Touch-Wood	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
lie	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Hours	O
before	O
it	O
kindled	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lighted	O
the	O
Touch-Wood	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Thatch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
Blaze	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
new	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
light	O
the	O
Touch-Wood	O
with	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Thatch	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
sending	O
up	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
Straw	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
Fire	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Touchwood	O
,	O
Tinder	O
and	O
Paper	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edgerly	I-pers
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
His	O
House	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Loder	I-pers
had	O
revealed	O
this	O
but	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wayman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
helped	O
him	O
to	O
turn	O
his	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Sheep	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
stuck	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Farrington	O
's	O
about	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Butcher	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assisted	O
in	O
dressing	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
Four	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thinks	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
between	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
break	O
of	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Day-Light	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Butcher	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Sheep	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
when	O
the	O
Sun	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
high	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
giving	O
no	O
Credit	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Loder	I-pers
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
they	O
granted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay-Mare	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
being	O
desirous	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
render	O
'd	O
himself	O
so	O
notorious	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
County	O
seems	O
desirous	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
made	O
a	O
publick	O
Example	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
remain	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
Oxford	O
the	O
next	O
Assizes	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Corner	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Curlis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charls	O
Ogilby	O
.	O
Transportation	O
21.	O
Anne	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Been	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
B	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clitheroe	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
,	O
Jane	O
Jacks	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Jones	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
Redmayne	O
,	O
Penelope	O
Ross	O
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
/	O
Anne	O
Smart	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Twist	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Franklin	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dennison	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
2.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Books	O
just	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
LA	O
Plum	O
Volante	O
.	O
Or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-hand	O
improved	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
most	O
Swift	O
,	O
Regular	O
,	O
and	O
Easy	O
Method	O
of	O
Short-hand-writing	O
yet	O
Extant	O
.	O
Composed	O
after	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
Practice	O
and	O
Improvement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Art	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Observation	O
of	O
other	O
Methods	O
and	O
intent	O
Study	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Aditions	O
of	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
amended	O
,	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Miraculous	O
Conversion	O
from	O
Popery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Glory	O
of	O
Divine	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Protection	O
of	O
Divine	O
Providence	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
God	O
Manifested	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
.	O
The	O
Word	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Exercising	O
the	O
Musker	O
and	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carbine	O
,	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
performed	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
B.	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Singing	O
Master	O
's	O
Guide	O
to	O
his	O
Scholars	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Psalms	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Translations	O
;	O
the	O
Old	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
By	O
several	O
Hands	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sternhold	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
Barton	O
,	O
Patrick	O
,	O
Tace	O
and	O
Brady	O
,	O
Milbourne	O
and	O
Sandys	O
.	O
Contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
Common	O
Use	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Tunes	O
in	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ewlem	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clarks	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
any	O
other	O
religiously	O
and	O
devoutly	O
disposed	O
to	O
make	O
Use	O
of	O
these	O
Instructions	O
.	O
Being	O
contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
common	O
Use	O
,	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
Ewlem	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
,	O
B	B-pers
,	I-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Children	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Alphabets	O
and	O
Syllables	O
,	O
with	O
short	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
of	O
dividing	O
Words	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Rules	O
for	O
true	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
Writing	O
of	O
English	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Two	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
useful	O
Words	O
,	O
whose	O
Spelling	O
or	O
sense	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Also	O
Christian	O
Names	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
fifth	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
Price	O
9	O
d.	O
The	O
Greatness	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Unspeakableness	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
thereof	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
the	O
Losing	O
in	O
First	O
Preached	O
in	O
Pinners-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
enlarged	O
,	O
and	O
published	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Shop	O
into	O
he	O
Sold	O
to	O
all	O
stationers	O
and	O
School-masters	O
in	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
,	O
Pieces	O
for	O
Christmas	O
,	O
Easters	O
and	O
Whitsunside	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
wholesale	O
and	O
retale	O
,	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
on	O
Copper-plates	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
II	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Jerusalem	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Temple	O
of	O
Solomon	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Geometry	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Haman	O
hanged	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Hunting-Piece	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Grammar	O
and	O
Writing-School	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Christ	O
's	O
Burial	O
.	O
10	O
The	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Show	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
Moses	O
in	O
the	O
Ark	O
of	O
Bull	O
rushes	O
.	O
12	O
History	O
of	O
Tobit	O
.	O
13	O
Christ	O
's	O
Ascension	O
.	O
14	O
The	O
seven	O
Sciences	O
.	O
15	O
Dorattis	O
and	O
Fawnia	O
.	O
16	O
History	O
of	O
Judith	O
and	O
Holosernis	O
.	O
17	O
The	O
four	O
Evangelists	O
.	O
18	O
Stool-Ball	O
.	O
19	O
Joseph	O
flying	O
into	O
Egypt	O
.	O
20	O
Crucifixion	O
;	O
And	O
many	O
others	O
in	O
whole	O
sheets	O
and	O
half	O
Sheets	O
:	O
Likewise	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
Elegiac	O
Poem	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Most	O
Sacred	O
Majesty	O
K.	O
George	O
,	O
engraven	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Also	O
Gospel	O
Mystery	O
Emblematically	O
illustrated	O
,	O
engraven	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Copper-plate	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
CATO	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Case	O
and	O
History	O
of	O
Self-Murder	O
,	O
argu	O
'd	O
and	O
Display	O
'd	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Principles	O
of	O
Reason	O
,	O
Justice	O
,	O
Law	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
Fortitude	O
,	O
Love	O
of	O
ourselves	O
and	O
our	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
Example	O
;	O
A	O
Solution	O
of	O
this	O
Problem	O
,	O
whether	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Sense	O
,	O
Goodness	O
,	O
and	O
Courage	O
,	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
,	O
Kill	O
Himself	O
?	O
Particularly	O
calculated	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Nation	O
:	O
Occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Stabbing	O
Himself	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instances	O
.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Lecture	O
,	O
deliver	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Henley	B-pers
,	I-pers
M.	I-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
Publish	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Hearers	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
J	O
.	O
Marshal	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
A	O
speedy	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
ITCH	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George's-Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
is	O
Sold	O
.	O
A	O
WATER	O
which	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
or	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
;	O
and	O
hath	O
been	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
Years	O
Experience	O
:	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Prepared	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
or	O
SCURVY-GRASS	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
Excellent	O
in	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
called	O
DAFFY	O
's	O
ELIXIR	O
,	O
truly	O
prepared	O
from	O
the	O
best	O
Ingredients	O
,	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
Published	O
,	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
,	O
of	O
A	O
PRACTICAL	O
TREATISE	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
Second	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
On	O
the	O
Simple	O
Gonorrhoea	O
,	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Embraces	O
,	O
Self-pollution	O
,	O
improperly	O
called	O
Onanism	O
,	O
or	O
Natural	O
Imbecillity	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Virulent	O
Gonorrhoea	O
,	O
or	O
Clap	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Lues	O
,	O
or	O
Grand	O
Pox	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
plainly	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
exact	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Differences	O
;	O
with	O
their	O
Signs	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
Prognosticks	O
,	O
and	O
Cures	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
,	O
their	O
Beginnings	O
,	O
Progress	O
,	O
and	O
fatal	O
Periods	O
,	O
when	O
neglected	O
or	O
unskilfully	O
managed	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
their	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
,	O
without	O
Violence	O
or	O
Injury	O
,	O
is	O
completed	O
.	O
With	O
proper	O
and	O
effectual	O
Remedies	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
Stages	O
,	O
prescribed	O
and	O
recommended	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
the	O
:	O
Proposterous	O
way	O
of	O
Venery	O
with	O
Machines	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
plan	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Dangers	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
little	O
expected	O
)	O
which	O
attend	O
that	O
vile	O
practice	O
.	O
Also	O
many	O
other	O
useful	O
Discoveries	O
relating	O
to	O
Infections	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
annexed	O
,	O
a	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
practice	O
of	O
Salivating	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Whole	O
fitted	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
Patients	O
as	O
young	O
Practitioners	O
.	O
By	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CAM	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-Church-Yard	O
;	O
also	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
E	O
Midwinter	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
;	O
C	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
J.	O
Hodges	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Mackenen	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
WHEREAS	O
I	O
JOHN	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
,	O
dwelling	O
in	O
Turn-wheel-lane	O
,	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beecher	O
,	O
Salter	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
ten	O
Years	O
periodically	O
troubled	O
with	O
windy	O
Eructations	O
and	O
four	O
Bechings	O
,	O
likewise	O
with	O
a	O
Pain	O
that	O
pierced	O
through	O
my	O
very	O
Back	O
and	O
Loins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Loss	O
of	O
Appetite	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Faculty	O
of	O
Physick	O
without	O
obtaining	O
any	O
lasting	O
Relist	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
numerous	O
Cures	O
perform	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
,	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
in	O
Laurence	O
Pountney's-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
great	O
Gates	O
on	O
the	O
Left-Hand	O
from	O
Cannon-street	O
.	O
I	O
apply	O
'd	O
myself	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
effectually	O
curved	O
me	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
desire	O
this	O
may	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
this	O
only	O
Reason	O
,	O
that	O
others	O
assisted	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Manner	O
may	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Relief	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
Witness	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
1730.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
.	O
Note	O
,	O
The	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
as	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
Chynigoons-Hall	O
.	O
Silver-Street	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
aforesaid	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
has	O
lately	O
prepared	O
two	O
Anti-Scorburick	O
Medicines	O
,	O
being	O
Pills	O
and	O
a	O
Spirit	O
,	O
which	O
excel	O
any	O
Thing	O
yet	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Purge	O
given	O
at	O
proper	O
Times	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
It	O
expels	O
the	O
numerous	O
Trains	O
of	O
Scorbutic	O
Symptoms	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Hypochondriac	O
and	O
Hysteric	O
Illnesses	O
have	O
their	O
Source	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
it	O
relieves	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
alters	O
and	O
changes	O
all	O
the	O
Juices	O
in	O
the	O
human	O
Body	O
,	O
thins	O
the	O
Lentor	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
sizy	O
,	O
viscid	O
,	O
coagulated	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
which	O
obstructs	O
the	O
Capillary	O
Vessels	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
Chilness	O
in	O
the	O
extream	O
Parts	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Heat	O
in	O
Hypochondriac	O
and	O
Hysteric	O
Paroxysms	O
,	O
renovates	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
restores	O
decay	O
'd	O
Nature	O
,	O
chears	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
revivers	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
and	O
opens	O
Obstructions	O
of	O
the	O
Viscera	O
,	O
gives	O
Rest	O
to	O
weary	O
,	O
tired	O
and	O
worn	O
out	O
Bodies	O
,	O
it	O
invigorates	O
and	O
inkindles	O
again	O
the	O
almost	O
extinguish	O
'd	O
natural	O
innate	O
Heat	O
,	O
making	O
the	O
Vital	O
Flame	O
to	O
burn	O
clear	O
,	O
removing	O
Weaknesses	O
and	O
Indispositions	O
,	O
and	O
restoring	O
the	O
Pristine	O
Health	O
.	O
The	O
Symptoms	O
are	O
cutaneous	O
Eruptions	O
,	O
as	O
red	O
,	O
yellow	O
or	O
black	O
Spots	O
upon	O
the	O
Arms	O
and	O
Legs	O
,	O
as	O
small	O
as	O
Flea-bites	O
,	O
sometimes	O
as	O
large	O
as	O
a	O
Crown-Piece	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
the	O
Limbs	O
are	O
beset	O
with	O
rough	O
scaly	O
Swellings	O
,	O
oftentimes	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
itching	O
of	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
frequently	O
taken	O
for	O
what	O
is	O
vulgarly	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Itch	O
.	O
The	O
Scurvy	O
perverts	O
the	O
Lympha	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
mortal	O
Enemy	O
to	O
the	O
nervous	O
System	O
;	O
for	O
Scorbutick	O
Persons	O
are	O
troubled	O
with	O
Weariness	O
,	O
Weakness	O
,	O
Sense	O
of	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dull	O
obscure	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Limbs	O
,	O
the	O
Appetite	O
is	O
either	O
too	O
stimulating	O
or	O
too	O
languid	O
,	O
the	O
Gums	O
are	O
liable	O
to	O
Excrescences	O
,	O
Swellings	O
and	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
rubb	O
'd	O
void	O
either	O
a	O
saltish	O
Blood	O
or	O
serous	O
Humour	O
,	O
the	O
Teeth	O
are	O
loose	O
and	O
corroded	O
,	O
the	O
Mouth	O
has	O
a	O
Stench	O
;	O
the	O
Spittle	O
is	O
very	O
salt	O
and	O
sometimes	O
acid	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
likewise	O
affected	O
with	O
nocturnal	O
Sweats	O
,	O
difficulty	O
of	O
Breathing	O
,	O
wandering	O
Pains	O
,	O
a	O
fat	O
Skin	O
is	O
found	O
sometimes	O
swimming	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Urine	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
these	O
Symptoms	O
are	O
rarely	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Second	O
Edition	O
of	O
,	O
The	O
Modern	O
Musick-Master	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
The	O
Universal	O
Musician	O
.	O
Containing	B-pers
,	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
An	O
Introduction	O
to	O
singing	O
,	O
after	O
so	O
easy	O
a	O
Method	O
,	O
that	O
Persons	O
of	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
may	O
(	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
)	O
learn	O
to	O
Sing	O
(	O
in	O
Tune	O
)	O
any	O
Song	O
that	O
is	O
set	O
to	O
Musick	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Directions	O
for	O
playing	O
on	O
the	O
Flute	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Scale	O
for	O
Transposing	O
any	O
Piece	O
of	O
Musick	O
to	O
the	O
properest	O
Keys	O
for	O
that	O
Instrument	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
newest	O
Method	O
for	O
Learners	O
on	O
the	O
German	O
Flute	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
greatest	O
Masters	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Instructions	O
upon	O
the	O
Hautboy	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
familiar	O
Method	O
than	O
any	O
extant	O
.	O
V.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
playing	O
on	O
the	O
Violin	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
Scale	O
,	O
shewing	O
how	O
to	O
stop	O
every	O
flat	O
or	O
sharp	O
Note	O
,	O
exactly	O
in	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
Shifts	O
of	O
the	O
Hand	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
The	O
Harpsicord	O
illustrated	O
and	O
improv	O
'd	O
,	O
wherein	O
is	O
shewn	O
the	O
Italian	O
Manner	O
of	O
Fingering	O
,	O
with	O
Sets	O
of	O
Lessons	O
for	O
Beginners	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
already	O
Proficients	O
on	O
that	O
Instrument	O
and	O
the	O
Organ	O
;	O
with	O
Rules	O
for	O
attaining	O
to	O
play	O
a	O
Thorough-Bass	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
is	O
included	O
,	O
A	O
large	O
Collection	O
of	O
Airs	O
,	O
and	O
Lessons	O
,	O
adapted	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
Instruments	O
,	O
extracted	O
from	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Handel	O
,	O
Bononcini	O
,	O
Albinoni	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
eminent	O
Masters	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
brief	O
History	O
of	O
Musick	O
,	O
wherein	O
is	O
related	O
the	O
several	O
Changes	O
,	O
Additions	O
,	O
and	O
Improvements	O
from	O
its	O
Origin	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Time	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
a	O
Musical	O
Dictionary	O
,	O
explaining	O
such	O
Greek	O
,	O
Latin	O
,	O
Italian	O
and	O
French	O
Words	O
as	O
generally	O
